TYRION LANNISTER: We have
suffered at each other's hands.
We have lost people
we love at each other's hands.
(DRAGON SCREECHING)
JAIME LANNISTER:
This isn't about noble houses,
this is about the living
and the dead.
And I intend to stay
amongst the living.
♪ (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
DAENERYS TARGARYEN:
I offer you a choice.
Bend the knee and join me,
or refuse, and die.
(MEN YELLING)
She is here to reclaim
the Seven Kingdoms.
The North is one of
those seven kingdoms.
JON SHOW: The Night King's army
grows larger by the day.
(YELLING)
We need allies. Powerful allies.
(WIGHT SCREECHES)
CERSEI LANNISTER:
The monsters are real.
Dragons, White Walkers,
Dothraki screamers...
Let the monsters
kill each other.
We will deal with
whatever is left.
♪ (MUSIC INTENSIFIES) ♪
DAENERYS: We are going
to destroy the Night King
and his army,
and we'll do it together.
SANSA STARK: He pledged to fight
for Daenerys Targaryen.
He's bent the knee.
BRANDON STARK:
He needs to know the truth.
Jon isn't really
my father's son.
He's the son of
Rhaegar Targaryen,
and my aunt, Lyanna Stark.
He's the heir to
the Iron Throne.
We need to tell him.
JON SNOW: The same thing
is coming for all of us...
And it is here.
♪ (MUSIC FADES) ♪
[♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
[PIG SQUEALS]
[DONKEY BRAYS]
[CHICKENS SQUAWKING]
[MARCHING]
[♪♪♪]
[MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[HORSES SNORTING]
[HORSE WHINNIES]
[HORSE NEIGHS]
You should
consider yourself lucky.
At least your balls
won't freeze off.
VARYS: You take great
offense at dwarf jokes,
but love telling eunuch jokes.
Why is that?
Because I have balls,
and you don't.
I warned you.
Northerners don't much trust
outsiders.
[DRAGON ROARS]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[♪♪♪]
[DRAGONS ROARING]
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
[HORSES NEIGHING]
[ROARS]
[♪♪♪]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Look at you.
[SNIFFLES]
You're a man.
Almost.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
JON: Where's Arya?
- Lurking somewhere.
JON: Queen Daenerys
of House Targaryen.
My sister, Sansa Stark,
the Lady of Winterfell.
Thank you for inviting us
into your home, Lady Stark.
The North is as beautiful
as your brother claimed,
as are you.
Winterfell is yours,
Your Grace.
We don't have time
for all this.
The Night King has your dragon.
He's one of them now.
The Wall has fallen,
the dead march south.
[♪♪♪]
SANSA: As soon as we
heard about the Wall,
I called all our banners
to retreat to Winterfell.
Lord Umber...
when can we expect
your people to arrive?
We need more horses and wagons,
if it please my lady.
And my lord.
And my queen.
Sorry.
SANSA: You'll have as
many as we can spare.
Hurry back to Last Hearth
and bring your people here.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
We need to send ravens
to the Night's Watch as well.
There's no sense in
manning the castles anymore.
We make our stand here.
At once, Your Grace.
"Your Grace."
But you're not. Are you?
You left Winterfell a king
and came back a...
I'm not sure
what you are now.
[PEOPLE MURMURING]
LYANNA: A lord?
Nothing at all?
- It's not important.
LYANNA: Not important?
We named you
King in the North.
[PEOPLE EXCLAIMING]
MAN:
King of the North!
You did, my lady.
It was the honor of my life.
I'll always be grateful
for your faith.
But when I left Winterfell,
I told you
we need allies or we will die.
I have brought
those allies home
to fight alongside us.
I had a choice,
keep my crown
or protect the North.
I chose the North.
[PEOPLE MURMURING]
If anyone survives
the war to come,
we'll have Jon Snow to thank.
He risked his life
to show us the threat is real.
Thanks to his courage,
we have brought with us
the greatest army
the world has ever seen.
We have brought
two full-grown dragons.
And soon, the Lannister army
will ride north
to join our cause.
[PEOPLE GRUMBLING
INDISTINCTLY]
I know, I know,
our people
haven't been friends
in the past.
But we must
fight together now...
or die.
May I ask,
how are we meant to feed
the greatest army
the world has ever seen?
While I ensured our stores
would last through winter,
I didn't account for Dothraki,
Unsullied
and two full-grown dragons.
What do dragons eat, anyway?
Whatever they want.
[HORSE NEIGHS]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
Hey, careful, lads.
We need every last bit of it.
MAN 1:
Sorry 'bout that.
Are these the last
of the wagons?
MAN 2:
Aye.
GENDRY: All right, let's
get it all to the forges.
My lord.
My lady.
The Lady of Winterfell.
Has a nice ring to it.
So does Hand of the Queen.
Depending on the queen,
I suppose.
Last time we spoke
was at Joffrey's wedding.
- Miserable affair.
- It had its moments.
Apologies
for leaving like that.
Yes,
it was a bit hard to explain
why my wife fled
moments after the king's murder.
We both survived.
Many underestimated you.
Most of them are dead now.
I'm sure
you weren't thrilled to hear
the Lannister
army's marching north.
You have every right
to be fearful of my sister.
No one fears her
more than I do.
- But I promise, you'll be safe...
- Cersei told you her army
was coming north
to fight for you?
She did.
And you believed her?
She has something
to live for now.
I believe she wants to survive.
I used to think you were
the cleverest man alive.
[♪♪♪]
ARYA:
You used to be taller.
JON:
How did you sneak up on me?
How did you survive
a knife through the heart?
I didn't.
[CHUCKLES]
- [SIGHS]
- [SCOFFS]
You still have it.
Needle.
Have you ever used it?
Once or twice.
[CHUCKLES]
Valyrian steel.
Jealous?
[SCOFFS]
Too heavy for me.
Where were you before?
I could've used your help
with Sansa.
She doesn't like your queen,
does she?
Sansa thinks
she's smarter than everyone.
She's the smartest person
I've ever met.
Now you're defending her?
[CHUCKLES]
You?
I'm defending our family.
So is she.
[SOFTLY]
Yeah.
[NORMALLY]
I'm her family too.
[♪♪♪]
Don't forget that.
Your Grace, I'm afraid I bring
terrible news.
The dead have
broken through the Wall.
Good.
[♪♪♪]
Why don't you just
get it over with and kill me?
[SIGHS]
But we're family.
The last Greyjoys
left in the world.
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
The last ones
with balls anyway.
[CHUCKLES]
If I kill you...
who can I talk to?
Hmm?
[SIGHS]
I've got a crew full of mutes.
It gets lonely at sea.
Are we in King's Landing?
Mm.
You picked the losing side.
Then I'll sail the Iron Fleet
somewhere else.
But first
I'm gonna fuck the queen.
[FOOTSTEPS LEAVING]
[PANTING]
[DOOR OPENS, THEN CLOSES]
CERSEI:
Twenty-thousand men, is it?
Yes, Your Grace.
A few died in transit.
They cheated at dice.
Or maybe I cheated.
Someone cheated.
They weren't good fighters.
You won't miss them.
- Horses?
- Two thousand.
And elephants?
HARRY: Uh, no
elephants, Your Grace.
That's disappointing.
I was told the Golden Company
had elephants.
HARRY: They are excellent
beasts, Your Grace,
but not well-suited
to long sea voyages.
In any event,
you are most welcome
here in King's Landing,
Captain Strickland.
We look forward to fighting
on your behalf, Your Grace.
EURON:
Am I most welcome here?
You are a true friend
of the crown
and an honored guest.
EURON:
Good.
As a true friend
and an honored guest...
[GRUNTS]
[WHISPERS] I was hoping
we could talk in private.
After the war.
That was our agreement.
Wars sometimes last years.
You want a whore, buy one.
You want a queen...
earn her.
How?
I've given her justice,
an army
and the Iron Fleet,
yet she gives me
no sign of affection.
My heart is nearly broken.
You're insolent.
- I've executed men for less.
- They were lesser men.
[♪♪♪]
[CHUCKLES]
[DOOR OPENS]
DIRAH: I hear the dragon burnt
up a thousand Lannister men.
CRAYA: Burnt up some
of my favorite boys.
DIRAH: Archie, was it?
- And William.
- Tall handsome William?
- Yeah, tall handsome William.
They said what's left of him
could fit in a wine glass.
I am the only man you ever met
who shot a dragon.
- Did you?
BRONN: Nearly killed it.
That's brave.
[MOANING SOFTLY]
[BRONN SIGHS]
CRAYA: That boy Eddie...
DIRAH: The ginger?
That's him. Came back
with his face burnt right off.
He's got no eyelids now.
How does he sleep
with no eyelids?
All right, can we stop talking
about the fucking dragons now?
QYBURN:
Ser Bronn of the Blackwater.
You're kidding me.
Apologies
for the interruption,
but the queen
did urge me to hurry.
Sorry, ladies.
Another time perhaps.
You ever get lonely,
I am partial to older gentlemen.
Poor girl. The pox will take her
within the year.
[COUGHS]
- Which girl?
QYBURN: The queen's brothers
made promises to you
and broke them.
Her Grace wants to rectify
their mistake.
She once gave me
a castle and a wife,
then rectified me
right out of them.
That was Ser Jaime's doing,
not hers.
When Queen Cersei
wants something,
she pays in advance
and in gold.
Several chests of it, in fact.
Waiting for you
in a wagon just outside.
So she wants to murder someone,
but she can't send her soldiers.
If it's the Dragon Queen
she's after...
She has other plans
for the Targaryen girl.
Yeah, well,
good luck with that.
Our queen's brothers
are unlikely
to survive
their Northern adventures.
But in the event
that they do...
[♪♪♪]
She has a keen sense
of poetic justice.
That fucking family.
QYBURN:
When the Citadel expelled me,
I thought I would die
poor and alone,
but in exchange for my service,
Queen Cersei made me her Hand.
What would she do
for the man
who rids her
of her treasonous brothers?
[♪♪♪]
[DOOR OPENS, THEN CLOSES]
[SIGHS]
I wanted those elephants.
[EURON SIGHS]
So...
how do I compare
to the fat king?
You're insulting
my late husband?
Are you offended?
Robert had a different whore
every night,
but he still didn't know
his way around a woman's body.
And the Kingslayer?
You enjoy risking your neck,
don't you?
[CHUCKLES]
Life is boring.
You're not boring,
I'll give you that.
[SIGHS]
Do I please the queen?
You might be the most
arrogant man I've ever met.
[WHISPERS]
I like that.
[CHUCKLES]
[NORMALLY]
But now I want to be alone.
[SIGHS SOFTLY]
[SOFTLY] I'm going to put
a prince in your belly.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[BOW STRING CREAKS]
[MEN GRUNTING]
- [FLESH SQUELCHES]
- [GASPS]
[PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
[BOTH GRUNT]
[♪♪♪]
YARA: Euron can't defend
the Iron Islands,
not if he's in King's Landing
with all his men and his ships.
We can take our home back.
Daenerys went north.
Daenerys will need
somewhere to retreat
if they can't hold the North.
Somewhere the dead can't go.
[MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
You're my queen.
I go where you command.
You want to go to Winterfell.
To fight for the Starks.
Go.
What is dead may never die.
But kill the bastards
anyway.
[♪♪♪]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
WOLKAN:
Welcome back, my lady.
If you'd follow me...
VARYS:
The Karstarks.
TYRION:
One of the better sigils.
Beats an onion, anyway.
Can't argue with that.
Not so long ago,
the Starks and the Karstarks
were slaughtering each other
on the battlefield.
Jon Snow brought peace
to the houses.
TYRION:
And our queen is grateful.
Her gratitude is lovely,
but that's not my point.
The Northmen are loyal
to Jon Snow, not to her.
They don't know her.
The Free Folk don't know her.
I've been up here a while,
and I'm telling you,
they're stubborn as goats.
You want their loyalty,
you have to earn it.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
I sense that you're leading
to a proposal.
A proposal
is what I'm proposing.
On the off chance
that we survive the Night King,
what if the Seven Kingdoms,
for once
in their whole shit history,
were ruled by a just woman
and an honorable man?
TYRION:
They do make a handsome couple.
VARYS: You overestimate
our influence.
Jon and Daenerys don't want
to listen to lonely old men.
I'm not that old.
Not as old as him.
[CHUCKLES]
Our queen
respects the wisdom of age.
Of course she does.
Respect is how the young
keep us at a distance,
so we don't remind them
of an unpleasant truth.
TYRION:
What is that?
Nothing lasts.
MAN:
Hey!
[MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
Your sister doesn't like me.
She doesn't know you.
If it makes you feel
any better,
she didn't like me either
when we were growing up.
She doesn't need
to be my friend...
but I am her queen.
If she can't respect me...
[MAN SPEAKS DOTHRAKI
INDISTINCTLY]
[IN DOTHRAKI]
What's the matter?
[IN ENGLISH]
The dragons are barely eating.
[DRAGONS GROWLING SOFTLY]
JON:
What's wrong with them?
They don't like the North.
Go on.
I don't know
how to ride a dragon.
Nobody does.
Until they ride a dragon.
What if he doesn't want me to?
Then I've enjoyed your company,
Jon Snow.
[SCOFFS]
[GRUNTS]
What do I hold onto?
Whatever you can.
- [DRAGON CHITTERS]
- [JON GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
[JON YELPS]
[YELLS]
JON:
Aah!
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
[WIND WHISTLING]
You've completely
ruined horses for me.
[LAUGHS]
We could stay
a thousand years...
no one would find us.
We'd be pretty old.
[CHUCKLES]
[♪♪♪]
It's cold up here
for a southern girl.
So keep your queen warm.
[DROGON GROWLS SOFTLY]
Don't be afraid.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
MAN 1:
That's good.
[MAN 1 SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
[HAMMER CLANKING]
MAN 2: Gendry?
MAN 3: He's here.
It isn't easy making a blade
that big with dragonglass.
You're saying you're good,
is that it?
I'm just saying
it's a tricky material to...
You know who makes weapons
for the wildlings?
Cripples and cocksuckers.
- Which one are you?
ARYA: Leave him be.
I heard you were here.
[♪♪♪]
You left me to die.
First I robbed you.
You're a cold little bitch,
aren't you?
Guess that's why
you're still alive.
That was a nice ax
you made for him.
You've gotten better.
Yeah, thanks. So have you.
I mean, you look good.
Thanks. So do you.
It's not a bad place to grow up,
if it wasn't so cold.
Stay close to that forge,
then.
- Is that a command, Lady Stark?
- Don't call me that.
As you wish, milady.
[MAN SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
[CHUCKLES]
ARYA:
Here's my wish.
Can you make it?
What do you need
something like this for?
Can you make it or not?
You already have a sword.
What's that?
It's Valyrian steel.
I always knew
you were just another rich girl.
[MAN SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY]
You don't know
any other rich girls.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Come in.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[SIGHS]
Lord Glover wishes us
good fortune,
but he's staying
in Deepwood Motte with his men.
"House Glover will stand
behind House Stark
as we have
for a thousand years."
Isn't that what he said?
SANSA: "I will stand
behind Jon Snow," he said.
"The King in the North."
I told you we needed allies.
SANSA: You didn't tell me you
were going to abandon your crown.
I never wanted a crown.
All I wanted
was to protect the North.
I brought two armies
home with me, two dragons.
And a Targaryen queen.
[SIGHS]
Do you think
we can beat the Army of the Dead
without her?
I fought them, Sansa. Twice.
You want to worry about
who holds what title,
I'm telling you
it doesn't matter.
Without her,
we don't stand a chance.
[SIGHS]
Do you have
any faith in me at all?
You know I do.
She'll be a good queen.
For all of us.
She's not her father.
[SIGHS]
No, she's much prettier.
[SCOFFS]
Did you bend the knee
to save the North
or because you love her?
[DOOR OPENS]
[MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Oh!
So you're the man?
Um...
Which man am I, Your Grace?
The one who saved Ser Jorah
when no one else could.
They could, they just wouldn't.
DAENERYS:
I'll have to make some changes
in the Citadel
when I take my throne.
A great service
merits a great reward.
SAMWELL: Oh, it's my honor
to serve you, Your Grace.
DAENERYS: Well, there must be
something I could give you.
If it's not too much trouble,
I could use a pardon.
For what crime?
Um...
I borrowed a few books
from the Citadel.
And also a sword.
- From the Citadel?
SAMWELL: From my family.
It's been in House Tarly
for generations.
It would've been mine
anyway, eventually,
but my father had other ideas.
Not Randyll Tarly?
You know him?
I offered to let him
retain his lands and titles
if he bent the knee.
[♪♪♪]
DAENERYS:
He refused.
[GULPS]
Well...
At least I'll be
allowed home again,
now that my brother's the lord.
Your brother
stood with your father.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
Hm.
Thank you, Your Grace.
For telling me.
And m...
- May I...?
- Of course.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SNIFFLES]
[HORSE NEIGHS]
[WHIMPERS]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
SAMWELL:
What are you doing out here?
Waiting, for an old friend.
It's time
to tell Jon the truth.
No, no.
You're his brother.
Shouldn't you tell him?
I'm not his brother.
He trusts you
more than anyone.
Now's the time.
[JON SIGHS]
[MAN GRUNTING, THUDS]
[MAN GROANING]
JON:
Sam?
I'm sorry, I know I'm not
supposed to be down here.
- Were you hiding from me?
- Of course not.
What are you doing
in Winterfell?
Or did you read every book
in the Citadel already?
What's wrong?
Gilly? Is she all right?
- She's good.
- Little Sam?
Don't you know?
Know what?
Daenerys...
she executed my father
and brother.
They were her prisoners.
She didn't tell you.
I'm so sorry.
We need to end this war.
Would you have done it?
Well, I've executed men
who disobeyed me.
SAMWELL:
You've also spared men.
Thousands of wildlings
when they refused to kneel.
I wasn't a king.
But you were.
You've always been.
I gave up my crown, Sam.
I bent the knee.
I'm not
King in the North anymore.
I'm not talking about
the King in the North.
I'm talking about the King
of the bloody Seven Kingdoms.
[♪♪♪]
Bran and I worked it out.
I had a High Septon's diary.
Bran had...
whatever Bran has.
What are you talking about?
Your mother...
was Lyanna Stark.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
SAMWELL:
And your father...
your real father
was Rhaegar Targaryen.
You've never been a bastard.
You're Aegon Targaryen,
true heir to the Iron Throne.
I'm sorry,
I know it's a lot to take in.
My father was the most
honorable man I ever met.
You're saying
he lied to me all my life.
No.
Your father... Well, Ned Stark.
He promised your mother
he'd always protect you.
And he did. Robert would have
murdered you if he knew.
You're the true king.
Aegon Targaryen,
Sixth of His Name,
Protector of the Realm,
all of it.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
- Daenerys is our queen.
SAMWELL: She shouldn't be.
- That's treason.
- It's the truth.
You gave up your crown
to save your people.
Would she do the same?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[♪♪♪]
[FOOTSTEPS GROWING LOUDER]
[ALL SCREAMING]
Stay back, he's got blue eyes!
I've always had blue eyes!
[SIGHING]
[GRUNTS]
Did you find anyone?
[♪♪♪]
EDD:
The Umber boy.
BERIC:
It's a message.
From the Night King.
His army's between us
and Winterfell. We're on foot.
We rode down from
Castle Black.
We can double up
on the horses.
If the horses last,
we'll get there before the dead.
We just have to hope
the Night King
doesn't come first.
- [SHRIEKING]
- [MEN CLAMORING]
[♪♪♪]
[SHRIEKING STOPS]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
MAN:
Keep moving! Straight up!
Stay together!
Don't fall behind!
[SIGHS]
[♪♪♪]
DAENERYS: When I was a child,
my brother would tell me
a bedtime story, about the man
who murdered our father.
About all the things we would
do to that man.
You never should have
trusted Cersei.
You never should have either.
ARYA STARK: Death...
it's got many faces, I look
forward to seeing this one.
How long do we have?
♪ (INTENSE MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
TORMUND: Before the sun
comes up tomorrow.
- (ARMY MARCHES, CLANKS)
- ♪ (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
The kind of pomp and majesty
of Dany's arrival,
it just felt like the natural
place to start the season.
The arrival was a way to capture
what was at stake
for Dany and for Jon.
Looking back
to the very beginning
and how young Maisie was
back then,
and wearing the Stark soldier's
helmet falling over her head,
and she just looks like
this little kid.
And now she's a grown woman,
and she's there watching again.
But this time, she steps aside
to let a little kid come in
to watch
'cause she remembers
how thrilling it was.
It's a whole new procession,
and so instead of Robert
arriving with Queen Cersei
and Jamie Lannister
and The Hound,
it's Daenerys coming
with Jon Snow.
I don't think the North
is the most welcoming place
to outsiders.
Dany's smart. She senses
that distrust, and she's...
gonna make the best
of a bad situation,
but that doesn't mean that
she likes it or she's happy.
When you're doing something good
for people,
and you get met
with what Sansa gives her
when they meet in the courtyard,
it's understandable
that she would be upset.
We've been with these characters
on a pretty regular basis
all the time for the past
however many years.
The fact they're coming back
together again
for the first time
means more to them
than it may mean to us.
Lady of Winterfell...
Has a nice ring to it.
So does Hand of the Queen...
depending on the queen,
I suppose.
I think that if Tyrion were
to have shown up
on his own to Winterfell,
he would've gotten
a much different reception
from Sansa than he did
coming as the Hand of the Queen,
Daenerys Targaryen.
There's also the specific thing
that happens in that scene,
which is Tyrion
has told everybody
that the Lannisters are coming
to join the cause,
and it's amazing to her
that this person
she thought was so smart
would ever
take Cersei at her word
on something like that.
I used to think you were
the cleverest man alive.
How did you survive a knife
through the heart?
I didn't.
DAVID BENIOFF:
Jon Snow and Arya
are two of the most important
characters in the story,
and they love each other
very deeply.
Arya was the only one
who treated Jon
like a real member of the family
when he was a child,
and he was the only one
who treated her
with the respect that she needed
when she was a kid.
Jon has invited this...
huge army of foreigners
into their home,
and Arya understands
why he did it,
but Arya's on Sansa's side.
You are defending her.
I'm defending our family.
So is she.
I'm her family too.
Don't forget that.
BENIOFF: Blood is definitely
thicker than water
when it comes to Starks.
Go on.
I don't know how to ride
a dragon.
Nobody does
until they ride a dragon.
No one's ever ridden a dragon
except for Dany.
Only Targaryens
can ride dragons,
and that should be a sign
for Jon.
Jon's not always the quickest
on the uptake,
but eventually gets there.
We wanted to kind of re-anchor
their relationship.
It seemed important for it
to involve the dragons,
since the dragons play
such an important role.
It's a major thing for her
when she sees
they have some kind
of connection to him,
they allow him
to be around them.
And when he flies up with her
and shows her where he used
to hunt as a kid,
I think she falls
even farther in love with him.
Seeing Jon and Dany
on the dragons together,
it's a Jon and Dany moment,
but it also seeds in the idea
that these creatures will accept
Jon Snow as one of their riders.
Don't be afraid.
(DROGON SNORTS)
One of the challenges,
but also one
of the exciting things
about this episode,
this whole season,
is bringing together characters
who have never met.
Sam has long been
one of the more important
characters in the story.
But he's never seen
Queen Daenerys,
and yet they're connected
by various threads.
The obvious one, which we know
from the beginning of the scene,
is Jorah.
Sam saved him, and so Jorah
owes him this great debt.
What none of them realize
until midway through this scene
is that they have another,
horrible connection.
There are all these things
that you know
about those characters
that the other characters
don't know.
And some of them
are very important.
Dany murdered
Samwell's father and brother.
That's a really complicated
thing for Sam
because he had a really fraught
relationship with his father.
Yet Sam's older brother
was not a bad person,
and died, really, quite bravely,
standing by his father's side.
John Bradley did
an excellent job.
The difference between
the way he takes the news
of his father's death
and the way he takes the news
of his brother's death,
it was a subtle thing
that he does
with very few words.
It's the kind of thing
that he could find out
in a number of different ways,
but it seemed like
a very ineffective preamble
and way into that later
moment.
Daenerys...
She executed
my father and brother.
I've executed men
who disobeyed me.
You've also spared men.
Thousands of wildlings
when they refused to kneel.
- I wasn't a king.
- But you were.
The fact that Jon's real parents
were who Jon's real parents were
is not news to us at this point,
but what we don't know
is the way that Jon
is going to take this.
How's the explosion
gonna look?
BENIOFF: Sam, as a brother
of the Night's Watch,
and Jon are more brothers than
Bran and Jon ever really were.
He knows it's gonna hurt Jon
and it's going to shatter
his whole worldview.
For all they know,
the Army of the Dead
could attack the next day,
and someone has to tell Jon
before that.
D.B. WEISS:
He's being told something
that he both knows is true
and can't handle.
So he tries to throw things
in front of it
to prevent him
from having to deal with
the... the truth of what
he's being told.
The thing he throws
in front of it here
is the fact that it means
his father was lying to him
his whole life.
SAMWELL TARLY:
You've never been a bastard.
You're a true heir
to the Iron Throne.
The truth that Samwell tells Jon
is probably the most
incendiary fact
in the entire world of the show.
We chose to play the whole thing
on Jon's face
because, as great a job
as John Bradley is doing
presenting this information,
he's really just presenting
information we know already.
- Daenerys is our queen.
- SAMWELL: She shouldn't be.
- That's treason.
- It's the truth.
♪ (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
VALERY LEGASOV:
All of the good we did...
it doesn't matter.
What does matter is that
to them, justice was done.
See, a just world...
is a sane world.
There was nothing sane
about Chernobyl.
♪ (EERIE MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
BORIS SHCHERBINA:
I'm pleased to report
that the situation in Chernobyl
is stable.
In terms of radiation...
I'm told it's the equivalent
of a chest X-ray.
No! Chernobyl is on fire.
And every atom of uranium
is like a bullet...
penetrating everything
in its path.
- (SCREAMING IN PAIN)
- Metal, concrete, flesh.
Now, Chernobyl holds
over three trillion
of these bullets.
(STATIC FEEDBACK)
Some of them will not stop
firing for 50,000 years.
Tell me how to put it out.
You are dealing with something
that has never occurred
on this planet before.
(HORNS BLARING)
(STATIC FEEDBACK)
(ANNOUNCEMENT IN RUSSIAN
OVER PA)
Cut the phone lines. Contain
the spread of misinformation.
- (PA CONTINUES)
- (STATIC FEEDBACK)
SHCHERBINA: What will happen
to our boys?
LEGASOV:
The pain is unimaginable.
- (PA CONTINUES)
- (STATIC FEEDBACK)
In three days to three weeks,
you're dead.
You can see him,
but you cannot touch him.
Do you understand?
- (PA CONTINUES)
- (STATIC FEEDBACK)
What happened on the night
of the accident?
MAN: You think the right question
will give you the truth?
There is no truth.
- (PATIENT SCREAMING)
- LEGASOV: What happened then...
(STATIC FEEDBACK)
...what happened after...
- (GUNSHOT)
- ...all of it...
All of it...
- (PA CONTINUES)
- (STATIC FEEDBACK)
Madness.
♪ (EERIE MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪