(WIND HOWLING)
(GHOST HOWLING)
(DOOR RATTLES)
(GHOST CONTINUES HOWLING)
(POUNDING DOOR)
(DOOR CLATTERING)
(GHOST HOWLING)
BLACK BROTHER: It's coming
from the courtyard.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
BLACK BROTHER:
It's the Lord Commander!
(ALL PANTING)
(PANTING)
Help me get him inside.
(CLATTERING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Thorne did this.
How many of your brothers
do you think you can trust?
Trust?
The men in this room.
DAVOS: Does the wolf
know you?
We need all the help
we can get.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
MELISANDRE: Ser Davos.
(DOOR CLOSES)
MELISANDRE:
I saw him in the flames
fighting at Winterfell.
I can't speak
for the flames,
but he's gone.
(CLAMORING)
BLACK BROTHER 1:
He was our Lord Commander.
BLACK BROTHER 2:
He never should have been!
(THUDDING)
(CHAIR SCRAPES)
(SHOUTING STOPS)
You all know why you're here.
Jon Snow is dead.
Who killed him?
I did.
(SHOUTING RESUMES)
And Bowen Marsh
and Othell Yarwyck
and the other officers
in this castle.
Murderers!
Traitors!
(ALL ARGUING)
(POUNDS ON TABLE)
You're right!
(SHOUTING STOPS)
We've committed treason,
all of us.
Jon Snow was
my Lord Commander.
I had no love for him.
That was no secret.
But I never once
disobeyed an order.
Loyalty is
the foundation on which
the Night's Watch is built.
And the Watch
means everything to me.
I have given my life,
we have all given our lives
to the Night's Watch.
Jon Snow was going to destroy
the Night's Watch.
He let the wildlings
through our gates
as no Lord Commander
has ever done before.
He gave them the very land
on which they reaved
and raped and murdered.
Lord Commander Snow did
what he thought was right,
I've no doubt about that.
And what he thought was right
would have been the end of us.
He thrust
a terrible choice upon us.
And we made it.
(MURMURING)
(WHIMPERING)
DAVOS: He'll have
seen we didn't come.
Thorne will have
made it official by now.
Castle Black is his.
I don't care who's
sitting at the high table.
Jon was my friend.
And those fuckers
butchered him.
Now we return the favor.
We don't
have the numbers.
We have a direwolf.
DAVOS: It's not enough.
I didn't know
Lord Commander Snow
for long,
but I have to believe
he wouldn't have wanted
his friends to
die for nothing.
If you were
planning to see tomorrow,
you picked the wrong room.
We all die today.
I say we do our best
to take Thorne
with us when we go.
We need to fight,
but we don't need to die.
Not if we have help.
Who is gonna help us?
You're not the only ones
who owe your lives
to Jon Snow.
Bolt the door.
Don't let anyone in.
I'll be back
as soon as I can.
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
(BOLT CLICKS)
RAMSAY: She was 11
the first time I saw her.
The kennelmaster's daughter.
She smelled of dog.
I wasn't much older,
but everybody was
already afraid of me.
You certainly were.
Myranda wasn't, though.
What could I do to her
that those hounds couldn't?
She was fearless.
There was nothing
she wouldn't do.
Your pain will be paid for
a thousand times over.
(SOFTLY) I wish you
could be here to watch.
MAESTER: Shall I have a grave
dug for her, my lord?
Or would you rather
the men build a pyre?
Buried, burned?
This is good meat.
Feed it to the hounds.
BOLTON: Your command
of the cavalry was impressive.
Thanks to you,
the false king
Stannis Baratheon is dead.
Do you know who
struck the killing blow?
No.
A shame.
I'd reward the man.
Still, a great victory.
Do you feel like a victor?
I rebelled against the crown
to arrange your marriage
to Sansa Stark.
Do you think that
burning wagons in the night
and mowing down tired,
outnumbered Baratheons
is the same as facing
a prepared and provisioned
Lannister army?
No.
A reckoning will come.
We need
the North to face it.
The entire North.
They won't back us
without Sansa Stark.
We no longer
have Sansa Stark.
You played your
games with her.
You played your games
with the heir to
the Iron Islands
and now they're
both gone.
I have a team
of men after them
with some of my best hounds.
They won't get far.
I'm glad to hear it.
Without Sansa,
you won't be able
to produce an heir.
And without an heir, well...
Let's hope
the maesters are right
and Lady Walda's
carrying a boy.
(HOUNDS BARKING)
(PANTING)
THEON: We can't stop.
THEON: We have to
cross here.
(SANSA PANTING)
(GASPS) I can't.
It's the only way to
throw off the hounds.
But it's too cold. I can't.
I won't make it. I'll die.
I've seen what his
hounds do to a person.
This way is better.
(SIGHING)
(HOUNDS CONTINUE BARKING)
(SANSA GASPING)
(SHIVERING)
(GASPING)
Over here. Come on.
(BOTH SHIVERING)
Sansa.
(HOUNDS BARKING)
(GASPS)
MAN: Tell them to settle down!
Stay here.
I'll lure them away.
No, I won't make it
without you.
You will.
Go north, only north.
Jon is Lord Commander
at Castle Black.
He'll help you.
(BARKING AND HOWLING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
MAN 1: See somebody, eh?
MAN 2: There they are!
MAN 3: Get them!
Where is Lady Bolton?
Dead.
Liar.
She broke her leg
jumping from the ramparts.
I left her to die
in the snow.
(BARKING)
Got something! Run!
(HORSE WHINNIES)
MAN: Hyah!
(BARKING)
(SANSA WHIMPERING)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
MAN 2: Resist. Stay.
(GROWLING, BARKING)
MAN 2: Stay.
I can't wait to see
what parts Ramsay
cuts off you this time.
(BARKING)
(GRUNTING)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
MAN: Rider!
Who is it?
It's a bloody woman.
(YELLS)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
(GROWLS)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
No! Please! Don't!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(SQUELCHES)
(GASPING)
Lady Sansa, I offer
my services once again.
I will shield your back
and keep your counsel
and give my life
for yours if need be.
I swear it by
the Old Gods and the New.
And I vow
that you shall always
have a place by my hearth
and...
Meat and mead at my table.
...meat and mead
at my table.
And I pledge to ask
no service of you
that might bring
you dishonor.
I swear it by
the Old Gods and the New.
Arise.
(SEAGULLS SCREECHING)
(DOOR OPENS)
HANDMAIDEN: Your Grace,
I'm sorry to disturb you.
A ship from Dorne has
sailed into the harbor.
Myrcella.
(SEAGULLS SCREECHING)
(BELL TOLLING)
Do you remember the first time
you saw a dead body?
Mother.
All I could think about
when she died
was what would
happen to her now.
Every day, every night,
what does Mama
look like now?
Has she started to bloat?
Has her skin turned black?
Have her lips peeled
back from her teeth?
I think about locking
Myrcella in a crypt.
I think about her
beautiful little face
starting to collapse.
(SHUSHING)
Don't think about it.
(SOFTLY) I have to.
I have to. It's not right
she has to suffer alone.
She's not suffering.
She's gone.
No one can hurt her anymore.
She was good.
From her first breath,
she was so sweet.
I don't know
where she came from.
She was nothing like me.
No meanness,
no jealousy, just good.
I know.
I thought if I could
make something so good,
so pure,
maybe I'm not a monster.
Listen... Listen to me.
She was my daughter
and I failed her.
No, I knew
this would happen.
The witch told me
years ago.
She promised me
three children and she
promised me they'd die.
"And gold their shrouds."
Everything she said came true.
You couldn't have stopped it.
It's prophecy. It's fate.
You don't believe that.
Of course I do.
You told me yourself
when Father died.
You said we had
to stay together.
You said people would
try to tear us apart,
take what's ours.
That was a prophecy, too.
I didn't listen to you,
and everything
you said came true.
Fuck prophecy.
Fuck fate.
Fuck everyone who isn't us.
We're the only
ones who matter,
the only ones in this world.
And everything
they've taken from us,
we're going to
take back and more.
We're going to take
everything there is.
UNELLA: "The seven hells
brim with the souls
of saintly men.
"They scream in agony
and their shame is so great,
"they do not feel the flames,
"for now they see if
not for a single sin
"they concealed,
they were saved."
I'd like to see my brother.
Confess.
Please.
How is he?
At least tell me that.
Confess.
I am the queen
and I demand to
see my brother.
Sinners don't make demands.
They make confessions.
(GASPS)
(DOOR OPENS)
HIGH PRIEST: Septa Unella.
(SIGHS) Our other
guests need you.
(GASPS)
There.
Septa Unella can be
overzealous at times.
I'll speak with her.
My brother,
can you tell me how he is?
It isn't Ser Loras
that brings me here.
Your husband
misses you dearly.
The love between
a man and wife is sacred.
It reflects the love
the gods have for all of us.
But sin leads us
away from the sacred.
And only confession
can purge sin.
I have nothing to confess.
So you believe
you are pure?
Perfect?
Wholly without sin?
None of us are.
You have
started down the path.
But you have
many miles to go.
(DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
DORAN: I always envied Oberyn.
He lived.
He truly lived.
Sailed around the world.
Fought men
from every country.
Lay with the most
beautiful women alive.
And men.
He experienced everything
while I sat here in Dorne
trying my best
to keep my people
alive and well fed.
But that is life.
We each have our roles.
Oberyn was born
to be an adventurer.
And I was born to rule.
ELLARIA:
The gods are not fools.
You would have been
a lousy adventurer.
And Oberyn,
he would have been
a terrible ruler.
Your mother is
a brilliant woman,
you know that?
MAESTER: Prince Doran.
The Princess Myrcella.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
When was the last time
you left this palace?
You don't know
your own people.
(SCOFFS)
Their disgust for you.
(DORAN COUGHING)
Elia Martell,
raped and murdered,
and you did nothing.
Oberyn Martell, butchered,
You're not a Dornishman.
(PANTING)
And you're not our prince.
My son, Trystane...
(SCOFFS)
Your son is weak,
just like you.
And weak men will
never rule Dorne again.
I told you I'm not hungry.
We're not here
to feed you.
We're here to kill you.
You want her
to do it or me?
We are family.
I don't want to hurt you.
(CHUCKLES)
Her or me?
You.
Good.
Smart boy.
You're a greedy bitch,
you know that?
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
TYRION:
We're never going to fix
what's wrong with this city
from the top of
an 800-foot pyramid.
We'll be fine.
We're dressed like
common merchants.
You walk like
a rich person.
You've spent
a lot of time studying
the way rich people walk?
You walk as though
the paving stones
were your personal property.
(SCOFFS) I used to steal
from people like you
when I was a boy.
TYRION: It's a good thing
you're not a boy anymore.
Because you have no cock.
(BABY COOING)
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
She thinks you
want to eat her baby.
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
(SPEAKS VALYRIAN)
VARYS: "Mhysa" means
"mother" in Valyrian.
TYRION: I know
what "mhysa" means.
VARYS: Who wrote it?
TYRION: Hard to know.
Our queen is not as
popular in Meereen
as she used to be.
The Sons of the Harpy?
Very possibly.
Daenerys Targaryen took away
their most valuable property,
told them human beings
weren't even property
to begin with.
You can see why
they're unhappy.
Of course,
it could also
be the freed men.
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
Many of the former slaves
feel that Daenerys
has abandoned them.
She did fly away
on a dragon
and not come back.
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
It's a problem.
TYRION: Fear has brought
Meereen to a standstill.
Whoever you are,
wherever you go,
someone in this city
wants to murder you.
We can't fight an enemy
we don't know.
VARYS: The Sons of the Harpy
planned their attack in the
fighting pits very carefully,
which means they take
orders from someone.
And have you started
looking for that someone?
My little birds have
already taken wing.
Soon they'll return,
singing songs of
men in gold masks.
(MEN SHOUTING IN VALYRIAN)
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
(BELL TOLLING)
(SHOUTING CONTINUES)
(BELL CONTINUES TOLLING)
(BELL TOLLING RAPIDLY)
Well, we won't be
sailing to Westeros
anytime soon.
Goat?
Ram.
Do you think our
friend got him?
Don't know anything else
that can melt a ram's horn.
We're on
the right path, then.
DAARIO: Perhaps she's
tired of being queen.
I don't think she
likes it very much.
She's too smart
to like it.
Maybe she's flown
somewhere else,
somewhere far away
from men like us.
I've been
all over the world.
There's no escaping
men like us.
There's no
escaping her, eh?
You keep coming back. Why?
You know why.
Isn't it frustrating
wanting someone
who doesn't want you back?
Of course it is.
You're a romantic.
I admire that.
Sometimes I look
at you and I think,
"So that's what I'll be
like when I grow old."
If you grow old.
If I grow old.
DAARIO: I hope I do.
I want to see what
the world looks like
when she's done conquering it.
So do I.
DAARIO: Huh, an army?
JORAH: Not an army.
A horde.
Dothraki?
They have her.
(CLAMORING)
(SHOUTS IN DOTHRAKI)
(GROANS)
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
(GRUNTS) No.
(CONTINUES SPEAKING
OTHER LANGUAGE)
(MEN LAUGHING)
(CONTINUES SPEAKING
OTHER LANGUAGE)
(DAENERYS GRUNTS)
(CONTINUES SPEAKING
OTHER LANGUAGE)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(DOG BARKING IN THE DISTANCE)
WOMAN:
But there has to be a price
to pay for everything.
MAN 1:
I know, but have you tried
telling him that?
(CHATTER CONTINUES)
Thank you.
MAN 2: Who'd go there
after what happened
to that Kingsguard?
MAN 3: Probably had it coming.
MAN 2: Maybe so,
but I'm not risking it.
MAN 3: Just can't do it.
MAN 2: All right.
WOMAN: Honesty as well.
He gets it.
(CHATTERING CONTINUES)
WAIF: Are you listening,
blind girl?
Do you hear them talking?
Do any of them talk to you?
No.
So sad.
(COINS JANGLE)
(GROANS)
Stand and fight,
blind girl.
I can't see.
That's your problem,
not mine.
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
See you tomorrow.
(POUNDING)
(GHOST GROWLING)
Ser Davos,
we have no cause to fight.
We are both anointed knights.
Hear that, lads?
Nothing to fear.
I will grant amnesty
to all brothers
who throw down their
arms before nightfall.
And you, Ser Davos,
I will allow you
to travel south
a free man
with a fresh horse.
DAVOS: And some mutton.
I'd like some mutton.
What?
I'm not much of a hunter.
I'll need some food
if I'm gonna make it
south without starving.
We'll give you food.
You can bring the Red Woman
with you if you like.
Or you can leave
her here with us,
whichever you choose.
But surrender by nightfall
or this ends with blood.
Thank you, Ser Alliser.
We'll discuss
amongst ourselves
and come back to you
with an answer.
Boys, I've been running
from men like
that all my life.
In my learned opinion,
we open that door...
And they'll
slaughter us all.
They want to come in,
they're gonna come in.
Aye, but we don't need to
make it easy for them.
Edd is our only chance.
It's a sad fucking statement
if Dolorous Edd
is our only chance.
There's always the Red Woman.
What's one redhead gonna do
against 40 armed men?
You haven't seen her do
what I've seen her do.