(BELL TOLLING)
(JINGLING)
(SHIVERING)
(DOOR RATTLING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
MAN: Your Grace.
The trial will be
getting under way soon.
(CLICKS)
(SOFT GRUNT)
(JINGLING)
You got my money?
Later. Go away.
(EXHALES)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Grand Maester.
(WHISPERING INAUDIBLY)
Ser Loras Tyrell.
Are you prepared
to stand trial
and profess your
guilt or innocence
before the Seven?
There'll be no
need for a trial.
(SCATTERED MURMURS)
I confess before
the Seven
and freely admit
to my crimes.
To which crimes
will you be confessing?
All of them.
I lay with other men
including the traitor
Renly Baratheon.
(CROWD GASPING)
I perjured myself
before the gods.
I am guilty of depravity,
dishonesty,
profligacy,
and arrogance.
I see that now.
I humble myself
before the Seven
and accept whatever punishment
the gods deem just.
The gods' judgment
is fierce,
but also fair.
The Warrior punishes those
who believe themselves
beyond the reach of justice.
But the Mother shows
her mercy to those
who kneel before her.
I take full responsibility
for my many sins
and unburden myself
of my desires.
My only remaining wish
is to devote my life
to the Seven.
May I be a living example
of their grace
for others to witness.
You understand fully
what this means?
I do.
I will abandon
the Tyrell name and
all that goes with it.
I will renounce my lordship
and my claims on Highgarden.
I will never marry
and I will never
father children.
HIGH SPARROW: Brother Loras,
(SHUDDERING)
I ask you
to dedicate your life
to the seven gods.
Will you fight to defend
your faith against
heretics and apostates?
I will.
(CONTINUES SHUDDERING)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING) No,
I can't let them...
Faith is the way,
Father.
(LORAS BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GROANS)
(DOOR OPENS)
TOMMEN: All right.
I'm ready.
I have to go. I'm...
I'm late for the trial.
MARGAERY: You mutilated him.
You gave me your word.
And I have kept
my word.
Once the Queen Mother's
trial is concluded,
Brother Loras
is free to leave.
And where is
the Queen Mother?
Her litter never
left the Red Keep.
It appears the Queen Mother
doesn't wish to attend
her own trial.
HIGH SPARROW:
Go to the Red Keep
and show her the way.
Get the others.
(PANTING)
Where's the king?
Elsewhere,
I'm afraid.
What's the meaning
of this?
I was told that...
Ah.
I have more
important things
to do with my time
than waste them
in the presence...
Please, Grand Maester.
I bear you no ill will.
Please forgive me
if you can.
(PANTING)
QYBURN: This pains me,
my lord.
Whatever your faults,
you do not deserve
to die alone in such
a cold, dark place.
But sometimes before
we can usher in the new,
the old must be put to rest.
(ALL GRUNTING)
(PYCELLE GROANING)
(FLESH SQUELCHING)
(GROANING CONTINUES)
The longer you wait,
the worse it'll be for you.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(WHEEZING)
What are you doing?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTING)
There's something wrong.
(CHUCKLES)
You have nothing
to fear, Your Grace.
The trial
will begin shortly.
Cersei is not here.
Tommen is not here.
Why do you think
they're not here?
If the accused
is not here, she will
be tried regardless.
We cannot escape
the justice of the gods...
Forget about the
bloody gods and listen
to what I'm telling you.
Cersei understands
the consequences
of her absence
and she is absent anyway,
which means she
does not intend to suffer
those consequences.
The trial can wait.
We all need to leave.
(SCOFFS)
(GRUNTING)
We all need
to leave now!
(SCATTERED CHATTER)
Loras.
Stay with me.
(ALL CLAMORING)
Let me through.
Let me through!
MARGAERY: Get out of my way!
(GROANING)
Let us through!
(GRUNTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(RUMBLING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(ALL SCREAMING
IN THE DISTANCE)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(GROANS)
(SPITS)
CERSIE: Confess.
Confess.
No.
CERSIE: Confess.
(SPITS)
(GASPING)
CERSIE: Confess.
It felt good.
Beating me,
starving me,
frightening me,
humiliating me.
You didn't do it because
you cared about my atonement.
You did it because
it felt good.
I understand.
I do things because
they feel good.
I drink because
it feels good.
I killed my husband
because it felt good
to be rid of him.
I fuck my brother
because it feels good
to feel him inside me.
I lie about
fucking my brother
because it feels good
to keep our son safe
from hateful hypocrites.
I killed your High Sparrow
and all his little Sparrows.
All his septons,
all his septas,
all his filthy soldiers,
because it felt good
to watch them burn.
It felt good to imagine
their shock and their pain.
No thought has ever
given me greater joy.
(SCOFFS)
Even confessing feels good
under the right circumstances.
You've always been quiet.
I said my face
would be the last thing
you saw before you died.
Do you remember?
Good.
I'm glad to see your face.
I'm ready to meet the gods.
What?
Now?
Today?
You're not
going to die today.
You're not going to die
for quite a while.
Ser Gregor.
This is Ser Gregor Clegane.
He's quiet, too.
Your gods have forsaken you.
This is your god now.
No.
Shame.
(CRYING)
(WAILING)
Shame.
(WAILING CONTINUES)
(SCREAMING)
MAN: I'm very sorry,
Your Grace.
Very sorry.
(ALL SHOUTING IN THE DISTANCE)
(DOOR CLOSES)
WALDER: For House Lannister!
ALL: Hear me roar!
(ALL CHEERING)
For House Frey!
ALL: We stand together!
(ALL CHEERING)
May we stand together
through the centuries,
good friends to the last.
(ALL CHEERING)
And when we drive our swords
through our enemies' hearts,
may we speak the words
of our alliance,
"The Freys and the Lannisters
"send their regards."
(ALL CHEERING)
(SCATTERED CHATTER)
You don't even have
to do anything, do you?
You just sit there,
a rich slab of beef,
and all the birds
come pecking.
You're welcome
to her.
She doesn't want me.
She wants your golden
fingers up her twat.
Those two have
their eyes on you.
(GIGGLING)
They have their
eyes on you, cunt.
Not my type.
Not blonde enough?
Ladies, have you
met Ser Bronn
of the Blackwater,
hero of the Battle
of Blackwater Bay?
There you go.
Maybe I'm not
in the mood.
Fuck it.
No need to call me
"ser" just because
I'm an anointed knight.
(WOMEN GIGGLING)
This came together
rather well.
Your father
would be pleased.
I'm sure he would be.
Huh.
Edmure is back
in a cell.
Can't go killing
my son by law.
It wouldn't be right.
Give the family
a bad name.
So the famous Blackfish
killed by foot soldiers, eh?
Legendary warrior,
everyone said.
Have you done
much fighting yourself,
Lord Frey?
I'm a bit old
for all that.
No, but back
in your day.
The purpose of fighting
is defeating your enemies,
isn't it?
I've defeated mine.
Riverrun belonged
to House Tully
for a thousand years.
Now it's mine.
What do you call that?
Victory.
Yes, you're a great conqueror.
Go on, mock me, boy.
You think I mind?
The Tullys
mocked me for years.
The Starks mocked me.
Where are they now?
You talk about war
as if you're an expert,
but the one battle
I remember you fighting,
you were captured
by Robb Stark, the Young Wolf.
But it doesn't matter.
Here we are now,
two kingslayers.
We know what it's like
to have them grovel
to our faces
and snigger
behind our backs.
We don't mind, do we?
Fear is a marvelous thing.
They don't fear
the Freys, though.
They fear the Lannisters.
We gave you the Riverlands
to hold the Riverlands.
If we have to ride north
and take them back for you
every time you lose them,
why do we need you?
Show me.
Your Grace,
there's no need...
Show me.
QYBURN: What are your thoughts
concerning the king's funeral?
As the Sept of Baelor
is no longer an option,
perhaps a ceremony
in the throne room?
He should be with
his grandfather,
his brother, his sister.
Burn him.
And bury his ashes
where the Sept once stood.
(HORSE WHINNYING)
MAN: Whoa. Whoa.
(RAVENS CAWING)
Hello.
From Lord Commander Snow
at Castle Black.
I'm...
I'm to be
the new maester.
Hmm.
According to our
records, Jeor Mormont
is Lord Commander.
He died.
We received no report from
the maester at Castle Black.
Maester Aemon became
quite ill shortly
after the election.
He's since passed away.
Which is why I'm here.
This is irregular.
Yes, well, I suppose
that life is irregular.
CITADEL MAESTER:
The archmaester will discuss
these irregularities with you.
In the meantime, you are
permitted to use the library.
Follow me.
No women or children.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SIGHS)
(CAWING)
When we had feasts,
our family
would sit up here
and I'd sit
down there.
Could have been worse,
Jon Snow.
You had a family.
You had feasts.
Aye, you're right.
I was luckier than most.
(PANTING)
What is that?
Tell him.
Tell him
who it belonged to.
The Princess Shireen.
Tell him what
you did to her.
Tell him!
(VOICE BREAKING)
We burned her
at the stake.
Why?
The army was trapped.
The horses were dying.
It was the only way.
You burned
a little girl alive!
I only do what
my Lord commands.
If he commands you
to burn children,
your Lord is evil.
We are standing here
because of him.
Jon Snow is alive
because the Lord willed it.
I loved that girl
like she was my own.
She was good.
She was kind.
And you killed her!
So did her father.
So did her mother.
Her own blood knew
it was the only way.
The only way for what?
They all died anyway.
You told everyone
Stannis was the one.
You had him believing it,
all of them fooled.
And you lied.
I didn't lie!
I was wrong.
DAVOS: Aye,
you were wrong.
How many died because
you were wrong?
I ask your leave
to execute this woman
for murder.
She admits to the crime.
Do you have anything
to say for yourself?
I've been ready
to die for many years.
If the Lord was done with me,
so be it, but he's not.
You've seen the
Night King, Jon Snow.
You know the Great War
is still to come.
You know
the army of the dead
will be upon us soon.
And you know I can
help you win that war.
Ride south today.
If you return to the North,
I'll have you hanged
as a murderer.
If you ever
come back this way,
I will execute you myself.
I'm having
the lord's chamber
prepared for you.
Mother and
Father's room?
You should take it.
I'm not a Stark.
You are to me.
You're the Lady of Winterfell.
You deserve it.
We're standing here
because of you.
The battle was lost
until the Knights
of the Vale rode in.
They came because of you.
You told me Lord Baelish
sold you to the Boltons.
He did.
And you trust him?
Only a fool
would trust Littlefinger.
I should have
told you about him,
about the
Knights of the Vale.
I'm sorry.
We need to trust each other.
We can't fight a war
amongst ourselves.
We have so many enemies now.
Jon.
A raven came
from the Citadel.
A white raven.
(SIGHS)
Winter is here.
Well, Father always
promised, didn't he?
OLENNA: The last time
a Tyrell came to Dorne,
he was assassinated.
A hundred red scorpions,
was it?
ELLARIA: You have
nothing to fear from us,
Lady Olenna.
OLENNA: You murder
your own prince,
but you expect me
to trust you?
We invited you
to Dorne because
we needed your help.
You came to Dorne
because you needed
our help.
What is your name
again? Barbaro?
Obara.
You look like
an angry little boy.
Don't presume to tell me
what I need.
Forgive my sister.
What she lacks
in diplomacy,
she makes...
Do shut up, dear.
Anything from you?
No? Good.
Let the grown women speak.
The Lannisters
have declared war
on House Tyrell.
They have declared war
on Dorne.
We must be allies now
if we wish to survive.
Cersei stole
the future from me.
She killed my son.
She killed my grandson.
She killed my granddaughter.
Survival is not
what I'm after now.
ELLARIA:
You're absolutely right.
I chose the wrong words.
It is not survival
I offer.
It is your heart's desire.
(DINGING)
And what is
my heart's desire?
Vengeance.
Justice.
Fire and blood.
Your ships
are nearly ready.
I saw them
painting the sails.
I'm curious to see
how the Dothraki do
on the poison water.
You're not coming
with us.
New strategy?
You want the Second Sons
to attack from the west coast?
If we take Casterly Rock,
the Lannisters will have
nowhere to run when
you hit King's Landing.
You're not going
to Westeros.
You're staying here
with the Second Sons.
There's finally
peace in Meereen.
You will keep the peace
while the people
choose their own leaders.
Fuck Meereen.
Fuck the people.
I'm here for you,
not them.
DAENERYS:
You promised me.
"My sword is yours.
My life is yours."
This is what I command.
If I'm going to rule
in Westeros, I'll need
to make alliances.
The best way to make alliances
is with marriage.
Who are you marrying
this time?
I don't know. Maybe no one.
But you need to lure
all the noble houses
to the table?
Are you a queen
or fish bait?
I can't bring
a lover to Westeros.
A king wouldn't
think twice about it.
So that's what you want?
To be my mistress?
I'm not proud.
I don't care what perfumed
aristocrat sits beside you
in the throne room.
I don't want a crown.
I want you.
I love you.
And I make you happy.
You know I do.
Bring me with you.
Let me fight for you.
I can't.
The dwarf told you
to do this?
DAENERYS: No one
tells me to do anything.
Clever fellow.
Can't argue
with his logic.
I'm no use to you
over there.
Don't get angry.
I'm not angry.
I'm full of self-pity.
Who comes after you?
Who can ever follow
Daenerys Stormborn,
the Mother of Dragons?
A great number of women,
I imagine.
Specific orders
will be left for you
regarding the welfare
of Meereen and
the Bay of Dragons.
The Bay of Dragons?
We can't call it
Slaver's Bay anymore,
can we?
You'll get that throne
you want so badly,
I'm sure of it.
I hope it brings
you happiness.
I pity the lords
of Westeros.
They have no idea
what's coming for them.
Farewell, Daario Naharis.
How did he take it?
No tears.
I know it was
hard for you.
You turned away a man
who truly loves you
because he would
have been a liability
in the Seven Kingdoms.
That's the kind of
self-sacrifice that
makes for a good ruler,
if it's any consolation.
It's not.
No, I suppose not.
I'm terrible
at consoling.
Yes, you really are.
All right, how about
the fact that this is
actually happening?
You have your armies,
you have your ships,
you have your dragons.
Everything you've ever
wanted since you were old
enough to want anything,
it's all yours
for the taking.
Are you afraid?
Good.
You're in the
great game now.
And the great
game's terrifying.
The only people who aren't
afraid of failure are
madmen like your father.
Do you know
what frightens me?
I said farewell
to a man who loves me.
A man I thought
I cared for.
And I felt nothing.
Just impatient
to get on with it.
He wasn't the first
to love you
and he won't
be the last.
Well, you have
completely failed
to console me.
For what it's worth,
I've been a cynic
for as long as
I can remember.
Everyone's always
asking me to believe
in things.
Family, gods,
kings, myself.
It was often tempting
until I saw where
belief got people.
So I said,
"No, thank you,"
to belief.
And yet, here I am.
I believe in you.
It's embarrassing, really.
I'd swear you my sword,
but I don't
actually own a sword.
It's your counsel I need.
It's yours.
Now and always.
Good.
I, um...
I had something
made for you.
I'm not sure
if it's right.
Tyrion Lannister,
I name you
Hand of the Queen.
You're not
one of mine,
are you?
No, my lord.
Didn't think so.
Too pretty.
(SMACKS)
(GROANS)
Where are my damn
moron sons?
Black Walder and
Lothar promised
to be here by midday.
They're here, my lord.
Well, what are they doing,
trimming their cunt hairs?
Tell them
to come here now.
But they're already
here, my lord.
Here, my lord.
They weren't easy to carve.
Especially Black Walder.
What...
My name is Arya Stark.
I want you to know that.
The last thing
you're ever going to see
is a Stark smiling
down at you as you die.
(UNSHEATHES KNIFE)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
(GURGLING)
LITTLEFINGER:
Forgive me, my lady.
If you're at prayer.
I'm done with all that.
I came here every day
when I was a girl.
I prayed to be
somewhere else.
Back then I only thought
about what I wanted,
never about what I had.
I was a stupid girl.
LITTLEFINGER:
You were a child.
What do you want?
I thought you knew
what I wanted.
I was wrong.
No, you weren't.
Every time I'm faced
with a decision,
I close my eyes and
see the same picture.
Whenever I consider
an action, I ask myself
will this action help to make
this picture a reality?
Pull it out of my mind
and into the world?
And I only act
if the answer is yes.
A picture of me
on the Iron Throne
and you by my side.
It's a pretty picture.
News of this battle will
spread quickly through
the Seven Kingdoms.
I've declared
for House Stark
for all to hear.
You've declared for
other houses before,
Lord Baelish.
It's never stopped you
from serving yourself.
The past is gone
for good.
You can sit here
mourning its departure
or you can prepare
for the future.
You, my love,
are the future
of House Stark.
Who should the North
rally behind?
A trueborn daughter
of Ned and Catelyn Stark
born here at Winterfell
or a motherless bastard
born in the South?
BENJEN: This is where
I leave you.
You're not coming
with us?
The Wall is not
just ice and stone.
Ancient spells were carved
into its foundations.
Strong magic
to protect men
from what lies beyond.
And while it stands,
the dead cannot pass.
I cannot pass.
(HORSE NICKERS)
Where will you go?
The Great War is coming
and I still fight
for the living.
I'll do what I can,
as long as I can.
Thank you,
Uncle Benjen.
I wish you both good fortune.
(BRANDON GRUNTS)
Are you sure
you're ready for this?
I'm the
Three-Eyed Raven now.
I have to be ready
for this.
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(WOMAN WAILING)
WOMAN: Ned?
YOUNG NED: Lyanna.
Is that you?
Is that really you?
You're not a dream?
No, I'm not a dream.
I'm here.
Right here.
I've missed you,
big brother.
I've missed you, too.
(CRYING)
I want to be brave.
You are.
I'm not.
I don't want to die.
You're not going to die.
Get her some water.
No, no water.
Just listen.
Is there a maester?
Listen to me, Ned.
(INAUDIBLE)
If Robert finds out,
he'll kill him.
You know he will.
You have to protect him.
Promise me, Ned.
Promise me.
(BABY WHIMPERING)
Promise me, Ned.
Promise me.
You can't expect
Knights of the Vale to side
with wildling invaders.
TORMUND: We didn't invade.
We were invited.
Not by me.
The free folk, the
Northerners, and the Knights
of the Vale fought bravely,
fought together, and we won.
My father used to say
we find our true friends
on the battlefield.
CLEY CERWYN:
The Boltons
are defeated.
The war is over.
Winter has come.
If the maesters are right,
it'll be the coldest one
in a thousand years.
We should ride home
and wait out
the coming storms.
JON: The war is not over.
And I promise you, friend,
the true enemy won't
wait out the storm.
He brings the storm.
(SCATTERED MURMURS)
Your son was butchered
at the Red Wedding,
Lord Manderly,
but you refused the call.
You swore allegiance
to House Stark, Lord Glover,
but in their hour
of greatest need,
you refused the call.
And you, Lord Cerwyn,
your father was skinned alive
by Ramsay Bolton.
Still you refused the call.
But House Mormont remembers.
The North remembers.
We know no king but
the King in the North
whose name is Stark.
I don't care
if he's a bastard.
Ned Stark's blood
runs through his veins.
He's my king
from this day
until his last day.
(SCATTERED CHATTER)
Lady Mormont speaks harshly
and truly.
My son died for Robb Stark,
the Young Wolf.
I didn't think we'd find
another king in my lifetime.
I didn't commit
my men to your cause
'cause I didn't want
more Manderlys
dying for nothing.
But I was wrong!
Jon Snow avenged
the Red Wedding!
He is the White Wolf.
The King in the North!
I did not fight
beside you on the field
and I will regret that
until my dying day.
A man can only admit
when he was wrong
and ask forgiveness.
There's nothing
to forgive, my lord.
There will be more
fights to come!
House Glover will
stand behind House Stark
as we have
for a thousand years!
And I will stand
behind Jon Snow,
the King in the North!
The King in the North!
(ALL CHEERING)
ALL: (CHANTING)
The King in the North!
SOLDIER: Company halt!
Halt!
Come on.
QYBURN: I now proclaim
Cersei of the House Lannister,
First of Her Name,
Queen of the Andals
and the First Men,
Protector of
the Seven Kingdoms.
Long may she reign.
ALL: Long may she reign.
(MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(SCREECHING)