(EXPLOSIONS)
(MAN 1 SHOUTS IN VALYRIAN)
(MEN GRUNTING)
(MAN 2 YELLS IN VALYRIAN)
(MAN 3 SHOUTS IN VALYRIAN)
(MAN SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(RUMBLING)
(WALLS RATTLING)
Despite appearances,
I think you'll find
the city's on the rise.
(EXPLOSIONS CONTINUE OUTSIDE)
Perhaps we
should take shelter.
The city's on the rise?
Meereen is strong.
Commerce has
returned to the markets.
The people are behind you.
(EXPLOSION CONTINUES)
Well, not all the people,
of course.
No ruler that ever lived
had the support
of all the people.
But the rebirth of Meereen
is the cause of this violence.
The Masters cannot
let Meereen succeed.
Because if Meereen succeeds,
a city without slavery,
a city without Masters...
(RUMBLING)
It proves that no
one needs a Master.
Good.
Shall we begin?
Do we have a plan?
I will crucify
the Masters.
I will set
their fleets afire,
kill every last one
of their soldiers,
and return their
cities to the dirt.
That is my plan.
You don't approve?
You once told me
you knew
what your father was.
Did you know his
plans for King's Landing
when the Lannister
armies were at his gates?
Probably not.
Well, he told my brother,
and Jaime told me.
He had caches of wildfire
hidden under the Red Keep,
the Guildhalls,
the Sept of Baelor,
all the major
thoroughfares.
He would have burned
every one of his citizens.
The loyal ones
and the traitors.
Every man,
woman, and child.
That's why Jaime
killed him.
This is entirely different.
You're talking
about destroying cities.
It's not entirely different.
I'd like to suggest
an alternate approach.
(EXPLOSION)
Once before,
I offered you peace.
If you had not
been so arrogant,
you could have
returned to your homeland
with a fleet of ships.
Instead, you will flee
Slaver's Bay on foot,
like the beggar queen
you are.
We are here to
discuss terms of surrender,
not to trade insults.
The terms are simple.
You and your foreign friends
will abandon the great pyramid
and the city of Meereen.
The unsullied you stole
from Kraznys mo Nakloz
will remain to be sold again
to the highest bidder.
The translator you stole
from Kraznys mo Nakloz
will remain to be sold again
to the highest bidder.
The dragons beneath
the great pyramid
will be slaughtered.
We obviously didn't
communicate clearly.
We're here to discuss
your surrender, not mine.
I imagine it's difficult
adjusting to the new reality.
(RUMBLING IN THE DISTANCE)
Your reign is over.
My reign has just begun.
(DRAGON SCREECHES)
(ALL SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(SCREECHING)
(ALL SHOUTING)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
(MEN SHOUTING IN THE DISTANCE)
(HORSES GALLOPING)
(ALL SHOUTING)
(ALL SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
Dracarys.
(TITTERING)
(ALL SHOUTING)
(WOOD CREAKING)
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
(DRAGONS SCREECHING
AT A DISTANCE)
(MEN YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
Thank you for the armada.
Our queen does love ships.
Now, last time we spoke,
we made a pact.
You violated that pact.
You declared war upon us.
Though our queen does
have a forgiving nature,
this cannot be forgiven.
Our queen insists
that one of you must die
as punishment
for your crimes.
It always seems a bit
abstract, doesn't it?
Other people dying?
Him. He should die.
BELICHO: Yes, him.
RAZDAL: He's not one of us.
He's an outsider, a lowborn.
He does not speak for us.
Please.
(GRUNTS)
(YEZZAN BREATHING HEAVILY)
Tell your people
what happened here.
Tell them you live by
the grace of her majesty.
When they come forward
with notions of retribution
or ideas about
returning the slave cities
to their former glory,
remind them
what happened
when Daenerys Stormborn
and her dragons
came to Meereen.
(DRAGONS SCREECHING
AT A DISTANCE)
(HORSES WHINNYING)
You don't have to be here.
Yes, I do.
(NICKERING)
My beloved wife.
I've missed you terribly.
Thank you for returning
Lady Bolton safely.
Now, dismount
and kneel before me,
surrender your army
and proclaim me
the true Lord of Winterfell
and Warden of the North.
I will pardon you
for deserting
the Night's Watch.
I will pardon
these treasonous lords
for betraying my house.
Come, bastard,
you don't have the men,
you don't have the horses,
and you don't
have Winterfell.
Why lead those poor
souls into slaughter?
There's no need
for a battle.
Get off your horse and kneel.
I'm a man of mercy.
You're right.
There's no need for a battle.
Thousands of men
don't need to die.
Only one of us.
Let's end this the old way.
You against me.
(CHUCKLING)
I keep hearing stories
about you, bastard.
The way people in
the North talk about you,
you're the greatest swordsman
who ever walked.
Maybe you are that good.
Maybe not.
I don't know
if I'd beat you.
But I know that
my army will beat yours.
I have 6,000 men.
You have, what, half that?
Not even?
Aye, you have the numbers.
Will your men
want to fight for you
when they hear you
wouldn't fight for them?
He's good. Very good.
Tell me, will you let
your little brother die
because you're too
proud to surrender?
How do we know
you have him?
(HORSE WHINNIES)
RAMSAY: Now,
if you want to save...
You're going to die
tomorrow, Lord Bolton.
Sleep well.
She's a fine woman,
your sister.
I look forward to
having her back in my bed.
And you're all
fine-looking men.
My dogs are
desperate to meet you.
I haven't fed
them for seven days.
They're ravenous.
I wonder which parts
they'll try first.
Your eyes?
Your balls?
We'll find out
soon enough.
In the morning,
then, bastard.
JON: If he was smart,
he'd stay inside the walls of
Winterfell and wait us out.
That's not his way.
He knows
the North is watching.
If the other houses
sense weakness on his part,
they'll stop fearing him.
He can't have that.
Fear is his power.
It's his weakness, too.
His men don't want
to fight for him.
They're forced
If they feel
the tide turning...
It's not his men
that worry me.
It's his horses.
I know what mounted
knights can do to us.
You and Stannis cut through us
like piss through snow.
We're digging trenches
all along our flanks.
They won't be able to hit us
the way that Stannis hit you,
in a double envelopment.
A pincer move.
They won't be able to
hit us from the sides.
Good.
It's crucial that we
let them charge at us.
They've got the numbers,
we need the patience.
If we let him buckle
our center, he'll pursue.
Then we'll have him
surrounded on three sides.
Did you really think
that cunt would
fight you man-to-man?
No.
But I wanted to
make him angry.
I want him coming
at us full tilt.
We should all
get some sleep.
TORMUND: Rest, Jon Snow.
We need you sharp tomorrow.
SANSA: So,
you've met the enemy,
drawn up your battle plans.
Aye, for what they're worth.
You've known him
for the space of
a single conversation,
you and your
trusted advisors,
and you sit around
making your plans
on how to defeat
a man you don't know.
I lived with him.
I know the way
his mind works.
I know how he
likes to hurt people.
Did it ever once occur
to you that I might
have some insight?
You're right.
You think he's going
to fall into your trap.
He won't.
He's the one
who lays traps.
JON: He's overconfident.
He plays with people.
He's far better
at it than you.
He's been doing
it all his life.
Aye, and what have I
been doing all my life?
Playing with broomsticks?
I fought beyond
the wall against worse
than Ramsay Bolton.
I've defended the wall
from worse than Ramsay Bolton.
You don't know him.
All right, tell me.
What should we do?
How do we get Rickon back?
We'll never get him back.
Rickon is Ned Stark's
trueborn son,
which makes him
a greater threat
to Ramsay than you,
a bastard, or me, a girl.
As long as he lives,
Ramsay's claim
to Winterfell
will be contested,
which means
he won't live long.
We can't give up
on our brother.
SANSA: Listen
to me, please.
He wants you to
make a mistake.
JON: Of course he does.
What should I do differently?
I don't know.
I don't know
anything about battles.
Just don't do
what he wants you to do.
Aye, that's good advice.
You think that's obvious?
Well, it is a bit obvious.
If you had asked
for my advice earlier,
I would have told you
not to attack Winterfell
until we had a larger force,
or is that obvious, too?
When will we have
a larger force?
We've pleaded with every
house that'll have us.
The Blackfish can't help us.
We're lucky to
have this many men.
It's not enough.
No, it's not enough.
It's what we have.
Battles have been won
against greater odds.
If Ramsay wins,
I'm not going
back there alive.
Do you understand me?
I won't ever let
him touch you again.
I'll protect you, I promise.
No one can protect me.
No one can protect anyone.
(SIGHS)
DAVOS: You think
there's hope?
TORMUND: I've never seen
these Bolton fuckers fight.
And they've never
seen the free folk fight,
so, yes, there's hope.
You want to avenge
your king, don't you?
It wasn't the Boltons
defeated Stannis.
It was Stannis himself.
I loved the man.
He lifted me up and
made me something.
But he had demons
in his skull
whispering foul things.
You saw these demons?
What?
No, it's a manner
of speaking.
Not actual demons.
Oh.
Well, you loved
that cunt Stannis
and I loved
the man he burned.
Mance didn't have
demons in his skull.
He didn't torch people
or listen to some red witch.
I believed in him.
I thought he was
the man to lead us
through the Long Night.
But I was wrong,
just like you.
Maybe that was our mistake,
believing in kings.
Jon Snow's not a king.
No, he's not.
I need a good drink
to help me sleep
the night before a fight.
You want some?
I have a jug of
sour goat's milk
stronger than any
of that grape water
you southern twats
like sucking on.
No, thanks.
It does sound delicious,
but I better
keep a clear head.
I can never sleep
the night before a battle.
So what do you
do all night?
I walk. Think and walk.
Think and walk
until I'm far
enough away from camp
that no one can hear
me shitting my guts out.
(LAUGHING)
Happy shitting.
(MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
My lady.
You weren't at
the war council.
I'm not a soldier.
Any advice?
Don't lose.
If I do, if I fall...
Don't bring me back.
I'll have to try.
I'm ordering you
not to bring me back.
I am not your servant,
Jon Snow.
You're in my camp.
I'm the commander.
I serve the Lord of Light.
I do what he commands.
How do you know
what he commands?
I interpret his signs
as well as I can.
If the Lord didn't
want me to bring you back,
how did I bring you back?
I have no power.
Only what he gives me,
and he gave me you.
Why?
I don't know.
Maybe you're only needed
for this small part of his
plan and nothing else.
Maybe he brought
you here to die again.
What kind of god
would do something like that?
The one we've got.
(HORN BLOWING)
(HORN CONTINUES)
Last time we saw each other
was at Winterfell, yes?
You were making
jokes about my height,
I seem to recall.
Everyone who makes a joke
about a dwarf's height
thinks he's the only person
ever to make a joke
about a dwarf's height.
"The height of nobility,"
"a man of your stature,"
"someone to look up to."
You're all making
the same five or six jokes.
It was a long time ago.
It was.
And how have things
been going for you since then?
Not so well, I gather.
Can't imagine you
would have murdered
the Stark boys
if things had
been going well.
I didn't murder
the Stark boys.
But I did things
that were just
as bad or worse.
And he paid for them.
Doesn't seem like it.
He's still alive.
It was complicated
for you, I'm sure,
growing up at Winterfell.
Never quite
knowing who you were.
But then, we all live
complicated lives, don't we?
You've brought us 100 ships
from the Iron Fleet
with men to sail them.
In return, I expect
you want me to
support your claim
to the throne
of the Iron Islands?
Not my claim. Hers.
And what's wrong with you?
I'm not fit to rule.
We can agree
upon that at least.
Has the Iron Islands
ever had a queen before?
No more than Westeros.
Our Uncle Euron
returned home
after a long absence.
He murdered our father
and took the
Salt Throne from Yara.
He would have
murdered us if we'd stayed.
Lord Tyrion tells me
your father was
a terrible king.
You and I have
that in common.
We do.
And both murdered
by a usurper as well.
Will their ships be enough?
With the former
Masters' fleet, possibly.
Barely.
There are more than
100 ships in the Iron Fleet.
THEON: There are,
and Euron is building more.
He's going to
offer them to you.
So why shouldn't
I wait for him?
The Iron Fleet
isn't all he's bringing.
He also wants
to give you...
His big cock,
I think he said.
Euron's offer is also
an offer of marriage, you see.
You won't get one
without the other.
And I imagine
your offer is free of
any marriage demands?
I never demand,
but I'm up for anything,
really.
THEON: He murdered our father
and would have murdered us.
He'll murder you
as soon as you
have what he wants.
The Seven Kingdoms.
All of them.
And you don't want
the Seven Kingdoms?
THEON: Your ancestors
defeated ours and took
the Iron Islands.
We ask you
to give them back.
And that's all?
We'd like you to help us
murder an uncle or two
who don't think
a woman's fit to rule.
Reasonable.
What if everyone
starts demanding
their independence?
She's not demanding,
she's asking.
The others are
free to ask as well.
Our fathers were evil men,
all of us here.
They left the world
worse than they found it.
We're not going to do that.
We're going to leave the world
better than we found it.
You will support my claim
as queen of the Seven Kingdoms
and respect the integrity
of the Seven Kingdoms.
No more reaving, roving,
raiding, or raping.
That's our way of life.
No more.
(HORSES NICKERING)
Do you like games,
little man?
Let's play a game.
Run to your brother.
The sooner
you make it to him,
the sooner you get
to see him again.
That's it.
That's the game.
Easy.
Ready?
Go.
No, you have to run,
remember?
Those are the rules.
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(GASPING)
Don't.
Prepare to charge.
MAN 1: Draw!
MAN 2: Draw!
MAN 3: Draw!
MAN 4: Loose!
Hyah! Hyah!
(WHINNIES)
Go! Go!
Follow your commander!
(MEN SHOUTING)
Run and fight!
(ROARS)
(ALL SHOUTING)
(GRUNTS)
MAN 1: Nock!
Draw!
MAN 2: Draw!
MAN 1: Loose!
MAN 2: Loose!
Hyah!
(WHINNYING)
(GRUNTS)
Now.
KARSTARK: Cavalry, charge!
(HORSES WHINNYING)
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(HORSES WHINNYING)
(EXHALES)
(JON GRUNTS)
(MEN GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
Nock!
MEN: Nock!
MAN 1: Draw!
MAN 2: Draw!
Draw!
MAN 3: Draw!
(GROANING)
We'll just kill our own men.
Stand down.
Loose!
MAN 3: Loose!
(WIND HOWLING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Get word...
(GROANING)
(SHOUTING)
(WHINNYING)
Loose!
(GRUNTING)
MEN: Loose!
(ALL GROANING)
Loose!
MEN: Loose!
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
We may as well be
taking shits back here.
Follow!
(ALL SHOUTING)
It's time, go.
Who owns the North?
MEN: We do!
Show me!
(MEN SHOUTING)
(YELLS)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING CONTINUES)
Hey!
(MEN SHOUTING)
(GRUNTS)
(SHIELDS CLANGING)
(BOLTON SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
MAN: Infantry, advance!
(BOLTON SOLDIERS
GRUNTING IN UNISON)
(YELPING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING CONTINUES)
(GROANS)
(MEN SHOUTING)
With me, lads!
Break their line!
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMING)
(SHOUTING)
(GRUNTING)
MAN: Help me!
(SCREAMING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(RIPPING)
MAN 1: Tormund!
MAN 2: Get him back!
BOLTON COMMANDER:
Infantry, advance.
(GRUNTING IN UNISON)
MAN 1: Both sides!
MAN 2: Fall back!
Fall back!
(GASPS)
Fuck this, come on!
(GRUNTS)
We're going home!
(MEN SHOUTING)
(GRUNTING)
(SHOUTING)
(CRIES OUT)
(CONTINUES GASPING)
(INHALING DEEPLY)
(GROANING)
(HORN BLOWING)
(KARSTARK GRUNTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(YELLING)
(CHOMPING)
(SCREAMS)
(SPITS)
(HORN CONTINUES)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(SHOUTS)
MAN 1:Open the gate!
(INDISTINCT YELLING)
MAN 2: Archers to the wall.
Their army's gone.
Our army's gone.
We have Winterfell.
They don't have
the men for a siege.
All we have to do is wait.
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
MAN 2: Archers! To the wall!
(MEN CLAMORING)
(POUNDING CONTINUES)
(GRUNTING)
(GIANT GROANING)
(ROARING)
(GROANING)
(ROARS)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(GRUNTING)
(EXHALES)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(JON GASPS)
You suggested
one-on-one combat,
didn't you?
I've reconsidered.
I think that sounds
like a wonderful idea.
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
(RAMSAY CHOKING)
(JON BREATHING HEAVILY)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
We're going to bury
my brother in the crypt
next to my father.
Jon.
Where is he?
(WATER DRIPPING)
(GROANS SOFTLY)
(COUGHS)
RAMSAY: Ah!
Sansa.
Hello, Sansa.
Is this where
I'll be staying now?
No.
Our time together is
about to come to an end.
That's all right.
You can't kill me.
I'm part of you now.
Your words will disappear.
Your house will disappear.
Your name will disappear.
All memory of
you will disappear.
(DOGS GROWLING)
(GROWLING CONTINUES)
My hounds will never harm me.
You haven't fed
them in seven days.
You said it yourself.
They're loyal beasts.
SANSA: They were.
Now they're starving.
(GROWLING CONTINUES)
(HISSING) Sit.
Down.
Down!
Down! Down!
(PANTING)
Down!
(SCREAMING)
(DOGS BARKING)
(CRUNCHING)
(RAMSAY CONTINUES SCREAMING)
(DOGS CONTINUE BARKING)