LADY CRANE: My son.
My firstborn son.
My child king, hush.
Listen to the gods,
for you they sing.
Fight no more, sweet child.
Your wars are won.
The wolves are buried
and the false stag done.
Shut your blue eyes,
my love.
Let the crown fall.
The Father above
beckons you to his hall.
In seventh heaven
I'll see you once more.
But now I seek vengeance
on Sansa the whore
and my brother the Imp
who killed his own king.
Born amongst lions,
our curse from within.
I will slay him, I swear.
With noose or with knife,
though it take me
a fortnight,
a moon or my life.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
BOBONO: What is that
I hear and smell?
Someone I'll
soon send to hell.
(AUDIENCE BOOING)
It's time to see
if truth they told
who said Tywin Lannister
shits gold.
MAN: Get the wig!
IZEMBARO:
You beast, you beast.
You killed my wife.
And now you've taken
your father's life.
(SIGHS)
No worse child ever
stained this land.
I curse the day
I named you. (GROANS)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
BOBONO: My greatest crime!
(THUDDING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
You're good at that.
Where did you learn?
I'm a jealous woman.
I've always liked bad men
and they've always liked me.
They'd come home,
wherever home
was that night,
stinking of some
whore's perfume.
So we'd fight and
I'd put a hole in them.
And then I'd feel terrible,
so I'd patch them up.
I got good at
patching them up.
And good at
putting holes in them.
(CHUCKLES) And that.
What happened
to the actress?
The one who
wanted you dead.
Bianca.
She'll have a hard time
finding work as an actress
after what I did
to her face.
(SLURPING) Mmm.
I never did learn to cook.
But eat.
Eat, you need it.
The company is moving on
to Pentos soon.
You should come with us.
I can't.
Why not?
Got a feeling you'd be
good at this sort of work.
And besides,
we need a new actress.
I don't think I could
remember all the lines.
Come with us.
What's left for you here?
You wouldn't be safe.
Not while she's
looking for me.
Who?
She doesn't have a name.
Where will you go?
Essos is east and
Westeros is west.
But what's west
of Westeros?
I don't know.
Nobody does.
That's where
all the maps stop.
The edge of
the world, maybe.
I'd like to see that.
(GROANS)
(SIGHS)
What's that?
Milk of the poppy.
I don't want any.
Sleep is the only way
you'll heal.
Trust me, if my soup
didn't kill you,
nothing will.
(MEN LAUGHING)
Thing about Gatins, right,
is he used to be pretty.
I was a famous kisser.
You lads know
how to kiss proper?
Course we do.
This is for masters,
this technique.
You're not ready.
I'm ready.
He says he's ready.
All right.
Now, pay attention.
You put your left hand
on the back
of the lady's head.
Your right hand holds
the small of the lady's
back like so.
Very romantic.
You take your
middle finger, yeah,
and you jam it
right up her bunghole.
(LAUGHING)
So fucking close!
It smells like
pussy to me.
Look at him.
You get hard, boy?
Fuck you!
Disgusting old twats.
(LAUGHING)
Got off on that, did you,
you old fuck?
(GASPS)
(GROWLS)
(GRUNTING)
(WHIMPERING)
Where's the other one?
The one with the yellow cloak.
Fuck you!
Those are your last words,
"Fuck you"? Come on,
you can do better.
Cunt!
You're shit at dying,
you know that?
(SHOUTING)
(SQUELCHING)
(THUDDING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(LOWING)
I'd call that
a successful gambit.
Would you?
Look around.
The city has
come back to life.
You made a pact
with fanatics.
I did and it worked.
If you shaved your beard
with a straight razor,
you'd say the razor worked.
That doesn't mean
it won't cut your throat.
Spoken like a man
who has never had to shave.
I'm going to miss you.
I know.
I hope you're right about
this expedition of yours.
If I don't return,
you'll know I was wrong.
We need friends
in Westeros.
And we need ships.
Most of all,
we need our queen.
She'll come back.
She has to.
My heart's been broken
too many times already.
I'll walk the rest
of the way myself.
I can't go off
on a secret mission
in the company of the most
famous dwarf in the city.
Varys.
The most famous dwarf
in the world.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Your Grace, several members
of the Faith Militant
have been permitted entry
to the Red Keep.
Have been permitted?
That's rather a tortured way
of putting it.
They demand to see you,
Your Grace.
Who permitted them
inside the Red Keep?
The king is aware
of their presence?
He is, Your Grace.
He's currently in his
chambers at prayer.
Your Grace,
His Holiness the High Septon
wishes to speak with you
at the Great Sept of Baelor.
His Holiness the High Septon
is welcome to see me here
in the Red Keep.
Your Grace, this is
not a request.
It is a request,
Cousin Lancel.
You are asking me
for something,
I'm refusing.
The High Septon
commands you.
Are you sure
you want to refuse him?
He promised me I could
stay in the Red Keep
until my trial.
He made no such promises.
If you refuse to come
of your own free will...
Get out.
Move aside, ser.
(RASPY BREATHING)
Order your man to step aside
or there will be violence.
I choose violence.
(GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
(SNAPPING)
Please tell His High Holiness
he's always welcome to visit.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Looks like a siege,
my lady.
You have a keen
military mind, Pod.
My lady. My lady.
Who goes there?
State your business!
My name is
Brienne of Tarth.
Please inform
Ser Jaime Lannister
I've come to speak with him.
Tell him I have his sword.
(MEN SHOUTING)
(GRUNTING)
Getting a bit old to be
a squire, aren't we?
(COUGHING)
(LAUGHING)
Podrick fucking Payne.
I thought you'd be
dead by now.
Not yet.
(LAUGHS)
Are they in there?
Uh-huh.
You think they're fucking?
What?
No.
Why not? I'd fuck her.
You'd fuck her,
wouldn't you?
I'm her squire.
Oh.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, he'd fuck her,
that's for sure.
And she'd fuck him,
don't you think?
The way she looks at him.
The way all women look at him
is frankly irritating.
I preferred working
with the little brother
on that account.
Come on, you're the one
with the magic cock.
You must have
shown it to her by now.
She's training me to fight.
Is she? Oh.
An hour in the morning,
an hour at night.
Every day.
Then how come an old cunt
like me can still sneak up
and murder you?
Well, that's a different
sort of fighting.
Now, that's the truth,
isn't it?
You want to learn
that sort of fighting?
All right.
All right, let's start
with your footwork.
Show me your stance.
Now listen to me, Pod.
See how your feet
are about a yard apart?
Lesson number one,
assume everyone
wants to hit you.
'Cause they do, Pod.
Everyone wants to hit
a fucking squire.
Do it again.
Come on, don't sulk.
JAIME: I never thought
you'd find her.
I just assumed
Sansa was dead.
Why would you assume that?
In my experience,
girls like her
don't live very long.
I don't think you know
many girls like her.
Well, I'm proud of you.
I am. You fulfilled
your oath to Catelyn Stark
against all odds.
Of course, my sister
wants Sansa dead.
The girl is still a suspect
in Joffrey's murder,
so there is that
complication.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I've come
for the Blackfish.
You're welcome to have him.
Lady Sansa desires to
take her ancestral seat
back from the Boltons
and assume her
rightful position as
Lady of Winterfell.
With what army does she plan
on taking Winterfell?
The Tully army.
They're a bit occupied
at the moment.
I was sent here to reclaim
Riverrun currently defended
by the Tully rebels,
so you can
see the conundrum.
The Tullys are rebels
because they're fighting
for their home?
Riverrun was granted
to the Freys by
royal decree.
As a reward for betraying
Robb Stark and slaughtering
his family.
Exactly.
We shouldn't argue
about politics.
You're a knight,
Ser Jaime.
I know there is
honor in you.
I've seen it myself.
I'm a Lannister.
Don't ask me to
betray my own house.
I do no such thing.
Take Riverrun
without bloodshed.
Ride south again
with your mission complete
and your army intact.
What do you propose?
Allow me to enter Riverrun
under a flag of truce.
Let me try to persuade
the Blackfish to give up
the castle.
Why would he abandon
his ancestral home?
Because you'll allow him
to lead the Tully forces
safely north.
(SIGHS)
Have you ever met
the Blackfish?
No.
He's even more stubborn
than you are.
All right.
Try to talk some
sense into the old goat.
He won't listen,
but his men might.
Not everybody wants to die
for someone else's home.
I need your word.
If I persuade him to
abandon the castle,
you'll grant us
safe passage north.
You have my word.
You have until nightfall.
(SIGHS)
You gave it to me
for a purpose.
I've achieved that purpose.
It's yours.
It will always be yours.
One last thing,
Ser Jaime.
Yes, Lady Brienne?
Should I fail to persuade
the Blackfish to surrender
and if you attack
the castle,
honor compels me to fight
for Sansa's kin.
Of course it does.
To fight you.
Let's hope it doesn't
come to that.
BLACKFISH: I've said no
three times already.
I have a signed letter
from your niece Sansa Stark...
I haven't seen her
since she was a child.
I don't know her signature.
I don't know you.
And I will not surrender.
Double the guards tonight.
The Kingslayer
wants to try us.
I can feel it.
As I have said,
my name is...
Yes, Brienne of Tarth.
I know your father.
Good man.
He always spoke
highly of you.
And if he were here now,
I'd tell him the same
I'm telling you.
If you think I'm abandoning
my family's seat on the
Kingslayer's word of honor,
you're a bloody fool.
Riverrun cannot stand
against the Lannisters
and the Freys.
We can stand longer than
your one-handed friend
thinks we can.
He's not my friend.
No?
Who gave you permission
to cross the siege line
and enter the castle?
Who gave you that sword
with the gold lion
on the pommel?
Ser Jaime kept his word
to your niece Catelyn Stark.
He sent me to find Sansa,
to help her as Catelyn wanted.
He gave me this sword
to protect her.
That is what I have done
and I will continue to do
until the day I die.
(CHUCKLES)
She's exactly
like her mother.
I don't have enough men
to help her take Winterfell.
You have more
than she does.
She wants her home back.
I understand that.
But this is my home.
And if Jaime Lannister
wants it,
he can bloody well take it
the way everyone else does.
Find the maester.
We need to get a raven
north to Sansa.
What should I write?
Tell her I failed.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(DOOR CREAKING SHUT)
There's to be
a royal announcement?
There is.
Why wasn't I informed?
There is to be
a royal announcement
in the throne room
at this very moment.
Where are you going?
To stand by my son.
Your place is
in the gallery
with the other ladies
of the court.
PYCELLE: Your Grace...
TOMMEN: Lords and ladies,
the Faith and the Crown
are the two pillars
that hold up this world.
One collapses,
so does the other.
The Father judges us all.
If you break his laws,
you will be punished.
After conferring with
His Holiness the High Septon,
we have determined
that Loras Tyrell and
Cersei Lannister's trial
will be held in
the Great Sept of Baelor
on the first day of
the Festival of the Mother.
(INDISTINCT MURMURS)
Furthermore, after much
prayer and reflection,
the Crown has decided
that from this day forward,
trial by combat will be
forbidden throughout
the Seven Kingdoms.
The tradition
is a brutish one,
a scheme devised
by corrupt rulers
in order to avoid true
judgment from the gods.
Cersei Lannister and
Loras Tyrell will stand trial
before seven septons
as it was in the earliest
days of the Faith.
Seven blessings to all.
CROWD: Seven blessings.
(DOOR OPENING)
Your Grace.
That old rumor
you told me about.
My little birds
investigated.
And?
Was it just a rumor
or something more?
More.
Much more.
MISSANDEI: You seem happy.
I am happy.
You should both be
happy as well.
Not so long ago,
this city was ready
to devour itself.
Now it's like a man reborn.
I will be happy
when our queen returns.
Why don't you drink?
Why don't either
of you ever drink?
Unsullied never drink.
Why not?
Rules.
And who made these rules?
Your former masters?
Those miserable old shits
didn't want you to be human.
Have a drink with me.
And you?
What's your excuse?
I have tried wine before.
It made me feel funny.
That's how you know
it's working.
Here's to our queen.
Anyone not drinking
is disrespecting our queen.
To Daenerys Stormborn,
Mother of Dragons,
Breaker of Chains,
long may she reign.
Long may she reign.
TYRION: Do you like it?
GREY WORM:
Tastes like it has turned.
Yes, yes. Fermentation.
One day, after our queen
has taken the Seven Kingdoms,
I'd like to have
my own vineyard.
Make my own wine.
The Imp's Delight.
Only my close friends
could drink it.
Tell me a joke,
Missandei of Naath.
I do not know any jokes.
Grey Worm?
Right.
Three lords
walk into a tavern.
A Stark, a Martell
and a Lannister.
They order ale,
but when the barkeep
brings them over,
each of them finds
a fly in his cup.
The Lannister, outraged,
shoves the cup aside
and demands another.
The Martell plucks the fly out
and swallows it whole.
The Stark reaches
into his cup,
pulls out the fly
and shouts,
"Spit it out, you wee shit.
Spit it out."
It's funnier in Westeros.
The Starks and the Lannisters,
I thought these were enemies.
Yes.
A joke is like a story,
Torgo Nudho.
Not a true story,
necessarily.
A story that's supposed
to make you laugh ideally.
Not at the moment, perhaps.
Missandei, do you
like the wine?
I do.
Tell a joke.
Two translators
are on a sinking ship.
The first says,
"Do you know how to swim?"
The second says, "No,
but I can shout for help
in 19 languages."
Ah! (LAUGHS)
That is the worst joke
I ever heard.
MISSANDEI: You don't even
know what a joke is.
I am soldier all my life.
You think I never hear joke?
You lied to us.
I make joke.
(LAUGHING)
More jokes.
I once walked into
a brothel with a honeycomb
and a jackass.
The madam says...
(BELL RINGING)
(GREY WORM
SHOUTING IN VALYRIAN)
(BELLS CONTINUE RINGING)
The Masters have come
for their property.
(MEN SHOUTING)
Lord Edmure.
I apologize for the way
the Freys treated you.
A man of your birth
deserves better.
You have my word
you'll be properly fed
and clothed from now on.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
I have your word?
(SCOFFS)
Oh, good.
Good, that's...
That's a fine thing.
My uncle will never
surrender the castle, ser.
Whatever game you're playing.
The Blackfish
is an old man.
A good death
is all he can hope for.
But you, you have
a child now, I've heard.
A son you sired
on your wedding night.
You're a potent man.
A son I've never met
born of a wife
that I haven't seen since
our first night together.
You should be
with them both.
I can arrange that,
you realize?
Comfortable rooms for you
at Casterly Rock.
A tutor for your boy,
knights to train him
to fight and to ride.
And when he comes of age,
he'll have a keep of his own.
Do you imagine yourself
a decent person?
Is that it?
After you've
massacred my family.
Kept me in a cell for years.
Stolen our lands.
I'll remind you that
our houses are at war.
I'm sorry if this conflict
has inconvenienced you,
but rebelling against
the Crown does have
consequences.
Says the man
who shoved his sword
through his king's back.
Did I give you the impression
that this was a negotiation?
It's not.
You understand.
On some level you understand
that you're an evil man.
I'll leave the judgments
to the gods.
Well, that is convenient
for you.
You're a fine-looking fellow,
aren't you?
(CHUCKLES)
Your square jaw,
your golden armor.
Tell me, I want to know.
I truly do.
How do you
live with yourself?
All of us have to believe
that we're decent, don't we?
You have to sleep at night.
How do you tell yourself
that you're decent
after everything
that you've done?
I was your sister's
prisoner once.
She hit me
on the head with a rock
if I remember correctly.
(LAUGHS)
Yeah.
She should have killed you.
Perhaps, but she didn't.
Catelyn Stark hated me
just like you hate me.
But I didn't hate her.
I admired her.
Far more than her husband
or her son.
Do you think I care
whom you admire
and whom you don't?
No, I don't, but I'm
telling you anyway
because you're my prisoner.
You don't have a choice.
The love she had
for her children,
I was a little awed by it.
Reminded me of my sister.
Oh.
Oh, I see.
You're a madman.
I'm not here
to trade insults.
Your sister was a strong...
Don't talk about Cat!
I'll talk about
whomever I want.
(GRUNTING)
She loved her children.
I suppose all mothers do,
but Catelyn and Cersei,
there's a fierceness
you don't often see.
They'd do anything to
protect their babies.
Start a war.
Burn cities to ash.
Free their worst enemies.
The things we do for love.
You didn't come here
to talk about our sisters.
(PANTING)
That's exactly
why I came here.
I love Cersei.
You can laugh at that
if you want. You can sneer.
Doesn't matter.
She needs me.
And to get back to her,
I have to take Riverrun.
I'll send for
your baby boy.
(GRUNTS)
And I'll launch him into
Riverrun with a catapult.
Because you don't matter
to me, Lord Edmure.
Your son doesn't
matter to me.
The people in the castle
don't matter to me.
Only Cersei.
And if I have to slaughter
every Tully who ever lived
to get back to her,
that's what I'll do.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(GROANS)
GUARD: Who goes there?
Edmure Tully,
son of Hoster Tully
and the rightful
Lord of Riverrun.
I demand entry.
Don't let him in.
He's the Lord of Riverrun.
I have to obey his commands.
He's been their captive
ever since they murdered
his king at the Red Wedding.
Why do you think the people
who murdered his king
at the Red Wedding
would decide to let him
come home?
Because it's a trap,
you idiot.
Don't let him in.
He's my lord, my lord.
I've sworn to serve
the Lord of Riverrun
and obey his commands.
You're not obeying
Edmure's commands.
You're obeying the fucking
Kingslayer's commands.
EDMURE: I demand entry.
My lord has given an order.
With a knife to his throat.
That is not a valid order.
Lower the drawbridge
and open the gate for Lord...
MAN: Aye, ser.
I'll have your head
before I surrender Riverrun.
You are not lord
of this castle, my lord.
Lower the drawbridge.
MAN: Aye, ser!
(CLANKING)
BLACK WALDER:
If you're wrong,
we've just surrendered
our most valuable prisoner.
Welcome home, my lord.
Command all the forces
within the castle
to lay down their arms.
Open the gates.
My lord...
Your lord has given
a command.
(CHAINS CLANKING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
MAN: Infantry, advance!
Find the Blackfish.
Put him in irons and
hand him over to the Freys.
Find him.
Go on.
Come with us.
I've run before
from the Red Wedding.
I'm not running again.
This is my family home.
Your family is in the North.
Come with us.
Don't die for pride when
you can fight for your blood.
You'll serve Sansa
far better than I ever could.
GUARD: All the way down!
Check that out!
Go on, now.
I haven't had a proper
sword fight in years.
I expect I'll make
a damn fool of myself.
We found the Blackfish,
my lord.
Good.
Bring him to me.
He died fighting, my lord.
(MEN SHOUTING)
TYRION: I was wrong.
I admit it.
MISSANDEI:
That changes nothing.
The Unsullied could mount
a defense off the beachhead.
If the slavers' forces...
No more talking from you.
Your talking gave us this.
And I have acknowledged that.
I'm trying...
You're trying to tell me
what the army should do.
You do not know
All right, what should
the army do?
We'll not go to the beach.
If we go to the beach,
the Masters will take
the pyramid.
The pyramid is the only place
in the city we can defend.
We stay here.
And then?
We wait for them
to come to us.
Then we fight them.
(CRASHING)
(THUDDING)
(CREAKING)
(DRAGON SCREECHES)
(HORSE WHINNIES IN DISTANCE)
(MEN SHOUTING)
Clegane.
What the fuck
you doing here?
Chasing them. You?
Hanging them.
Any particular reason?
They're our men.
Or they were.
They attacked a nearby sept
and murdered the villagers.
Why do you want them?
Same reason.
I was helping build it.
They killed
a friend of mine.
You've got friends?
Not anymore.
They're mine.
It's the Brotherhood's
good name they've
dragged through the dirt.
Fuck your name.
They're mine.
I killed you
once before, Dondarrion.
Happy to do it again.
Drop that arrow,
you bloody girl.
Tougher girls than you
have tried to kill me.
You can have one of them.
Two.
No, no, no.
We're not butchers.
We hang them.
Hanging?
All over in an instant.
Where's the punishment
in that?
They die.
We all bloody die.
Except this one here.
I'll only gut one of them.
BERIC: No.
I'll chop off one hand.
We gave you two of the three
out of respect for your loss.
That's generous.
Bunch of nances.
There was a time I would have
killed all seven of you
just to gut these three.
You're getting old,
Clegane.
He's not.
(GRUNTS)
Please don't.
I'll give you anything.
(CHOKING)
(CHOKING CONTINUES)
Got anything to eat?
(HORSE WHINNYING
IN DISTANCE)
Enjoying yourself?
I prefer chicken.
You ought to join us.
We could use you.
I tried joining.
Didn't work out for me.
Clegane, we're here
for a reason.
The Lord of Light is keeping
Beric alive for a reason.
He gave a failed, drunk priest
the power to bring him back
for a reason.
We are part of something
larger than ourselves.
Lots of horrible shit
in this world
gets done for something
larger than ourselves.
Cold winds are rising
in the North.
And you're going
to go stop them?
We need good men
to help us.
Last time you saw me,
you wanted to execute me.
BERIC: True enough.
But the Lord of Light
gave you the power
to defeat me.
Why?
(LAUGHS)
I beat you because
I'm better than you, Beric.
I was better than you before
you started yammering on
about the Lord,
and I'm better than you now.
BERIC: Aye,
you're probably right.
You're a fighter.
You were born a fighter.
You walked away
from the fight.
How did that go?
Good and bad,
young and old,
the things we're fighting
will destroy them all alike.
You can still help a lot more
than you've harmed, Clegane.
It's not too late for you.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(GROANS)
(THUDDING)
(GASPING)
Lady Crane?
If you'd have done your job,
she would have
died painlessly.
Instead...
The Many-Faced God
was promised a name.
He must always receive
what is his.
You can't change that.
I can't change that.
No one can.
And now he's been
promised another name.
(GRUNTS)
Hey!
Get out!
Yah!
(GRUNTS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(MAN COUGHING)
(GASPS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(GRUNTS)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(PANTING)
Hey!
Yah!
(MAN SHOUTS)
(SCREAMS)
(CROWD CLAMORING)
Ah!
(GRUNTS)
(CROWD CLAMORING)
WOMAN: My basket!
(PANTING)
(GASPING)
(WHIMPERING)
(ARYA PANTING)
It will all be over soon.
On your knees
or on your feet?
Haven't we been through
this already?
That won't help you.
You told her to kill me.
Yes.
But here you are.
And there she is.
Finally a girl is no one.
A girl is Arya Stark
of Winterfell
and I'm going home.