(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
SANSA: Yes?
(DOOR OPENS)
For you, my lady.
How far is Mole's Town?
Sansa.
Lady Brienne.
When I heard you had
escaped Winterfell,
I feared the worst.
You have no idea
how happy I am
to see you unharmed.
"Unharmed"?
What are you
doing here?
I rode north with
the Knights of the Vale
to come to your aid.
They're encamped at
Moat Cailin as we speak.
To come to my aid?
Did you know
about Ramsay?
If you didn't know,
you're an idiot.
If you did know,
you're my enemy.
Would you like to hear
about our wedding night?
He never hurt my face.
He needed my face, the face
of Ned Stark's daughter.
But the rest of me,
he did what he liked
with the rest of me
as long as I could
still give him an heir.
What do you think he did?
I can't begin
to contemplate...
What do you think
he did to me?
Lady Sansa asked
you a question.
He beat you.
Yes, he enjoyed that.
What else do you
think he did?
LITTLEFINGER:
Sansa, I...
What else?
Did he cut you?
Maybe you did know
about Ramsay all along.
I didn't know.
I thought you knew
everyone's secrets.
I made a mistake,
a horrible mistake.
I underestimated
a stranger.
The other things he did,
ladies aren't supposed to
talk about those things,
but I imagine brothel keepers
talk about them all the time.
I can still feel it.
I don't mean in
my tender heart
it still pains me so.
I can still feel
what he did in my body
standing here right now.
I'm so sorry.
You said
you would protect me.
LITTLEFINGER: And I will.
You must believe me
when I tell you that I will.
SANSA: I don't
believe you anymore.
I don't need you anymore.
You can't protect me.
You won't even be able
to protect yourself if I tell
Brienne to cut you down.
And why shouldn't I?
Do you want me
to beg for my life?
If that's what
you want, I will.
Whatever you ask
that is in my power,
I will do.
What if I want you
to die here and now?
Then I will die.
You freed me from
the monsters who
murdered my family,
and you gave me
to other monsters
who murdered my family.
Go back
to Moat Cailin.
My brother and I
will take back
the North on our own.
I never want
to see you again.
I would do anything
to undo what's been
done to you.
I know that I can't.
Will you allow me to say
one more thing before I go?
Your great-uncle
Brynden the Blackfish
has gathered what remains
of the Tully forces
and retaken Riverrun.
You might consider
seeking him out.
The time may come
when you need an army
loyal to you.
I have an army.
Your brother's army.
Half-brother.
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTING)
(ARYA GROANS)
You're not ready.
You should go home
before it's too late.
(GRUNTS)
(CLATTERING)
(GROANS)
You'll never be one
of us, Lady Stark.
She has a point.
(SNIFFLES)
None of the first
Faceless Men were born
to lords and ladies.
They began as slaves
in the mines of Valyria.
Who was the first?
He was no one.
The Many-Faced God
taught him how
to shed his face
and how
to give the gift.
The man taught
others in exchange
for their service.
Many served,
many more gifts
were given.
Soon all the masters
and overseers were gone
and the Faceless Men fled.
ARYA: Where did they go?
Here.
They founded the free
city of Braavos and
built this house.
These were the faces
they wore in life
when they were
not wearing others.
The first Faceless Men.
And now a girl
is one of them,
if a girl desires.
A girl has no desires.
Who?
JAQEN: An actress
who calls herself
Lady Crane.
She performs at the theater
in Sheelba Square.
A girl has been
given a second chance.
There will not be a third.
One way or another,
a face will be
added to the hall.
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
(HORN BLOWING)
(SCATTERED LAUGHTER)
(ACTOR CRIES OUT)
Murdered by a boar.
The great big
hairy whore.
He dug in his tusks,
and dug out my guts,
and soon I am no more.
Come, Father,
in bed you must lie.
I love you, Father.
Please don't die.
Shut up, you swine!
Cersei, more wine.
(SCATTERED LAUGHTER)
I feel the winds
of winter as they
lick across the land.
And our son alone on
that cold, cold throne
without a guiding hand.
Who will teach him strength?
Who will teach him grace?
To whom will he turn
when it's time to learn to
look darkness in the face?
Ned Stark will do fine.
Now, bring me more wine.
(GRUNTING)
Ooh... What's happened
here, then?
He brought you here,
Ned Stark,
'cause you're the brightest
fellow in the land.
You should be king of us all
and I should be your Hand.
We men of the North
are right good hands
at keeping people lawful.
I'd ask him for
permission, but he
smells too bloody awful.
(YELLING)
I die. I die.
And here,
I now must lie.
Oh, woe. Oh, no...
(SPUTTERING NOISE)
Oh, I am about to go.
(SPUTTERING)
Will you stay on
as Joffrey's Hand?
The Iron Throne's
what I demand.
You cannot.
I can.
You will not.
I will.
You dare not.
I dare yes.
ACTRESS: The line
of succession.
ACTOR: What's that mean?
ACTRESS: The
proper progression.
ACTOR: What's that mean?
The lawful ascension.
What's that mean?
So move along,
give me my chair
and there won't
be no more trouble.
(GROANS)
But we had a deal
all done and dusted.
I'm starting to think
you can't be trusted.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Save my father.
Truly you should.
Killing the man
will do you no good.
Save him, please.
Show him mercy.
Show the people what
a good king should be.
Good people,
you may all relax.
My father's friend
shall be spared the...
(EXCLAIMS)
ACTRESS PLAYING
SANSA: (CRYING)
Father! No!
Father...
ACTOR PLAYING TYRION:
Worry not, all is well.
I have here a decree
from my father
Tywin Lannister, the
richest man you'll see.
He proclaims me
Hand of the King.
The position's
mine for life.
And he's given me
permission to take
Sansa as my wife.
(GASPING)
(GROANS)
You'll learn that
what I lack in height,
I make up for in appetite.
So let's forget about
your plight, and go
rehearse our wedding night.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
It's a wart. Two warts.
I've got two fucking
warts on my cock.
Well, don't worry, love.
They usually go away
in five or six years.
Oh. Wash this, darling.
It stinks of me.
You can do better,
Bianca, dear.
You must do.
I had two lines.
There are no small parts.
You rang very false.
I rang very false?
What you need, love,
is for someone
to ring you true.
BIANCA: You weren't
complaining about me
last night.
BOBONO: May I get you
some wine, Lady Crane?
LADY CRANE:
I'm a rum girl, Bobono.
You need to know
that if we're going
to be intimate.
Of course we're going
It's only a matter of time.
(POURING)
To our children.
May they have
your talent.
And your filthy mind.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
A girl will
poison the rum.
Lady Crane is the
only one who drinks it.
If a girl could use
one of the faces
from the hall...
A girl is not ready.
She's a good actress.
So a man has heard.
Seems like a decent woman.
Does death only come
for the wicked and leave
the decent behind?
No.
Who wants her dead?
That does not matter.
The price was paid.
The younger actress.
She's jealous because
Lady Crane is better.
A girl must decide
if she wants to serve
the Many-Faced God.
A girl has decided.
A servant does
not ask questions.
(RAVEN CAWING)
(ALL WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY)
(TWIG SNAPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
MAN: No! No! No!
(SCREAMING)
It was you.
You made the White Walkers.
We were at war.
We were being slaughtered.
Our sacred trees
cut down.
We needed to
defend ourselves.
From whom?
From you.
From men.
PRIEST: We speak
in the presence
of the Drowned God.
In his name we gather
today to choose a new
king as our leader.
Who makes a claim?
I am Yara Greyjoy,
daughter of Balon Greyjoy,
King of the Iron Islands.
I claim
the Salt Throne.
We've never
had a queen.
Not once.
There are many things
we've never done.
We've never made our
mark upon the world.
The great lords of
Westeros pay us no mind
until our little raids
buzz through their kingdoms
long enough to
become a nuisance.
Then they swat us down.
They conquer us,
humiliate us,
and go right back to
forgetting we exist.
ALL: Aye!
We are a sea people.
Our god is a sea god.
ALL: Aye!
When I am queen,
we will build
a fleet that...
You shall not
be queen!
I am not finished!
Yes, you are!
A woman will not
lead us.
Not when Balon's own
male heir has returned.
I am Theon Greyjoy,
last living son
of Balon Greyjoy.
And she is your
rightful ruler.
ALL: Aye!
Those of you that have
sailed under her, and there
are many of you here,
you know what she is.
ALL: Aye!
She is a reaver.
She is a warrior.
ALL: Aye!
She is ironborn!
We will find
no better leader.
This is our queen.
(ALL CHEERING)
ALL: (CHANTING)
Yara! Yara! Yara!
MAN: I'm Euron Greyjoy.
I claim
the Salt Throne.
Niece.
Nephew.
Little Theon.
Heard you managed
to fuck things
right into the ground.
(SCATTERED LAUGHTER)
EURON: Captured a castle
you couldn't keep.
Got yourself
taken prisoner.
Even heard
you have no cock.
Explains why
you think a woman
can be king.
When did you
return, Uncle?
EURON: A few days ago.
I had some things
to take care of.
Long overdue.
I'm glad you're here.
Now I know what my first
act as queen will be.
To execute the man
who killed my father.
(SCATTERED CHATTER)
I did.
I killed him.
Threw him right
over a rope bridge,
and watched him fall.
He was leading
us nowhere,
and we would still
be heading there
if it weren't for me.
No one loved him.
No one wanted
to follow him.
He led us into two
wars we couldn't win.
I apologize to you
all for not killing
him years ago.
THEON: That would
have been hard to do.
You weren't here.
Last I heard, you were
gallivanting around the world
having a grand old time.
"Gallivanting"?
That the sort of thing
you start to say
once your dick
gets chopped off?
Did the great lords
of Westeros teach
you words like that?
You were gone.
Yara was here.
Being ironborn.
Leading ironborn.
Getting ready to bring
us back to glory.
EURON: And how
will she do that?
I will build the
largest fleet the
world has ever seen.
Right idea,
except I'm the one
who's going to build
the Iron Fleet
because I'm the one
who knows how to use it.
I've been all over
the world.
I've seen more of it
than all of you combined.
And across the sea
there is a person
who hates the great
lords of Westeros
just as much as we do.
Someone with
a large army,
three large dragons,
and no husband.
I'm going to build
that fleet
and I'm going
to gallivant right over
and give it to
Daenerys Targaryen
along with my big cock.
(SCATTERED LAUGHTER)
You're going to seduce
the Dragon Queen?
I'm not going to
seduce her. The Iron
Fleet will seduce her.
And together
we're going to take
the Seven Kingdoms.
I wasn't born to be king.
I paid the iron price,
and here I stand.
(ALL CHEERING)
(CHANTING) Euron!
Euron! Euron! Euron!
Euron! Euron!
May Euron, your servant,
be born again from
the sea as you were.
Bless him with salt.
Bless him with stone.
Bless him with steel.
Listen to the waves.
Listen to the god.
He is speaking to us
and he says,
"We shall have no king
but Euron Greyjoy."
Let the sea wash your follies
and your vanities away.
Let the old Euron drown.
Let his lungs
fill with seawater.
Let the fish eat
the scales off his eyes.
What is dead may never die.
But rises again
harder and stronger.
(RETCHING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(COUGHING)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
What is dead
may never die.
ALL: What is dead
(ALL CHEERING)
Where are my
niece and nephew?
Let's go murder them.
AERON: They stole
our best ships.
Won't be enough
to save them.
Go back
to your homes.
Chop down every
tree you can find.
Quarter-saw the timber
and start building.
I want every man
bending planks.
I want every woman
spinning flax for sails.
Build me 1,000 ships.
And I will give
you this world.
I banished you, twice.
You came back, twice.
And you saved my life.
So I can't take you back,
and I can't send you away.
You must
send me away.
Is there a cure?
I don't know.
How long does it take?
I don't know that either.
But I've seen what happens
when it goes far enough.
I'll end things before that.
I'm sorry.
(CRYING) I'm so sorry.
Don't be.
All I've ever wanted
was to serve you.
Tyrion Lannister
was right.
I love you.
I'll always love you.
Goodbye, Khaleesi.
Do not walk away
from your queen,
Jorah the Andal.
You have not
been dismissed.
You pledged yourself to me.
You swore to obey my commands
for the rest of your life.
Well, I command
you to find the cure,
wherever it is
in this world.
I command you
to heal yourself,
and then return to me.
When I take
the Seven Kingdoms,
I need you by my side.
In the last fortnight
since our pact
with the Masters,
how many killings
have been carried out
by the Sons of the Harpy?
None.
And how many Masters
have been butchered
by the free men?
Two, but that was
the day of the pact.
Since then, nothing.
So, it's safe to say
that a fragile peace
has taken hold.
For now.
"For now" is the best
we get in our profession.
It's not enough.
Considering the
city was on the
brink of civil war,
I'd say it's
a good start.
It's not enough for
Meereen to have peace.
They need to know
Daenerys is
responsible for it.
The Sons of the Harpy
have a good story.
Resist the foreign invaders.
Our queen has
an even better story.
Mother of Dragons,
Breaker of Chains,
all that.
The people know who
brought them freedom.
Yes, but do they know
who brought them security?
Who brought about
an end to the violence?
We need someone
the people trust,
someone they know
cannot be bought
or influenced.
Sounds like quite the hero.
Where would we find him?
Who said anything
about "him"?
(MAN SPEAKS VALYRIAN)
(TYRION SPEAKS VALYRIAN)
That's about the extent
of my Valyrian.
Thank you for traveling
all this way.
I know from personal
experience how uncomfortable
the journey can be.
The truth is
we need your help.
We had hoped that
we could somehow
persuade you to...
You don't need
to persuade me.
I came to help.
Daenerys Stormborn
is the one who
was promised.
From the fire
she was reborn to
remake the world.
TYRION: Yes.
She has freed the slaves from
their chains and crucified
the masters for their sins.
TYRION: She did indeed.
Her dragons are
fire made flesh,
a gift from
the Lord of Light.
But you heard all of
this before, haven't you?
On the Long Bridge
of Volantis.
The dragons will
purify nonbelievers
by the thousands,
burning their
sins and flesh away.
Ideally we'd avoid
purifying too
many nonbelievers.
The Mother of Dragons
has followers of
many different faiths.
You want your queen
to be worshipped and obeyed.
And while she's gone, you
want her advisors to be
worshipped and obeyed.
I'd settle for obeyed.
KINVARA: I will summon
my most eloquent priests.
They will spread the word.
Daenerys has been sent
to lead the people
against the darkness
in this war, and in the
great war still to come.
That sounds
most excellent.
A man named
Stannis Baratheon
was anointed
as the chosen one
by one of
your priestesses.
He, too, had
a glorious destiny.
He attacked
King's Landing
and was soundly
defeated by the man
standing beside me.
Last I had heard,
he had been
defeated again,
this time at Winterfell,
and this time for good.
We'd be most grateful
for any support you
could provide the queen.
I suppose it's hard
for a fanatic to
admit a mistake.
Isn't that the whole
point of being a fanatic?
You're always right.
Everything is
the Lord's will.
But men and women
make mistakes.
Even honest servants
of the Lord.
VARYS: And you, an honest
servant of the Lord,
why should I trust
you to know any more
than the priestess
who counseled Stannis?
My friend has a healthy
skepticism of religion,
but we are all loyal
supporters of the queen.
Everyone is what they are,
and where they
are for a reason.
Terrible things
happen for a reason.
Take what happened
to you, Lord Varys,
when you were a child.
If not for your
mutilation at the hand of
a second-rate sorcerer,
you wouldn't be here
helping the Lord's Chosen
bring his light
into the world.
Knowledge has
made you powerful.
But there's still so
much you don't know.
Do you remember what
you heard that night
when the sorcerer
tossed your parts
in the fire?
You heard a voice
call out from the flames.
Do you remember?
Should I tell you
what the voice said?
the name of the
one who spoke?
We serve the same queen.
If you are her true
friend, you have
nothing to fear from me.
(RAVEN CAWING)
(GRUNTING)
(WIND WHISTLING)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(SCREAMING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
He saw me, the Night King!
He saw me!
He touched you.
I don't know.
He was close, but...
He touched you.
He knows you are here.
He'll come for you.
But he can't get in.
He can now.
His mark is on you.
You must leave,
all of you.
Come on, Hodor.
Help me with the sledge.
Hodor.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
The time has come.
The time for what?
For you to become me.
But am I ready?
No.
JON: We can't defend the
North from the Walkers and
the south from the Boltons.
If we want to survive,
we need Winterfell,
and to take Winterfell,
we need more men.
DAVOS: Aside from
the Starks and the Boltons,
the most powerful
houses in the North
are the Umbers,
the Karstarks,
and the Manderlys.
The Umbers
and the Karstarks
have already declared
for the Boltons,
so we're not doing
so well there.
The Umbers gave
Rickon to our enemies.
They can hang.
But the Karstarks
declared for Ramsay
without knowing they
had another choice.
Uh, I beg your
pardon, my lady,
but they know that
a Stark beheaded
their father.
I don't think we can
count on them either.
How well do you know
the North, Ser Davos?
Precious little, my lady.
SANSA: My father always said
Northerners are different.
More loyal,
more suspicious
of outsiders.
They may well be loyal,
but how many rose up
against the Boltons
when they betrayed
your family?
I may not know the North,
but I know men.
They're more or less
the same in any
corner of the world
and even the
bravest of them
don't want to see
their wives and children
skinned for a lost cause.
If Jon's going
to convince them
to fight alongside him,
they need to believe
it's a fight they can win.
There are more than
three other houses
in the North,
Glover, Mormont,
Cerwyn, Mazin, Hornwood.
Two dozen more.
Together they
equal all the others.
We can start
small and build.
SANSA: The North remembers.
They remember
the Stark name.
People will still
risk everything for it,
from White Harbor
to Ramsay's own door.
I don't doubt it.
But Jon doesn't have
the Stark name.
No, but I do.
Jon is every bit as much
Ned Stark's son as Ramsay
is Roose Bolton's.
And there are also the Tullys.
They're not Northern,
but they will back us
against the Boltons
without question.
I didn't know
the Tullys still
had an army.
My uncle the Blackfish
has reformed it
and retaken Riverrun.
How do you know that?
Ramsay received
a raven before
I escaped Winterfell.
That's good.
The Blackfish is a legend.
His support would
mean a great deal.
Stark, Tully,
a few more houses,
almost starts to look
like a winning side.
I've sworn to protect
you, my lady.
You heard them.
We need more men,
and my uncle has an army.
We can send
the Blackfish a raven.
Can't risk Ramsay
intercepting it.
It has to be you.
Ride for Riverrun.
My uncle will talk
to you and you'll know
how to talk to him.
(SIGHS)
What is it?
I don't like leaving
you here alone.
With Jon?
BRIENNE: Not him.
He seems trustworthy.
A bit brooding,
perhaps.
I suppose that's
understandable,
considering.
The others, though.
Davos and the
Red Woman helped a man
murder his own brother
with blood magic.
And when Stannis
paid for his crime,
where were they?
Already out looking
for a leader with
better prospects.
And that wildling
fellow with the beard...
Jon isn't Tormund.
Jon isn't Davos, the
Red Woman, or Stannis
for that matter.
Jon is Jon.
He's my brother.
He'll keep me safe.
I trust him.
Then why did
you lie to him
when he asked you
how you learned
about Riverrun?
New dress?
I made it myself.
Do you like it?
Yeah, it's...
I like the wolf bit.
Good, because
I made this for you.
I made it like the one
Father used to wear.
As near as
I can remember.
Thank you, Sansa.
You're welcome.
Don't knock it down
while I'm gone.
I'll do my best.
Good luck.
Should we close the gate,
Lord Commander?
I'm not the Lord...
(CLEARS THROAT) Yeah,
close the bloody gate.
(RAVEN CAWING)
MEERA: We can
go home now, Hodor.
Well, maybe not home,
home, but somewhere
that isn't a cave.
HODOR: Hodor.
Eat something
that isn't moss.
I want an egg.
How do you like 'em?
Boiled? Fried up
with some butter?
(CHUCKLES) Hodor.
With a rasher of bacon
and some blood sausage.
Hodor.
(GASPS)
(ICE CRACKLING)
Get Bran and run!
(WHITE WALKERS SNARLING)
Bran. Bran, wake up.
Bran.
Hodor. Hodor.
Bran, wake up!
MAN 1: Take him to the Vale.
MAN 2: Gods keep you
on the King's Road.
WOMAN: Take it easy.
Watch yourself.
Hodor.
Hodor. Hodor.
Help me!
(GRUNTS)
LEAF: Go!
Go!
(FIRE HISSING)
(SCREECHING)
(GRUNTING)
RICKARD: Remember
that you are a Stark.
Comport yourself
with dignity at the Vale
and try to stay
out of fights.
YOUNG NED: Yes, Father.
RICKARD: But if you
have to fight,
win.
Bran! Bran, wake up!
(LOUD THUD)
(SNARLING)
(SHOUTS)
(YELPS)
(SUMMER GROWLING)
Bran! Bran, wake up.
Bran! Bran, wake up!
Hodor. Hodor.
(LOUD THUD)
(WHITE WALKER SNARLING)
You have to wake up.
We need Hodor.
Hodor. Hodor.
MEERA: Bran, we need Hodor.
Bran, you have to wake up.
We need Hodor.
(SCREECHES)
Hodor. Hodor.
Bran, we're all
going to die!
Bran, wake up!
We're all going to die!
Bran! Bran!
Bran, you have to wake up.
We need Hodor.
Hodor. Hodor.
Warg into Hodor now!
Bran, wake up.
We need Hodor.
Warg into Hodor now. Now!
Listen to your
friend, Brandon.
HODOR: Hodor. Hodor.
Hodor. Hodor.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
MEERA: Summer!
LEAF: Go.
Go!
(SUMMER YELPING)
(SUMMER SQUEALING)
(PANTING)
THREE-EYED RAVEN:
The time has come.
Leave me.
(SNARLING)
What are you doing?
Go!
(GRUNTS)
(SNARLING CONTINUES)
(GRUNTING)
Hodor, hurry.
Hodor.
(GRUNTING)
Hold the door!
(DOOR BANGING)
(GRUNTING)
Hold the door!
WOMAN: Wylis?
What's the matter?
MEERA: Hold the door!
Come on, son.
BOTH: Hold the door!
(GRUNTING)
Hold the door!
Hold the door! Hold door!
Hold door! Hold the door!
Hold the door!
Hold door! Hold door!
Hold door! Hodor!
Hodor! Hodor!
Hodor. Hodor.
Hodor.