(MAN BREATHING HEAVILY)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(CONTINUES BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GHOST PANTING)
(WHINING)
(GASPING)
(JON GRUNTS)
Easy, easy. easy.
What do you remember?
They stabbed me.
Olly...
He put a knife
in my heart.
I shouldn't be here.
The lady brought
you back.
Afterwards, after they
stabbed you, after you
died, where did you go?
What did you see?
Nothing.
There was nothing at all.
The Lord let you
come back for a reason.
Stannis was not the prince
who was promised,
but someone has to be.
Could you give us a moment?
(DOOR CREAKING)
(SOFTLY)
You were dead.
And now you're not.
That's completely
fucking mad,
seems to me.
I can only imagine
how it seems to you.
I did what I thought
was right,
and I got murdered for it.
Now I'm back.
Why?
I don't know.
Maybe we'll never know.
What does it matter?
You go on.
You fight for as
long as you can.
You clean up as much
of the shit as you can.
I don't know
how to do that.
I thought I did,
but I failed.
Good.
Now go fail again.
(DOOR OPENS)
They think you're
some kind of god.
The man who returned
from the dead.
I'm not a god.
I know that.
I saw your pecker.
What kind of god would
have a pecker that small?
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(WINCES)
(JON WINCING)
Your eyes
are still brown.
Is that still
you in there?
I think so.
Hold off on burning
my body for now.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
That's funny.
(JON SNIFFLES)
You sure that's
still you in there?
(BOTH LAUGH)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(SAMWELL GROANS)
You all right?
Yes. Yes, I'm fine.
Did I ever tell you
I used to think the sea
was called "the see"
because it was nothing
but water as far as
the eye could see?
I don't think so.
Sea, see.
They're spelled different,
but they sound the same.
Yeah. They do.
It was before I learned
how to read, obviously.
Sam, are you
going to be sick?
(RETCHING)
Won't be long.
We'll be in the south soon.
I'm excited to see Oldtown.
Captain says it's the
most beautiful city
in Westeros.
Are you going
to vomit again?
No. No, no, no. Um...
The Citadel doesn't
admit women.
There won't be
a place for you there,
or for little Sam.
I stayed at Castle
Black. There's no
women allowed there.
The Citadel
isn't Castle Black.
I don't have a Jon Snow
or Maester Aemon to
help me bend the rules.
I'll stay
in Oldtown, then.
By yourself?
With a baby and
no money?
So if we're not going
to Oldtown, where
are you taking me?
To my home. Horn Hill.
My father's...
Well, my father.
But my mother's
a kind woman and
my sister's lovely.
They'll take care
of you both.
"Wherever you go,
I go, too."
That's what you said.
(STUTTERS)
I said that because
I want you and
Little Sam to be safe.
That's all I want.
To become a maester
so I can help Jon
when the time comes,
so you'll be safe.
Us and everyone
else in the world.
I don't care about them.
Well, no, I do,
but I don't really.
(CHUCKLES)
I care about you and him.
I know that, Sam.
And he does, too.
You're the only
one who ever has.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
If you think it's for
the best, we trust you.
I'd feel better if you
threw something at me
and stormed off.
I'd never do that to
the father of my son.
(SAM COOS)
(RETCHING)
(COUGHS)
(HORSES WHINNYING)
(HORSES WHINNY
IN THE DISTANCE)
(HORSES APPROACHING)
That's my father.
The man beside him
is Howland Reed,
Meera's father.
Ser Arthur Dayne.
The Sword of the Morning.
Father said he was
the best swordsman
he ever saw.
Lord Stark.
I looked for you
on the Trident.
We weren't there.
Your friend, the Usurper,
would lie beneath the ground
if we had been.
The Mad King is dead.
Rhaegar lies beneath
the ground.
Why weren't you there
to protect your prince?
Our prince
wanted us here.
Where's my sister?
I wish you
good fortune in
the wars to come.
And now it begins.
No. Now it ends.
(YELLING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(SHOUTS)
(GURGLES)
(GROANS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
He's better
than my father.
Far better.
But Father beat him.
Did he?
I know he did.
Heard the story
a thousand times.
(GURGLES)
(GRUNTS)
He stabbed him
in the back.
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
What's in the tower?
That's enough for
one day. We'll visit
again another time.
I want to see
where he's going.
Time to go.
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
Father!
(GASPS)
Why did you do that?
Take me back there.
I want to go back.
No.
(RAVEN CROWS)
He heard me.
Maybe.
Maybe he heard
the wind.
He heard me.
The past is already
written. The ink is dry.
What's in that tower?
I want to go back there.
I've told you many times,
stay too long where
you don't belong and
you will never return.
Why do I want to return?
So I can be a cripple again?
So I can talk to
an old man in a tree?
You think I wanted
to sit here
for 1,000 years
watching the world
from a distance
as the roots
grew through me?
So why did you?
I was waiting for you.
I don't want to be you.
(CHUCKLES)
I don't blame you.
You won't be here
forever. You won't be
an old man in a tree.
But before you leave,
you must learn.
Learn what?
Everything.
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(DOOR OPENS)
I don't know how
you stand it in all
that leather.
If we could
have the room.
You look lovely today,
my dear. You really do.
How you climbed all
those steps without
breaking a sweat.
If you're going to torture
me, just call them back
and get on with it.
I am not
a torturer.
Though it
so often is what
people deserve.
And it does
provide answers.
But they're usually
the wrong answers.
My job is to find
the right answers.
Do you know
how I do that?
I do it by making
people happy.
I'd like to make
you happy, Vala.
That's your name,
isn't it? Vala.
(CHUCKLES) That's all right.
I know who you are
and what you've done.
You've done a lot.
You've sacrificed
your body for a cause,
which is more
than most people do.
And you've helped the Sons
of the Harpy murder the
Unsullied and the Second Sons.
The Unsullied
and the Second Sons
are foreign soldiers,
brought here by a foreign
queen to destroy our city
and our history.
I understand.
Well, that makes
perfect sense from
your perspective.
I have a different
perspective, of course.
I think it's important
that you try to see things
from my perspective,
just as I will try to
see them from yours.
Because that is the
only way that I can
make you and Dom happy.
That is how you
pronounce it, "Dom"?
I'm afraid I don't really
speak the language.
Such a handsome boy.
Those big, brown eyes.
Good luck keeping
the ladies away.
Yes, you're a true
liberator, aren't you?
You won't torture me,
you'll just threaten my son.
Children are blameless.
I have never hurt them.
Your boy is in no
immediate danger,
this I swear to you.
But between us, dear,
you did conspire to kill
the queen's soldiers.
We both know the
penalty for that crime.
How will poor Dom
get on without
his mother?
And with his
breathing problem.
If I tell you anything,
they'll kill me.
So either you
kill me or they do.
Yes, from your
perspective, this
is a problem.
There is a third
option, though.
A ship leaving
tomorrow for Pentos.
I've already booked
passage for a woman
and her young son.
I'll even throw
in a bag of silver
to help you start again.
Though I'm afraid we'll
have to ask one of our
leather-clad friends
back in to carry it.
Far too heavy for me.
The boat sails at dawn.
You need to decide now.
A new life for
you and Dom, or...
What should we
do while we wait?
To pass the time,
what should we do?
What should
we talk about?
You speak 19 languages.
You must occasionally
use some of them
to talk about things.
You two, you spend
a great deal
of time together.
What would you
be talking about
if I weren't here?
Patrol.
When I am going on
patrol with the Unsullied.
What we see on patrol.
Who we captured on patrol.
That's good.
That's very good.
But that's a report.
I was thinking more
of a conversation.
A wise man once said,
"The true history of the world
"is the history of
great conversations
in elegant rooms."
Who said this?
Me. Just now.
All right, no conversations.
Let's play a game.
You don't play games?
Either one of you, ever?
Games are
for children.
My master Kraznys
would sometimes
make us play games.
There, that's a start.
Only the girls.
Oh...
No, no, no.
Not that.
Of course,
not that.
Innocent games.
Fun games.
Drinking games.
MISSANDEI: We do not drink.
Until you do.
All right. No drinking.
We can play without drinking.
It's a wonderful game.
I invented it.
Here's how it works.
I make a statement
about your past.
If I'm wrong, I drink.
And if I'm right...
(GASPS)
Maybe we can't play
without drinking.
(DOOR OPENS)
Oh, you took
your time.
VARYS: Sorry.
I was busy learning
who funds the
Sons of the Harpy.
Some things
you can't rush.
You found out?
The Good Masters
of Astapor and the
Wise Masters of Yunkai.
With help from their
friends in Volantis.
TYRION: You see?
You don't even
have to worry about
the local rebellion.
We only have to worry
about the three rich
foreign cities paying for it.
We conquered Astapor
and Yunkai once.
We will do it again
and execute the Masters.
If the Unsullied march
off to re-conquer
Astapor and Yunkai,
who will remain
to defend the free
people of Meereen?
If we do not fight them,
how can we stop them?
We cannot.
The Masters speak
only one language.
They spoke it to
me for many years.
I know it better
than my mother tongue.
If we want them
to hear us, we must
speak it back to them.
May it be the last
thing they ever hear.
You may be right.
So we will
fight them?
Possibly.
Possibly?
It's a conversation.
Tell me, can
your little birds
get a message
to the Good Masters
of Astapor, the Wise
Masters of Yunkai,
and benevolent
enslavers of Volantis?
Of course. Men can
be fickle, but birds
I always trust.
(CHILDREN MUTTERING)
QYBURN: Your eye looks
much better, Arthur.
How's your mother's jaw?
Better.
And your father?
No one's seen him.
And no one will.
That worked out
rather nicely.
Will Lord Varys
ever come back?
I don't think so.
Do you miss him?
He was nice.
He called us
his little birds.
He gave us sweets.
It's funny you should
mention that.
Guess what I happened
to find today.
Candied plums
from Dorne.
(LAUGHING)
Now remember,
if any of your friends
like sweets or need help,
they can always come to me.
All I need in return
are whispers.
(DOOR OPENS)
QYBURN: No need
to be afraid.
This is Ser Gregor.
He's friends with
all my friends.
Run along now.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Varys's little birds?
Your little birds
now, Your Grace.
What did you do
to him exactly?
I haven't been able
to get a clear answer.
Oh, a number of things.
Does he understand
what we're saying?
I mean, to the extent that
he ever understood complete
sentences in the first place.
He understands well enough.
So tell him to march
into the Sept
and crush the
High Sparrow's head
like a melon.
The High Sparrow has
hundreds of Faith Militant
surrounding him.
Ser Gregor can't
face them all.
And he won't have to.
He'll only have
to face one.
Has the Faith leveled
official charges yet?
Not yet.
That is one trial by combat
I look forward to watching.
Don't stop at the city.
I want little birds
in Dorne, in Highgarden,
in the North.
If someone is planning
on making our losses
their gains,
I want to hear it.
If someone is laughing
at the queen
who walked naked through
the streets covered in shit,
I want to hear.
I want to know who they are.
I want to know where they are.
PYCELLE: As bad
as Lord Varys was,
Qyburn is worse.
I told them all. I told them.
He's arrogant, dangerous.
You don't get thrown
out of the Citadel
without good reason.
And no one listened
to my advice.
So here we are.
And what he's done
to Gregor Clegane
is an abomination.
We never sanctioned
this experiment.
And I, for one,
think it would be
in our best interest
to have the beast...
(PYCELLE FLATULATES)
Can I help you?
Why are you here?
My mother...
I was invited,
my dear,
to help deal
with several
troublesome issues,
such as the
queen's imprisonment.
Thank you
for bringing it up.
It's well past
time we addressed
the abuses I endured.
Margaery is the queen.
You are not the queen
because you're not
married to the king.
I do appreciate these
things can get a bit
confusing in your family.
This is a Small
Council meeting.
You have no position
on the Small Council.
I'm the Lord Commander
of the Kingsguard.
The Lord Commander of the
Kingsguard does have a
position on the Small Council.
Grand Maester Pycelle,
would you sanction
that statement?
Well, uh...
(MUTTERS)
I would say Ser Gerold
Hightower had a seat on
the Mad King's council.
Of course,
that was the Mad King.
King Robert saw
things differently.
And King...
What about Myrcella's
death, Uncle?
Do you consider the
murder of your own blood
a troublesome issue?
The same women who
murdered Myrcella
have overthrown
House Martell and
taken control of Dorne.
We've got a lot to discuss.
All of us, together.
And seeing as you
cannot make us leave,
we best get on with it.
No, we cannot make you leave.
And you cannot make us stay.
Not unless you're
gonna have that thing
murder us all.
(DOOR OPENS)
(GROANS SOFTLY)
Your Grace.
My mother would like
to see her daughter's
final resting place.
Ah, I'm sorry, Your Grace.
That's not possible. Not yet.
When will it
be possible?
When she's fully
atoned for her sins.
You cut off her hair
and marched her naked
through the streets
in front of the
whole city.
That wasn't
the full atonement?
No.
She must stand trial
before seven septons,
so we can learn
the true extent
of her sins.
I want you to let
her see Myrcella's
resting place.
I am the king.
You are.
And what does
that mean to you?
It means
a great deal to me.
The Crown and the
Faith are the twin
pillars of the world.
Do you know
who told me that?
Your mother.
My mother
who is unclean?
My mother who still needs
to atone after all
you've put her through?
How do you think
the Mother Above
first came to us?
How did men and women
first come to feel the
Mother's presence, hmm?
It was through
their own mothers.
There's a great deal
of falsehood in Cersei.
You know that.
But when she speaks
of you, the Mother's
love outshines it all.
Her love for you is more
real than anything
else in this world
because it doesn't
come from this world.
But you know that.
You've felt it.
You've seen her
when she talks to you.
Yes.
It's a great gift.
One I never had.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Envy.
One more thing
for me to atone for.
Your Grace, do you...
May I? Do you mind?
It's my knees.
Of course.
(CHUCKLES)
When your mother
made her walk
of atonement,
she did it to
get back to you.
I still don't understand
why you want to put her
through any more than
she's already endured.
It's not what I want.
It's what the gods want.
They make their will known
to us, and it's up to us
to either accept or reject it.
Please.
If we're to be just and
good, then we accept it.
All of us, even kings.
A true leader avails himself
of the wisest counsel he can.
And no one is wiser
than the gods.
My grandfather once
said something similar.
Except for the part
about the gods.
The gods worked through him
whether he knew it or not.
As they work
through your mother.
There's so much
good in all of us.
The best we can do
is to help each
other bring it out.
(SCRAPING)
(ARYA GASPS)
Who are you?
ARYA: No one.
(GROANS)
Who were you before
you came here?
Arya Stark.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Tell me about
Arya Stark's family.
Her father
was Eddard Stark.
Her mother
was Catelyn Stark.
She had one sister,
Sansa, and four brothers.
(GROANS)
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
Three brothers.
Robb, Bran, Rickon.
(ARYA GROANS)
And a half-brother Jon.
And where
are they now?
ARYA: They may be dead
for all a girl knows.
(SNIFFING)
Tell me about the Hound.
(GRUNTING)
ARYA: Also dead.
ARYA: Arya Stark left him
to die. He was on her list.
He was not on
her list anymore.
She had taken
him off it.
Why? Didn't she want
him dead any longer?
ARYA: She did
and she did not.
She sounds confused.
Yes, she was.
Who else was on
Arya Stark's funny
little list?
(GROANING)
ARYA: Cersei Lannister.
Gregor Clegane.
Walder Frey.
WAIF: That's a short list.
That can't be everyone
you want to kill.
Are you sure you're
not forgetting someone?
Which name would you
like a girl to speak?
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
JAQEN: If a girl tells
me her name, I will
give her eyes back.
A girl has
no name.
Come.
If a girl is truly no one,
she has nothing to fear.
Who are you?
No one.
The Umbers are
a famously loyal house.
Famously loyal
to the Starks.
And you,
Lord Karstark,
your people share blood
with the Starks, don't they?
But here we are.
Times change.
When my father became
Warden of the North,
your house refused
to pledge their banners.
Your father was a cunt.
My beloved father,
the Warden...
Your father was a cunt,
and that's why
you killed him.
I might have done
the same to my father
if he hadn't have
done me the favor
of dying on his own.
My father was poisoned
by our enemies.
Mmm.
Why have you
come to Winterfell,
Lord Umber?
The bastard Jon Snow
led an army of wildlings
past the Wall.
We're farther north
than any of you fuckers.
Wildlings come down,
we always have to
fight them first.
I like fighting wildlings.
Been doing it all me life.
But there are too
many of them for us
to beat back alone.
So now you've
come seeking help?
We need to help
each other.
The colder it gets,
the farther south those
goat-fuckers will roam.
Won't take them
long to get here.
You think a horde
of wildlings can
take Winterfell?
If they get Jon Snow
leading them, maybe.
He knows this place
better than we ever will.
Pledge your banners
to House Bolton,
swear loyalty to me
as Warden of the North,
and we will fight together
to destroy the bastard
and all his wildling friends.
I'm not kissing
your fucking hand.
Traditionally a bannerman
kneels before his lord.
I'm not doing that either.
Why would I trust a man
who won't honor tradition?
Your father
honored tradition.
Knelt for Robb Stark.
Called him King of the North.
Was Robb Stark right
to trust your father?
Then it appears we're
at a bit of an impasse.
Fuck kneeling and
fuck oaths. I've got
a gift for you.
A girl, I hope.
I prefer redheads.
A girl, aye.
(SMALLJON LAUGHS)
A wild one.
I like them wild.
And a boy,
nice and young.
The way Karstark
likes them.
(PANTING)
Who's this?
Rickon Stark.
How do I know
that's Rickon Stark?
Welcome home,
Lord Stark.
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
It's time.
If you have
any last words,
now is the time.
You shouldn't be alive.
It's not right.
Neither was killing me.
My mother's still
living at White Harbor.
Could you write her?
Tell her I died
fighting the wildlings.
I had a choice,
Lord Commander.
Betray you or betray
the Night's Watch.
You brought
an army of wildlings
into our lands.
An army of murderers
and raiders.
If I had to do it all over
knowing where I'd end up,
I pray I'd make the
right choice again.
I'm sure you would,
Ser Alliser.
I fought, I lost.
Now I rest.
But you, Lord Snow,
you'll be fighting
their battles forever.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(CHOKING, GASPING)
We should burn
the bodies.
You should.
What do you want
me to do with this?
Wear it. Burn it.
Whatever you want.
You have Castle Black.
My watch is ended.