(RAVENS CAWING)
(CAWING CONTINUES)
(WINGS FLUTTER)
(WEAPONS CLANKING, ECHOING)
(BOYS GRUNTING, ECHOING)
(GROANS)
Give him
another go, Ned.
That's my father.
And my Uncle Benjen.
Keep your shield up
or I'll ring your
head like a bell.
(GRUNTING)
They were all
so happy.
So were you, once.
(HORSE WHINNIES)
Stop showing off.
BENJEN: Lyanna!
My Aunt Lyanna.
I've seen her statue
in the crypt.
My father never
talked about her.
BENJEN: Would you
get out of here?
We're sparring.
Who are you gonna spar
with when Ned goes off
to the Eyrie?
BENJEN: I don't know.
What about him?
Wylis, come here.
Hodor?
But he's got
giant's blood.
And you've
got training.
Sounds like
a fair match to me.
Benjen always lifts
his chin when
he's about to charge.
And lowers it when
he's going to dodge,
my lady. (CHUCKLES)
Hodor talks?
You leave the fighting
to the little lords, Wylis.
Come along, now.
It's no place for you.
Oh, Nan, look
at the size of him.
If he ever learned
to fight, he'd be
unstoppable.
Well, he's never
going to learn to fight
because he's a stable boy.
So leave him be.
It is time to go.
Please, a little longer.
(GASPS)
(RAVEN CAWS)
You finally show me
something I care about,
and then you drag me away.
It is beautiful
beneath the sea,
but if you stay
too long,
you'll drown.
I wasn't drowning.
I was home.
(RAVEN CAWS)
(SIGHING)
BRAN: Wylis.
Hodor.
I saw you as a boy.
You could talk.
What happened?
Hodor.
Where's Meera?
(HODOR GRUNTS)
BRAN: You shouldn't be here.
It's not safe
outside the cave.
MEERA: It's not
safe anywhere.
I saw that Hodor
wasn't always Hodor.
(CHUCKLES) Hodor.
His real name is Wylis.
And he could talk and
fight and... And then...
What's wrong?
The three-eyed raven
says there's a war coming.
And we're going to
fight it in there?
(SCOFFS)
Brandon Stark
needs you.
MEERA: For what?
I sit in there and
I watch him have his visions
and nothing ever happens.
He isn't going to
stay here forever.
and out there,
he needs you.
ALLISER: It's time, Ser Davos.
Open the door and
the men inside can rejoin
their brothers in peace.
We'll even set the wolf
free north of the Wall,
where it belongs.
Nobody needs
to die tonight.
(DAVOS EXHALES HEAVILY)
I've never been
much of a fighter.
Apologies for what
you're about to see.
(GHOST GROWLING)
Come on.
(GROWLING)
(LOUD THUDDING)
(THUDDING CONTINUES)
(ALL SHOUTING)
Attack!
(YELLING AND GRUNTING)
Fight, you cowards!
(GRUNTS)
(GROWLS)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
You fucking traitor.
The only traitors here
are the ones who
shoved their knives
into their Lord
Commander's heart.
For thousands of years, the
Night's Watch has held Castle
Black against the wildlings.
Until you.
(YELLING)
(ALLISER GRUNTING)
Throw them into
the cells where
they belong.
(GRUNTING)
(DOOR OPENS)
TORMUND: Took a lot of knives.
I'll have my men get
the wood for a fire.
Bodies to burn.
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
MAN: Shh, hey.
Right, so there
she is, high and
mighty Queen Cersei,
tits and arse jiggling
in the breeze.
All of a sudden,
she looks my way.
Gives me a little
smile like, "Well?"
So, all right, you know,
I've never been shy
and I'm blessed down south,
so I pull it
right out.
She's never seen
anything like it.
I mean, she's used
to her brother,
and from what I hear,
Jaime Lannister's half
an inch shy of an inch.
(PEOPLE EXCLAIM AND LAUGH)
She sees it,
and I swear to the gods,
she licks her lips.
(ALL LAUGH)
Well, you all know me.
You know
I wouldn't lie
about this.
(ALL LAUGH)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(URINATING STOPS)
(SQUELCHING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(DOG BARKING)
(DOOR OPENS)
Get out of my way.
King's orders,
Your Grace.
What are
the King's orders?
He would like you
to remain in the Red Keep,
Your Grace,
for your
own protection.
You're barring me
from attending my own
daughter's funeral?
Forgive me, Your Grace.
by the King's command,
I cannot let you pass.
I would like to
speak to my son.
He has left
the Red Keep,
Your Grace.
(SWORDS CLANKING)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(EXHALES)
She grew up.
JAIME: Almost.
Have we caught
Prince Trystane's
killers?
I expect
it was mother.
Your mother
wouldn't do that.
Yes, she would.
Are you angry
with her?
Of course not.
Then why didn't
you let her come?
She has every
right to be here.
They told me she
wouldn't be allowed
in the sept.
If she had tried...
They're not
putting your mother
in a cell ever again.
Not while
I'm here.
Why haven't you
gone to see her?
(SIGHS)
Everything she endured,
she did it for you.
Don't you think
I know that?
I'm sorry.
But I can't.
Why not?
When the Faith Militant
seized her and Margaery,
what did I do?
When they paraded
her through the
streets like a whore,
what did I do?
We all fail sometimes.
The King is supposed to be
the Protector of the Realm.
If I can't even protect
my own wife or my own
mother, what good am I?
Go and see your mother
and ask her to forgive you.
Your Grace.
Lord Commander.
I want to see
my wife.
The gods wait for
Queen Margaery to confess her
crimes and seek their mercy.
The King must
wait as well.
Go and see your
mother, Tommen.
You're a bold man.
(CHUCKLES)
On the contrary,
I fear a great deal.
The Father, the Mother,
the Warrior.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Do you know why
we use these stones?
To remind us
not to fear death.
We close our eyes
on this world and
open them on the next.
You must long
for the next life.
(SCOFFS)
In truth,
I fear that, too.
You imprisoned and
humiliated my sister.
Your sister sought
the gods' mercy
and atoned for her sin.
What about my sins?
I broke a sacred
oath and stabbed
my King in the back.
I killed my own cousin.
When the gods judged
my brother guilty, I helped
him escape their justice.
What atonement do I deserve?
You would spill blood
in this holy place?
Oh, the gods won't mind.
They've spilled more blood
than the rest of us combined.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Go on, then.
I deserve it.
We all do.
We are weak,
vain creatures.
We live only by
the Mother's mercy.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
They should be closer
if you mean for
them to save you.
I don't.
Hmm.
They'd never reach me
before you struck.
I've fought
against worse odds.
No doubt many
of us would fall.
But who are we, hmm?
We have no names,
no family.
Every one of us is
poor and powerless.
And yet together...
(CHUCKLES)
We can overthrow
an empire.
(BIRD SCREECHING)
(DOOR OPENS)
TOMMEN: Mother.
Did they put her
in the red gown
or the gold?
Gold.
Good. It was
always her color.
I'm sorry for
keeping you here.
I shouldn't have,
but I was...
I didn't want to
lose you again.
I understand.
I'm glad to see you.
I know I should
have come sooner.
I wanted to.
I was wrong.
It's all right.
No, it isn't.
I should have executed
all of them.
I should have pulled
down the sept onto
the High Sparrow's head
before I let them
do that to you,
as you would
have for me.
You raised me
to be strong,
and I wasn't.
But I want to be.
Help me.
(SOFTLY) Always.
(TUTTING)
If I lost my cock,
I'd drink all the time.
Meaning no offense.
(CHUCKLES)
He makes dwarf jokes,
I make eunuch jokes.
I do not make
dwarf jokes.
You think them.
(VARYS SIGHS)
VARYS: So...
The fleet.
It's been burned.
We are searching for the
men who burned the ships,
but nobody saw anything.
Surely, there's
some good news
lurking somewhere.
Astapor and Yunkai
have stopped
asking us for aid.
Perhaps they can
tell us their secret.
The Masters have
retaken both cities.
Outside of Meereen,
the whole of Slaver's Bay
has returned to the slavers.
TYRION: What about
the dragons?
We have two of them here,
beneath the pyramid.
They are not eating.
They haven't touched
any food since
Queen Daenerys left.
Daenerys is the
dragon queen.
Can't very well let
the dragons starve,
that's obvious.
If a dragon does not
want to eat, how do you
force him to eat?
Dragons do not
do well in captivity.
How do you know this?
TYRION: That's what I do.
I drink
and I know things.
The dragons Aegon used
to conquer Westeros
ranged over
hundreds of miles.
then Daenerys's ancestors
started chaining
them up in pens.
A few generations later,
The last dragons were
no larger than cats.
They must be unchained
or they'll waste away.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
Missandei,
how many times were
you in the company
of these dragons?
Many times.
And did they
ever harm you?
Never.
Dragons are intelligent.
More intelligent
than men according
to some maesters.
They have affection
for their friends
and fury for their enemies.
I am their friend.
Do they know that?
They will. It's time
they had their supper.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(METAL SCRAPING, CLANGING)
(GROWLING)
(CHAINS RATTLING)
(ROARS)
(GROWLING)
I'm friends
with your mother.
(ROARING)
I'm here to help.
Don't eat the help.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
(ROARING)
When I was a child,
an uncle asked
what gift I wanted
for my name day.
I begged him
for one of you.
"It wouldn't even have
to be a big dragon,"
I told him.
"It could be little,
like me."
Everyone laughed like
it was the funniest thing
they had ever heard.
Then my father told me
the last dragon had
died a century ago.
I cried myself to
sleep that night.
But here you are.
(CLANKING)
(GASPS)
(GROWLING)
Next time I have
an idea like that,
punch me in the face.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(FEMALE MERCHANT SHOUTING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
WAIF: What's your name?
(COINS CLINK)
(GRUNTS)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
What's your name?
No one.
(SCOFFS)
I don't believe that.
(GRUNTS)
You don't
believe that.
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
(SHOUTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
JAQEN: Who are you?
No one.
If a girl says her name,
a man will let her sleep
under a roof tonight.
A girl has no name.
If a girl says her name,
a man will feed her tonight.
A girl has no name.
If a girl says
her name, a man will
give her eyes back.
A girl has no name.
Come.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
Leave it.
A girl is not
a beggar anymore.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
HARALD: We came upon
the bodies on our way here.
Half a dozen men?
Your best hunters?
They obviously had help.
I didn't think Lady Sansa
killed them all by herself.
Thank you for this
report, Lord Karstark.
We know
where she's going.
Her brother's
at Castle Black.
Ned Stark's last
surviving son?
Jon Snow is a bastard,
not a Stark.
So was I, Father.
HARALD: Your hold
on the North will
never be secure
as long as a Stark can
walk through that door.
Castle Black isn't defended
on the southern side.
And the few men left
are barely men at all.
Farm boys and thieves.
With a small force,
we could storm the castle,
kill Jon Snow...
Murder the Lord Commander
of the Night's Watch?
You'd unite every house
in the North against us.
We don't need every
house in the North.
The Umbers, the Manderlys
and the Karstarks
command more soldiers
than all the other
houses combined.
With their support,
none could challenge us.
The Starks lost my house
the day King Robb cut
off my father's head.
(SNIFFS) It's time for
new blood in the north.
If you acquire
a reputation
as a mad dog,
you'll be treated
as a mad dog.
Taken out back and
slaughtered for pig feed.
WOLKAN: My Lords.
Lady Walda has
given birth.
A boy. (CHUCKLES)
Red-cheeked
and healthy.
My congratulations,
Lord Bolton.
Congratulations, Father.
I look forward
to meeting
my new brother.
You'll always
be my firstborn.
Thank you
for saying that.
It means a great
deal to me.
(SQUELCHING)
(GROANING)
RAMSAY: Maester Wolkan,
send ravens to all
the northern houses.
Roose Bolton is dead.
Poisoned by our enemies.
How did he die?
Poisoned by his enemies.
You're talking
to your lord.
Use respect.
Forgive me,
my lord.
Send for Lady Walda
and the baby.
She's resting, my lord.
At once, my lord.
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
(MEN SHOUTING)
There he is.
Isn't he wonderful?
May I hold him?
(STUTTERS)
Of course.
Little brother.
Lord Bolton
sent for us.
Have you seen him?
Of course.
Follow me, Mother.
(DOGS BARKING)
Where is Lord Bolton?
(BARKING CONTINUES)
(CLANGING)
Get down!
(BARKING STOPS)
(BABY CRYING)
WALDA: It's all right.
It's all right. Come on.
(WALDA SHUSHING)
It's cold out here, Ramsay.
I need to feed him.
Ramsay, where
is your father?
Ramsay.
Where is Lord Bolton?
I am Lord Bolton.
(BABY CRYING)
Ramsay.
Ramsay, please.
I'll leave Winterfell.
I'll go back to
the Riverlands.
Please.
Ramsay.
(BABY CRYING)
He's your brother.
I prefer being
an only child.
(DOGS GROWLING)
(WHISTLES)
(BARKING)
(SCREAMING)
(FLESH TEARING)
BRIENNE: I saw her
with a man.
I don't think
he hurt her.
She didn't want
to leave him, he didn't
want to leave her.
You don't know
which way she went?
I spent three days
looking for her.
She disappeared.
How'd she look?
She looked good.
She wasn't exactly
dressed like a lady.
No, she wouldn't be.
What happened
at Winterfell?
I should have gone
with you while
I had the chance.
It was a difficult
choice, my lady.
We've all had to make
difficult choices.
(HORSE WHINNYING)
THEON: We shouldn't
be lighting fires.
It's not safe.
He won't stop
hunting us.
We just have
to make it to
Castle Black.
Once we're with Jon,
Ramsay won't be
able to touch us.
Jon will have me killed
the moment I step
through the gate.
I won't let him.
I'll tell him the truth
about Bran and Rickon.
And the truth about
the farm boys I killed
in their place.
And the truth
about Ser Rodrik,
who I beheaded.
(SIGHS)
And the truth about Robb,
who I betrayed.
When you take the black,
all your crimes are forgiven.
I don't want
to be forgiven.
I can never make
amends to your family
for the things I've done.
They'll keep you safer
than I ever could.
You're not
coming with us?
(GASPS)
I would have taken you
all the way to the Wall.
I would have died
to get you there.
(CRYING)
May I take
one of the horses?
Where will you go?
Home.
(WAVES CRASHING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
YARA: The Glovers have
retaken Deepwood Motte.
And the ironborn
who held it?
They died
fighting to a man.
What is dead
may never die.
But they did, and our
invasion died with them.
Deepwood Motte was
our last stronghold
on the mainland.
BALON: Then we
will take more.
Why? For more
pinecones and rocks?
Because I order it.
We can defeat
anyone at sea,
but we'll never
hold lands and castles
against mainland armies.
Not if our captains
defy my orders,
abandon their posts,
and sacrifice our men
on foolish missions.
I won't apologize for
trying to rescue Theon.
Then where is he?
Where is your kingdom?
We took those castles
because the Northerners
marched off to war.
That war is over.
The last time we
provoked them too far,
I watched from that window
as they breached our walls
and knocked down our towers.
I lost two brothers
that day.
And I lost three sons.
The War of the Five Kings,
they call it.
Well, the other
four are dead.
When you rule the iron
islands, you can wage
all the peace you want.
But for now, shut your mouth
and obey, or I will make
another heir who will.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(WAVES CRASHING)
(WIND HOWLING)
(BRIDGE CREAKING)
BALON: Let me pass.
You fool, move aside
for your King.
EURON: Haven't
I always, brother?
I thought you'd be rotting
under some foreign sea by now.
What is dead
may never die.
Has the custom changed
since I've been gone?
Aren't you supposed
to repeat the words?
You can mock our
god without my help.
I don't mock
the Drowned God.
I am
From Oldtown to Qarth,
when men see my sails,
they pray.
(WIND HOWLS)
(CHUCKLES)
You're old, brother.
You've had your time.
Now let another rule.
I heard you lost your mind
during a storm
on the Jade Sea.
They tied you to the mast
to keep you from
jumping overboard.
They did.
And when the storm passed,
you cut out their tongues.
I needed silence.
What kind of an ironborn
loses his senses
during a storm?
I am the storm, brother.
The first storm
and the last.
And you're in my way.
(BALON SCREAMS)
(THUDS)
(PANTING)
Lord, take your
servant Balon back
beneath the waves.
Feed the creatures
of your kingdom
on his flesh.
Pull his bones down to your
depths to rest beside his
ancestors and his children.
ALL: What is dead
may never die.
YARA: I'm going to
find out who did this.
I'm going to feed
them to the sharks
while they live.
I swear it by
the Salt Throne.
The Salt Throne is not
yours to swear upon,
not unless the
Kingsmoot chooses you.
My father would have
wanted me to rule.
Your father does
not get to choose.
The law is clear.
Perhaps you'll win.
Perhaps you'll be
the first woman in history
to rule the ironborn.
And perhaps not.
(KNOCKING)
Come in.
(DOOR OPENS)
I'm sorry, my lady.
Didn't mean to interrupt.
You interrupt nothing.
I assume you know
why I'm here.
I will after you tell me.
It's about
the Lord Commander.
The former Lord Commander.
Does he have to be?
What are you asking?
Do you know of any magic
that could help him?
Bring him back?
If you want to help him,
leave him be.
Can it be done?
There are some
with this power.
How?
(SOFTLY) I don't know.
Have you seen it done?
I met a man who came
back from the dead,
but the priest
who did it...
It shouldn't
have been possible.
But it was.
It could be now.
Not for me.
Not for you?
I saw you drink
poison that should
have killed you.
I saw you give birth
to a demon made
of shadows.
Everything I believed,
the great victory
I saw in the flames...
(SHAKILY)
All of it was a lie.
You were right all along.
The Lord never
spoke to me.
Fuck him, then.
Fuck all of them.
I'm not a devout man,
obviously.
Seven gods, drowned
gods, tree gods,
it's all the same.
I'm not asking the
Lord of Light for help.
I'm asking the woman
who showed me
that miracles exist.
I never had this gift.
Have you ever tried?
(MELISANDRE CHANTING
IN VALYRIAN)
(SIZZLES)
(CONTINUES CHANTING
IN VALYRIAN)
(CONTINUES CHANTING FAINTLY)
(SIGHS) Please.
(SCOFFS)
(WHIMPERS)
(GASPING)