(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
(MEERA PANTING)
(WIND WHOOSHING)
(GASPS)
Burn them all!
Where's my sister?
(GRUNTING)
(CAWING)
Burn them all!
(SNARLING)
(GRUNTING, CONTINUES PANTING)
(STRAINING)
(CRYING)
(SOFTLY) Please.
(CONTINUES CRYING)
Burn them.
Burn them all!
(SNARLING)
AERYS: Burn them all!
(SCREAMING)
(SNARLING CONTINUES)
(MEERA SOBBING)
Meera.
They found us.
(WIND WHOOSHING)
(SNARLING)
MEERA: I'm so sorry.
(NEIGHING)
(SNARLING CONTINUES)
(GRUNTS)
Come with me, now.
The dead don't rest.
(NEIGHING)
It's so green.
Oh, yes.
Once you get south
of the Riverlands,
very different
sorts of trees
start to take over.
Maple, elm,
beech, poplar.
(SAMWELL CHUCKLES)
The odd willow.
And, of course,
now that summer's over,
you'll start seeing
the autumn colors
coming in.
Still, you'll find
more green here
than anywhere else.
You're nervous.
You're a nervous talker.
That's not any better,
being a nervous mute.
I didn't think
I'd ever come
back here,
after my father made
me renounce my title
and inheritance
and, well, threatened
to kill me if I didn't.
A person just doesn't
feel welcome at that point.
And I certainly didn't
expect to be introducing
him to my family.
So you know
what to tell them.
That little Sam
is your baby.
Yes, now that's
very important.
If he thinks that little Sam
is his grandchild,
he'll take you in.
He'll get an education.
He'll learn to read.
And you can help
teach him. Huh?
What did you tell
your family about me?
I told them I met
you in the North.
Did you tell them
how far north?
Well, it wasn't a very
large piece of parchment.
You didn't tell them
where I'm really from?
I'm a wildling?
The thing is...
My father doesn't
like wildlings.
He hoped I'd make a man
of myself by "killing
some bloody wildlings,"
so it's probably
a good subject to avoid
if at all possible.
I think we're here.
Sam.
Oh, Sam.
Oh, hello, Mother.
I never thought
I'd see you again.
You look wonderful.
Oh.
(SAM GRUNTS)
(CHUCKLES)
Talla?
Gods, you're
a woman now.
Father says I have
to marry Symun Fossoway.
He has yellow teeth...
That's enough, Talla.
Oh, um...
Mother,
this is Gilly.
Oh, my.
You are lovely.
I am happy to know
you, Lady Tarly.
Oh, and...
And this,
this is our
son Samwell.
Hello, little one.
(CHUCKLING)
It's me,
your grandmother.
(CHUCKLING)
May I hold him?
Yes, of course.
Oh...
You have a curious
mind, I can tell.
You'll be a scholar
like your father.
Where is father?
And Dickon?
They're on a hunt.
They'll join us
for dinner.
Come inside.
Such a journey.
You must be exhausted.
Come, you'll be
wanting a bath
after all that travel.
And a dress
for dinner.
You can wear
one of mine.
What's your color?
Midnight blue
or silver?
Silver, maybe.
Come.
You can choose
one in my bedroom
if you want.
TOMMEN: Is there
no other way?
You're afraid
for her?
Of course
I'm afraid for her!
It just seems
very dangerous.
She'll be protected
the entire way.
The Faith Militant are
very stern with those
who overstep their bounds.
(CHUCKLES) And
Queen Margaery
isn't your mother.
I suspect the gods
will predispose
the common people
to gentleness
on her behalf.
She's truly opened
her heart to them.
She's always been very
devoted to the poor
and the unfortunate.
And now she's devoted
to the gods as well.
Would you like
to see her?
(DOOR OPENS, CREAKING)
Have they hurt you?
Have they
mistreated you?
No, Your Grace.
I've missed you.
More than
you could know.
We'll be together
again soon,
and everything
will be better
than it was before.
Better how?
Soon the...
Walk of atonement.
He says there's
no other way.
Have you spoken
to him at all,
the High Sparrow?
Yes, a few times.
Have you?
Yes, I have.
He's not quite what we
thought he was, is he?
(CHUCKLES) You think
I'm mad. I sound mad.
No. No, you don't.
You could never.
You're right,
he's not.
He's a lot more...
He is.
There's something
about him.
His way of looking
at the world.
It's not an easy thing,
admitting to yourself
what you really are.
It's taken me a while.
He's helped me.
What are you
talking about?
You're a good person.
You've always been
a good person.
You're the best
person I know.
(LAUGHS)
I was just telling
him about your
devotion to the poor.
Ah, yes, I visited
their hovels,
and I fed them soup,
and I made sure
I was seen doing it.
(BOOK THUDDING)
I never gave them
what they really
needed, though.
I've had lots of time
to think about how good
I was at seeming good.
All those stories
I told myself
about who I was
and why I did
the things I did.
There were so many
lies in those stories.
I don't understand.
It's all right.
It really is.
It's such a relief
to let go of those lies.
What about Loras?
I love my brother.
I will always
love my brother.
His soul is pure
and perfect.
His sins don't
erase that purity,
they only obscure it.
He just needs
to atone for them.
We all do.
Sooner or later,
one way or another.
The gods have
a plan for us all.
It's hard
to walk in this.
It's beautiful.
You're beautiful.
This venison,
it's very tasty.
Is it from
today's hunt?
Well, no.
We haven't been able
to cure that one yet.
This is last week's.
Oh, uh...
(CHUCKLES)
Of course.
Sorry.
Long journey.
(GIGGLES)
Brought it down
from 70 yards.
One shot.
Oh! That's
a fair distance.
So do you do much
hunting up at the Wall?
Oh, yes. Yes.
A good amount.
North of the Wall,
you don't hunt,
you don't eat.
Mostly deer,
or is it elk
as well?
Rabbits.
Sometimes squirrels.
I say "we,"
it's my friend
Jon mostly.
Sometimes Edd.
And Gilly.
She's quite
a good hunter
as well.
Huntress.
LADY TARLY:
I imagine it's common
where you're from.
We once met a man,
Lord Umber from Last Hearth,
wasn't it, Randyll?
Who said he taught
all his daughters
how to hunt.
TALLA: Your father
taught you to hunt?
Our father would
never teach us.
I think our father
could learn a thing
or two from your father.
That's enough of that.
Samwell, would you
care for more bread?
Oh, um...
Yes. Yes, please.
Thank you, Mother.
Not fat enough already?
I traveled south
under orders from
the Lord Commander.
He wants me to...
I read your letter.
You're to be
a maester.
Yes.
And once I have
my chain, I'll return
to Castle Black.
I thought the
Night's Watch might
make a man of you.
Something resembling
a man at least.
You managed to stay
soft and fat.
Your nose
buried in books.
Spending your life
reading about the
achievements of better men.
I'll wager you still
can't sit a horse
or wield a sword.
Randyll, to be Maester
of the Night's Watch
is a great honor.
He can wield
a sword.
He killed a Thenn.
He killed
a White Walker.
(LAUGHING)
There's no such thing.
I saw it with my own
eyes on our way down
to Castle Black.
He drove a dagger
into the Walker's heart.
He risked his own
life to save mine
more than once.
He's a greater warrior
than either of
you will ever be.
Your way down
to Castle Black?
Where did he kill
a White Walker?
Where are you from?
How'd you come
to meet my son?
The Night's Watch
came to our keep.
Where?
Gilly.
North of the Wall.
North of the Wall?
You're a wildling.
The Seven Kingdoms have
waged war against these
savages for centuries,
and here I sit,
hosting one in my hall,
thanks to my son.
See that sword?
It's called Heartsbane.
It's been in our family
for 500 years.
It's Valyrian steel.
Only a handful of them
left in the world.
It's supposed
to go to my firstborn
son after I die.
To him.
He will never
wield that sword.
If he were to become
Lord Tarly of Horn Hill,
it would be the
end of this house.
I took you for
a Mole's Town whore
when I saw you,
and I made
my peace with that.
Who else would
have him?
But I overestimated him.
No.
It was a wildling whore
that seduced my son.
This you getting
back at me, boy?
Hmm?
Bringing that to my table
and making me dine with it?
And you got what you
were after, didn't you?
A bastard.
A half-breed bastard.
Your invitation
into our home.
Come, my dear.
Talla.
I've lost my appetite.
He dishonors us.
You dishonor yourself.
Your mother's a fine woman.
You're not worthy of her.
To please her, I'll take
the wildling in. She can
work in the kitchens.
The bastard
will be raised here.
But this will be the
last night you ever
spend at Horn Hill.
I'm sorry I let him
treat you that way.
I was afraid he'd turn
you and little Sam away.
I'm not angry at you.
I'm angry that
horrible people
can treat good people that
way and get away with it.
When do you
have to go?
First light.
(EXHALES)
(SAM CRYING)
Say good-bye
to him for me.
You're not what
he thinks you are, Sam.
He doesn't know
what you are.
Good-bye, Gilly.
Sam?
We're leaving.
What?
Get your things.
I don't have
any things.
What are you doing?
We belong together.
All of us.
What about your
mother and sister?
Oh, they'll
understand.
(SAM COOING)
Your sister's dress.
She won't mind.
Looks better
on you anyway.
Sam.
That's your
father's sword.
It's my
family's sword.
Sam.
Won't he come
for it?
He can
bloody well try.
(AUDIENCE CHATTERING)
The lion and
the rose are one.
I thank
the gods above.
And to you,
my beauteous bride,
I pledge
undying love.
ALL: Hail King Joffrey.
Hail Queen Margaery.
I'll drink a toast
to my new queen,
for there is
no one fairer.
Dear Uncle, will you
share my joy and
be my royal cupbearer?
Drink long and deep,
my noble king,
from this cup
of sweet wine.
The last drink
he shall ever take.
And vengeance
shall be mine.
(LAUGHING)
(AUDIENCE DISAPPROVINGLY
MURMUR)
(AUDIENCE BOOING)
(EXCLAIMING)
(AUDIENCE GASPING)
Poison!
Murder!
I gasp. I die.
I limp.
And it was he
that poisoned me.
My evil Uncle Imp.
(LAUGHING)
(AUDIENCE BOOING)
My firstborn son.
My golden lion
foully, falsely slain.
I pray you found
a lasting peace,
free from strife
and pain.
Hear my prayer,
O cruel gods.
Take my life instead.
For I cannot face
another day when
my sweet boy is dead.
O woe.
(CRYING) O grief.
O darkest day,
my heart is full
of sorrow.
All hope is lost.
All joy is gone.
And there is no tomorrow.
(APPLAUSE, CHEERING)
What is that
I hear and smell?
Someone I'll soon
send to hell.
It's time to see
if truth they told,
who said
Tywin Lannister
shits gold.
(GASPS)
(AUDIENCE GASPS)
You beast.
You killed my wife,
and now you've taken
your father's life.
No worse child ever
stained this land.
Curse the day
I named you.
(SCREAMING)
(FARTING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
My greatest crime.
Now I must flee,
and sail across
the narrow sea
to do unto you
more treachery.
Don't fear winter.
Fear me!
(LAUGHING)
ACTOR PLAYING TYWIN:
Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I give you Bianca,
Clarenzo.
I give you Bobono.
I give you Camello.
And last but not least,
sweet Lady Crane.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Give this a good beating.
Shake those fleas out.
That's a dear.
That crowd was shit.
Girl.
What are you
doing back here?
Nothing.
I saw you the other
day in the audience.
How many times
have you seen
this stupid play?
Three times.
Did you pay?
No.
I remember when
the players came
to my village.
I didn't have
any money,
so I snuck in.
Just like you.
Saw the painted faces,
the costumes,
listened to the songs,
cried when the
young lovers died
in each other's arms.
I ran off and joined
them the next day,
never looked back.
You're very good.
My final speech
is shit.
But to be fair
to myself, which
I always like to be,
the writing's no good.
So change it.
It would all just be
farting, belching, and
slapping without you.
How would you change it?
The queen loves her
son more than anything.
And he was taken
from her before she
could say good-bye.
She wouldn't just cry.
She would be angry.
She would want
to kill the person
who did this to her.
What's your name?
Mercy.
You have
very expressive
eyes, Mercy.
Wonderful eyebrows.
Do you like pretending
to be other people?
I have to go.
My father's
waiting for me.
Lady Crane,
they loved you.
They were sweet.
Or drunk.
Drunkenly sweet.
No laugh
for Ned's death.
These people are
worse than animals.
But they loved her.
They all love her.
Yes, you are
adored by people
and animals alike.
I do what I can
with what I'm given.
(CHUCKLES)
"With what
you're given"?
Well, I was thinking...
We're all thinkers
now, are we?
Full to the tits
with ideas.
I didn't mean...
You have ideas,
I have ideas,
he has ideas.
Why should my ideas
have any more
value than yours
simply because
I've been doing this
my whole life?
Who is anyone
to judge my work?
This is my profession.
I know what I'm doing.
You have
no right to
an opinion.
(GASPS)
Careful of that one.
She wants you dead.
And?
As I expected.
A shame.
A girl had many gifts.
You promised me.
Don't let her suffer.
(DRAMATIC INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
Company, halt!
My lord.
My friends,
the hour has come.
Madness has
overtaken this city
and grasped
in its claws
my children.
But now we must
drive it back under the
rocks whence it came.
Madness has
had its day!
SOLDIER: Forward, march!
Rich or poor,
noble or common,
if we sin,
we must atone.
Margaery of House Tyrell
came to us a sinner.
She stood before the gods
in the holy Sept and lied.
She turned a blind eye
to her brother's sins.
She disgraced her house,
her king, and herself.
(CROWD CHATTERING)
SOLDIER: Company, halt!
Face front!
Turn!
HIGH SEPTON: Lord Tyrell.
Ser Jaime.
Sorry to interrupt.
We're here for
Queen Margaery and
Ser Loras Tyrell.
Give them to us,
and we'll be on our way.
I don't have the authority
to give them to you.
And you don't
have the authority
to take them.
MAN: That's right.
(CROWD CHATTERING)
(EXCLAIMS)
SOLDIER: Lock spears!
(SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
I speak for King Tommen
of House Baratheon,
first of his name.
The gods don't
recognize his authority
in this matter.
You've already insulted
one great house.
It won't happen twice.
Every last Sparrow
will die
before Margaery Tyrell
walks down that street.
To die in the service
of the gods would please
each and every one of us.
We yearn for it.
But there is no call
for it today.
There will be
no walk of atonement.
(CROWD CHATTERING)
Order up.
Queen Margaery
has already atoned
for her sins
by bringing another
into the true light
of the Seven.
Together we announce
a new age of harmony.
A holy alliance
between the Crown
and the Faith.
(CROWD CHEERING)
WOMAN: Long live
King Tommen and bless
you, Queen Margaery!
The Crown
and the Faith
are the twin pillars
upon which the world rests.
Together we will restore
the Seven Kingdoms to glory.
(CROWD CHEERING)
What's happening?
He's beaten us.
That's what's happening.
When you attack
the Faith, you attack
the Crown.
Anyone who attacks
the Crown is unfit
to serve as Lord Commander
of the Kingsguard.
I've been a member
of the Kingsguard since
before you were born.
You don't have
to do this. You don't
have to do anything.
I have to answer
to the gods.
Not when you're
sitting in that chair.
The Crown's decision
on this matter is final.
Will I be walking
naked in the streets?
Or will I spend
a few months in the
Sept dungeons first
to teach me about
the gods' mercy?
You have served your
house and your king
faithfully for many years.
And you will
continue to do so.
But not in this city.
You've lost it?
BLACK WALDER: Yes, Father.
It's a castle,
not a bloody sheep.
Presumably you still
know where it is.
You didn't
lose Riverrun.
You let the Blackfish
take it from you.
He surprised us.
He knows the castle
better than anyone.
You did lose
the Blackfish after
the Red Wedding.
You had him right
here in this hall,
and you let him leave.
And when I told you
to hunt him down
and kill him,
you couldn't find him.
That's what it means
to lose something.
Now he's come back
and taken Riverrun.
I don't think it's
fair to blame us...
For 300 years we
kissed Tully boots,
swore oaths to them
and their stinking
fish banners.
Not again.
Riverrun is ours.
Take it back.
We don't have
the men.
We've got 10 times
as many men as
the damn Blackfish.
BLACK WALDER: The Mallisters
have risen against us.
And the Blackwoods.
LOTHAR: The Brotherhood
Without Banners is rallying
the commoners against us,
raiding our supply
trains and camps.
BLACK WALDER:
Riverrun can withstand
a siege for a year.
If I want excuses,
I'll put her in charge.
They're laughing at us.
All across the Riverlands,
right down to King's Landing,
they're laughing at us.
I hear it in my sleep!
I'm not dead yet,
unfortunately for you.
And I'll not leave
this world until they all
choke on that laughter.
Take that castle back.
He'll never
yield, Father.
Oh!
He'll yield.
You'll show him
the knife you used
to kill Robb Stark's child
in its whore mother's belly,
and you'll show him
the knife you used
to open
his niece's throat.
And you'll remind him
who it was
that got married
at the Red Wedding
in the first place.
His nephew.
Cheer up,
Lord Edmure.
You're going home.
I'm being sent
to deal with
the Blackfish.
Apparently Walder Frey
can't manage it on his own
because he's 400 years old.
Sent me with an army
to the Riverlands and a siege
that could last months.
Better you're elsewhere
at the head of an army
than in the Sept dungeons.
I'm not going
to the Riverlands.
(POURING)
What, then?
I'm going to give Bronn
the largest bag of gold
anyone's ever seen
and have him gather
the best killers he knows.
I'll take them to the
Sept, and I'll remove
the High Sparrow's head
and every other
Sparrow head I can find.
You can't.
He has our son!
He stole our son!
He's torn our family apart.
How should we treat people
who tear us apart?
We should treat
them without mercy,
and we will.
But if you kill the
High Sparrow, you won't
leave the Sept alive.
And without you,
this is all for nothing.
Stand at the head
of our army
where you belong,
where father wanted you.
Show our men where
their loyalties belong.
Show them what
Lannisters are,
what we do
to our enemies.
And take that stupid
little castle back because
it's ours and because you can.
You'll stand trial soon.
I need to be here for you.
It will be a trial
by combat.
I have the mountain.
They've made us both
stronger, all of them.
They have no idea
how strong we are.
No idea what
we're going
to do to them.
We've always
been together.
We'll always
be together.
We're the only
two people
in the world.
Why did you help us?
The three-eyed raven
sent for me.
The three-eyed
raven's dead.
Now he lives again.
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
When I last saw you,
you were a boy.
A fearless boy.
Loved to climb
the castle walls,
frighten his mother.
Who are you?
Uncle Benjen.
The last letter Jon
wrote me said you had
been lost beyond the Wall.
I led a ranging party
deep into the North
to find White Walkers.
They found us.
A White Walker
stabbed me in the gut
with a sword of ice.
Left me there to die.
To turn.
The children found me.
Stopped the Walker's
magic from taking hold.
How?
The same way they
made the Walkers
in the first place.
You saw it yourself.
Dragonglass.
A shard of dragonglass
plunged into your heart.
You are
the three-eyed
raven now.
I didn't have time
to learn. I can't
control anything.
You must learn
to control it before
the Night King comes.
Drink.
One way or another,
he will find his way
to the world of men.
When he does,
you will be there
waiting for him.
And you will be ready.
(MAN SHOUTING COMMAND)
Everything all right?
How many days'
ride to Meereen?
A week at best.
How many ships
will I need to bring
my khalasar to Westeros?
Dothraki and all their
horses, the Unsullied,
the Second Sons...
1,000 ships easily.
Probably more.
And who has that many?
Nobody.
Nobody yet.
So we ride for Meereen,
and after that
we sail for Westeros.
And what then?
I take what is mine.
You weren't made to sit
on a chair in a palace.
What was I made for?
You're a conqueror,
Daenerys Stormborn.
Wait here.
(SCREECHING)
(HORSES NICKERING, NEIGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(DRAGON SCREECHING)
(SCREECHING)
(HORSES NEIGHING)
(ALL YELLING)
(ROARING)