(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Where you gonna go?
South.
What you gonna do?
(EXHALES)
Get warm.
(CLANKING)
I was with you
at Hardhome.
We saw what's
out there.
We know
it's coming here.
How can you leave us now?
I did everything
I could. You know...
You swore a vow.
Aye, I pledged my life
to the Night's Watch.
I gave my life.
For all nights to come.
They killed me, Edd,
my own brothers!
You want me to stay
here after that?
(HORN BLOWING)
MAN 1: Riders approaching!
MAN 2: Open the gate!
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
(EXHALES)
(GASPING)
This is good soup.
Do you remember
those kidney pies
Old Nan used to make?
With the peas
and onions?
Mmm.
We never should
have left Winterfell.
Don't you wish
we could go back
to the day we left?
I want to scream at myself,
"Don't go, you idiot."
How could we know?
I spent a lot of time
thinking about what
an ass I was to you.
I wish I could
change everything.
We were children.
I was awful,
just admit it.
(CHUCKLES)
You were
occasionally awful.
(SCOFFS)
I'm sure I can't
have been great fun.
Always sulking in
the corner while
the rest of you played.
Can you forgive me?
There's nothing
to forgive.
Forgive me.
All right.
All right, I forgive you.
(LAUGHS)
(COUGHING)
You'd think after
thousands of years,
the Night's Watch
would have learned
how to make a good ale.
Mmm.
(JON SNIFFS)
Where will you go?
Where will we go?
If I don't watch over you,
Father's ghost will
come back and murder me.
Where will we go?
I can't stay here,
not after what happened.
There's only one
place we can go.
Home.
Well, should we tell
the Boltons to pack up
and leave?
We'll take it
back from them.
I don't have an army.
How many wildlings
did you save?
They didn't come
here to serve me.
They owe you
their lives.
You think they'll be safe
here if Roose Bolton
remains Warden of the North?
Sansa.
Winterfell is
our home.
It's ours.
And Arya's and
Bran's and Rickon's.
Wherever they are,
it belongs to our family.
We have to fight for it.
I'm tired of fighting.
It's all I've done
since I left home.
I've killed brothers
of the Night's Watch.
I've killed wildlings.
I've killed men
that I admire.
I hanged a boy
younger than Bran.
I fought
and I lost.
If we don't take
back the North,
we'll never be safe.
I want you to help me.
But I'll do it myself
if I have to.
My lady.
Ser Davos.
Will you stay here
at Castle Black?
I will do as
Jon Snow commands.
You serve
Jon Snow now?
He's the Prince
That Was Promised.
Forgive me, my lady,
I had thought
that was Stannis.
What happened
down there?
There was a battle.
Stannis was defeated.
And Shireen?
What happened
to the princess?
BRIENNE: I saw
what happened.
I saw Stannis' forces
defeated in the field.
My lady,
I'm Ser Davos Seaworth.
We've met before.
I was Kingsguard
to Renly Baratheon.
Before Renly
was assassinated
with blood magic.
That's in the past now.
Yes, it's in the past.
It doesn't mean
I forget.
Or forgive.
He admitted it,
you know.
Who did?
Stannis.
Just before
I executed him.
(SIGHS)
(HORSES APPROACHING)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
The Defender
of the Vale!
Uncle Petyr!
(GRUNTS)
My lord.
Come and see.
I missed your
name day. Go on.
(GASPS)
(SCREECHES)
A falcon!
A gyrfalcon.
Greatest and
rarest of birds.
Last time
I saw you, Baelish,
you told me you were
taking Sansa Stark home
with you to the Fingers.
Indeed I was.
And yet,
not long ago,
we received reports that
she has been married to
Ramsay Bolton in Winterfell.
On our way to the Fingers,
we were set upon by
a large force of Bolton men.
Seemed to know
exactly when
we were traveling
and exactly whom
we were transporting.
Do you take me
for a fool?
Tell me, Lord Royce,
how many people knew
of my travel plans
with Sansa Stark?
I shared my
intentions with you
and no one else.
Slander a man
in his own home,
you might find yourself
crossing swords with him.
LITTLEFINGER:
Your home is the Vale.
The Lord of the Vale
stands before us.
And only his judgment
concerns me.
ROBIN: (SCOFFS)
Should we throw him
through the Moon Door?
My lord.
My lord, I have
always been faithful
to House Arryn.
To your father,
to your mother,
and now to you.
Do you believe him,
Uncle Petyr?
(SCREECHING)
Lord Royce has
served the Vale well.
He's enjoyed
a distinguished
military career.
If we could trust
his absolute loyalty,
he would make
a capable commander
in the wars to come.
You can trust
my absolute loyalty,
my lord.
I think he deserves
one more chance.
What do you say?
Fine.
I bring good news.
My friends in the North
tell me Sansa has
escaped Winterfell.
I expect she's headed to
Castle Black where her brother
serves as Lord Commander.
But she won't
be safe there.
Not with
the Boltons after her.
(SIGHS)
(HORSES NEIGHING)
She's my cousin.
We should help her.
That was
my instinct as well.
Our lord has spoken.
Gather the Knights
of the Vale.
The time has come
to join the fray.
(BIRDS SCREECHING)
GREY WORM: You invite
the enemy into our city.
TYRION: I did.
As a clever man
once told me,
"We make peace
with our enemies,
not our friends."
I don't make peace
with the queen's enemies.
I kill the queen's enemies.
Yes, that's the
military approach.
And how has
that worked here
in Meereen?
I represent
the diplomatic
approach.
Our queen tried to make
peace with the Masters,
and they tried to murder her.
We enter these
negotiations
with open eyes.
Trust me.
My own recent experience
with slavery has taught me the
horrors of that institution.
How many days
were you a slave?
(STAMMERS) Long
enough to know.
Not long enough
to understand.
I bought this dwarf
for a single gold honor.
And somehow, you've risen
to the top of the Great
Pyramid of Meereen.
It's most impressive.
And now you speak
for the Good
Masters of Astapor.
Here's to reversals
of fortune.
We came here to
meet the queen,
and instead we're greeted
by a dwarf and a eunuch.
TYRION: Let's make
this simple, shall we?
Tell me what you want.
We want you to
leave Slaver's Bay.
Take your dragons
and your mercenaries
and go.
Queen Daenerys
won't stay in
Meereen forever.
Her path takes
her westward.
When we last met,
I offered her ships,
so she could
return to Westeros
where she belongs.
She refused them.
She refused them
because hundreds
of thousands
of men, women and children
still lived in chains.
As they have since
the dawn of time.
Not anymore.
Oh, you think
you're a free man now?
You still
follow orders.
Just because your master
has silver hair and tits
doesn't mean
she's not a master.
Friends, friends.
Friends.
Please.
There have always been
those with wealth and power
and those with nothing.
That is the way of the world.
I'm not here to change
the way of the world.
Slavery is
the way of
our world.
You don't need slaves
to make money.
There haven't been
slaves in Westeros
for hundreds of years,
and I grew up richer
than any of you.
But our queen recognizes
that she erred
by abolishing slavery
without providing a new
system to replace it.
So, here is the
queen's proposal.
Slavery will never
return to Meereen,
but she will give
the other cities
of Slaver's Bay
time to adjust
to the new order.
What does that mean?
Instead of abolishing
slavery overnight,
we will give you
seven years to end
the practice.
Slaveholders will be
compensated for their losses,
of course, at fair prices.
In exchange, you will
cut off your support for
the Sons of the Harpy.
We do not support
Fine, fine, but you will
cut it off all the same.
I do hope you accept,
my friends.
You will not receive
a better offer.
(RINGING)
Let us sail on the
tide of freedom
instead of being
drowned by it.
And as a parting gift
to our honored guests.
Give freedom
a chance.
See if it doesn't taste
every bit as good
as what came before.
(WHISPERING IN VALYRIAN)
(TYRION SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
Perhaps I should
translate for you.
MAN: We speak
the common tongue.
Excellent.
You met with
the slavers today.
TYRION: I did.
Our brothers and sisters
died fighting these scum.
Now you invite them
to our city and drink
wine with them?
TYRION: I imagine
this room was built
so the rulers could
intimidate the ruled.
But I am not
your ruler.
I'm not the
Breaker of Chains.
I'm not
the Unburnt.
And I am certainly not
the Mother of Dragons.
You are a stranger here.
So why do you represent
Meereen in these talks
with our enemies?
Because our queen
chose me as her advisor.
Until she returns
from her travels...
When does she return?
Soon. You have my word.
We don't know you.
We don't trust you.
We know Torgo Nudho.
We fight with him
against the Masters.
We trust him.
And that is exactly
why Grey Worm took part
in these negotiations.
As commander of
the Unsullied, he knows
how to defeat the slavers.
And he knows when
it is time to make peace.
You have made peace
with the slavers?
TYRION: We offered terms.
(SPEAKS VALYRIAN)
(EXHALES)
Do not use me
for your lies.
Those men
respect you.
They respect me because
they know who I am.
They know I am loyal.
As do I.
I am loyal to my queen,
not you. If you betray
her work, you are my enemy.
I am not betraying
her work. I am trying
to save her city.
You promised the slavers
they could keep slavery.
For a short time.
Seven years
is not a short
time for a slave.
You're right.
Slavery is a horror
that should be
ended at once.
War is a horror that
should be ended at once.
I can't do
both today.
You are wrong
to trust these men.
I don't trust
the Masters.
I trust their
self-interest.
They're trustworthy if they're
convinced that working with
me is in their self-interest.
You don't know them.
You don't understand them.
We are not human
in their eyes.
They look at me
and see a weapon.
They look at her
and see a whore.
They look at me and
they see a misshapen
little beast.
Their contempt
is their weakness.
They'll underestimate us
every time, and we will
use that to our advantage.
You will not use them.
They will use you.
That is what they do.
(BIRD SCREECHING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
You all right?
Why don't you sit
and catch your breath?
I'm fine.
(CHUCKLES)
I don't think you
could ride the dragon.
Twenty years ago, maybe.
What?
Our queen.
She's wild,
you know.
Don't let her
size fool you.
It's hard enough for me,
and I'm a young man.
You...
I don't think your
heart could take it.
Must make you angry
that our queen chose me.
Makes me sad.
You'll disappoint
her before long.
She'll move on.
We'll all
disappoint her
before long.
We need each other
right now. After we're
done needing each other...
Oh, I don't want
to fight you,
Jorah the Andal.
What do I have to gain?
If I win, I'm the shit
who killed an old man.
If I lose, I'm the shit
who was killed by an old man.
You didn't get
much discipline
as a child, did you?
None.
(GRUNTS)
The road running through
the Horse Gate, they
call that the godsway.
Eastern Market,
Western Market.
When Khal Drogo died,
she was supposed
to come here and join
the Dosh Khaleen,
the widows of the
dead khals.
That's where they'll
have taken her.
The Temple of
the Dosh Khaleen.
What are you doing?
It's forbidden
to carry weapons
in the sacred city.
Isn't it forbidden to
sneak into their city
and steal their khaleesi?
If they spot us
and we're unarmed,
we'll say we're
traders heading for
the Western Market.
But if they
see weapons...
You're asking a dog
to hand over his teeth.
There's 100,000 of them
down there. We can't
fight our way out.
We wait till dark,
and then we'll find her.
(STUTTERING)
I'm very attached
to this knife.
Don't worry.
It didn't touch you.
You know what happens?
I know what happens.
I'll do it myself.
(DRUM MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHATTER)
(MOANING)
I should have been
born a Dothraki.
(MEN SPEAKING DOTHRAKI)
Come on.
(CONTINUES IN DOTHRAKI)
(SPEAKS DOTHRAKI)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(SHOUTING IN DOTHRAKI)
(BONE CRACKS)
(CHOKING)
(SQUELCHES)
(GASPING)
Told you, I'm very
attached to this knife.
You all right?
If they find a body
with a stab wound,
the whole city will
be looking for us.
(GRUNTING)
(THUDS)
Huh.
(WOMEN MURMURING IN DOTHRAKI)
(SPEAKS DOTHRAKI)
Mmm-hmm.
No, don't hurt her.
She'll give us away.
We have to go now.
(WHIMPERING)
We will never get out
of Vaes Dothrak alive.
All we can
do is try.
No.
We can do
more than that.
And you're
going to help me.
(SPEAKS DOTHRAKI)
If I were to let
you leave right now,
where would you go?
(DOOR CLOSES)
What would
you seek out?
I'd go to my brother,
my husband, my family.
Of course,
but for you, that
means seeking out
money, finery, power.
Seeking out your family
means seeking out sin.
I'm not maligning you.
I sought those
things out, too.
To the exclusion
of all else.
My father was a cobbler.
He died when I was young
and I took over his shop.
He was a simple man
and he made simple shoes.
But I found that
the more work I put
into my shoes,
the more people
wanted them.
You know, fine leather,
ornamentation, detailing,
and time.
Time, most of all.
Dozens of hours
spent on a single pair.
Quality takes time.
(CHUCKLES) Yes.
I imagine you've worn
a year of someone's
life on your back.
The highborn liked
to cover their feet
with my time,
and they paid well
for the privilege.
I used their money
to buy a taste of
their lives for myself.
Each time I indulged,
I felt myself ascending
to something better.
And one day, you walked
through a graveyard
and realized it was
all for nothing,
and set out on the
path to righteousness.
Book of the Stranger,
verse 25.
You know The
Seven-Pointed Star.
Septa Unella reads
it to me. At me.
Yes, yes, she does
enjoy reading at people.
You're close.
But it wasn't
a graveyard.
It was a feast.
I bought old fine wine
and young pretty girls,
and invited my friends
to come and share it all.
We passed around the wine,
passed around the women,
and soon we fell
into a stupor.
I woke before dawn.
I could barely stand.
Everyone else was asleep on
the couches or on the floor,
lying in heaps next
to their fine clothes.
The truth of their
bodies laid bare.
I could smell them
beneath the incense
and the perfume,
and the fine food
that had already
started to turn.
And I saw it with
perfect clarity.
I saw what my sins were.
The gold I had,
the wine I drank,
the women I used,
my ceaseless struggle
to maintain my position.
It was all part of a story.
A story I was telling
myself about who I was.
A collection of lies
that would disappear
in the light.
The people I was trying
to climb away from,
the beggars in the street,
the poor,
they were closer to
the truth than I ever was.
So, what did you do?
I left to go
and find them.
I didn't even
put on my shoes.
I walked out the door
and never went back.
Come, let's go
and see him.
Who?
Your brother.
(DOOR LOCKS)
Loras.
(SOBBING)
Listen to me.
You need to stay strong.
I can't stay strong.
I never was strong.
You are strong.
You are the future
of our house, the
future of our family.
I don't care about that.
Shh! Shh.
Have you told them that?
That you don't care?
I just want it to stop.
Help me.
(SOBBING)
They want me
to help you.
They want me to help
tear you down.
That's why he's
letting me see you.
I know it is.
And if either of us
give in to what they
want, then they win.
Let them win.
Just make it stop.
Please.
(SOBBING)
All right.
PYCELLE: And now, how
to avert disaster with
our current predicament.
This High Sparrow.
I have dealt with
fanatics of every
description, Your Grace.
Not setting them off,
that's the most
important thing.
You are beset with enemies,
both within and without.
What are you
doing here?
I am advising
the king on our
current predicament.
Leave.
I am a member of
the Small Council.
The king...
Is this a Small
Council meeting?
Obviously not.
I'm here to lend my
wisdom and my support.
Thank you for
your counsel,
Grand Maester.
That will be
all for now.
Your Grace.
Since I've missed
the past several Small
Council meetings,
I wanted to speak
to you about
a few things.
I've been thinking
about the High Sparrow.
As have we all,
unfortunately.
We need to be
careful in dealing
with such a man.
To prevent things from
escalating any further.
We have to be careful
not to antagonize him.
He has Margaery.
We can't put
her at risk.
He's dangerous.
Look at me.
What did they do to me?
To the king's own mother?
It's all right.
It's done.
It's in the past.
And of course,
Margaery's safety
is paramount.
You don't like
Margaery, do you?
Whether I like her or not
is completely unimportant.
Margaery is the queen.
Queens must command respect.
Kings even more so.
Not just for
their own sake,
but for everyone's.
The High Sparrow
has no respect
for kings or queens.
No respect for anything
in this world.
He has no use for the
things of this world.
He wants to knock them down,
and replace them with what?
With fantasies.
With beggars
in the street.
With nothing.
Mother.
There's something
I want to tell you.
Something the High
Sparrow told me.
You've spoken with him?
I promised him
I wouldn't tell anyone.
If he found out...
It would be a breach
of confidence which
he would not take lightly,
given his constant
prattling about the truth.
I am your mother.
You can always trust me.
(DOOR OPENS)
The Small Council meeting
has been postponed
on the king's orders.
I would have thought
we were perfectly
clear the first time.
You're not welcome.
You once spoke of your
respect for our father
because he understood
the necessity of working
with one's rivals.
My dear, you have
been stripped of your
dignity and authority,
publically shamed
and confined
to the Red Keep.
(CHUCKLES) What's
left to work with?
JAIME: Cersei is
the mother of the king.
She has the king's ear
and his trust.
And the king has
been speaking regularly
with the High Sparrow
about Queen Margaery
and Ser Loras.
The High Sparrow seized
power knowing full well
we'd bicker amongst
ourselves instead
of seizing it back.
Here we are.
Well done to us.
Now the future of the
Seven Kingdoms rests
in his dirty peasant hands.
In a few days,
he'll have
a trial for me.
But before that,
Queen Margaery will make
her walk of atonement.
Yes, Margaery will repent
her sins before the good
people of the city.
Oh, no.
That cannot happen.
That will not happen.
I agree.
You've got
the second largest
army in Westeros.
You'll bring them
into the city,
stop Queen Margaery's
humiliation before it starts,
and take her back
into Crown custody.
The king has ordered me
to take no action
against the High Sparrow
or the Faith Militant
out of fear for
the queen's safety.
You will take
no action at all.
When the Tyrell armies come,
you will stand down.
Were you expressly
forbidden from
standing down?
No, but if the king
should call...
The whole thing will be over
before anyone can call
on you to do anything.
When the High Sparrow
is in custody,
or dead, preferably,
and Margaery's back
at Tommen's side,
do you think
the king will be angry
at the outcome?
You hate these
fanatics as much
as we do.
You hate what
they've done
to your son.
Do you want Lancel back?
Or have you given
him up for good?
Of course I want him back.
Then stand aside
and let the people
that took him from
you be destroyed.
If it doesn't go as planned,
the Sparrows have many
friends in this city.
We'll have civil war.
Many will die.
Many will die
no matter what we do.
Better them than us.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(FIRE CRACKLING)
YARA: They told me
you were home, and
I didn't believe it.
"Theon Greyjoy?" I said.
"He's dead.
"He's been dead
a long time."
He let you go?
I escaped.
I can't hear you.
Look at me.
Men died trying
to rescue you.
Good men.
My men.
I'm sorry.
You were my brother.
You were a spoiled
little cunt, but you
were my brother,
and I risked
everything for you.
And you betrayed me.
I know. (SNIFFLES)
I know,
and I'm sorry.
Stop saying that.
He broke me.
He broke me
into 1,000 pieces.
I know.
You don't know.
He sent us one
of those pieces.
That's why
I came for you.
(SOBBING)
Why did you
come here?
Where else
could I go?
You heard father was
dead and you thought
you'd claim the crown?
No. No, I only heard
he died after we docked.
You happen to show up
on Pyke right before
the Kingsmoot?
I didn't know.
You think any ironborn
wants you to be king?
After what you've done?
I don't want
to be king.
What do you want?
I should have
listened to you.
You're the only...
That doesn't matter
anymore. Stop crying.
Look at me!
Tell me
what you want.
You should rule
the Iron Islands.
Let me help you.
They've cleaned
you up nicely.
You know who I am?
A lord.
Yes.
You've seen
my banners?
The flayed man.
Does that worry
you at all?
You eat them after?
(CHUCKLES)
No.
(SCOFFS)
Then I've seen worse.
You served the Starks?
Aye.
They put me in chains
and put a sword
at my throat,
so I served them.
The Starks have been
gone for a long time,
but you kept
protecting Rickon.
He'd fetch a good price
to the right buyer.
I served his family
a long time.
Didn't get no wages.
Way I see it,
I'm owed.
Be that as it may,
Rickon's not yours
to sell anymore.
He's mine.
So, what use could
I possibly have for you?
(SCOFFS)
I can give you
what you want.
And you're sure you
know what that is?
Same thing men
always want.
And when they
really want it,
they give it
a bath first.
(MOANS)
You're
a good talker.
I like that.
(CHUCKLES)
You're a much
better talker than
Theon Greyjoy.
That so?
I had to work hard
to get him talking.
But he talked.
They all do.
He told me everything.
All about the Stark boys,
who helped them escape
and how she did it.
(GAGGING)
(CLATTERING)
(GRUNTING)
(SIGHS)
MAN: Open the gate!
Sorry about the food.
It's not what
we're known for.
That's all right.
There are more
important things.
(DOOR OPENS)
A letter for you,
Lord Commander.
I'm not Lord
Commander anymore.
(DOOR OPENS)
(WIND WHOOSHING)
"To the traitor and
bastard, Jon Snow.
"You allowed thousands
of wildlings past the Wall.
"You have betrayed
your own kind. You have
betrayed the North.
"Winterfell is mine, bastard.
"Come and see.
"Your brother Rickon
is in my dungeon.
"His direwolf's skin
is on my floor.
Come and see.
"I want my bride back.
"Send her to me, bastard,
and I will not trouble you
or your wildling lovers.
"Keep her from me,
and I will ride north
"and slaughter every
wildling man, woman and babe
living under your protection.
"You will watch as
I skin them living.
You..."
Go on.
It's just more
of the same.
"You will watch as
my soldiers take turns
raping your sister.
"You will watch as
my dogs devour your
wild little brother.
"Then I will spoon your
eyes from their sockets
"and let my dogs do the rest.
"Come and see.
"Ramsay Bolton,
Lord of Winterfell and
Warden of the North."
Lord of Winterfell
and Warden of the North.
His father's dead.
Ramsay killed him.
And now he has Rickon.
We don't know that.
Yes, we do.
How many men does
he have in his army?
I heard him say 5,000
once when he was talking
about Stannis' attack.
How many do you have?
That can march
and fight?
Two thousand.
The rest are children
and old people.
You're the son
of the last true
Warden of the North.
Northern families
are loyal. They'll fight
for you if you ask.
A monster has taken
our home and our brother.
We have to go
back to Winterfell
and save them both.
(SPEAKS DOTHRAKI)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(ALL LAUGHING)
(SHOUTING)
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTING)
(DOTHRAKI SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING)