GREY WORM: (READING)
"My name
"is Grey Worm.
"I come from
"the Summer Ills."
MISSANDEI: "Isles."
"Summer Isles."
GREY WORM: "Summer Isles."
(BOTH SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
I am from
an island called Naath.
(GREY WORM SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
When they took you?
When did they take me?
I was five years old.
You remember your home?
I remember
when they rowed us
away from shore.
How white the beaches were.
How tall the trees.
And I remember
my village burning.
Smoke rising into the sky.
Do you remember your home?
Unsullied.
Always Unsullied.
Before Unsullied, nothing.
That's not true.
Perhaps one day
you will return to
the Summer Isles.
I don't want return.
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
"Kill the masters."
Kill the masters.
DAENERYS: How are
the lessons coming?
MISSANDEI:
Very well, Your Grace.
Missandei is
teacher good,
my queen.
You'll have to
continue later.
It's time.
(GRUNTING)
(SLAVES MURMURING)
(WEAPONS CLATTERING)
(ALL SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(GASPS)
(SLAVES CHANTING IN VALYRIAN)
(SCREAMING)
SLAVES: (CHANTING) Mhysa!
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
DAENERYS:
Remind me, Ser Jorah,
how many children
did the Great Masters
nail to mileposts?
163, Khaleesi.
That was it.
(SHOUTS IN VALYRIAN)
BARRISTAN: Your Grace,
may I have a word?
The city is yours.
All these people,
they're your subjects now.
Sometimes it is
better to answer
injustice with mercy.
I will answer injustice
with justice.
(MASTER GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
(MASTERS SCREAMING)
(SCREAMS ECHOING)
(SWORDS CLANKING)
(PANTING)
(GROANING)
What the hell was that?
That was me knocking
your arse to the dirt
with your own hand.
You're a rare talent.
When you're fighting
cripples, anyway.
You learned to fight
like a good little boy.
I'll bet that thrust
through the Mad King's back
was pretty as a picture.
You want to
fight pretty or
you want to win?
You talk to my
brother this way?
All the time.
He got used to it.
JAIME: Do you think
he did it?
No.
Oh, he hated
the little twat, sure.
But who didn't?
And poison's not his style.
Or murder.
You want to know for sure,
why don't you ask him?
You haven't been
to see him yet, eh?
We're done for today.
Your brother ever tell you
how I came into his service?
You stood for him in
his trial by combat
at the Eyrie.
Aye.
But only when Lady Arryn
demanded the trial
take place that day.
You were his first choice.
He named you
for his champion
because he knew you would
ride day and night to
come fight for him.
You gonna fight for him now?
JAIME: To tell you the truth,
this isn't so bad.
Four walls.
A pot to piss in.
I was chained to a wooden
post covered in my own
shit for months.
Is that supposed to
make me feel better?
Maybe a bit.
I'm sorry
I didn't come sooner.
It's complicated.
So how is our sister?
How do you think?
Her son died in her arms.
Her son?
Don't.
You know what's coming?
Hmm.
My trial for regicide.
I know
the whole bloody country
thinks I'm guilty,
that one of
my three judges
has wished me dead
more times than I can count.
And that judge is my father.
As for Cersei,
well, she's probably
working on a way
to avoid a trial altogether
by having me killed.
She did ask.
So, should I turn around
and close my eyes?
Depends.
Did you do it?
The Kingslayer brothers.
You like it?
I like it.
You're really asking
if I killed your son?
Are you really asking
if I'd kill my brother?
How can I help you?
You could set me free.
You know I can't.
Then there's really
nothing else to say.
What do you want me to do?
Kill the guards?
Sneak you out of the city
in the back of a cart?
I'm the Lord Commander
of the Kingsguard.
Sorry, I'd forgotten.
I'd hate for you to do
something inappropriate.
Inappropriate?
You're accused of
killing the King.
Freeing you is treason.
Except I didn't do it.
Which is why
we're having a trial.
Oh!
A trial.
If the killer threw himself
before the Iron Throne,
confessed to his crimes,
and gave irrefutable
evidence of his guilt,
it wouldn't matter
to Cersei.
She won't rest until
my head's on a spike.
Not just yours.
She's offering
a knighthood to whomever
finds Sansa Stark.
Sansa couldn't
have done this.
She had more
reason than anyone
in the Seven Kingdoms.
Do you think
it's a coincidence
she disappeared
the same night Joffrey died?
No, but
Sansa's not a killer.
Not yet, anyway.
(WOOD CREAKING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Where are you taking me?
I'm getting married
to your Aunt Lysa.
She's waiting for us
at the Eyrie.
You'll be safe there.
Did you kill Joffrey?
Did I kill Joffrey?
I've been in
the Vale for weeks.
I know it was you.
And who helped me
with this conspiracy?
There was Ser Dontos.
You used him to get me
out of King's Landing,
but you would never
trust him to kill the King.
Why not?
Because you're too
smart to trust a drunk.
Then perhaps
it was your husband.
No.
How do you know?
I just do.
You're right.
He wasn't involved
in Joffrey's death.
But you were.
Do you remember
that lovely necklace
Dontos gave you?
I don't suppose you noticed
that a stone was
missing after the feast.
The poison.
I don't understand.
The Lannisters gave
you wealth, power.
Joffrey made you
the Lord of Harrenhal.
A man with no motive
is a man no one suspects.
Always keep
your foes confused.
If they don't know who
you are or what you want,
they can't know what
you plan to do next.
I don't believe you.
If they catch you,
they'll put your head
on a spike just
like my father's.
You'd risk that
just to confuse them?
So many men,
they risk so little.
They spend their
lives avoiding danger.
And then they die.
I'd risk everything
to get what I want.
And what do you want?
Everything.
My friendship
with the Lannisters
was productive.
But Joffrey,
a vicious boy with
a crown on his head,
is not a reliable ally.
And who could trust
a friend like that?
Who could trust you?
I don't want friends like me.
My new friends
are predictable.
Very reasonable people.
As for what
happened to Joffrey,
that was something
my new friends
wanted very badly.
Nothing like
a thoughtful gift
to make a new friendship
grow strong.
MARGAERY: I can't believe
you're going.
Leaving me alone here
with these people.
OLENNA: The time
has come, my dear.
There's nothing more
tedious than a trial.
Except perhaps
these gardens.
If I have to take one
more leisurely stroll
through these gardens,
I'll fling myself
from the cliffs.
(MARGAERY LAUGHS)
OLENNA: Have you
been to see Tommen yet?
No.
Have they even
agreed to the match?
No one tells me anything.
I wasn't originally
meant to marry your
grandfather Luthor.
He was engaged to my sister,
your great-aunt Viola.
I was to be given to
some Targaryen or other.
Marrying a Targaryen
was all the rage back then.
But the moment
I saw my intended,
with his twitchy
little ferret's face
and ludicrous silver hair,
I knew he wouldn't do.
So the evening
before Luthor was to
propose to my sister,
I got lost on my way back
from my embroidery lesson
and happened
upon his chamber.
(LAUGHS)
How absentminded of me.
Mmm-hmm.
The following morning,
Luthor never made
it down the stairs
to propose to my sister
'cause the boy
couldn't bloody walk.
And once he could,
the only thing he wanted
was what I'd given him
the night before.
I was good.
I was very good.
You are even better.
But you need
to act quickly.
Cersei may be vicious,
but she's not stupid.
She'll turn
the boy against you
as soon as she can.
And by the time
you're married,
it'll be too late.
Luckily for you,
the Queen Regent
is rather distracted
at the moment.
Mourning her
dear departed boy.
Accusing her
brother of his murder,
which he didn't commit.
He could have done.
But he didn't.
You don't know, Grandmother.
But I do know.
You don't think
I'd let you marry
that beast, do you?
What? I don't understand.
Shh.
Don't you worry yourself
about all that.
You just do what
needs to be done.
JON: Bring it through!
(SWORDS CLANGING)
And again.
(LAUGHS)
Very nice. Good.
A lot of wildlings fight
with a weapon in each hand.
First thing you want to do
is disarm them to
try and even the odds.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Let's see what you can do.
Olly, you just
watch for now.
I can fight.
Have you ever
held a sword before?
I was the best archer
in our hamlet.
(MEN LAUGHING)
I was!
I believe you.
We'll go hunting
for rabbits one day.
Right now, watch and learn.
You two.
Take it slow,
try and disarm each other.
(SHOUTS)
(GROANS)
You know how to fight.
You could have
gone easier on him.
He wouldn't have
learned anything that way.
ALLISER: Lord Snow.
What do you think
you're doing?
Grenn and I
were helping them.
Grenn's a ranger.
You're a steward.
Maybe you forgot that
while you were off
with your wildling bitch,
but I didn't.
Someone has to train them.
And that someone isn't you.
Go find
a chamber pot
to empty.
Go on. Do it.
You traitor's bastard.
Give me an excuse.
Mormont's not here
to protect you now.
Get back to work.
Now!
I said now!
The bastard's well-liked.
You're not.
You think I care
if they like me?
We're at war.
For now.
But you can't be
acting commander forever.
There will be a choosing.
The old maester
will insist on it.
You might
reconsider his request
to march on Craster's.
Let the mutineers
take care of Snow.
Or you might be
taking orders from him
the rest of your life.
A bastard, eh?
Took you for highborn.
My father was highborn.
My mother wasn't.
Name's Locke.
Jon Snow.
You fight well.
What brought you up here?
A sense of duty.
I wanted to do my part
for the safety of the realm.
(LAUGHING)
I was a game warden
in the Stormlands.
Fed a prized partridge
to my hungry kids.
I was stupid enough
to get caught.
Chose the Wall
over losing my hand.
Figured I wouldn't
have to suck up to
any highborn cunts here.
ALLISER: Come on,
get on with it.
What are you
waiting for? Summer?
Guess I was wrong.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
You sent for me,
Your Grace?
Your Grace.
How formal of you.
How many Kingsguards
are posted outside
Tommen's door?
Ser Boros is on duty tonight.
Tomorrow I believe...
So one?
You have one man
guarding the future king?
I promise you
Tommen's safe.
We're protecting him.
The way you
protected Joffrey?
Why did Catelyn Stark
set you free?
What?
I've been
wondering for months.
Ever since that great cow
brought you back
to the capital.
Why did she set you free?
You know why. She'd hoped
I'd send her daughters
back to her.
She hoped
or did you promise?
I swore by all the gods
that if her
daughters were alive,
I'd return them to her.
So you made a sacred vow
to the enemy.
I wanted to
get back to you.
Should I have
told her to fuck off?
You didn't mean it, then?
You have no loyalty
to Catelyn Stark?
Catelyn Stark's dead.
So if I told you to
leave the capital right now
and find Sansa,
if I told you to find
that murderous little bitch
and bring me her head,
would you do it?
I know you went
to see Tyrion.
That creature who
murdered our son.
I had to see him.
I had to know for myself.
And?
He didn't do it, Cersei.
You've always pitied him.
Our poor little brother.
Abused by the world,
despised by his
father and sister.
He'd kill us all if he could.
I want four men
at Tommen's door
day and night.
That will be all,
Lord Commander.
(DOOR OPENS)
(SIGHS)
Ser Pounce?
(DOOR CREAKS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
TOMMEN: How did you get
past the Kingsguard?
Kingsguard.
I don't think you're
supposed to be here.
Mother doesn't allow
me to have visitors
at night.
I'm not a visitor,
Your Grace.
Word has it
I'm to be your bride.
Did you know that people
in arranged marriages
often never meet
until their wedding day?
Before we decide to
spend our lives together,
we ought to get to
know one another.
Don't you think?
Yes.
But if my mother found out...
It can be our secret.
Hmm?
If we're going to
be man and wife,
we'll have a few
secrets from her, I hope.
So, Your Grace...
Yes?
Tell me a secret.
(SER POUNCE MEOWS)
(MARGAERY LAUGHS)
Hello. Aren't you
a proper fellow?
That's Ser Pounce.
Very handsome.
Joffrey didn't like him.
He threatened
to skin him alive
and mix his innards
up in my food
so I wouldn't know
I was eating him.
That's very cruel.
You don't strike me as cruel.
No.
I don't think I am.
That's a relief.
Because you know
what happens when we marry?
We say our vows in
front of the High Septon.
And after the ceremony,
there's a feast.
When we marry,
I become yours.
Forever.
It's getting late.
(SIGHS)
I should go.
May I come and
visit you again?
(MARGAERY CHUCKLES)
All right, then.
Remember,
our little secret.
(DOOR CLOSES)
BRIENNE:
"Ser Jaime Lannister.
"Knighted and
named to the Kingsguard
in his 16th year.
"At the sack of
King's Landing,
murdered his king, Aerys II.
"Pardoned by
Robert Baratheon.
"Thereafter known
as the Kingslayer."
It's the duty of
the Lord Commander
to fill those pages.
And there's still
room left on mine.
Valyrian steel.
Mmm.
It's yours.
I can't accept this.
It was reforged
from Ned Stark's sword.
You'll use it to
defend Ned Stark's daughter.
You swore an oath
to return the Stark girls
to their mother.
Lady Stark's dead.
Arya's probably dead, too,
but there's still
a chance to find Sansa
and get her somewhere safe.
I've got
something else for you.
I hope I got your
measurements right.
I'll find her.
For Lady Catelyn.
And for you.
I almost forgot.
I have one more gift.
BRIENNE: I don't
need a squire.
Of course you do.
He'll slow me down.
My brother
owes him a debt.
He's not safe here.
You'll be keeping him
from harm. It's chivalry.
I won't slow you down, ser.
My lady.
I promise
I'll serve you well.
See? He's a good lad.
You'll get along.
Compliments
of Lord Tyrion.
His ax from the Blackwater.
What are you
waiting for, a kiss?
Ready the lady's horse.
They say the best
swords have names.
Any ideas?
Oathkeeper.
Goodbye, Brienne.
PODRICK: Come on, move.
I should never
have taken her away.
JON: She wasn't safe here.
She's not safe out there.
I should have known.
You told us
there were wildlings
south of the Wall.
If they're raiding
the smaller villages,
Mole's Town could be next.
Castle Black could be next.
I should go back for Gilly.
We have orders.
No one's to
leave the castle.
I remember when
you disobeyed orders
and rode south to help Robb.
And I remember
who came after me
and brought me home.
I know how hard it is,
Sam, believe me.
When you told me about
Bran going beyond the Wall,
all I could think about was
getting my strength back
so I could go and find him.
I wish I could
have convinced him
to come back with me.
I tried. Really, I did.
How fast could they travel?
A crippled boy
being pulled on a sledge
by a simpleton?
I don't know.
They'd pass
wildling villages.
They could try and find
shelter at one of them.
The wildlings have
joined up with Mance.
Every village or
sheltered place
will be deserted.
Except...
SAM: Craster's?
You think Bran
might have found...
LOCKE: Snow.
I don't mean
to interrupt.
Thorne wants to see you.
Your foray to Craster's Keep,
I'll sanction it.
But I won't order
anyone to go with you.
Volunteers only.
Thank you,
Ser Alliser.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Brothers.
(CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE)
I'm going beyond
the Wall to Craster's Keep
to capture the mutineers
holed up there
or kill them.
I'm asking for
volunteers to come with me.
There's 60 miles of wilderness
between here and Craster's,
and Mance Rayder has an army
bearing down on us,
but we have to do this.
Our survival may depend
on us getting to
these mutineers
before Mance does.
They know the Wall.
They know our defenses.
If Mance learns what
they know, we're lost.
But if that's not enough,
then consider this.
If the Night's Watch
are truly brothers,
then Lord Commander Mormont
was our father.
He lived and died
for the Watch
and he was betrayed
by his own men.
Stabbed in the back
by cowards.
He deserved far better.
All we can give
him now is justice.
Who will join me?
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
I can't let a recruit
come north of the Wall.
Then let me
say my vows.
If it's a fight
you're heading for,
then you need
men who know how.
Thank you, brothers.
(WOMEN WHIMPERING)
WOMAN: No, don't.
Don't, please.
WOMAN 2: Please don't.
Ow! You're hurting me.
Karl Tanner from Gin Alley
drinking wine
from the skull of
Jeor fucking Mormont.
Any command for us,
Lord Commander?
What's that?
Fuck 'em till they're dead?
(GROANS)
Did you hear that, boys?
Fuck 'em till they're dead.
Rast.
Go outside and
feed the beast.
We should kill that thing.
You should shut
your fucking hole,
ugly little cunt.
You look like
a fucking ballsack. Ugly.
Look at
your stupid cunt face.
I could piss
in any gutter and
soak five of you.
Know how much they
paid me to kill a man
in King's Landing?
Seven silvers.
They told me a man's name
and that man never
saw daylight again.
None of them cocksuckers
got away from me.
Haven't lost a fight
since I was nine.
Maybe it's time.
What do you think? Eh?
Maybe you're the man.
Eh, cunt?
I wouldn't stand a chance.
None of us would.
I was a fucking
legend in Gin Alley.
A fucking legend!
I would take any knight,
any time.
You fucking cunts
in steel plate.
Fucking cowards.
(BABY COOING)
WOMEN: A gift for the gods.
A gift for the gods.
What the fuck is that?
Craster's last child.
A boy.
What am I supposed
to do with him?
What did Craster do?
Kill 'em before
they could grow up
and do the same to him?
All right.
Don't need
another mouth to feed.
Hand him over.
He didn't kill them.
He offered them.
To who?
To the gods.
The White Walkers.
WOMEN: (CHANTING)
A gift for the gods.
Shut up!
So,
if it worked for him...
(CRYING)
...let's give the Walkers
what they want.
(BABY CONTINUES CRYING)
Rast is headed that way.
(BABY FUSSING)
(CRYING)
(LIGHT GROWLS)
(GROWLING)
Pink-eyed fuck.
You thirsty?
(GROWLS)
Fuck! (GROANS)
(CROWS CAWING)
(WIND HOWLING)
(ICE CRACKLING)
(BARKS)
(BABY CRYING IN DISTANCE)
Hodor.
Do you hear that?
Is that a baby?
It's coming.
I'm going out there.
No, we need to
stay together.
I'm going.
(BABY CRYING)
(GHOST HOWLING)
(SUMMER GROWLS)
(GASPS)
MEERA: Bran.
HODOR: Hodor.
Bran, what happened?
It's Summer. He's hurt.
They've caught him
in a trap.
Who?
I didn't see, but they
have my brother's wolf.
They have Ghost.
BRAN: They're Night's Watch.
Look.
Jon might be here.
If Jon was here,
why would they put
his wolf in a cage?
(WOMAN WHIMPERING)
(GASPS)
(MEN SHOUTING)
They might have been
Night's Watch once,
not anymore.
We're not safe here.
We need to go.
BRAN: No.
Bran, we need to go now.
I'm not leaving
without Summer.
Can you remember
where the cage was?
The east side of the keep.
If I'm not back soon,
we'll meet...
(GROANS)
Hodor.
(ALL SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(GROANS)
Hodor.
If I was your size,
I'd be king of
the fucking world.
(MEN LAUGHING)
Help him up.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
This is nice.
Fine leather.
You're no wildling.
Important. Highborn.
Who are you?
(GRUNTS)
You see, where I come from,
a commoner like me
slaps a little lord
like you,
I'd lose me right hand.
But we're a long way
from home, aren't we?
And then the two of you,
fancy-looking folks
north of the Wall creeping
through the woods.
Isn't that a bit odd?
I like your curly hair.
My mom had
curls like that.
Beautiful brown curls.
Why'd you drag
a crippled boy
all the way up here?
Hmm?
See, you haven't
played this game before.
A highborn hostage,
that's valuable.
But three of them,
that's a lot of
mouths to feed.
RAST: What the fuck's
wrong with him?
Come here.
(SCREAMS) No, please.
Please, let me help him.
KARL: Who are you?
Please.
Who are you?
I'm Brandon Stark
of Winterfell.
(JOJEN GAGGING)
It's Jon Snow's brother.
It's Meera.
I'm right here.
And I thought
this was gonna be
another boring day.
MEERA: I'm right here.
(WIND HOWLING)
(ICE CRACKLING)
(BABY COOING)
(BABY CRYING)
(COOING)
(CRACKLING)