(CLANGING)
(PEOPLE TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
(LAUGHS)
Here we are.
(LAUGHTER)
(LOUD CONVERSATIONS)
Ready?
(BELCHING)
The Rains of Castamere.
You fucking deaf?
(MAN LAUGHS)
Same wrong guess
every fucking time.
Listen, you cunt.
ALL: Oh!
(BELCHING)
The Bear and the Maiden Fair.
(ALL CHEERING)
Yes!
There's a man
with an ear.
Too bad you got
a hangnail for a cock.
(LAUGHING)
First time I saw you
with your breeches down,
I thought you were a eunuch.
(ALL LAUGHING)
You've seen it, girls.
Like a baby snail
peeking out of its shell.
(LAUGHS)
Your baby was
crying this morning.
Woke me up.
You hear me?
Yes.
Well, got anything to say?
I'm sorry.
(CHUCKLES) I don't
care if you're sorry.
Keep that baby quiet,
or I will.
Don't you ever touch him.
(CHUCKLES)
Little wildling bitch.
You should have stayed
with your own kind.
(HOOTING)
Are you listening
to me?
Shut your mouth.
What?
(HOOTING CONTINUES)
It's just an owl,
you dumb bitch.
No, it's not.
(HOOTING)
(BLADE SWISHING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
(YELLING)
(GRUNTS)
(COUGHS)
(CLATTERING)
(BABY FUSSING)
(BABY FUSSES)
Shh.
(SCREAMING CONTINUES
DISTANTLY)
I should never
have left her there.
You couldn't
have known.
Of course
I could've.
They've been raiding
the villages close by.
And we just cower in here
while they slaughter
our brothers.
Our brothers had orders
to stay at Castle Black.
So it's all right, then?
Black Jack and Kegs
and Mully chopped to pieces
'cause they broke the rules?
I didn't say it was all right.
I'm saying they shouldn't
have been there.
We're pledged to guard
the realms of men.
She's dead because of me.
We can't even guard
Mole's Town.
We can't go after them.
You know that.
It's what they want.
SAMWELL: And little Sam.
As if I cut
their throats myself.
Maybe she managed
to hide herself.
I thought all of you was dead.
You went up north with Mormont
and no one came back.
Not for ages.
But then you did.
She survived Craster,
and he was the worst shit
I've ever met.
She survived
the long march to the Wall.
She survived a White Walker,
for fuck's sake.
She might have got out.
She might have.
If they hit Mole's Town,
then we're next.
Mance and his army
must be close.
GRENN: 100,000 of them.
And there's what,
105 of us left?
You counting Black Jack,
Kegs, and Mully?
102.
How do 102 men stop 100,000?
Whoever dies last,
be a good lad
and burn the rest of us.
Once I'm done with this world,
I don't want to come back.
DAENERYS: You think
he was spying on you?
MISSANDEI: No, not spying.
DAENERYS: The Dothraki
think outsiders are ridiculous
taking shame
in the naked body.
They make love under the stars
for the whole khalasar to see.
Yes, Your Grace.
But you are not Dothraki.
No.
Well, I don't see
why it matters.
Grey Worm isn't interested.
None of the Unsullied care
what's under our clothes.
He was interested.
What?
I believe he was interested.
When the slavers
castrate the boys,
do they take all of it?
All of it?
(STAMMERS)
The pillar and the stones.
I don't know, Your Grace.
Haven't you ever wondered?
Yes, Your Grace.
GREY WORM: Missandei.
(BOTH SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
The lessons you give I
in Common Tongue,
these are precious to I.
"To me."
To me.
I don't remember
teaching you
the word "precious."
Jorah the Andal,
he teaches I...
He teaches me this word.
Do you remember the name
you were given at birth?
I remember nothing.
Only Unsullied.
When they cut you,
do you remember that?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry
they did that to you.
Why?
Why sorry?
It's a terrible thing
to do to a boy.
If the Masters never cut me,
I never am Unsullied.
I never stand in
the Plaza of Pride
when Daenerys Stormborn
orders us to kill the Masters.
I never am chosen
to lead the Unsullied.
I never meet Missandei
from the island of Naath.
I am sorry I...
For today,
I am sorry.
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
(HORSES WHINNYING)
RAMSAY: Kraken.
Mmm. Strong, as long
as they're in the sea.
When you take them
out of the water,
no bones.
They collapse under
their proud weight
and slump into
a heap of nothing.
You'd think they'd know that.
Unfortunately,
they're not very bright.
What do you tell them?
I'm Theon Greyjoy,
son of Balon,
heir to the Iron Islands.
And what are you really?
I'm Reek.
Are you sure?
You do look
very much like a lord.
Formidable, proud.
I'm Reek.
Until when?
Always.
Forever.
That's right.
Until you're
rotting in the ground.
Remember what you are
and what you're not.
Bring me Moat Cailin.
(CAWING)
No closer.
Who are you?
(GRUNTS)
(MEN COUGHING)
(FLIES BUZZING)
I'm Kenning,
commander of this garrison.
And you say
you're Theon Greyjoy?
Yes.
And why should I
believe that?
I was born on Pyke
to Balon Greyjoy.
His third and last living son.
I am your prince.
I swear it by the Drowned God.
What is dead may never die.
MEN: What is dead
may never die.
And if you were my prince,
why are you marching
with a Bolton army?
Lord Bolton took me
captive after Winterfell.
He sent me to treat
with you in good faith
as your fellow ironborn.
And what does
Lord Bolton want?
You are fading from sickness,
you are badly outnumbered,
and you're hundreds
of miles from the sea.
Lord Bolton implores you
to protect your men
and abandon this fortress
you can no longer hold.
Do this, and he will be
just and fair with you
as he has been with me.
The Boltons will give you
safe passage
to the Stony Shore.
He wants us to surrender?
My own father, your king,
surrendered years ago
to Robert Baratheon.
I watched him bend the knee.
There was no shame there.
He fought with honor,
as did you.
(GROANS)
(MUTTERING) "No shame."
"Fought with honor."
I'm sorry, I didn't hear.
(SPITS)
"No shame."
"Fought with honor."
Only a whipped dog
would speak this way.
Or a woman.
(WHIMPERING)
Are you a woman, boy?
You don't know...
The ironborn
will not surrender.
(MUMBLING) My name is Reek...
You go tell your
master that, Theon Greyjoy,
or whoever the fuck you are.
(QUIETLY) Reek.
What in the hell
are you muttering?
Reek.
If we yield, we live?
Is that what it says
on this paper here?
Yes.
Have your men
raise the white flag
and open the gates.
You're going home.
RAMSAY:
You didn't really think
I'd let them go, did you?
It's fallen out of fashion,
flaying.
Sad, but true.
Traditions are important.
Where are we
without our history? Eh?
Yes, my lord.
Will we go home now?
I believe we will.
To our new home.
ROYCE: You have foreign blood,
don't you, Baelish?
A great-grandfather
from Braavos, yes.
I suppose all of our ancestors
came from somewhere else
originally.
ROYCE: Our forebears
settled the Vale
thousands of years ago.
We've fought off
invaders ever since.
The beauty of
the Vale is matched
only by the nobility
of its great families.
Lady Arryn often told me that
you were her rock, Lord Royce.
She told me nothing
about you, Baelish.
But I didn't need
to hear from her.
Moneylender. Whoremonger.
You've been licking
Tywin Lannister's boots
so long,
it's a wonder your
tongue's not black.
My lord...
And when Jon Arryn named you
Master of Coin, no one cared.
Always been a grubby job.
Why not let
a grubby man do it?
But when I heard
you were lurking here,
fawning over the Lady Arryn...
Lady Arryn invited me.
She and I have been
close since childhood.
Yes, we all know
how close you were.
Lady Arryn's predilections
were her own affair.
Her death is our affair.
Of course.
Her suicide shattered us all.
She was an odd fish.
Everyone knew that.
But suicide?
She adored that boy of hers.
I don't see her
abandoning him.
Not by choice.
ROYCE:
Strange that within days
of your arrival,
you've married Lady Arryn
and she's fallen
through the Moon Door.
She was always
prone to melancholy.
My lady wasn't
meant for a world
as brutal as ours.
We were told there
was a witness. A girl.
A niece of yours,
I believe.
A girl with no learning
and scattered wits.
I assure you,
she would be of no help.
We'd like to speak with her.
Let me fetch her.
ANYA: No need.
We prefer to hear
her testimony unadulterated.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Come closer, child.
You have nothing to fear
from us or him.
Lord Baelish here
is your uncle?
Your name is Alayne?
Perhaps you would
feel more comfortable
if Lord Baelish left the room.
My lady...
I wasn't asking you.
He can stay.
Speak up, girl, you're not
a damn kitchen mouse.
Tell us what you saw.
I'm sorry, Lord Baelish.
I have to tell the truth.
I'll tell you everything.
Please, Alayne,
leave nothing out.
My name is not Alayne.
It's Sansa Stark,
eldest daughter of
Lord Eddard Stark.
Lord Royce,
we met when you
came to Winterfell.
You were escorting
your son Ser Waymar
to the Wall.
Sansa Stark?
You tell lies right
to my face, you little worm?
Lord Baelish has told
many lies.
All to protect me.
Since my father was executed,
I have been
a hostage in King's Landing.
A plaything for
Joffrey to torture
or Queen Cersei to torment.
They beat me,
they humiliated me,
they married me to the Imp.
I had no friends
in King's Landing,
except one.
He saved me.
Smuggled me away
when he had the chance.
He knew I'd be
safe here in the Eyrie
with my own blood,
my Aunt Lysa.
But the Lannisters
have friends everywhere.
Even the Vale.
He made me swear
not to tell
anyone my true name.
Your secret is
safe with us, my lady.
ROYCE: Your father grew up
right here in these halls.
We hunted together many times.
He was a fine man.
Tell us what happened
to your aunt, Sansa.
You knew her well,
my lords, my lady.
She was a troubled woman.
She always loved Lord Baelish.
She told me herself.
From the moment he arrived
at the gates of Riverrun,
a boy of eight
carrying everything he owned
in a little sack.
She confessed to me
she never loved Lord Arryn.
She did
as her father commanded,
as so many of us have.
When the gods
finally allowed her
to be with Lord Baelish,
she was so happy. For a time.
My aunt was a jealous lady.
She was terrified
that Lord Baelish
didn't love her anymore.
That he would abandon her
for a younger woman.
And then,
one day she saw him kiss me.
Lady Sansa.
It was a peck on the cheek,
Lord Royce, nothing more.
Lord Baelish is
my uncle now, by marriage.
He's always
been so kind to me.
I was so happy to
be here, to be free.
All because of him.
But my aunt turned on me.
She cursed me.
Called me a whore.
Promised to throw me
through the Moon Door.
When Lord Baelish
tried to calm her,
she struck him.
She said she didn't
want to live anymore.
She stood on the edge
of that Moon Door.
He tried to reason with her,
promised her
she was the only one
he had ever loved,
but she stepped
through those doors
and she was...
(SHUSHING)
It's not your fault,
sweet girl.
It's not your fault.
ROYCE:
You could see it in the way
she raised that boy.
Feeding him from her own teats
when he was 10 years old.
Lord Royce!
This is hardly the time.
Apologies, my lady.
And to you as well, Baelish.
We treated you a bit harshly.
You want justice, Lord Royce.
I can hardly complain
about that.
I want the same.
ANYA: Not much justice to be
meted out in suicide,
is there?
For Lysa, no.
But for her son?
Only 20 years ago,
the knights of the Vale
rode behind Jon Arryn,
Ned Stark, Robert Baratheon.
They fought together
to overcome the Mad King.
And since then,
Arryn and Royce,
Corbray, Waynwood,
all the great houses
of the Vale watched
from the corner.
A timid boy
at a tavern brawl.
Are you questioning
our courage?
I want to know
which side you're on.
Do you support the Lannisters,
the house that executed
your friend Ned Stark?
Of course we don't support
the damn Lannisters.
No? Catelyn Stark
begged her sister
for support, and Lysa refused.
By staying out of the fray,
you've allowed Tywin Lannister
to destroy his rivals
on every compass point.
Who stands against him now?
Who would you have us back,
Lord Baelish?
Robb Stark is dead.
I'd have you back Robin Arryn,
Lord of the Vale.
Robin Arryn is
a sickly little boy.
And sickly little boys
sometimes become powerful men.
More often they die young.
I adored Lysa
with all my heart,
but she loved her son so much
she became overprotective.
He needs to learn
how to swing a sword,
how to ride a horse.
Aye, it's time.
Yes.
Time for him to tour the Vale,
to visit all the castles
in his domain.
Time for Robin
to leave the nest.
(GRUNTING)
BOY: Ser Barristan.
Yes?
Who sent you?
Ser Barristan.
Ser Jorah.
Have I forgotten
a council meeting?
No.
What's this?
A royal pardon signed
by Robert Baratheon.
You spied on her.
Who gave you this?
Does it matter?
Have you told her?
I wanted to tell
you first, man-to-man,
rather than go
behind your back.
Let me speak
with her in private.
You'll never be
alone with her again.
Why did the usurper
pardon you?
If we could speak alone.
No, speak to me here.
Explain it to me.
Who do you think
sent this to Meereen?
Who profits?
This is the work
of Tywin Lannister.
He wants to divide us.
If we're fighting each other,
we're not fighting him.
The pardon was signed
the year we met.
Why were you pardoned?
Unless you're saying
this document was forged.
It is not forged.
Why, then?
I sent letters to Varys,
the spymaster of
King's Landing.
What was the content
of these letters?
Information.
What information?
When you and Viserys
arrived in Pentos.
His plan to marry
you to Khal Drogo.
When you were married.
When your brother died.
You told him I was
carrying Drogo's child?
I...
Yes or no?
Khaleesi.
Don't call me that.
Did you tell him I was
carrying Drogo's child?
Yes.
That wine merchant
tried to poison me
because of your information.
I stopped you from
drinking his wine.
Because you knew
it was poisoned.
I suspected.
You betrayed me
from the first.
Forgive me.
I never meant...
Please, Khaleesi, forgive me.
You sold my secrets to
the man who killed my father
and stole
my brother's throne...
I have protected you,
fought for you,
killed for you.
...and you want
me to forgive you?
I have loved you.
Love?
How can you say that to me?
Any other man,
and I would have you executed.
But you,
I do not want you
in my city dead or alive.
Go back to your masters
in King's Landing.
Collect your pardon,
if you can.
Daenerys, please.
Don't ever presume
to touch me again
or speak my name.
You have until dusk
to collect your things
and leave this city.
If you're found in Meereen
past break of day,
I'll have your head
thrown into Slaver's Bay.
Go.
Now.
(FOOTSTEPS RECEDING)
Moat Cailin is yours, Father.
Walk with me.
Has there been
any word from Locke?
No.
Unimportant.
A cripple, a young boy.
None of the northern lords
have seen them.
Dead most likely.
Most of the ironborn
have fled the North.
Now more will follow,
thanks to you.
Tell me what you see.
Moors, fields, hills.
Nothing.
Not nothing. The North.
Ride 700 miles that way,
you're still in the North.
400 miles that way.
300 miles that way.
The North is larger
than the other
six kingdoms combined.
And I am
the Warden of the North.
The North is mine.
Now tell me,
what is your name?
Ramsay Snow.
No, not Ramsay Snow.
Open it.
From this day
until your last day,
you are Ramsay Bolton,
son of Roose Bolton,
Warden of the North.
(GASPING)
You honor me.
I swear I will
uphold your name
and your tradition.
I will be worthy
of you, Father,
I promise.
Come, Reek,
I'll be needing a bath.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
Yes?
(DOOR CLOSES)
First time I saw you,
you were just a child.
A girl from the North
come to the capital
for the first time.
You're not a child any longer.
Why did you help me?
They would have thrown you
through the Moon Door
if they found you guilty.
That's not an answer.
If they'd have executed you,
what would they
have done with me?
I don't know.
Neither do I.
Better to gamble
on the man you know
than the strangers you don't?
And you think you know me?
I know what you want.
Do you?
ARYA: I thought
it'd make me happy,
but it doesn't.
Not really.
HOUND: Nothing
makes you happy.
Lots of things
make me happy.
Like what?
Killing Polliver,
killing Rorge.
So you're sad because
you didn't get to
kill Joffrey yourself,
is that it?
At least I could have
been there to watch.
I wanted to see
the look in his eyes
when he knew it was over.
Aye, nothing in the world
beats that look.
You protected him
for most of his life.
You think you
could have saved him?
I wasn't the damn wine-taster.
Little shit deserved
to die, but poison...
Poison's a woman's weapon.
Men kill with steel.
That's your
stupid pride talking.
It's why you'll
never be a great killer.
I'd have killed Joffrey
with a chicken bone
if I had to.
(LAUGHS)
I'd pay good money
to see that.
(GROANS)
You should have
let me burn it.
It's a fleabite.
That fleabite's got you
walking a lot slower
than you used to.
Well, we won't
have to walk
too much further.
You really think
my aunt will pay for me?
Aye.
I've never even met her.
Doesn't matter.
You're her blood.
Family, honor,
all that horseshit.
It's all you lords and ladies
ever talk about.
I'm not a lady.
KNIGHT: Who would pass
the Bloody Gate?
The bloody Hound,
Sandor Clegane.
And his
traveling companion,
Arya Stark,
niece of your lady Lysa Arryn.
Then I offer my condolences.
Lady Arryn died.
Three days ago.
(LAUGHING)
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
I've never left home before,
Uncle Petyr.
I'm afraid to leave.
You shouldn't be.
The Lord of the Vale
belongs in the Eyrie,
Mother said.
It's not safe outside.
It wasn't safe
for her inside.
People die
at their dinner tables.
They die in their beds.
They die squatting
over their chamber pots.
Everybody dies
sooner or later.
Don't worry about your death.
Worry about your life.
Take charge of your life
for as long as it lasts.
That is what it means
to be Lord of the Vale.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Shall we go?
(GULPING)
Wine always helps.
I thank you for it.
Trial by combat.
Deciding a man's
guilt or innocence
in the eyes of the gods
by having two other men
hack each other to pieces.
Tells you something
about the gods.
How much longer?
Soon.
Do you think
Oberyn has a chance?
The Red Viper of Dorne.
You don't get a name like that
unless you're deadly, right?
I've never seen him fight.
Oh, he's going to die.
I'm going to die.
Oberyn believes in himself.
That's putting it mildly.
What's the punishment
for regicide?
Drawing and quartering?
Hanging?
Breaking at the wheel?
Beheading.
Seems rather ordinary.
And he was my nephew as well,
so what is that?
Fratricide is brothers
and filicide is sons.
(URINATING)
Nepoticide. That's the one.
Matricide, patricide,
infanticide, suicide.
There's no kind of killing
that doesn't have
its own word.
Cousins.
You're right.
There is no word
for cousin-killing.
Well done.
Do you remember Cousin Orson?
Orson Lannister?
Of course.
Wet-nurse dropped him
on his head
and left him simple.
Simple?
Used to sit
all day in the garden
crushing beetles with a rock.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(CHUCKLES) Nothing
made him happier.
Nothing made you happier.
You'd think being
tormented from birth
would have given you
some affinity
for the afflicted.
On the contrary.
Laughing at
another person's misery
was the only thing
that made me feel
like everyone else.
The joke wore thin, though.
For you. You drifted away.
I had other interests.
Yes, other interests.
But I stayed with Orson.
Why?
I was curious.
Why was he smashing
all those beetles?
What did he get out of it?
First thing I did was ask him.
"Orson, why are you smashing
all those beetles?"
He gave me an answer.
"Smash the beetles.
Smash 'em."
(GRUNTING)
I wasn't deterred.
I was the smartest person
I knew.
Certainly I had
the wherewithal
to unravel the mysteries
that lay at
the heart of a moron.
So I went to
Maester Volarik's library.
Volarik.
Tried to touch me once.
Turns out, far too much
has been written
about great men
and not nearly
enough about morons.
Doesn't seem right.
In any case,
I found nothing
that illuminated the nature
of Orson's affliction
or the reason behind
his relentless
beetle slaughter.
So I went back to the source.
I may not have been
able to speak with Orson,
but I could observe him,
watch him
the way men watch animals
to come to
a deeper understanding
of their behavior.
And as I watched,
I became more and more
sure of it.
There was
something happening there.
His face was like
the page of a book
written in a language
I didn't understand.
But he wasn't mindless.
He had his reasons.
And I became possessed
with knowing what they were.
I began to spend
inordinate amounts
of time watching him.
I would eat my lunch
in the garden,
chewing my mutton
to the music of...
(GRUNTING)
And when I
wasn't watching him,
I was thinking about him.
Father droned on
about the family legacy,
and I thought
about Orson's beetles.
I read the histories
of Targaryen conquests.
Did I hear dragon wings? No.
I heard...
(GRUNTING)
And I still
couldn't figure out
why he was doing it.
And I had to know,
because it was horrible
that all these
beetles should be
dying for no reason.
Every day around the world,
men, women, and children
are murdered by the score.
Who gives a dusty fuck about
a bunch of beetles?
I know. But still
it filled me with dread.
Piles and piles of them,
years and years of them.
How many countless living,
crawling things
smashed and dried out
and returned to the dirt?
In my dreams I found myself
standing on a beach
made of beetle husks
stretching as far
as the eye could see.
I woke up crying,
weeping for their
shattered little bodies.
I tried to stop Orson once.
He was twice your size.
He just pushed me
aside with a "cuhn"
and kept on smashing.
Every day,
until that mule
kicked him in the chest
and killed him.
So what do you think?
Why did he do it?
What was it all about?
I don't know.
(BELLS TOLLING)
Good luck today.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CROWD CLAMORING)
Looks like
very light armor.
I like to move around.
You could at least
wear a helmet.
You shouldn't
drink before a fight.
You learned this
during your years
in the fighting pits?
I always drink before a fight.
It could get you killed.
It could get me killed.
Today is not the day I die.
(CROWD CHEERING)
You're going to fight that?
I'm going to kill that.
ELLARIA: He is the biggest man
I've ever seen.
Size does not matter
when you are
flat on your back.
Thank the gods.
(HORN BLOWS)
In the sight of gods and men,
we gather to ascertain
the guilt or innocence
of this...
...man, Tyrion Lannister.
May the Mother
grant them mercy.
May the Father give them
such justice as they deserve.
And may the Warrior guide
the hand of our champion...
(HORN BLOWS)
Don't leave me
alone in this world.
Never.
(CROWD CHEERING)
Have they told you who I am?
Some dead man.
I am the brother
of Elia Martell.
And do you know
why I have come
all the way to this
stinking shit-pile of a city?
For you.
I'm going to hear you
confess before you die.
You raped my sister.
You murdered her.
You killed her children.
Say it now,
and we can make this quick.
(GRUNTING)
Say it. You raped her.
You murdered her.
(SHOUTS)
You killed her children.
(GROWLS)
You raped her!
You murdered her!
You killed her children!
(BOTH GRUNT)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(GROANS)
You raped her!
You murdered her!
(SCREAMS)
You killed her children!
(GROANS)
(CROWD CLAMORING)
Wait. Are you dying?
No. You can't die yet.
You haven't confessed.
Say it.
Say her name. Elia Martell.
You raped her.
You killed her children.
Elia Martell.
Who gave you the order?
Say her name!
You raped her!
You murdered her!
You killed her children!
Say her name.
Say it!
(GRUNTS)
(TEETH RATTLE)
Elia Martell.
(SCREAMING)
I killed her children,
then I raped her.
Then I smashed
her head in like this!
(SCREAMING)
The gods have made
their will known.
Tyrion Lannister,
in the name of King Tommen
of the House Baratheon,
First of His Name,
you are hereby
sentenced to death.