(SEAGULLS CALLING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
Your Grace, if you'd like
to sit, I'm sure that...
We've been here
since midday.
DAVOS: Easterners have
a different sense of time.
Once I was waiting
for Salladhor Saan
here in Braavos.
Together, we were going
to run three shiploads
of the finest...
(DOORS CLOSE)
Welcome to the Iron Bank.
Please, sit.
What can we do for you,
Lord Stannis?
This is Stannis of
the House Baratheon,
King of the Andals
and the First Men,
Lord of the Seven Kingdoms
and Protector of the Realm.
The Iron Throne is
currently occupied
by Tommen of
the House Baratheon,
King of the Andals
and the First Men,
Lord of the Seven Kingdoms
and Protector of the Realm.
He shares
no blood with me.
He is a bastard
born of incest.
As was his brother
before him.
Yes.
We have heard this story.
It's not a story.
It's the truth.
The king's grandfather
tells a different story.
A story about
a jealous uncle
whose attempts
to usurp the throne
from the rightful king
cost the Seven Kingdoms
dearly
in blood and gold.
Gold you loaned him.
And you feel
your blood gives you
a claim on our gold?
More than any man living.
Across the Narrow Sea,
your books are filled
with words like "usurper"
and "madman"
and "blood right."
Here, our books are
filled with numbers.
We prefer
the stories they tell.
More plain.
Less open to interpretation.
How many fighting men
remain loyal to you?
4,000.
And how many ships
do you have?
DAVOS: Uh...
The ones still afloat,
Ser Davos,
not at the bottom
of Blackwater Bay.
(CLEARS THROAT) Thirty-two.
And how much
wheat and barley
and beef and pork do you
produce on Dragonstone
to feed your 4,000 men
on your 32 ships?
None.
You can see why these
numbers seem unlikely
to add up to a happy ending
from our perspective.
I'm afraid
we must respectfully
decline your request.
But we thank you
for paying us
the honor of your visit.
DAVOS: My lord.
I'm not a lord,
Ser Davos Seaworth.
You would not be
either here.
In Braavos,
thieves are not
rewarded with titles.
I didn't do the thieving.
That would be the pirates.
I just moved what they stole
from one place to another.
This is the payment
that was demanded by
King Stannis for my crimes.
I consider it
an honest accounting.
He's an honest man and
he's your best chance
to get back the money
you've sunk into Westeros.
Which is a lot.
Wars are expensive.
The war is over.
As long as Stannis lives,
the war is not over.
Who's the real power
in King's Landing?
Ser Davos...
Humor me.
Tywin Lannister.
How old is
Tywin Lannister?
Sixty-seven.
And when he dies,
who's in command?
A half-grown boy,
the product of incest?
Cersei Lannister,
a queen whose
people despise her?
Jaime Lannister,
a man best known
for killing the king
he was sworn to protect?
When Tywin's gone,
who do you back?
That is a problem
for another time.
I think it's
a problem for now.
There's only one
reliable leader left
in Westeros.
Stannis.
He's got the birthright.
He's in his prime.
He's a tried and tested
battle commander.
And he doesn't just talk
about paying people back,
he does it.
SALLADHOR: The lookout
sees a pirate ship
sailing their way.
The captain shouts
to his first mate,
"Bring me my red shirt."
The first mate brings
the red shirt and
the captain puts it on.
And when the pirates
try to board,
the brave captain leads
his men to victory.
A few days later,
the lookout screams,
"Two pirate ships!"
The crew is shivering
like scared mice.
But the courageous
captain hollers,
"Bring me my red shirt!"
After the battle,
the first mate asks,
"Captain, why do you
call for your red shirt
before battle?"
The captain replies,
"So that if I am stabbed,
you will not see me bleed."
The next morning
the lookout screams,
"Ten pirate ships!
We are surrounded!"
The crew goes silent.
They all look to
their brave captain,
waiting for his usual command.
Calm as ever,
the captain bellows...
WHORES: "Bring me
my brown pants!"
(BOTH LAUGH)
DAVOS: You think
they ever met a pirate
who didn't tell
them that joke?
Davos.
(DAVOS CHUCKLES)
I heard you were
rotting in a dungeon
in Dragonstone.
Only half rotted.
(LAUGHING)
Join us, my friend.
This is Lhara.
(EXCLAIMS)
And this is...
I am Lhara.
(SQUEALS)
(SALLADHOR LAUGHS)
She's an artist,
this one, truly.
No time, I'm afraid.
We sail at sunrise.
We?
You, me. We.
(SCOFFS)
Once I thought
this man loved me.
Now I know he despises me.
He wants to see me die poor
and alone on some cold...
You won't be alone.
And you won't be poor.
There's a chest
of the good stuff
left back at your house.
I gave it to your wife.
(WHORES LAUGHING)
You're not my friend,
my friend.
(CHUCKLES)
I'll see you at sunrise.
YARA: "I give you
until the full moon
"to order all ironborn
scum out of the North
"and back to those
shit-stained rocks
you call home.
"On the first night
of the full moon,
"I will hunt down
every islander
still on our lands
"and flay them living,
"the way I flayed
the 20 ironborn scum
I found at Winterfell.
"In the box you'll
find a special gift.
"Theon's favorite toy.
"He cried when I
took it away from him.
"Leave the North now
or more boxes will
follow with more Theon."
Signed, "Ramsay Snow,
"natural born son
of Roose Bolton,
"Lord of the Dreadfort
"and Warden of the North."
(MOANING)
MYRANDA: Yes!
YARA: They skinned
our countrymen
and they mutilated
my brother,
your prince.
Your prince!
Everything
they've done to him,
they've also done to you.
MYRANDA: Yes!
YARA: As long as
they can hurt our prince
with impunity,
the word "ironborn"
means nothing.
(MOANING LOUDLY)
(GRUNTS)
Go left.
(MEN WHISPERING)
(GROANS)
Theon Greyjoy.
(STAMMERING)
I don't know...
I'm here for Theon Greyjoy.
Take me to the dungeons.
He's not
in the dungeons.
(DOGS SNUFFLING)
(RASPY BREATHING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(ALARM BELL TOLLING)
Last cage on the right.
Thank you.
(GURGLES)
(SWORDS CLANGING)
MAN: This way!
(BARKING)
(WHIMPERING)
We're going home.
THEON: No!
(BARKING CONTINUES)
It's all right.
It's me, Yara.
You can't trick me.
Tell him you
couldn't trick me.
I'm not tricking you,
Theon. I'm saving you.
Not Theon! Reek!
My name is Reek!
MAN: They're here.
If they catch us in here,
we're trapped.
Help me with him.
No, you can't!
You're Theon Greyjoy.
No, I don't believe her!
I know who I am!
I'm Reek! Loyal Reek!
Good Reek!
I've always been Reek!
(THEON WHIMPERING)
This is turning into
a lovely evening.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
THEON: I'm Reek!
Loyal Reek!
(SCREAMING)
Theon!
Give me my brother
and no more of
your men will die.
You've got bigger balls
than he ever did.
But with those
big balls of yours,
how fast can you run?
(BARKING)
(CAGE RATTLING)
(DOGS BARKING)
YARA: Make for
the ship, now.
MAN: But your brother?
My brother is dead.
RAMSAY: I have
a treat for you.
A reward.
Reward?
Yes, Reek.
Those creatures who
came in the night,
they wanted to
take you away.
And you didn't let them.
You remained loyal.
I didn't want them
to take me.
(VOICE BREAKING)
I was so scared.
I didn't want them...
Yes, Reek.
It's a bath.
For you.
Remove those rags.
Now.
(BREATH QUIVERING)
The britches,
too, Reek.
Take them off.
(WHIMPERING)
(WATER SPLASHES)
(WHIMPERS)
(GASPS)
Do you love me, Reek?
Yes, of course, my lord.
Good.
Because I need you
to do something for me.
Something very important.
There's a castle.
Some bad men
hold this castle.
I need your help to
take this castle back.
But how can...
I need you to play a role.
To pretend to be
someone you're not.
Pretend to be who?
Theon Greyjoy.
(WATER SPLASHES)
(ROCK THUDS)
(ROARING)
(GOAT BLEATING)
(DRAGON SCREECHING)
(SPEAKS VALYRIAN)
He is a goatherd.
He says he prayed
for your victory
against the slave masters.
I thank him
for his prayers.
(SPEAKS VALYRIAN)
(GOATHERD SPEAKS VALYRIAN)
It was your
dragons, he says.
They came this
morning for his flock.
(SPEAKS VALYRIAN)
He hopes he has not
offended Your Grace,
but now he has nothing.
Tell this man I am
sorry for his hardship.
I cannot bring
back his goats...
(MISSANDEI TRANSLATING)
...but I will see he
is paid their value
three times over.
(SPEAKS VALYRIAN)
Send the next one in.
Queen Daenerys.
Tales of your beauty
were not exaggerated.
I thank you.
Mine is one of the
oldest and proudest
families in Meereen.
Then it is my honor
to receive you.
My father,
one of Meereen's
most respected
and beloved citizens,
oversaw the restoration
and maintenance of
its greatest landmarks.
This pyramid included.
For that, he has my gratitude.
I should be
honored to meet him.
You have, Your Grace.
You crucified him.
I pray you'll
never live to see
a member of your family
treated so cruelly.
Your father crucified
innocent children.
My father spoke out
against crucifying
those children.
He decried it as
a criminal act,
but was overruled.
Is it justice to answer
one crime with another?
I am sorry you
no longer have a father,
but my treatment of
the masters was no crime.
You'd be wise
to remember that.
What's done is done.
You are the queen
and I am a servant
of Meereen.
A servant who does
not wish to see
its traditions eradicated.
And what traditions
do you speak of?
Of funeral rite.
Proper burial in the
Temple of the Graces.
My father and 162
noble Meereenese
are still nailed
to those posts,
carrion for vultures,
rotting in the sun.
Your Grace, I ask
that you order
these men taken down
so that they might
receive proper burials.
And what of the slave
children these noble
Meereenese crucified?
They were rotting
in the sun as well.
Would you have begged me
for their right
to a proper burial?
Your Grace, I cannot
defend the actions
of the masters.
I can only speak
to you as a son
who loved his father.
Let me take his body down.
Let me have him
brought to the temple
and buried with dignity
so that he might find
peace in the next world.
Bury your father,
Hizdahr zo Loraq.
Thank you, my queen.
How many more?
There are 212
supplicants waiting,
Your Grace.
212?
Send the next one in.
These meetings aren't
always going to be
this early, are they?
I was up late last night.
So, does this mean
I am a master
of something now?
Coins, ships?
Lord Tywin and I
already determined that
I shall be
the Master of Ships
long before you...
Lord Tywin,
it's a great honor
to have been
granted a seat
on this council. I...
TYWIN: The trial
begins this afternoon.
We only have the morning
for affairs of state.
So, shall we begin?
VARYS: Sandor Clegane
has been spotted in
the Riverlands, my lord.
A coward and a traitor.
My birds tell me
the Hound slaughtered
five of our soldiers.
I believe the phrase
"fuck the king"
was uttered.
Disgraceful.
TYWIN: What
would it take to make
the common soldier
stupid enough to try
his luck with the Hound?
VARYS: Ten silver stags
seems a generous bounty.
Make it 100.
What else?
More whispers from
the east, my lord.
The Targaryen girl?
Daenerys has taken up
residence in Meereen.
She has conquered the city
and rules as its queen.
Conquered with what?
VARYS: She commands
an army of Unsullied,
my queen.
Some 8,000 strong.
She has a company
of sellswords,
the Second Sons.
She has two knights
advising her,
Jorah Mormont and
Barristan Selmy.
And she has three dragons.
Baby dragons.
Larger every year,
Your Grace.
Mormont is spying
on her for us.
No longer.
He appears to be
fully devoted to her.
As for Ser Barristan,
it would seem he
took his dismissal
from the Kingsguard
a bit harder
than anticipated.
He's an old man.
He wasn't fit to
protect my son.
Joffrey didn't
die on his watch.
Dismissing him
was as insulting
as it was stupid.
Don't tell me
you're worried about
a child halfway
across the world.
A child with two
seasoned warriors
counseling her
and a powerful army at
her back, Your Grace.
Lord Varys is right.
I have been to Essos
and seen
the Unsullied firsthand.
They are very impressive
on the battlefield.
Less so in the bedroom.
Dragons haven't won
a war in 300 years.
Armies win them
all the time.
She must be dealt with.
How, my lord?
By force?
Eventually, if it
comes to that.
Can your little birds
find their way into Meereen?
Most certainly,
my Lord Hand.
Mmm.
Lord Tyrell, be a good man.
Fetch my quill and paper.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Prince Oberyn.
Lord Varys.
Only Varys. I'm not
actually a nobleman.
No one is under
obligation
to call me lord.
And yet everyone does.
You seem
quite knowledgeable
about the Unsullied.
Did you spend
much time in Essos?
Five years.
May I ask why?
'Tis a big and
beautiful world.
Most of us live and
die in the same corner
where we were born
and never get
to see any of it.
I don't want
to be most of us.
Most of us aren't princes.
(CHUCKLES)
You are from Essos.
Where? Lys?
I have an ear for accents.
I've lost
my accent entirely.
I have an ear
for that as well.
Hmm.
How did you get here?
It's a long story.
One you don't like
telling people.
People I trust.
My paramour Ellaria,
she would find you
very interesting.
You should come
to the brothel
and meet her.
We brought our own wine,
not the swill
they serve here.
We have some lovely
boys on retainer, but...
You did like boys before?
Really?
Girls? Hmm.
I hope you won't be
offended when I say
I never would have guessed.
Not at all.
But I was never interested
in girls, either.
What then?
Nothing.
Everybody is interested
in something.
Not me.
When I see what
desire does to people,
what it's done
to this country,
I am very glad to
have no part in it.
Besides, the absence
of desire
leaves one free to
pursue other things.
Such as?
(DOOR UNLOCKS)
Let me guess,
I've been pardoned.
Really?
Father's orders.
Well, we mustn't
disappoint Father.
(CROWD MURMURING)
MAN: Kingslayer!
I, Tommen of
the House Baratheon,
First of my Name,
King of the Andals
and the First Men,
and Lord of
the Seven Kingdoms,
do hereby recuse
myself from this trial.
Tywin of the House Lannister,
Hand of the King,
Protector of the Realm,
will sit as judge
in my stead.
And with him Prince Oberyn
of the House Martell
and Lord Mace of
the House Tyrell.
And if found guilty,
may the gods
punish the accused.
Tyrion of
the House Lannister,
you stand accused
by the Queen Regent
of regicide.
Did you kill
King Joffrey?
No.
Did your wife,
the Lady Sansa?
Not that I know of.
How would you say
he died, then?
Choked on his pigeon pie.
So you would
blame the bakers?
Or the pigeons.
Just leave me out of it.
(CROWD MURMURING)
The crown may call
its first witness.
MERYN:
Once we'd got King Joffrey
safely away from the mob,
the Imp rounded on him.
He slapped the king
across the face
and called him
a vicious idiot
and a fool.
(CROWD GASPS)
It wasn't the first time
the Imp threatened Joffrey.
Right here in
this throne room,
he marched up
those steps and called
our king a halfwit.
Compared His Grace
to the Mad King
and suggested he'd
meet the same fate.
And when I spoke in
the king's defense,
he threatened to
have me killed.
Oh, why don't you
tell them what
Joffrey was doing?
TYWIN: Silence.
Pointing a loaded
crossbow at Sansa Stark
while you tore at her
clothes and beat her.
Silence!
You will not speak
unless called upon.
You're dismissed, Ser Meryn.
"Basilisk venom,
"widow's blood,
"wolfsbane,
"essence of nightshade,
"sweetsleep,
"tears of Lys,
"demon's dance..."
(MUMBLING)
"...blindeye..."
I think you have
made your point,
Grand Maester.
You have a lot of
poison in your store.
Had, Prince Oberyn.
My stores were plundered.
By whom?
By the accused,
Tyrion Lannister,
after he had me
wrongfully imprisoned.
TYWIN: Grand Maester,
you examined
King Joffrey's corpse.
Was it without question
poison that killed him?
Without question.
(CROWD MURMURING)
This was found on the body
of Dontos Hollard,
the king's fool.
He was last seen
spiriting Sansa Stark,
the wife of the accused,
away from the feast.
She wore this necklace
the day of the wedding.
Residue of the most
rare and terrible poison
was found inside.
Was this one of
the poisons stolen
from your store?
It was.
The strangler.
(CROWD GASPS)
A poison few in the
Seven Kingdoms possess.
And used to strike down
the most noble child
the gods ever put
on this good earth.
(CROWD MURMURING)
CERSEI: "I will
hurt you for this.
"A day will come
when you think you
are safe and happy
"and your joy will turn
to ashes in your mouth
"and you will know
the debt is paid."
Your own brother
said this to you?
Shortly before
the Battle
of Blackwater Bay.
I confronted him
about his plans
to put Joffrey on
the front lines.
As it turned out,
when the attack came,
Joff insisted
on remaining
at the battlements.
He believed his presence
would inspire the troops.
Tyrion said,
"And you will know
the debt is paid."
What debt?
I discovered he'd
been keeping whores
in the Tower of the Hand.
I asked him to confine
his salacious acts
to the brothel where
such behavior belongs.
He wasn't pleased.
Thank you, Your Grace,
for the courage
of your testimony.
MACE: Do you remember
the precise nature
of this threat?
VARYS: I'm afraid
I do, my lord.
He said, "Perhaps you should
speak more softly to me, then.
"Monsters are dangerous
"and just now kings
are dying like flies."
And he said this to you
at a meeting of
the Small Council?
VARYS: Yes.
After we received word
of Robb Stark's death.
He didn't seem
gladdened by the news.
Perhaps his marriage
to Sansa Stark
had made him
more sympathetic
to the northern cause.
(CROWD MURMURING)
You're excused,
Lord Varys.
Father, may I ask
the witness one question?
One.
You once said
that without me,
this city would have
faced certain defeat.
You said the histories
would never mention me,
but you would not forget.
Have you forgotten,
Lord Varys?
Sadly, my lord,
I never forget a thing.
We will adjourn for now.
Toll the bells
in an hour's time.
GUARD: Clear the court!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
JAIME: You'd condemn
your own son to death?
I've condemned no one.
The trial is not over.
This isn't a trial.
It's a farce.
Cersei has
manipulated everything
and you know it.
I know nothing
of the sort.
You've always hated Tyrion.
He killed his king.
As did I.
Do you know the last order
the Mad King gave me?
To bring him your head.
I saved your life
so you could
murder my brother?
It won't be murder.
It'll be justice.
Justice?
I'm performing
my sworn duty
as Hand of the King.
If Tyrion is found guilty,
he will be
punished accordingly.
He'll be executed.
No, he'll be
punished accordingly.
Once you said,
"Family is what lives on.
"All that lives on."
You told me about
a dynasty that
would last 1,000 years.
What happens
to your dynasty
when Tyrion dies?
I'm a Kingsguard,
forbidden by oath to
carry on the family line.
I'm well aware.
What happens
to your name?
Who carries the lion banner
into future battles?
Your nephews?
Lancel Lannister?
Others whose names I
don't even remember?
What happens to my dynasty
if I spare the life of
my grandson's killer?
It survives through me.
I'll leave the Kingsguard.
I'll take my place
as your son and heir
if you let Tyrion live.
Done.
When the testimony's
concluded and
a guilty verdict rendered,
Tyrion will be given
the chance to speak.
He'll plead for mercy.
I'll allow him to
join the Night's Watch.
In three days' time,
he'll depart
for Castle Black
and live out his
days at the Wall.
You'll remove your
white cloak immediately.
You will leave
King's Landing
to assume
your rightful place
at Casterly Rock.
You will marry
a suitable woman
and father children
named Lannister.
And you'll
never turn your back
on your family again.
You have my word.
And you have mine.
(BELL TOLLING)
Not going well, is it?
You're going to
be found guilty.
Oh, you think so?
And when you are,
you need to enter
a formal plea for mercy
and ask to be
sent to the Wall.
Father's agreed to it.
He'll spare your life
and allow you to join
the Night's Watch.
Ned Stark was
promised the same thing
and we both know
how that turned out.
JAIME:
Father is not Joffrey.
He'll keep his word.
How do you know?
Do you trust me?
Keep your mouth shut.
No more outbursts.
This will all
be over soon.
The crown may call
its next witness.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
State your name.
Shae.
Do you swear by
all the gods that
your testimony will
be true and honest?
I swear it.
Do you know this man?
Yes. Tyrion Lannister.
How do you know him?
I was handmaiden to
his wife Lady Sansa.
This man stands accused
of murdering King Joffrey.
What do you know of this?
I know that he's guilty.
(CROWD GASPS)
He and Sansa
planned it together.
(CROWD MURMURING)
TYWIN: Silence!
Continue.
SHAE: She wanted
revenge for her father,
her mother, her brother.
She blamed their
deaths on the king.
Tyrion was happy to help.
He hated Joffrey.
He hated the queen.
He hated you, my lord.
He stole poison from the
Grand Maester's chamber
to put in Joffrey's wine.
OBERYN: How could you
possibly know all this?
Why would he
reveal such plans
to his wife's maid?
I wasn't just her maid.
I was his whore.
(CROWD MURMURING)
MACE: I beg your pardon?
You said you were his...
His whore.
How did you come to
be in his service?
He stole me.
I was with another man,
a knight in your
lordship's army.
But when Tyrion
arrived at the camp,
he sent one of his
cutthroats into our tent.
He broke the knight's arm
and brought me
to Lord Tyrion.
"You belong to
me now," he said.
"I want you to fuck me
like it's my last
night in this world."
(CROWD LAUGHS)
Silence!
(LAUGHING STOPS)
And did you?
Did I what?
Fuck him like
it was his last
night in this world?
(CROWD LAUGHS)
I did everything
he wanted.
Whatever he told
me to do to him.
Whatever he felt
like doing to me.
I kissed him where he wanted.
I licked him where he wanted.
I let him put himself
where he wanted.
I was his property.
I would wait in his
chambers for hours
so he could use me
when he was bored.
He ordered me to call
him "my lion," so I did.
I took his face in
my hands and said,
"I am yours
and you are mine."
(CROWD MURMURING)
Shae.
Please don't.
I am a whore.
Remember?
That was before
he married Sansa.
After that,
all he wanted was her.
But she wouldn't
let him into her bed.
So he promised to kill
King Joffrey for her.
(CROWD CLAMORING)
Father,
I wish to confess.
(CROWD QUIETS)
You wish to confess?
I saved you.
I saved this city
and all your
worthless lives.
I should have let
Stannis kill you all.
(CROWD CLAMORING ANGRILY)
TYWIN: Tyrion.
Do you wish to confess?
Yes, Father.
I'm guilty.
Is that what
you want to hear?
You admit you
poisoned the king?
No, of that I'm innocent.
I'm guilty of a far
more monstrous crime.
I am guilty
of being a dwarf.
You are not on trial
for being a dwarf.
TYRION: Oh, yes, I am.
I've been on trial for
that my entire life.
Have you nothing to
say in your defense?
TYRION:
Nothing but this...
I did not do it.
I did not kill Joffrey,
but I wish that I had.
Watching your
vicious bastard die
gave me more relief
than 1,000 lying whores.
(CROWD MURMURING)
I wish I was
the monster
you think I am.
I wish I had enough poison
for the whole pack of you.
I would gladly give my life
to watch you all swallow it.
Ser Meryn.
(CROWD SHOUTING)
Escort the prisoner
back to his cell.
I will not give my life
for Joffrey's murder.
And I know I'll get
no justice here.
So I will let the gods
decide my fate.
I demand
a trial by combat.
(CROWD SHOUTING)
(THE RAINS OF
CASTAMERE PLAYING)