(FIRE CRACKLING)
(THE RAINS OF
CASTAMERE PLAYING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Magnificent.
Mmm-hmm.
Looks fresh-forged.
It is.
No one's made
a Valyrian steel sword
since the Doom of Valyria.
There are three living smiths
who know how to rework
Valyrian steel.
The finest of them
was in Volantis.
Came here to King's Landing
at my invitation.
Where did you get
this much Valyrian steel?
From someone who
no longer had need of it.
You've wanted
one in the family
for a long time.
And now we have two.
Two?
The original weapon
was absurdly large.
Plenty of steel
for two swords.
Well, thank you.
It's glorious.
(GRUNTS)
You'll have to
train your left hand.
Any decent swordsman
knows how to use both hands.
You'll never be as good.
No.
But as long as I'm better
than everyone else,
it doesn't matter.
You can't serve
in the Kingsguard
with one hand.
Where's that written?
I can and I will.
The Kingsguard
oath is for life.
The war is over.
The King is safe.
The King is never safe.
How many people
in this city alone
would love to see
his head on a pike?
Other knights
protected the King
while you were a prisoner.
They will continue to do so
when you go home.
Home?
You'll return to Casterly Rock
and rule in my stead.
You are the Lord
of Casterly Rock.
I am the King's Hand.
My place is here.
I don't expect to
see the Rock again
before I die.
You know what
they call me?
Kingslayer. Oathbreaker.
Man without honor.
Now you want me to
break another sacred vow.
You won't be
breaking anything.
There is a precedent
to relieve a Kingsguard
of his duties.
The King will
exercise that prerogative.
No.
No?
I don't believe I
asked you a question.
There's my answer.
If you think
your bloody honor
comes before your...
My bloody honor
is beyond repair,
but my answer is still no.
I don't want Casterly Rock,
a wife, children.
What do you want?
Supper would be nice.
For 40 years I've
tried to teach you.
If you haven't learned
by now, you never will.
Go.
If serving as
a glorified bodyguard
is the sum of your ambition,
go serve.
I suppose you
want the sword back.
Keep it.
A one-handed
man with no family
needs all the help he can get.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(GOATS BLEATING)
How many Dornishmen
does it take to fuck a goat?
Please don't.
BRONN: Seems to me
the smart place to
meet travelers
is in a tavern.
That way, one party is late,
the other party can
drink some ale inside.
This is the Prince of
Dorne we're waiting for,
not one of your
sellsword friends.
If he's so damned important,
how come they sent you
to meet him?
There's bad blood between
the Martells of Dorne
and the Lannisters
of Casterly Rock.
Has been for years.
And just in case
the Martells of Dorne
are looking to spill
some Lannister blood,
it may as well be yours, eh?
No need for cynicism.
I happen to be
an accomplished diplomat.
Oh.
Ah, here we are.
(CLAPPING)
TYRION:
Can you read the sigils?
Yellow balls?
Wild lemons on a purple field,
House Dalt of Lemonwood.
A vulture grasping
a baby in its talons,
House of Blackmont.
A crowned skull,
the Manwoodys of Kingsgrave.
Boy knows his
Dornish houses.
I need a sigil.
And House Martell,
a red sun pierced
by a spear?
I don't see it,
my lord.
Well met, my lords.
His Grace King Joffrey
welcomes you in his name.
My lord father,
the King's Hand,
sends his greetings as well.
I am Tyrion Lannister
of Casterly Rock,
Master of Coin.
Forgive me.
I don't see
Prince Doran
in your company.
The prince's health
forces him to
remain at Sunspear.
He sends his brother,
Prince Oberyn,
to attend the royal wedding.
The King will be
delighted to enjoy
the company of a warrior
as renowned as
Prince Oberyn.
Will he?
Where is Prince Oberyn?
Arrived before dawn.
Not a man for
welcome parties.
Very well. My lords,
these fine men
from the City Watch
will escort you
to your quarters
in the Red Keep.
You must be weary
after such a long journey.
Some accomplished
diplomacy that was.
Now where?
We must find
Prince Oberyn
before he kills somebody,
or several somebodies.
How do you plan on finding
a single Dornishman
in a city this big?
You're famous for
fucking half of Westeros.
You just
arrived at the capital
after two weeks of bad road.
Where would you go?
I'd probably go to sleep,
but I'm getting old.
Look at this one.
How lovely is she?
Beautiful.
But pale.
We like them
pale in the capital.
Shows they don't
work the fields.
Do I frighten you?
You like?
Timid bores me.
Hmm.
You're a bit of mischief,
aren't you?
I think she likes you.
(CHUCKLES)
She has good taste.
You're not timid,
are you?
(LAUGHS) Not timid.
Do you like women?
When they look
like her, my lord.
This one will do nicely.
OLYVER: Very good, my lady.
Oh, I'm not a lady.
A term of courtesy
in this establishment.
A lie anywhere.
Why not use
the right words?
I'm a bastard.
She is a whore.
And you're what?
A procurer.
Any of the others?
(SIGHING) The two
girls can leave.
(OLYVER SNAPS FINGERS)
You stay.
I'm afraid I'm not
on offer, my lord.
Everyone who works
for Littlefinger
is on offer.
Take off your clothes.
We'll be here a while.
My lord.
I am a prince, boy.
(WOMAN MOANS)
Have you ever
been with a prince?
Can't say I have.
I'm wildly expensive.
(SCOFFS)
Take off your clothes.
Which way
do you like it?
(GASPS)
My way.
MAN:
♪ And so he spoke,
and so he spoke
♪ That Lord of Castamere
♪ But now the rains... ♪
Oberyn.
♪ Weep o'er his hall... ♪
Oberyn, don't.
♪ With no one there to hear
♪ Yes now the rains
weep o'er his hall
♪ And not a soul to hear ♪
You lost, friend?
Forgive me for staring.
I don't see many
Lannisters where I'm from.
Dornishmen in
the capital.
We don't like the smell.
(LAUGHS)
Come with me, lover.
Gods, look at this one.
Sirs, if you follow me,
I'll arrange for
a private room.
Why are you wasting
a woman like this
on a Dornishman?
Bring him a shaved goat
and a bottle of olive oil.
(LAUGHS)
OBERYN: Hmm.
Do you know why all the world
hates a Lannister?
You think your gold
and your lions
and your gold lions
make you better than everyone.
May I tell you a secret?
You're not a golden lion.
You're just a pink little man
who is far too
slow on the draw.
(SCREAMING)
Longsword is
a bad option in
close quarters.
When I pull my blade,
your friend starts bleeding.
Quite a lot, I'm afraid.
So many veins in the wrist.
(GROANING)
He'll live if you get
him help straightaway.
So, decisions.
(CONTINUES GROANING)
Prince Oberyn,
forgive the intrusion.
We heard there might be...
(MAN SCREAMS)
...trouble.
Apologies, my love.
(DOOR CLOSES)
I'm here to welcome
you to the capital.
Ellaria Sand,
my paramour.
The King's own Uncle Imp.
Tyrion,
son of Tywin Lannister.
If there's anything I can do
to make your stay
at King's Landing...
What are you?
His hired killer?
It started that way, aye.
Now I'm a knight.
How did that
come to pass?
Killed the right people.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
We'll need a few more girls.
Girls, yes?
You don't partake?
Oh, I partook.
Now I'm married.
Prince Oberyn,
a word in private?
Seems I visited
the Lannister brothel
by mistake.
Oh, they take all kinds.
Even Dornishmen.
TYRION:
The King is very grateful
that you traveled all
this way for his wedding.
Let us speak truth here.
Joffrey is insulted.
I am only the second son.
Well, speaking as
a fellow second son,
I have grown rather used
to being the family insult.
(OBERYN CHUCKLES)
Why did you come
to King's Landing?
I was invited to
the royal wedding.
I thought we
were speaking truth.
The last time I
was in the capital
was many years ago.
Another wedding.
My sister Elia and
Rhaegar Targaryen,
the Last Dragon.
My sister loved him.
She bore his children.
Swaddled them, rocked them,
fed them at her own breast.
Elia wouldn't let
the wet nurse touch them.
And beautiful,
noble Rhaegar Targaryen
left her for another woman.
That started a war,
and the war ended right here,
when your father's
army took the city.
I wasn't actually present.
They butchered
those children.
My nephew and niece.
Carved them up
and wrapped them
in Lannister cloaks.
And my sister,
you know what
they did to her?
I'm asking you a question.
I've heard rumors.
Hmm.
So have I.
The one I keep hearing
is that Gregor Clegane
the Mountain
raped Elia and
split her in half
with his great sword.
I wasn't there.
I don't know what happened.
If the Mountain
killed my sister,
your father gave the order.
Tell your father I'm here.
And tell him the Lannisters
aren't the only ones
who pay their debts.
(DRAGONS SCREECHING)
(GROWLS)
(SCREECHING)
(CHUCKLES)
(SCREECHES)
(SHUSHING)
(SCREECHING)
(GASPS)
(SHUSHING)
(ROARS)
(GASPS)
(SCREECHES)
They're dragons,
Khaleesi.
They can never be tamed.
Not even by their mother.
Ser Barristan.
Your Grace.
Where's Daario Naharis?
Where's Grey Worm?
Gambling, Your Grace.
Gambling?
CROWD: Mhysa. Mhysa.
How long have
they been at it?
Since midnight,
Your Grace.
Ser Worm is
stronger than he looks.
But I can see his
arms beginning to shake.
What's the prize
to winning this
stupid contest?
The honor of
riding by your side
on the road to Meereen.
That honor goes to
Ser Jorah and Ser Barristan,
as neither of them
kept me waiting
this morning.
You two will ride
in the rear guard
and protect the livestock.
The last man holding his sword
can find a new
queen to fight for.
(DAARIO GROANING)
(BOTH SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
You need to eat something.
Pigeon pie.
No, thank you.
Lemon cakes?
You love lemon cakes.
Tell her she needs to eat.
My lady, you do need to eat.
I don't want to eat.
If I could have
a moment alone
with my wife.
She needs to eat.
TYRION:
I can't let you starve.
I swore to protect you.
My lady,
I am your husband.
Let me help you.
How can you help me?
I don't know,
but I can try.
I lie awake all night
staring at the canopy,
thinking about
how they died.
I could get you
essence of nightshade
to help you sleep.
Do you know what
they did to my brother?
How they sewed
his direwolf's head
onto his body?
And my mother.
They cut her
throat to the bone
and threw her
body in the river.
What happened
to your family was
a terrible crime.
I didn't know
your brother.
He seemed like a good man,
but I didn't know him.
Your mother,
I admired her.
She wanted to
have me executed,
but I admired her.
She was a strong woman.
And she was fierce
when it came to
protecting her children.
Sansa.
Your mother would
want you to carry on.
You know it's true.
Will you pardon me, my lord?
I'd like to
visit the godswood.
Of course. Prayer
can be helpful, I hear.
I don't pray anymore.
It's the only place I can go
where people don't talk to me.
SHAE: My lion.
What are you doing?
What does it look like?
Come here.
How many times
have I told you?
You can't visit me here.
I know. We have come
to a dangerous place.
Have you forgotten me?
Do you know how
long it's been?
Of course I haven't forgotten.
I want you.
Don't you want me?
Things are a bit
tense right now.
What things?
My nephew the King
wants to murder me.
My wife hates me
because my father
murdered her family.
Oberyn Martell wants to murder
everyone whose last
name is Lannister.
You need to relax.
Don't you want to relax?
What's wrong?
I told you.
It's not a good time.
It's never a good time.
You have your
child bride now.
Shae.
Do you love her?
Love her? I barely
know her. She's a child.
She despises me.
That's not an answer.
I don't love her.
You tried to
ship me away.
Ship you away?
Give me diamonds
and make me disappear.
What are you talking about?
If you want me to leave,
just say it.
Say it!
Shh.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You want me to stay?
(GROANS)
A work of art.
The craftsmanship
is excellent.
You like it so much,
you're welcome
to chop off your
own hand and take it.
You're such an ingrate.
I spent days
with the goldsmith
getting the details
just right.
Days?
Better part
of an afternoon.
There, how does that feel?
Uh...
A hook would be
more practical.
Elegant, I think.
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
CERSEI:
Thank you for your help
with the other matter.
QYBURN:
The symptoms have abated?
Gone completely.
I am in your debt,
Maester Qyburn.
Not a maester, Your Grace,
but happy to help
whenever I can.
(DOOR OPENS)
Odd little man.
I've grown fond of him.
(DOOR CLOSES)
He's quite talented.
What symptoms?
(CHUCKLES)
Symptoms that are
not your concern.
You let him touch you?
You jealous?
I'm surprised.
You never let
Pycelle near you.
(LAUGHS) You think
I'd let that old lecher
put his hands on me?
He smells like a dead cat.
I'm not sure I've
ever smelled a dead cat.
Well, they smell
like Pycelle.
You drink more
than you used to.
Yes.
Why?
Hmm. Let's see.
You started a brawl
in the streets with
Ned Stark
and disappeared
from the capital.
My husband died in
a tragic hunting accident.
It must have been
traumatic for you.
My only daughter was
shipped off to Dorne.
We suffered through a siege.
A rather short siege.
That I didn't
expect to survive.
And now I'm
marrying my eldest son
to a wicked little
bitch from Highgarden,
while I'm supposed
to marry her brother,
a renowned pillow-biter. So...
Father disowned me today.
He can't disown you.
You're all he's got.
You're forgetting Tyrion.
(SCOFFS)
You don't really
plan on staying
in the Kingsguard, do you?
Staying in
the Kingsguard means
I live right here in
the Red Keep with you.
Not now.
I want...
Not now? When?
I've been back for weeks.
Something's changed.
Everything's changed.
You come back
after all this time
with no apologies and one hand
and expect everything
to be the same?
What do you want
me to apologize for?
For leaving me.
You think I wanted
to be taken prisoner?
Don't know what you wanted.
You weren't here.
You left me alone.
Every day I was a prisoner,
I plotted my escape.
Every day.
I murdered people
so I could be here with you.
You took too long.
I...
What are you saying?
You took too long.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Come in.
JAIME: Go away.
Forgive me, Your Grace.
You told me to come
at once if there was
anything important.
(BLOWING)
You plan on killing
all the crows yourself?
Do you plan on sitting here,
scratching your
balls till winter?
We wait for Mance's orders.
You sent a man over
the Wall at the full moon.
If he's not back yet,
he's not coming back.
And what is it you want?
March on Castle Black
with just this lot?
Your pretty crow said
a thousand men
are nesting there.
He's a liar.
He is?
Shouldn't it be "he was"?
You said you put
three arrows in him.
I did.
I've seen you slip a shaft
through a rabbit's
eye at 200 yards.
If that boy's still walking,
it's 'cause you let him go.
(WHISTLING)
Thenns.
I fucking hate Thenns.
Mance sent you?
(GRUNTS)
How did you find us?
(CAWS)
You came from the south,
not the north.
Took a detour.
Got some supper
from a village down that way.
Why does the meat down here
taste so much better
than it does on
our side of the Wall?
Help yourself.
(CHUCKLES)
Maybe everything's
just better fed down here.
Fat and lazy.
Easier for us.
(CHUCKLES)
You didn't see us coming?
Lost your warg?
And that baby crow
you had with you,
lost him, too?
I'll answer to Mance.
I won't answer to you.
She yours?
I'm not anybody's.
Too scrawny.
Not like those
crows at Castle Black.
Think of them
stuck in their larders,
stuffing their faces
with ham and blood sausage
and stew, getting
nice and fat and marbled.
I know we've had our
differences, Tormund,
but just one time
before you die,
you really ought
to try crow.
MAN: Draw.
Loose.
JON: Last time I saw him,
he was in the courtyard
at Winterfell.
He said, "Next time I see you,
you'll be all in black."
I was jealous of
Robb my whole life.
(GROANS)
The way my father
looked at him,
I wanted that.
He was better than
me at everything.
Fighting and hunting
and riding
and girls.
Gods, the girls loved him.
I wanted to hate him,
but I never could.
Sometimes I want
to hate you.
You're better than
me at everything.
Except reading.
(LAUGHS)
They're, um...
They're ready for you.
He's wanted to
hang me for a while.
Now's his chance.
No one's going to hang you.
You've done nothing wrong.
I've done plenty wrong.
So you admit you
murdered Qhorin Halfhand?
JON: I didn't murder him.
No?
You put your sword
through a brother
of the Night's Watch.
What do you call that?
He wanted me
to kill him.
A bastard son of a traitor.
What would you expect?
The Halfhand
believed our
only chance to
stop Mance was to get
a man inside his army.
Don't talk about the Halfhand
as if you knew him.
He was my brother.
Then you'd know
he'd do anything
to defend the Wall.
The free folk would
have boiled him alive,
but letting me kill him...
JANOS: The free folk?
Listen to him.
He even talks
like a wildling now.
Aye, I talk like a wildling.
I ate with the wildlings.
I climbed the Wall
with the wildlings. I...
I laid with
a wildling girl.
You admit to
breaking your vows, then?
I do.
The law is the law.
The boy must die.
If we beheaded every ranger
who lay with a girl,
the Wall would be
manned by headless men.
There's a difference
between sneaking off to
the Mole's Town brothel
and sleeping with the enemy.
While we sit here
debating which
rules I broke,
Mance Rayder
marches on the Wall
with an army of 100,000.
Impossible.
You can't get 50
wildlings together
before they start
killing each other.
100,000.
He's united the Thenns,
the Hornfoots,
the ice-river clans.
He has giants
fighting for him.
(LAUGHS) Giants?
Have you ever been
beyond the Wall, ser?
I commanded the City Watch
of King's Landing, boy.
And now you're here.
You must not have been
very good at your job.
How dare you?
There's a band of
wildlings south of
the Wall already,
led by Tormund Giantsbane.
I killed their warg
and three others.
They shot me
full of arrows.
Their orders are to
attack Castle Black
from the south
when Mance
hits it from the north.
The signal for
the attack will
be a bonfire.
Mance said it would
be the greatest fire
the North has ever seen.
That's the truth.
All the truth.
Do you intend to execute me,
or am I free to go?
None of us are free.
We are men of
the Night's Watch.
But we won't be taking
your head today,
Jon Snow.
Go on.
I am acting commander here,
Maester Aemon.
Yes, you are.
And I don't trust
the bastard.
He told the truth.
And you always know
when a man's telling a lie?
How did you acquire
this magical power?
I grew up in
King's Landing.
OLENNA: No.
You're a queen,
not an ox.
Your grandfather
gave me a necklace
just like this one
for my 51st nameday.
The wedding is
in a fortnight,
Grandmother.
You can't say
no to everything.
Nonsense.
My little dears,
go and speak
to the jewelers
of King's Landing.
Tell them who you are,
who sent you.
The one who brings
me the best necklace
will get to
keep the next best.
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
The Margaery Tyrell
who walks into the Sept
a fortnight from now
will inspire
a thousand songs.
How sad it will be
if she's wearing
rubbish like that.
Perhaps I should
just let Joffrey
choose it for me.
End up with a string
of dead sparrow heads
around my neck.
You watch that.
Even here, with me.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
My word.
My lady.
Please pardon me
for interrupting.
My name is
Brienne of Tarth.
We know who you are.
We've heard all about you.
But hearing is one thing.
Aren't you just marvelous!
Absolutely singular.
I hear you knocked my
grandson into the dirt,
like the silly
little boy he is.
My lady, I know this
is a very busy time
for you,
but if I could just
have a moment.
You dare not refuse.
A shadow?
With the face of
Stannis Baratheon.
I swear to you
by all the gods
it was Stannis.
He plunged his sword
through Renly's heart
and disappeared.
One day, I will
avenge our king.
Joffrey is our king now.
I meant no offense.
And you've given none.
All the Kingsguard
will be on duty.
Ser Boros will
be stationed here.
Ser Preston will
be stationed here,
beside the primary
entertainment.
Your Grace?
Huh?
One guard at the thing.
Go on.
Ser Meryn will guard
Lady Margaery and Tommen.
I've always guarded
the King himself,
my lord.
Ever since your absence.
And I thank you
for it, Ser Meryn.
All very good.
I don't expect any trouble.
The people love their King.
They know who keeps them fed.
Margaery Tyrell,
I've heard.
By my leave.
They know I saved the city.
I won the war.
The war's not won.
Not while Stannis lives.
I broke Stannis
on the Blackwater.
Pity you weren't
there to help, Uncle.
My apologies, Your Grace.
I was rather busy.
Busy getting captured.
So this is
the famous
Book of Brothers?
All the great deeds
of all the great Kingsguard.
Ser Arthur Dayne.
The Sword of the Morning.
(CHUCKLES)
Led the attack
on the Kingswood Brotherhood.
Defeated the Smiling Knight
in single combat.
Ser Duncan the Tall.
(LAUGHS)
Four pages.
He must have been
quite a man.
So they say.
Ser Jaime Lannister.
Hmm. (CHUCKLES)
Someone forgot to write down
all your great deeds.
There's still time.
Is there?
For a 40-year-old
knight with one hand?
How can you
protect me with that?
I use my left hand
now, Your Grace.
Makes for more
of a contest.
(SCOFFS)
DAENERYS: Have you
ever been to Meereen?
Several times, Your Grace,
with Master Kraznys.
And?
They say a thousand
slaves died
building the Great
Pyramid of Meereen.
And now an army
of former slaves
is marching to her gates.
You think the Great
Masters are worried?
If they're smart,
Your Grace.
You were told to ride
at the back of the train.
Yes, My Queen.
But I need to speak to you
about something important.
A matter of strategy.
Your Grace.
All right, what is
this matter of strategy?
A dusk rose.
Would you like to walk
at the back of the train
instead of riding?
And this one's
called lady's lace.
Would you like to
walk without shoes?
You have to know
a land to rule it.
Its plants, its rivers,
its roads, its people.
Dusk rose tea eases fever.
Everyone in
Meereen knows that.
Especially the slaves
who have to make the tea.
If you want
them to follow you,
you have to become
a part of their world.
Strategy.
Harpy's Gold.
No tea from this one.
Beautiful but poisonous.
You are a gambler,
aren't you?
Your Grace.
(SOLDIER SHOUTS IN VALYRIAN)
There's one on
every mile marker
between here and Meereen.
How many miles are there?
163, Your Grace.
BARRISTAN: I'll tell
our men to ride ahead
and bury them.
You don't need to see this.
You will do no such thing.
I will see each and
every one of their faces.
Remove her collar
before you bury her.
BRIENNE: There she is.
JAIME: Yes.
And?
You made a promise.
To return the Stark
girls to their mother,
who is now dead.
To keep them safe.
Arya Stark hasn't been seen
since her father was killed.
Where do you think she is?
My money's on dead.
There's a certain
safety in death,
wouldn't you say?
And Sansa Stark is
now Sansa Lannister.
Bit of a complication.
A complication
does not release
you from a vow.
What do you want me to do?
Kidnap my sister-in-law?
And take her where?
Where would she
be safer than here?
Look me in the eye
and tell me that
you think
she'll be safe
in King's Landing.
Are you sure
we're not related?
Ever since I've returned,
every Lannister I've seen
has been a miserable
pain in my ass.
Maybe you're a Lannister, too.
You've got the hair
for it, if not the looks.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(FOOTSTEPS STOP)
(GASPS)
(STAMMERING)
It's all right.
You're drunk.
Yes.
I have good reason to be.
Once I was a knight.
Now I'm only a fool.
Don't you know me?
Ser Dontos. The King's
nameday celebration.
I'm sorry.
I should have remembered.
I can't accept your apology.
I may be a fool,
but I'm a living fool,
thanks to you.
Anyone would
have done the same.
But only you did.
I can never repay you.
You gave me my life.
But this is worth
more than my life.
It belonged to my mother,
and her mother before her.
House Hollard
was strong once.
House on the rise.
That's all that's
left of those days,
thanks to a few sad,
fat drunks like me.
I can't take it.
It's very kind of you,
but I can't.
I don't have
anything else left.
That's all.
Take it. Wear it.
Let my name
have one more
moment in the sun
before it disappears
from the world.
I'll wear it with pride,
Ser Dontos.
Yeah.
(FLIES BUZZING)
ARYA: When
am I going to get
a horse of my own?
HOUND:
The little lady
wants a pony.
The little lady wants
away from your stench.
Horses aren't
easy to come by.
Even if they were,
you think I'm gonna
put you on your own horse?
Watch the only thing
of value I've got in
the world ride away?
Why don't you
have any money?
Didn't you steal
anything from Joffrey
before you left?
No.
You're not very smart,
are you?
I'm not a thief.
You're fine with
murdering little boys,
but thieving is beneath you?
A man's got
to have a code.
You think I'm gonna escape?
Where would I go?
I'd be dead by
nightfall without you.
My family's gone.
I've got no one.
You've got
an aunt in the Vale.
Your rich Aunt Lysa.
After I sell you to her,
maybe she'll have
enough left over
to buy you that
pony you want so much.
ARYA: I'm hungry.
You're hungry.
Five horses, five men.
More than I feel
like killing on
an empty stomach.
(MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
I know him.
The small one.
His name is Polliver.
He captured us and
took us to Harrenhal.
(BOTH URINATING)
He killed Lommy.
What the fuck's a Lommy?
He was my friend.
Polliver stole my sword
and put it right
through his neck.
He's still got it.
HOUND: Got what?
My sword Needle.
Needle?
Of course you
named your sword.
Lots of people
name their swords.
Lots of cunts.
(FOOTSTEPS RETREATING)
What are you...
Get back...
My brother gave me
that sword.
Get back here.
He killed my friend.
I don't care if
he ate your friend.
We're not going in there.
(MEN LAUGHING)
MAN: Come on,
give it up.
(WOMAN WHIMPERING)
MAN: Come here.
(WHIMPERING CONTINUES)
Let's have a feel, eh?
Leave it.
(WOMAN WHIMPERS)
MAN: Come here.
INNKEEPER:
Please, she's a good girl.
Shut your mouth
and pour us more ale,
and we may not
take her with us
when we're done with her.
I know you.
You're the Hound.
Pour our new friend
some ale.
What brings you
so far north?
I could ask the same of you.
What are you doing up here?
Just keeping
the King's peace.
No need. The war's over.
So I've heard.
Stannis defeated
at the Blackwater.
Robb Stark
killed at the Twins.
And where am I
for all of it?
Stuck with your brother.
Meaning no offense.
None taken.
He's good, the Mountain is.
Best at what he does.
But torture, torture.
You spend enough time
putting the hammer to people,
you start to feel
like a carpenter
making chairs.
Drains the fun
right out of it.
And what's life
without a little fun?
(POLLIVER CHUCKLES)
But I don't need to
tell you that, eh?
She's all right.
I've had better.
(LAUGHS)
You know what?
You should come with us.
His kind, they've always
got something hidden
away somewhere.
Gold, silver,
more daughters.
Always something
if you know how
to make them talk.
And there's plenty of him
between here and
King's Landing.
You could do
well for yourself.
We certainly have been.
I'm not going to
King's Landing.
Think about it.
We could do whatever we like,
wherever we go.
These are the
King's colors.
No one's standing
in his way now.
Which means no one's
standing in ours.
(MEN LAUGHING)
Fuck the King.
(LAUGHING STOPS)
When I heard that
Joffrey's dog had
tucked tail
and run from
the Battle of
the Blackwater,
I didn't believe it.
But here you are.
Here I am.
Bring me one of
those chickens.
You got money
to pay for it?
You paid for it?
(LAUGHS) No.
But we're the King's men.
So, you got money?
Not a penny.
I'll still take
that chicken.
Tell you what.
We'll trade you.
One of our little chickens
for one of yours.
Give us a go
at your friend.
Lowell there likes
them a bit broken in.
(MEN CHUCKLE)
You're a talker.
Listening makes me thirsty.
(SIGHS)
And hungry.
Think I'll take
two chickens.
You don't understand
the situation.
I understand that
if anymore words
come pouring out
your cunt mouth,
I'm gonna have to eat
every fucking chicken
in this room.
You lived your
life for the King.
You're gonna die
for some chickens?
Someone is.
(HOUND GRUNTS)
(MAN SHOUTING)
(WOMAN WHIMPERING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(MEN GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
Something wrong
with your leg, boy?
(STAMMERING)
What do you mean?
Can you walk?
I've got to carry you?
Carry me?
Fine little blade.
Maybe I'll pick
my teeth with it.
(GASPS)
(GURGLING)