JAIME: I made
a deal for you,
to keep your ungrateful
head on your neck
a little while longer.
TYRION: I'm sorry,
what am I grateful for?
The opportunity to
live and die at the Wall
as punishment
for a crime
I did not commit?
You threw your life away.
It's not a joke.
You understand that,
don't you?
Of course it's a joke,
just not a very funny one.
I couldn't listen
to her standing there,
telling her lies.
I couldn't do it.
You fell in love
with a whore.
Yes.
And I was stupid
enough to think
that she had fallen
in love with me.
That deal you made,
it was everything
Father wanted.
You do see that?
He gets you back
as his heir.
The future
Lord of the Rock.
And he ships me off
to Castle Black,
out of sight at last.
All so perfect.
It felt good to take
that from him.
He knows I'm innocent
and he's willing to
sacrifice me anyway.
He's willing to
sacrifice any of us.
Not you.
You're the golden son.
You could kill a king,
lose a hand,
fuck your own sister,
you'll always be
the golden son.
Careful.
I'm the last
friend you've got.
At least I got to tell
them what they really are.
Yes, brilliant speech.
They'll be talking
about it
for days to come.
I thought you
were a realist.
Didn't realize
you'd die for pride.
Don't give up
on me just yet.
I survived one
trial by combat,
even though you weren't
there to save me.
I can't save you
this time either.
My training has proved
that I can't beat a
stable boy with my left hand.
Where's your
sense of adventure?
Even if you lose,
imagine the look
on Father's face
when you fall.
(CHUCKLES)
Our family name snuffed
out with a single
swing of the sword.
It is tempting.
(LAUGHS)
Well...
Bronn fought for me once,
he'll do it again.
If he wins,
I expect I'll be
in his debt for
the rest of my life.
If he wins.
Will you find him for me?
Who does Cersei plan
on naming as a champion?
I hope it's
Ser Meryn Trant.
I'd enjoy watching Bronn
disembowel that
pompous child beater.
No.
Not Ser Meryn.
(SHOUTING)
(GASPING)
GUARD: Go on, move it.
And you.
Come on.
(SHOUTING)
Mercy.
Please.
Please, mercy.
(GRUNTING)
(SHOUTS)
CERSEI: Ser Gregor.
Welcome to the capital.
Thank you for riding
here so quickly.
You seem to be
in good form.
Who am I fighting?
Does it matter?
Could be food.
Could be soldiers.
(MAN GROANING)
You shouldn't be
sitting out here
like this.
Where else to sit?
Tried to walk
back to me hut,
hurt too much.
Then I remembered
they burned me hut down.
Who were "they"?
I stopped asking
a while ago.
That's not going
to get better.
Doesn't seem so.
A bad way to go.
Haven't you had enough?
Of what?
I know.
Time to go.
Take matters
into me own hands.
(GROANS)
The thought has
occurred to me.
So why go on?
Habit.
Nothing could be
worse than this.
Maybe nothing is
Nothing isn't better
or worse than anything.
Nothing is just nothing.
Who are you?
My name is Arya.
Arya Stark.
You her father?
Her captor.
Bringing her to
her aunt for ransom.
A fair exchange,
that is.
Always held to the notion
of fair exchange
in all my dealings.
You give me, I give you.
Fair.
A balance.
No balance anymore.
(GROANS)
Could I have a drink?
Dying is thirsty work.
Wish it were wine.
So do I.
(GRUNTS)
That's where the heart is.
That's how you kill a man.
(GRUNTING)
(NECK SNAPS)
(GROANING)
The fuck you doing?
There's a price
on your head.
Guess that's what
the king does when
you tell him to fuck off.
The king's dead.
He drank poisoned wine
at his own wedding.
The bounty on you
is for killing
Lannister soldiers.
A hundred silver stags.
And you thought
you were going
to collect it?
Didn't think
very hard, did you?
You were Yoren's
prisoners when he was
taking me to the Wall.
He told me he'd fuck
me bloody with a stick.
This day's really
not working out
the way you planned.
He on your little list?
He can't be.
I don't know his name.
What's your name?
Rorge.
Thank you.
(GASPS)
You're learning.
(HORN BLOWING)
MAN: Rangers returning!
(HAMMERING METAL)
MAN: They return!
Rangers returning!
Greetings.
MAN: Didn't think
I'd see you again.
All right, Jon?
Welcome back, brother.
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
Lord Snow.
(GHOST GROWLS SOFTLY)
This is no place
for wild beasts.
Lock him away,
or I'll let Hobb throw
him in tonight's stew.
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
Come on, Ghost.
Mance's army was closing
in on Craster's Keep
when we left.
We saw their campfires
from Osric's Hill.
They'll reach the Wall
before the next full moon.
I'm surprised you
didn't ride over
and say hello.
The King-beyond-the-Wall
is your old friend, isn't he?
We need to prepare.
We've been preparing.
We should
seal the tunnel.
(MEN MURMURING)
Plug it with rocks and ice.
Flood it and let it freeze.
ALLISER: And how
would we range north?
We wouldn't.
MAN: Coward!
You would cut off our legs,
pluck out our eyes,
leave us cowering
behind the Wall hoping
for the storm to pass?
We can't defend the gate
against 100,000 men.
This castle has stood
for thousands of years.
The Night's Watch
has defended her
for thousands of years.
And in all those
centuries, we have
never sealed the tunnel.
Have you ever seen
a giant, Ser Alliser?
I have.
The tunnel's gate
won't stop them.
The bars on those gates
are four inches thick.
Cold-rolled steel.
And they won't stop them.
Remind me which
order you belong to,
Lord Snow.
The stewards.
Are the stewards
responsible for
maintaining the tunnel?
No.
Who would that be?
The builders.
Ah, the builders.
First Builder Yarwyck,
Lord Snow here
recommends
sealing the tunnel,
leaving us unable to
carry out our duties
as sworn brothers
of the Night's Watch.
Do you agree with him?
No.
ALLISER: Given
your deep knowledge
of the wildling
army, Lord Snow,
you and Tarly will
take night duties
atop the Wall
until the full moon.
(MEN LAUGHING)
Moving on.
First Builder, we'll need
100 barrels of pitch
brought atop the Wall.
YARWYCK: Aye.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
My lord.
You have new clothes.
Do you like 'em? Eh?
Gloves are doeskin.
Softer than
a virgin's thighs.
I sent for you days ago.
I've been a bit busy.
Doing what?
My lonesome
bachelor days are over.
I'm to wed
Lollys Stokeworth.
Lollys Stokeworth?
She doesn't strike me
as your sort of girl.
I wouldn't say I had
a single sort of girl.
She's dim-witted.
If I wanted wits,
I'd marry you.
When my sister arranged
this love match,
did she mention
that Lollys has
an older sister?
Falyse.
Aye, I did know.
And you understand the
rules of inheritance?
Falyse is 40 and barren.
She still gets
Castle Stokeworth
when her father dies.
She does.
Unless she
happens to perish
before her father.
Then Lollys
gets the castle.
What? Ladies fall
from their horses
and snap their
pretty necks
all the time.
You and my sister
deserve each other.
Why did you bother
to come here?
You once said if
anyone ever asked me
to sell you out, you'd
double their price.
Is it two wives you
want or two castles?
One of each will do.
But if you want me
to kill the Mountain
for you,
it'd better be
a damn big castle.
I'm a bit short on
castles at the moment.
But I can offer you
gold and gratitude.
I have gold.
What can I buy
with gratitude?
You might be surprised.
A Lannister always
pays his debts.
Your sister's
a Lannister, too.
My wife is heir
to Winterfell.
If I emerge from this
with my head still
on my shoulders,
I may one day rule
the North in her name.
I could carve you out
a big piece of it.
If and may and could.
It's bloody cold up north.
Lollys is soft and warm.
And close.
If I gave you the choice
between fucking Lollys
and fighting the Mountain,
you'd have your britches
down and your cock out
before I could blink.
Does he frighten
you so much?
I'd be a bloody fool if
he didn't frighten me.
He's freakish
big and strong.
And quicker than
you'd expect for
a man of that size.
Maybe I could take him,
dance around
until he's so tired
of hacking at me,
he dropped his sword,
get him off
his feet somehow.
But one misstep
and I'm dead.
Why should I risk it?
Because you're my friend.
Aye, I'm your friend.
And when have you
ever risked your life
for me?
I like you,
pampered little
shit that you are.
I just like
myself more.
I understand.
I'm sorry it has
to be this way.
Why are you sorry?
Because you're an evil
bastard with no
conscience and no heart?
That's what I liked about
you in the first place.
We had some
good days together.
Yes, we did.
(BANGS ON DOOR)
What will you do?
I suppose
I'll have to kill
the Mountain myself.
Won't that make
for a great song?
I hope to hear them
sing it one day.
(BIRD SCREECHING)
How did you get in here?
Your door is well guarded,
but your window is not.
I swam to an island
a mile offshore
for these.
Don't do that again.
Never met a woman
who didn't like
wildflowers.
These are my
private quarters.
If I want you here,
I will summon you.
Forgive me, my queen.
I live to serve you.
Tell me why you're here.
I came to ask a favor.
I only have two
talents in this world.
War and women.
You are staying here
in Meereen to rule.
That is a wise decision.
I respect it.
But here in Meereen,
I cannot pursue
my talents.
I've ordered
the Second Sons
to patrol the streets to
stop the revenge killings.
You've ordered us
to be night watchmen.
And as for women,
there are thousands
in Meereen
you can pursue.
There is only one,
and she does
not want me.
You swore me your sword.
My sword is yours
till the day I die.
So if I command you
to stay in Meereen
and patrol the streets?
I'll stay in Meereen
and patrol the streets.
Send me to kill
your enemies.
Any enemy anywhere.
Let me do what I do best.
Very well.
Do what you do best.
Take off your clothes.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
Oh.
Come in, my queen. Please.
I didn't mean to
disturb you, my lady.
You could never.
I just wanted to speak
with you before we left.
Could you bring me
that vial over there?
The blue one.
No, not that one.
You don't even want
to touch that one.
Next to it.
That's the one.
(INHALES)
When I looked into
the flames this morning,
the Lord spoke to me.
He said,
"Tonight, you will have
your last good bath
in a long while.
"Make it count."
A joke.
(CHUCKLES LIGHTLY)
Not a very good one,
I'm afraid.
It was. I...
Humor isn't my strength.
That's because
most jokes are lies
and you're devoted
to the truth.
If they're lies,
my lady, aren't
they best avoided?
Not always.
Most of these
powders and potions
are lies.
Deceptions to make men
think they witnessed
our Lord's power.
Once they step into
his light, they will see
the lie for what it was,
a trick that led
them to the truth.
A pinch of this
powder in a bonfire
will send a flaming column
screaming towards the sky.
And this one
creates a black smoke
that will make
the bravest man
piss himself with fear.
And a drop of this
in any man's wine will
drive him wild with lust.
Did you use it
with Stannis?
No.
Don't be upset.
Men never crave what
they already have.
It's only flesh.
It needs what it needs.
No act done in
service of the Lord can
ever be called a sin.
I thank God every day
for bringing you to us.
And Stannis to you.
He wants to bring
Shireen with us.
I think that would
be ill-advised.
My daughter has
heretical tendencies,
as you're well aware.
I don't know if her
doubt is real or simply
meant to spite me,
but whichever the case,
she should stay home.
I understand
how you feel.
But that is impossible.
Why?
You don't need
powders and potions,
my queen.
You don't need lies.
You are strong
enough to look into
the Lord's light
and see his truth
for yourself.
However harsh it is.
However hard for
us to understand.
You don't need my help,
but I will need yours soon.
When we set sail,
your daughter
must be with us.
The Lord needs her.
Jorah the Andal.
Are you here
to see our queen?
She's in a good mood.
Khaleesi.
You're here early.
Later than some.
You don't approve?
It's not
a question of approval,
it's a question
of trust.
You neither
approve nor trust.
Why would I?
The man's
a sellsword.
Didn't you fight for
the Golden Company
before pledging your
sword to my brother?
I did.
I trust you.
Daario Naharis
killed his captains
and dumped their
heads at your feet
when he grew tired
of their commands.
How could you
ever have faith
in a man like that?
I could never have
faith in a man
like Daario.
That's why I've sent
him and the Second Sons
to retake Yunkai.
You have?
I have.
Without you there
to rule, Khaleesi,
I fear the masters will
simply bide their time,
wait for the invaders
to leave and
reassert control.
That is why
I've ordered Daario
to execute every
master in Yunkai.
The masters tear babies
from their mothers' arms.
They mutilate little
boys by the thousands.
They train little girls
in the art of
pleasuring old men.
They treat men
like beasts,
as you said yourself.
Herding the masters
into pens and slaughtering
them by the thousands
is also treating
men like beasts.
The slaves you freed,
brutality is all
they've ever known.
If you want them to
know something else,
you'll have to
show it to them.
And repay the slavers
with what? Kindness?
A fine? A stern warning?
It's tempting to see
your enemies as evil,
all of them,
but there's good and evil
on both sides in
every war ever fought.
Let the priests argue
over good and evil.
Slavery is real.
I can end it.
I will end it,
and those behind it.
I sold men into
slavery, Khaleesi.
And now you are helping me
show them to freedom.
I wouldn't be here
to help you if Ned Stark
had done to me
what you want to do to
the masters of Yunkai.
The man who came
to me the other day
about burying his father.
Hizdahr zo Loraq?
He will accompany
the Second Sons
and serve as my
ambassador to Yunkai.
He will tell the masters
what has happened
in Meereen.
He will explain
the choice they
have before them.
They can live in my new
world or they can die
in their old one.
Well, go and catch
Daario before he leaves.
Tell him I
changed my mind.
Yes, Khaleesi.
No.
Tell him you
changed my mind.
HOUND: (GRUNTS) Rat cunts.
Fucking whore.
You're doing it wrong.
You need to burn away
that horrible bit there.
Otherwise it's gonna
get infected and fester.
I know you don't
like fire, but if you
don't do it right...
No fire.
It'll only take a second.
It won't hurt that much.
No fire!
Shut up about it.
About everything.
Thanks to you,
I'm a walking
bag of silver
anywhere the Lannisters
hold sway.
Which is everywhere
between where we are now
and where we're going.
I'm as stupid as that hog
you stuck back
in the village,
getting myself cut
and stabbed and bitten.
No reward is worth
this much trouble.
Wish I'd never
laid eyes on you.
You say your brother
gave you that sword.
My brother gave me this.
It was just like you
said a while back.
Pressed me to the fire
like I was a nice
juicy mutton chop.
Why?
Thought I stole
one of his toys.
I didn't steal it.
I was just
playing with it.
The pain was bad.
The smell was worse.
But the worst thing
was that it was
my brother who did it.
My father,
who protected him,
told everyone my
bedding caught fire.
You think you're
on your own?
Let me wash it out
and help you sew
it up at least.
BRIENNE: Bit of comfort
never hurt anyone.
We've been sleeping
in ditches
the last few weeks.
I think we can treat
ourselves to a featherbed
for the night
and a hot meal
not cooked by you.
Couldn't agree
more, my lady.
Just don't start
expecting
silk underclothes.
Not working for your
former lord any longer.
Yes, my lady.
Don't get drunk.
No, my lady.
HOT PIE: Can I
get you anything else?
No, this will do
nicely, thank you.
Kidney pie is wonderful.
Thanks.
I do my best.
A good kidney pie
is all about
the ingredients.
Flour, lard,
water, eggs, milk.
Easy enough. But the meat,
peacetime or not,
getting your hands on
a good bottom round steak
and calves' kidneys
is not easy.
I mean,
some people settle for
plain old beef kidneys.
Got no right to
cook anything, them.
Oh, and the gravy.
Don't get me started
on the gravy.
Very difficult
to get right.
See, a lot of people
give up on the gravy.
You cannot give up.
No gravy, no pie.
Simple as that.
That's nice armor.
Are you a knight?
No.
Oh, it's just
people with armor
are usually knights.
Generally speaking.
From King's Landing,
though, aren't you?
From there myself originally.
Flea Bottom born and bred.
What brings you
to these parts?
We're looking for someone.
Someone in particular?
Maybe they came in here.
A lot of people come
in here. Just the other
day we had 17...
A girl, tall, red hair,
very pretty.
Her name is Sansa Stark,
but she may be using
a different name.
Starks?
What, like them lot
from "Winterhell"?
No, ain't seen
anyone like that.
I heard they was
all traitors.
Don't need no
traitors in here.
I pledged my life
to their mother
Catelyn Stark.
I swore to her I'd bring
her daughters home.
Sure I can't get you
a bit more kidney pie?
What?
It's nothing, my lady.
You wouldn't be screwing
your face up like that
if it was nothing.
Don't want to offend,
my lady. Truly, I don't.
You're not interesting
enough to be offensive.
The Lannisters
want Lady Sansa.
The Lannisters have money.
People kill for money.
I don't think we should
be telling people
we're searching
for Lady Sansa.
My lady. My lord.
Could I have a word?
What about?
Not kidney pie.
You seem like
a proper lady.
Someone who could be trusted.
I never met
no Sansa Stark.
But I know her sister.
Arya.
No one's seen Arya Stark
since her father
was beheaded.
She's presumed dead.
She weren't when I
last spoke to her.
When was that?
Heading up north
with the Night's Watch.
She was all
dressed up as a boy.
Like your ladyship,
only without the armor.
Going by the name Arry.
So what
happened to her?
Well...
The quick version.
The Lannisters
took us prisoner.
We escaped.
The Brotherhood
took us prisoner.
They sold me to the innkeep.
They were gonna sell
Arya to her mother
at Riverrun along
with another prisoner.
Big ugly fellow.
Foul mouth and a face
like a half-burnt ham.
Not friendly.
The Hound.
That's the one.
If you find her,
could you give her this?
She liked the last
one I gave her,
but, well, this one
turned out better.
Um...
You were saying?
BRIENNE:
Her mother's dead,
grandfather's dead,
Walder Frey is the new
lord of Riverrun.
The Brotherhood isn't
going to Riverrun.
They'll take her to
the Eyrie, my lady.
Why the Eyrie?
Her aunt, Lysa Arryn.
Catelyn Stark's sister.
She's Arya's last
living relative
with money.
She hates
the Lannisters.
Lord Tyrion made sure
I knew which
house married which
and who hated who.
BRIENNE: Sansa
could be there, too.
PODRICK: Could be.
You sure about this?
No.
(DOOR OPENS)
I imagined you'd be
back at the brothel
at this hour.
I did spend some time with
an absolutely stunning
blonde the other day.
Mmm. Do tell.
I've got every kind
of filth down here
except the kind I like.
Your sister.
Oh.
Cersei approached me.
We spoke a great deal
about her daughter.
How worried your
sister is about her.
She was trying
very hard to pretend
she had not come to
sway me against you.
I think she may have
even believed it herself.
Making honest feelings
do dishonest work
is one of her many gifts.
It was difficult for her
to hide her true intentions.
It is rare to
meet a Lannister
who shares my enthusiasm
for dead Lannisters.
She desperately wants
to see you killed.
She didn't need
to bother you.
It looks as though
I've taken care
of that myself.
The joy she will feel
when my head
leaves my neck.
She's wanted this
for a long time.
Yes, I know.
We met, you and I.
Many years ago.
I think I would have
remembered that.
Unlikely.
You had just been born.
Our father brought
me and my sister Elia
with him on a visit
to Casterly Rock.
My first time
away from Dorne.
I didn't like anything
about the Rock.
Not the food,
not the weather,
not your accents.
Nothing.
But the biggest
disappointment,
you.
You and my family
have more in common
than you might admit.
The whole way from Dorne
all anyone talked about was
the monster
that had been born
to Tywin Lannister.
A head twice the
size of his body,
a tail between his legs,
claws, one red eye,
the privates of both
a girl and a boy.
That would have made
things so much easier.
When we met your sister,
she promised she
would show you to us.
Every day we would ask.
Every day she
would say, "Soon."
Then she and your brother
took us to your
nursery and...
...she unveiled the freak.
Your head was a bit large,
your arms and legs
were a bit small,
but no claw.
No red eye. No tail
between your legs.
Just a tiny pink cock.
We didn't try to hide
our disappointment.
"That's not a monster,"
I told Cersei.
"That's just a baby."
And she said,
"He killed my mother."
And she pinched your
little cock so hard,
I thought she
might pull it off.
Until your brother
made her stop.
"It doesn't matter,"
she told us.
"Everyone says
he will die soon.
"I hope they are right.
"He should not have
lived this long."
Well, (SNIFFLES)
sooner or later,
Cersei always gets
what she wants.
And what about
what I want?
Justice
for my sister
and her children.
If you want justice,
you've come to
the wrong place.
I disagree.
I've come to
the perfect place.
I want to bring those
who have wronged
me to justice.
And all those
who have wronged me
are right here.
I will begin with
Ser Gregor Clegane,
who killed my
sister's children
and then raped her
with their blood
still on his hands
before killing her, too.
I will be your champion.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Hello, Robin.
What are you doing?
I'm building my home,
Winterfell.
At least I think I am.
I haven't been back
there in a very long time.
Why did you leave?
It's a long story.
I stay here
in the Eyrie.
Mother says it's dangerous
on the roads and I have
to keep myself safe
because I'm
the Lord of the Vale
and a very
important person.
Yes, you certainly are.
When will you go back?
Probably never.
My family doesn't
live there anymore and
someone burned it down.
Oh.
Does Winterfell
have a Moon Door?
No, I'm afraid not.
It's not high up
in the mountains.
It's down on the ground.
That sounds dangerous.
(CHUCKLES)
How do you
make people fly?
We don't.
What do you do with
all the bad people
and the scary people
and the people
you don't like?
I never did anything
with them at all.
Girls didn't
take part in that
where I came from.
Well, I'm Lord of the Vale.
When I grow up,
I'll be able to fly
anybody who bothers me.
Or you.
When we get married,
you can tell me if you
don't like somebody
and then we can
bring them back here
and, whoosh!
Right through
the Moon Door.
I like the sound of that.
Let's put a Moon Door
in your Winterfell.
All right.
It can go in here
in this big tower.
Be careful.
You've ruined it.
Now I'm going to have to
rebuild the whole thing.
I didn't ruin it.
You did.
It was already ruined
because it didn't
have a Moon Door.
I was fixing it.
Knocking things down
isn't fixing them.
It's ruining them.
I didn't ruin it!
You're being stupid.
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(GASPS)
(SOBBING)
Robin, I'm sorry, I...
LITTLEFINGER: Children.
I hit him.
Yes, I saw.
I shouldn't have done that.
No.
His mother should have,
a long time ago.
Consider it a step in
the right direction.
If he tells Aunt Lysa...
Let me worry
about Aunt Lysa.
I was trying to remember
what everything looked like.
I'll never see it again.
A lot can happen
between now and never.
If you want to
build a better home,
first you must
demolish the old one.
Why did you really
kill Joffrey?
Tell me why.
I loved your mother more
than you could ever know.
Given the opportunity,
what do we do to
those who've hurt
the ones we love?
In a better world,
one where love
could overcome
strength and duty,
you might have
been my child.
But we don't live
in that world.
You're more beautiful
than she ever was.
Lord Baelish...
Call me Petyr.
(WIND WHISTLING)
You wanted to see
me, Aunt Lysa?
Come here, Sansa.
Do you know how
far the fall is?
No.
Neither do I, precisely.
Hundreds of feet.
It's fascinating
what happens to bodies
when they hit the rocks
from such a height.
The impact breaks
them right apart.
Like eggs dropped
on the floor.
Sometimes pieces
remain intact.
You'll find the head
sitting on its own.
Every hair in place.
Blue eyes staring
at nothing.
I know what you did.
I'm so sorry,
Aunt Lysa.
I never should
have hit Robin.
I promise it won't happen...
Don't be coy with me,
you little whore.
You kissed Petyr.
I didn't.
You don't understand.
I saw you.
You can't lie to me
because I saw it
with my own eyes.
He kissed me.
I pulled away.
Liar! Whore!
(WHIMPERING)
He is mine!
My father, my husband,
my sister,
they all stood between us
and now they're all dead.
That's what happens
to people who stand
between Petyr and me.
Look down!
LITTLEFINGER: Lysa!
Let her go.
You want her?
This empty-headed child?
Let her go.
She's just like her mother.
She'll never love you.
I lied for you.
I killed for you.
Why did you
bring her here?
I'll send her away.
I swear on my life.
I swear to all the gods.
Let her go, Lysa.
(SOBBING)
(SANSA WHIMPERING)
Oh, my sweet wife.
My sweet, silly wife.
(LYSA SOBBING)
I have only
loved one woman,
only one,
my entire life.
Your sister.
(SCREAMING)