(WIND WHOOSHING)
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
What was she like?
She had red hair.
Oh?
How big were her feet?
What do you want me to say?
I want you to tell me
what it was like
to have someone.
To be with someone.
To love someone
and have them love you back.
We're all gonna die
a lot sooner
than I'd planned.
You're the closest
I'll ever get to knowing.
So you and Gilly never?
No. She just had a baby.
And she never offered.
But if she had,
you would have?
You'd have broken
your vows?
The interesting thing is,
our vows never specifically
forbid intimate relations
with women.
What?
"I shall take no wife."
Yes, that's in there.
There's no denying that.
"I shall father no children."
It's very specific.
But what our vows
have to say about
other activities
is open to interpretation.
I don't think Ser Alliser
cares much for
interpretation.
Anyway, there's
nothing for him
to interpret.
We didn't.
So what's it like?
It's...
There's this
whole other person.
And you're wrapped up in them,
and they're wrapped up in you.
And you...
For a little while,
you're more than just you.
You're...
Well, I don't know.
I'm not a bleeding poet.
No, you're really not.
What did I get for it?
An arrow six inches
from my heart.
There'll be arrows
for all of us soon.
There will.
They've already done
the worst thing to me
they could ever do.
Go get some sleep, Sam.
I'll take this watch.
(SCREECHES)
Did I ever tell
you about her?
Sheila?
Yes.
That was a night
to remember.
Of course,
I'd had a good
bit to drink.
(CHUCKLES)
Her fangs were sharp,
but she knew how
to use them.
And she was nice
and soft down below.
No, she was no
ordinary beast.
Many is the man who...
I know you never
fucked a bear.
You know you never
Right now,
I don't want to think about
the bear you never fucked.
Right now,
all I want to
think about is
each one of these arrows
finding its way
into a crow's heart.
We could be
waiting here a while.
Good.
The longer we wait,
the more arrows I'll have.
(OWL SCREECHING)
They came up here
to our land
and put up a big wall
and said it was theirs.
Then they started
hunting us down.
But this time,
we're the ones
doing the hunting.
You've got a lot to
say about killing.
Even more words
than arrows.
Back in those villages,
I killed just as
many of them as you did.
More, I reckon.
Yes, but none of those
were your crow lover.
I probably killed
him already.
STYR: So you've said.
And if not,
the only thing left
of him is gonna be
his fun bits
hanging around me neck.
STYR: More words.
Know what I think you
do when you see him?
Serve him up
a nice juicy
slice of ginger minge.
(MEN LAUGHING)
What,
you've been thinking about
that ginger minge?
Wondering what
it tastes like?
Maybe I have.
Jon Snow is mine.
Anyone else tries
to kill him,
I'll have an arrow
for them.
And not one of
your bald friends
is fast enough to stop me.
And what is it
that couldn't wait
until morning, Tarly?
Maester Aemon.
How did you know...
That it was you?
Who else but
Samwell Tarly
would be wasting candles
to read in the middle
of the night?
Let me help you.
Oh, no need.
I know my way
around this library
better than any other
place in Castle Black.
Thousands of books
and no eyes to read them.
Old age is
a wonderful source
of ironies,
if nothing else.
But you didn't
answer my question.
What are you reading?
Maester Faull.
Ah.
The wildlings.
I can assure you that
the closest Maester Faull
ever got to a wildling
was this very library.
But what he says
about what they do,
it's all true.
It's exactly what
the survivors of
their raids report.
Yes, imagine the stories
wildlings tell about us.
Love is the death of duty.
I told that to your
friend Jon Snow once.
He didn't listen,
and neither did you.
Which is why you've abandoned
your watch atop the Wall
to come here and read
about the terrible things
that may have happened
to the girl you love.
I don't love her.
Yes, you do.
No.
Heard it in your voice
when you first
brought her to me.
I remember how it sounds.
I was in love once.
You were?
You can imagine
all manner of horrors
befalling that poor
girl and her child.
Is it so difficult
to imagine that
an old person was once,
more or less, like you?
I'm sorry, Maester.
I didn't mean it
like that.
Do you know who I
was before I came here?
What I could have been
if I'd only said the word?
Of course you do.
I met many girls
when I was Aemon Targaryen.
A future king always does.
Some of them
were quite forward
in their attempts
to win my affections.
One of them succeeded.
I was very young.
Who was she?
Ah.
I could tell you
everything about her.
Who she was, how we met,
the color of her eyes
and the shape of her nose.
I can see her
right in front of me.
She's more real
than you are.
We could spend all night
trading tales of lost loves.
Nothing makes the past
a sweeter place to visit
than the prospect
of imminent death.
Go to bed, Tarly.
PYP: I'm sorry,
I can't open the gate
for nobody. Orders.
GILLY: You don't understand.
They killed everyone.
Everyone but my baby.
And they're out there.
I saw them on my way here.
They may have seen me.
They may have followed me.
Please.
PYP: I'm sorry, I can't.
GILLY:
If they find us out here,
you don't know
what they'll do.
Pyp! Open the gate.
I can't.
Sam, is that you?
Yes.
Thorne gave me strict orders
to not open the gate.
Oh, Pyp,
open the fucking gate!
I never heard
you curse before.
Yes, well,
best get used to it.
(GILLY PANTING)
Are you all right?
(BABY COOING)
You're all right, yeah.
Of course you are,
my brave little fella.
It was horrible.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't know
until I got back.
Don't let them
send me away, Sam.
Never.
I know there's
no women allowed.
Anyone who tries
to throw you out
will be having words with me.
From now on,
wherever you go, I go, too.
(HORN BLOWING)
MAN 1: Get ready!
MAN 2: Man the gate!
MAN 1: Ready yourselves!
MAN 3: Make haste! Prepare!
MAN 1: Up on the Wall!
Quickly! Up!
MAN 3: How many are there?
(HORN BLOWING)
(SCREECHES)
Beyond the trees!
It's time.
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(HORN BLOWING)
Light them up!
Light them all!
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(HORN CONTINUES BLOWING)
Move!
Pick up the pace!
Come on!
(GRUNTING)
Here we go, boys.
There's one.
There's two.
Come on,
let's get the next load.
That's the last of the oil,
Ser Alliser.
100,000 you say?
Yes, ser.
You can say it
if you like.
We should have
sealed the tunnel
while we had the chance,
like you suggested.
It was a difficult
decision either way, ser.
Do you know what
leadership means,
Lord Snow?
It means that
the person in charge
gets second-guessed by
every clever little
twat with a mouth.
But if he starts
second-guessing himself,
that's the end
for him,
for the clever little twats,
for everyone.
This is not the end.
Not for us.
Not if you lot
do your duty for
however long it
takes to beat them back.
And then you get
to go on hating me,
and I get to go on wishing
your wildling whore
had finished the job.
(HORN BLOWING)
SAMWELL:
You'll be safe down here.
I'll check on you
as soon as I can.
You're leaving me again?
I'm not leaving you.
You're going up there
and we're staying down here.
That's leaving.
You said from now on
we'd stay together.
I didn't mean
in the same room.
What are you
going to do out there?
Help my brothers.
How?
You're going to
fight the free folk
when they come?
They'll kill you.
In Mole's Town,
they killed everyone.
I can't just
hide here with you
while they're
fighting out there.
Why not?
You won't matter up there.
You will down here.
I am a man of
the Night's Watch, Gilly.
I made a promise
to defend the Wall,
and I have to keep it,
because that's what men do.
Promise me you won't die.
I promise you I won't die.
(LOCK CLICKS)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(MEN SHOUTING)
There's a lot more wildlings
on the other side of
the Wall than this side.
We've got loads of
weapons and things.
It's the perfect
place for us to be.
I've never
thrown a spear before.
I've never held
a sword with a proper edge.
This is no place
for me to be.
You're not afraid?
Of course I'm afraid.
There's a band of
wildlings coming to kill us.
If you're afraid of
a band of wildlings,
how in seven hells
did you manage to
kill a White Walker?
I didn't know I
was going to kill it.
But I had to do something.
I didn't have any choice.
It was going to kill
Gilly and take the baby.
If someone had asked
me my name right then,
I wouldn't have known.
I wasn't
Samwell Tarly anymore.
I wasn't a steward
in the Night's Watch,
or son of Randyll Tarly,
or any of that.
I was nothing at all.
And when you're
nothing at all,
there's no more
reason to be afraid.
But you're afraid now?
Yes, well,
I'm not nothing anymore.
YGRITTE:
Most of their men are up top.
Didn't count more than
20 down here. Leftovers.
They got a big fat one
and a little bony
one manning the front.
How high are the walls?
Well, we'll be up and over
before they know
what's happened.
STYR: Let's kill some crows!
(WILDLINGS CHEERING)
Come on!
(WILDLINGS YELLING)
(HORN BLOWING)
MAN: Come on, brothers!
(SHOUTING)
(BELLOWING)
(INAUDIBLE)
(SHOUTING)
Archers, nock.
Everyone else, hold.
Grenn, no!
(BARREL CRASHES)
I said nock and hold,
you cunts!
Does nock mean draw?
MEN: No, ser!
Does fucking hold
mean fucking drop?
MEN: No, ser!
You all plan to
die here tonight?
MEN: No, ser!
That's very good to hear.
Draw!
(HORN BLOWS)
No, down below!
(WILDLINGS SHOUTING)
(BOW STRINGS TWANGING)
ALLISER: Draw! Light them up.
(SCREAMS)
TORMUND: Come on, get up!
They're attacking
the southern gate!
ALLISER: Now?
JANOS: Now.
I'm going down there.
Brother Slynt,
you have the Wall.
What?
What are you fucking
waiting for? Loose!
You heard the man. Loose!
(SHOUTING)
(ALL YELLING)
(GROANS)
You, over there.
Did you get one?
No.
Shit, Pyp!
Shit.
Sam.
Yeah?
I think we're gonna die.
(GROANS)
If you keep missing,
we will.
(SCREAMS)
Come on!
Brothers!
A hundred generations
have defended this castle.
She's never fallen before.
She will not fall tonight.
Those are Thenns at our walls.
They eat the flesh
of the men they kill.
Do you want to fill the belly
of a Thenn tonight?
MEN: No!
Tonight we fight.
And when the sun rises,
I promise you,
Castle Black will stand!
(CHEERING)
The Night's Watch will stand!
MEN: Yes!
With me now! Now with me!
(MEN YELLING)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(BELLOWING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
No discipline. No training.
Gang of thieves,
that's all this is.
I commanded the City Watch
of King's Landing.
Those men obeyed orders.
We can't just let
them attack the gate.
The bars of those gates are
four inches of
cold-rolled steel.
Those are giants
riding mammoths down there!
Do you think your
cold-rolled steel
is gonna stop them?
No such thing as giants.
A story for the children.
Brother Slynt.
We just got word
that Ser Alliser
needs you below.
You're the most
experienced man
he's got, ser,
and he needs you.
Needed below?
Yes.
Archers, nock your arrows!
MAN: Nock arrows!
Draw!
Loose!
They won't summit
before dawn.
How do you know that?
Because I've made that climb.
I think they're in
a bigger hurry than you were.
MAN: Hold the bridge!
Hold, wait for it!
Come on with the rocks!
Nock!
Draw!
Loose!
(SCREAMS)
Down!
(GRUNTING)
(LAUGHS)
(SCREAMING) No!
To the gate.
Come on, let's move.
Come on, up there!
It's gonna open.
(GRUNTS)
I got one right through
the heart. He's dead.
Oh.
Is it over?
No.
Well, then...
(GASPS)
You're all right.
(GURGLING)
I'll get help.
(SHUSHING)
Maester Aemon is coming.
He's gonna make it all right.
(SHUSHING)
Now.
Now!
(WHISTLES)
(BELLOWS)
(BELLOWING)
(GATE CREAKING)
The outer gate won't hold.
Take five men,
hold the inner gate.
Aye.
Hold the gate.
If they make it through...
They won't.
Come on, Hill.
And you, Cooper.
You three, on me!
(HORN BLOWING)
Come on, you lazy bastards!
Oil.
Oil on the ramp!
Protect the gate!
(YELLS)
(GROANS)
Get him inside.
Hold that fucking gate!
Hold it!
We need more men down here.
We have to hold the gate.
But we need men here.
Tell Jon. He's in command.
Let's go.
Get me to the top!
You hear me?
Your name's Olly, right?
Listen to me, Olly.
Get me to the top.
And when we give the signal,
bring us back down.
You hear me?
Find a weapon, Olly.
Fight them.
(METAL GROANING)
(MAMMOTH SCREAMS)
(SCREAMING)
Clear the way! Let's go!
Out of the way!
Get out of here!
(GRUNTS)
(ROARS)
Cut the rope!
(MEN SCREAMING)
Wait! No!
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
We need more archers.
Here I am.
Come on.
Come on. Quickly.
What are you
doing up here?
The wildlings
are over the walls.
Ser Alliser's fallen.
The castle won't
stand much longer.
Edd, you have the Wall.
If they try
the mammoths again,
drop fire on them.
If the climbers get too high,
drop the scythe on them.
Come, brothers.
Now fight with me!
Might as well enjoy
our last night, right, boys?
Light the fuckers up!
Nock! Draw!
Loose!
How are we gonna stop that?
Shot 20 arrows
in him already.
You heard Jon.
We hold the gate.
Jon Snow's not
Lord Commander.
We hold the gate!
(QUAVERING)
Mother, save me.
Father, save me.
The gods aren't down here.
It's the six of us.
You hear me?
Please.
Night gathers and
now my watch begins.
It shall not end
until my death.
I shall take no wife,
hold no lands,
father no children.
I shall wear no crowns
and win no glory.
Win no glory.
ALL: I shall live
and die by my post.
I am the sword
in the darkness.
I am the watcher on the walls.
I am the shield that
guards the realms of men.
I pledge my life and honor
to the Night's Watch
for this night and
all the nights to come!
(GIANT ROARING)
I don't want you out there.
You can't protect me forever.
There won't be
anywhere to hide
if the castle falls.
I need him more
than I need you.
(GROWLS)
We need you, boy.
(SCREAMS)
Ha!
(SHOUTING)
(YELLS)
(GASPING)
(ARROW THUDS)
(GASPS)
(GASPING)
Jon Snow.
Hush. Don't talk.
Do you remember that cave?
We should have
stayed in that cave.
We'll go back there.
You know nothing,
Jon Snow.
Drop the scythe, boys!
(SCREAMING)
Hoist her up.
MAN: Hoist her up!
(CHAIN CLANKING)
(MEN GRUNTING)
They've had enough
for one night.
(CHEERING)
Don't cheer too loud.
They still outnumber us
1,000 to one.
(GROANING)
(ROARING)
Tormund.
It's over.
Let it end.
This is how a man ends.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Put him in chains.
We'll question him later.
I should have thrown you
from the top
of the Wall, boy!
Aye.
You should have.
(LOCK CLICKING)
(GASPS)
(DOOR OPENS)
Whoa, it's me.
I promised you, didn't I?
(SCUFFLES)
SAMWELL: We held them off.
JON: For one night.
This is a great victory.
A great victory?
Mance was
testing our defenses.
He almost made it through.
And he has more giants.
He has more mammoths.
He has 1,000
times as many men.
They'll hit us
again tonight.
Maybe we can hold them
off for a day or two,
but we'll never beat them.
Where are we going?
Going to find Mance.
You can't do that.
No one gave you
any orders.
Who's left
to give orders?
The wildling
army's only an army
because of Mance.
He united 100
warring tribes.
Without Mance,
they lose their leader.
They lose their purpose.
They go back to
fighting each other.
Scatter back to their homes.
Without Mance?
You're going to kill him?
I'm gonna try.
They'll never let you
within 100 yards of him.
And even if they did,
even if you
managed to kill him...
They'll kill me?
If I don't go,
they'll kill me anyway.
They'll kill
the rest of us, too.
SAMWELL:
They won't just kill you.
They'll boil you,
flay you, make it last days.
You're right.
It's a bad plan.
What's your plan?
They held the gate.
Get some brothers
down here to help you.
We need to burn the bodies.
Raise the outer gate.
Then lower it again
as soon as I'm out.
(METAL CLINKING)
What are you doing?
I promised Mormont
I'd never lose it again.
In case I don't come back.
Jon.
Come back.