HIGH SEPTON:
May the Warrior
grant him courage
and protect him in
these perilous times.
May the Smith
grant him strength
that he might bear
this heavy burden.
And may the Crone,
she that knows
the fate of all men,
show him the path
he must walk
and guide him
through the dark places
that lie ahead.
In the light of the Seven,
I now proclaim Tommen
of the House Baratheon,
First of His Name,
King of the Andals
and the First Men
and Lord of
the Seven Kingdoms.
Long may he reign!
ALL: Long may he reign!
(CHEERING)
Special day.
(CROWD CHATTING)
Your Grace.
CROWD: Your Grace.
There he is.
Long may he reign.
He sits the throne
like he was born to it.
Yes. He wasn't,
though, was he?
No, he wasn't.
You still mourn
for Joffrey?
He was my husband.
My king.
He would have been
your nightmare.
Your Grace,
I feel...
You knew exactly
what he was.
I did, too.
You never love
anything in the world
the way you love
your first child.
Doesn't matter
what they do.
And what he did,
it shocked me.
Do you think
I'm easily shocked?
No.
The things he did
shocked me.
He's only a boy.
A good, decent boy.
He always has been.
Who was the last
decent king, I wonder?
He could be the first man
who sits on that throne
in 50 years
to actually deserve it.
It would be some consolation,
wouldn't it?
For all the horror
that put him there.
He will need help
if he's going
to rule well.
He has you.
A mother is not enough.
You're still interested
in being queen?
(SCOFFS)
After all that's happened?
It sounds strange,
but I am...
I haven't even
given any thought to it,
what comes next.
It would be a great
honor, of course.
But I will have to speak
to my father about it.
Yes, speak to your father.
I'll speak to mine.
We may be faced
with an alarming number
of weddings soon.
(CHUCKLES)
I won't even know
what to call you.
Sister?
Or Mother?
(CHUCKLES)
JORAH: King Joffrey
Baratheon is dead.
Murdered at his own wedding.
BARRISTAN: And we've taken
the Meereenese navy,
Your Grace.
The Second Sons
took the navy.
Who told you to?
No one.
So why did you do it?
I heard
you liked ships.
How many ships?
93, Your Grace.
How many men
can they carry?
9,300,
not counting sailors.
Would that be enough
to take King's Landing?
The Lannisters have more.
BARRISTAN:
They've been fighting
Joffrey's wars for years.
They're tired, dispersed.
And now their
king is dead.
8,000 Unsullied,
2,000 Second Sons
sailing into
Blackwater Bay
and storming the gates
without warning.
It's hard to say.
It could be enough.
But we're not fighting
to make you queen
of King's Landing.
10,000 men can't
conquer Westeros.
BARRISTAN: The old houses
will flock to our queen
when she crosses
the Narrow Sea.
JORAH: The old houses
will flock to
whichever side
they think will win,
as they always have.
There's other news.
From Yunkai.
Without the Unsullied
to enforce your rule,
the Wise Masters
have retaken control
of the city.
They've reenslaved
the freedmen
who stayed behind
and sworn to take
revenge against you.
And in Astapor,
the council you installed
to rule over the city
has been overthrown
by a butcher named Cleon
who's declared
himself "His
Imperial Majesty."
DAENERYS:
Please leave me.
Not you, Jorah.
It appears my liberation
of Slaver's Bay isn't
going quite as planned.
You could sail for Westeros
and leave it all behind.
A boy sits
on the Iron Throne.
A boy many believe
to be a bastard
with no right to it.
They've never been
more vulnerable.
You counselled me
against rashness
once in Qarth.
I didn't listen.
That all worked out well.
(CHUCKLES)
How can I rule
seven kingdoms
if I can't control
Slaver's Bay?
Why should
anyone trust me,
follow me?
You're a Targaryen,
the Mother of Dragons.
I need to be
more than that.
I will not let
those I have freed
slide back into chains.
I will not sail
for Westeros.
What, then?
I will do
what queens do.
I will rule.
Pull up your hood.
A memorable shade.
But how would
they know?
You know what kind of stories
poor men enjoy the most?
Ones about rich girls
they'll never meet.
Is this the only way
into the Eyrie?
The mountains
are impassable.
If you want to
get to the Eyrie,
you need to go through
the Bloody Gate.
It doesn't matter
how large your army is,
if you attack this gate,
you do it on this road,
three men abreast,
and get slaughtered
like goats.
The first
Lords of the Vale
didn't have much,
but they had these mountains
and they knew how to use them.
And the fortress
they built here
has never been overcome.
Not once in 1,000 years.
Know your strengths,
use them wisely,
and one man can
be worth 10,000.
KNIGHT: Who would
pass the Bloody Gate?
Lord Petyr Baelish
and his niece Alayne.
Stand to.
KNIGHTS: Stand to!
Welcome back,
Lord Baelish.
(GATE CLANKING)
(DOOR OPENS)
Uncle Petyr!
LITTLEFINGER: My lord.
Oh.
I have
brought you a gift.
Lord Baelish.
My lady.
Look what Uncle Petyr
brought me.
A beautiful gift
for a beautiful boy.
It's a pleasure to
make your acquaintance,
Lady Arryn.
My name is...
Oh, do take down
that hood, child.
Don't you think
I know who you are?
You think I'd let
my intended leave the Eyrie
on urgent business
without knowing
what that business was?
I let him go
so he could bring
you here to me.
My flesh and blood.
It's wonderful to
meet you, Aunt Lysa.
You mustn't call me that
in front of anyone else.
I understand.
No one can know
you're here.
It would put us in
a very precarious position.
I would never
say a thing.
The Lannisters
want to destroy us.
They've been
trying for years.
Now they know
what it feels like.
ROBIN: Mummy said
they killed your mother
and they chopped off
your brother's head.
They did,
and my father's.
They killed my father,
too, with poison.
I wanted to make
the little Lannister
baby man fly, (CHUCKLES)
but Mother said
I couldn't.
Make him fly?
Through the Moon Door.
(GIGGLES)
LYSA: And on top
of everything else,
they made you marry
that filthy troll.
They made us both.
Lord Tyrion
didn't want to.
LYSA:
I don't believe that.
Did he force
himself on you?
No. We never...
LYSA: Good.
Robin, this is
your cousin Sansa.
But you're not
to call her Sansa
in front of anyone
but Uncle Petyr
and myself.
Do you understand?
Sansa, this is
my son Robin.
It's a pleasure
to meet you, Robin.
Robin, show Sansa
to her chamber.
Take the back stairs.
Go. We'll speak soon.
What took you so long?
Arranging for
the ascension
of King Tommen I,
extricating Sansa,
getting her here alive.
She's here.
We've spent more
than enough time on her
for one evening.
Let's get married tonight.
Ought we not...
...inform the Lords of the
Vale about the ceremony?
(HUFFS) There's only
one Lord of the Vale.
The others can all hang.
Lurking and
simpering on the stairs
like buzzards
the moment my husband died,
trying to get
their claws in me.
I do think that we
could wait until...
I'm done waiting, Petyr.
We had our wedding night
many years ago.
Or don't you remember?
Like it was yesterday.
What wife would do for you
the things I've done?
What wife would trust you
the way I've trusted you?
When you gave me those drops
and told me to pour
them into Jon's wine,
my husband's wine.
When you told me to
write a letter to Cat
telling her it was the...
(LYSA MOANING)
The deed is done.
Faded into nothing.
Only speaking of it
can make it real.
Tonight it is, then.
(LAUGHS)
Let me bathe and dress
for the occasion.
Once I'm presentable,
I'll call on
the Septon immediately.
I'm warning you.
I'm going to scream
when my husband
makes love to me.
So loud they'll hear me
clear across the Narrow Sea.
(LYSA SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
TYWIN: When will
the wedding take place
in your mind?
CERSEI: As soon
as decency permits.
After we've allowed Tommen
the appropriate time
to mourn his brother
and Margaery to
mourn her husband.
A fortnight?
That seems reasonable.
No jugglers,
no jousting dwarves,
no 77-course meals.
And your wedding to Loras?
Shortly after Tommen's.
Shortly?
A fortnight.
I know you don't like them.
I didn't like your husband.
Used to pat me
on the back a lot.
I didn't trust him.
We had that in common.
You don't need to
make formal alliances
with people you trust.
Then whom
can we trust?
Ourselves alone.
The Tyrells
are our only true rivals
in terms of resources
and we need them
on our side.
Robert wasn't
particularly rich.
Robert had me
funding him.
Wars swallow gold
like a pit in the earth.
I suppose that explains
why we did so well
in the last one.
Do you know
how much gold was mined
in the Westerlands
this past year?
Haven't a clue.
Your best guess.
Pounds, tons, ounces?
Doesn't matter.
The answer is the same.
Can't be.
Our last working mine
ran dry three years ago.
Then how do we pay
for anything?
The crown owes
the Iron Bank of Braavos
a tremendous amount of money.
How much?
A tremendous amount.
There must be someone
at the Iron Bank
you can speak to,
come to some
arrangement.
The Iron Bank
is the Iron Bank.
There is no someone.
Someone does work there.
It is comprised of people.
And a temple
is comprised of stones.
One stone crumbles
and another
takes its place.
And the temple holds its form
for 1,000 years or more.
That's what
the Iron Bank is,
a temple.
We all live in its shadow
and almost none of us know it.
You can't run from them.
You can't cheat them.
You can't sway them
with excuses.
If you owe them money
and you don't want
to crumble yourself,
you pay it back.
Vesting
the Tyrells in the crown
will help a great deal.
It's for the good
of the family,
I understand that.
I'm not sure
my brothers do.
I know you're
building a strong case
against Tyrion.
And as a mother,
that is your right.
But as a judge,
I cannot discuss
the trial with you.
I respect that.
We don't need
to discuss it.
The Lannister legacy
is the only thing
that matters.
You've started wars
to protect this family.
Turned your back on Jaime
for refusing to
contribute to its future.
What does Tyrion deserve
for lighting
that future on fire?
ARYA: Joffrey.
Cersei.
Walder Frey.
Meryn Trant.
Tywin Lannister.
The Red Woman.
Beric Dondarrion.
Thoros of Myr.
Ilyn Payne.
The Mountain.
Would you shut up?
I can't sleep
until I say the names.
The names
of every fucking
person in Westeros?
Only the ones
I'm going to kill.
(CHUCKLES)
Hate's as good
a thing as any
to keep a person going.
Better than most.
We come across my brother,
maybe we can both
cross a name off our list.
If he were
here right now,
what would you do?
I'd tell him
to shut the fuck up
so I can get some sleep.
Go on, get it over with,
your list of doomed men.
I'm almost done.
Only one name left.
Go on.
The Hound.
SANSA: Thank you.
Your mother always
had a sweet tooth.
Really?
Oh, yes.
At suppertime,
she would go straight
for honey cakes,
candied almonds, custard.
Anything sweet.
Eventually, your grandfather
had to assign a septa
to watch her at meals.
Cat was the firstborn
daughter after all.
It was important that
she remain desirable
so Father could arrange
a good match for her
and she was
starting to get fat.
My mother fat?
(BOTH CHUCKLE LIGHTLY)
She never let me
have my pudding
until I'd finished
all my proper food.
This is before she
married your father
and moved to the North.
By the time you were born,
your father's austerity
had become hers.
Marriage changes people.
(GASPS)
I didn't mean
for you to stop.
Enjoy them.
How do you like them?
They're delicious.
Where did you get the lemons?
You can't grow them up here.
Oh, gods, no.
Petyr had three crates
brought all the way
from King's Landing.
He knew you liked
lemon cakes.
He's so kind.
He really
cares for you.
Think where you'd be
without him.
In their clutches,
on trial for murder.
Yes. I'm very lucky.
He feels
responsible for you.
Oh, I know he does.
I'm so grateful.
Why?
Why does he feel
responsible for you?
Well, I'm half Tully.
He loved your family
so much.
Loved your mother.
No.
That's what
you wanted to say.
He loves you, Aunt Lysa.
He's married to you.
Your mother
never loved him.
Cat always went straight
for the sweetest thing.
The most obvious thing.
Your Uncle Brandon.
Your handsome, arrogant,
cruel Uncle Brandon.
He almost killed
Petyr in a duel.
And your mother
loved him anyway.
And now Petyr
is risking his life
to save you,
the daughter of a woman
who didn't love him.
No more than those
whores in his brothels.
Has he told you
about them?
No.
He hasn't told you
about the vile things
they do with their bodies,
they let him
do with their bodies?
Never.
Are you pregnant?
What? No, I told you.
Lord Tyrion and I never...
I wasn't asking
about Tyrion.
What have you let
Petyr do with your body?
Aunt Lysa, no, I...
Your young, pretty body.
Nothing. I'm a virgin.
Don't lie to me.
You're hurting me.
I'll know if you lie.
I'm a virgin, I swear it.
He loves you, Aunt Lysa.
All he says is
that I'm stupid.
I'm a stupid little girl
with stupid dreams
who never learns,
and I'm a terrible liar,
so I should always
tell the truth.
And I swear to you that
he has never touched me.
Not once, not ever.
(SHUSHING)
It's all right.
It will all be all right.
You'll be a widow soon.
They'll execute that dwarf
for murdering the king
and you'll be free
to marry Robin.
You'll be
the Lady of the Vale.
Hmm.
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(GRUNTING)
Didn't they teach you
how to ride a horse?
Yes, my lady,
when I was young.
There wasn't much
call for it with
Lord Tyrion, though.
He preferred litters.
Perhaps you should
have stayed with him.
It's not going to be
a pleasant journey for you.
It could take weeks
to get to the Wall,
depending on the weather.
PODRICK:
That's a long way off.
Well, Lady Sansa's
brother's at Castle Black.
If I were her,
that's where I'd go.
Feel free to
stop at any point.
Never, my lady.
I'm your squire.
I've made it this
far in the world
without a squire.
I don't see why
I need one now.
All knights have squires,
my lady.
I'm not a knight.
And I'm not a slaver, either.
I don't own you.
I swore an oath,
my lady.
I am releasing
you from that oath.
That means
you could leave.
I know.
What do you think
will happen
if you leave?
They'll say I wasn't
a very good squire.
(HORSE NICKERS)
(WHINNIES)
The hell you doing?
Practising.
What, ways to die?
No one's going
to kill me.
They will if you
nance around like that.
That's no way to fight.
It's not fighting.
It's water dancing.
Dancing?
Maybe you ought
to put on a dress.
Who taught you
that shite?
The greatest swordsman
who ever lived.
Syrio Forel, the First Sword
to the Sealord of Braavos.
Braavos. (SCOFFS)
Greasy-haired
little bastard,
I bet.
They all are.
What do you know
about anything?
I bet his hair
is greasier than
Joffrey's cunt.
It was not.
Was? He dead?
Yes.
How?
He was killed.
Who by?
Meryn Trant. That's
why Ser Meryn's on my...
Meryn Trant?
The greatest swordsman
who ever lived killed
by Meryn fucking Trant?
He was outnumbered.
Any boy whore
with a sword
could beat three
Meryn Trants.
Syrio didn't have a sword.
Or armour. Just a stick.
The greatest
swordsman who ever lived
didn't have a sword?
(LAUGHS)
All right.
You have a sword.
Let's see what
he taught you.
Go on, do it for
your Braavosi friend.
Dead like all the rest
of your friends.
(GRUNTS)
Your friend's dead
and Meryn Trant's not
'cause Trant had armour
and a big fucking sword.
(BIRD CALLING)
Your Grace.
Prince Oberyn.
Writing letters?
A poem, actually.
May I show you
the gardens?
I couldn't very well
refuse a royal escort.
No, you couldn't.
I didn't realise
you were a poet.
Not a very good one.
For your paramour?
For one of
my daughters.
You have several,
don't you?
Eight.
Eight?
Eight daughters?
OBERYN: The fifth
is difficult.
I named her after
my sister Elia.
Beautiful name.
Yes.
But I can't say it
without turning sad.
And after I turn sad,
I grow angry.
Perhaps that's why
she's difficult.
The gods love
their stupid jokes,
don't they?
Which joke is that?
You're a prince
of Dorne.
A legendary fighter.
A brilliant man feared
throughout Westeros.
But you could not
save your sister.
I'm a Lannister.
Queen for 19 years.
Daughter of the most
powerful man alive.
But I could not
save my son.
What good is power
if you cannot protect
the ones you love?
We can avenge them.
Yes, we can avenge them.
You really believe
Tyrion murdered your son?
I know he did.
We will have a trial
and we will
learn the truth.
We'll have a trial,
anyway.
I haven't seen
my daughter
in over a year.
OBERYN:
The last time I saw her,
she was swimming
with two of my girls
in the Water Gardens.
Laughing in the sun.
I want to believe that.
I want to believe
she's happy.
You have my word.
We don't hurt
little girls in Dorne.
Everywhere in the world,
they hurt little girls.
Would you bring her
a gift for me?
I wasn't there
for her nameday.
I don't know when
I'll see her again.
Anything at all.
The best shipwrights
in King's Landing
have been working
on it for months.
Myrcella loves
the open water.
OBERYN:
I will have it sailed down
to Sunspear for her.
Please tell her
her mother
misses her very much.
PODRICK: Oh, no.
No, no.
Hells.
Gods.
Did you remove the skin?
No, my lady.
Have you ever cooked
a rabbit before?
No, my lady.
Did you ever cook
anything for Lord Tyrion?
No, my lady.
That was the cooks.
(GROANS)
What are you doing?
I'm helping you
with your armour.
I've been removing
my own armor
for quite some time,
thank you very much.
What exactly did you
do for Lord Tyrion?
I brought him his meals
and cleared his table
when he was finished.
I kept his clothing
and linens clean.
Carried his messages
and returned the replies.
Mostly I poured wine.
Whilst in
Lord Tyrion's service,
did you ever do anything
remotely related to combat?
I killed a man.
Who?
A Kingsguard.
He tried to kill Lord Tyrion
at the Blackwater.
How did you kill
a Kingsguard?
I pushed a spear through
the back of his head.
Bloody ridiculous.
Help me with these straps.
(WOMAN WHIMPERING)
(RAST LAUGHING)
RAST: Hey.
Get up.
(WOMAN SOBBING)
MAN: That's it,
lad, put it inside.
Get the fire going again.
We're all freezing.
MAN: Aye.
We need you in the journey.
BOY: I promise I'll do it.
MAN: I've got
to have a piss.
(PIGS GRUNTING)
(WOMEN WHIMPERING)
Now keep quiet.
(RATTLES)
(LANTERN SQUEAKING)
(COUGHING)
You need water.
It doesn't matter.
Of course it matters.
You mustn't let
anything stop you.
They already
have stopped me.
No.
You're not here.
You're far from here.
What does that mean?
(CROWS CAWING)
At the hill.
A great weirwood tree.
You've seen it, too.
Meera and I,
even Hodor,
we're only here
to guide you.
He's waiting for you.
We have to find it.
You have to make it.
We will.
This isn't the end.
Not for you.
Not yet.
MEERA: How...
...will we know the end?
You'll know.
(FOOTSTEPS)
LOCKE: Brothers.
You do move quiet.
How many?
Eleven men.
Most of them already drunk.
No guards posted.
They don't seem to
have a care in the world.
We'll carve them up
like walnut pie.
Karl was
the top paid cutthroat
in Flea Bottom.
I've seen what he
can do with a knife.
Have you seen what
I can do with a knife?
(CHUCKLES) Not yet.
There's a hut on
the west side of the keep.
We should steer clear of it.
Why?
They've got some hounds
chained up inside.
Closer we can get without
the dogs sniffing us,
the better.
New moon tonight.
(SIGHS) Get some rest.
We move at sundown.
I've always liked
a girl with curls.
A touch of class.
You take whatever's left.
Get her up.
BRAN: Stop.
Stop. What are you doing?
HODOR: Hodor.
Hodor.
Stop.
Stop!
HODOR: Hodor.
BRAN: Stop!
(MEERA GRUNTING)
Please.
Hodor.
Please, get off her!
Please, leave her alone!
BRAN: Please, stop. Stop.
What are you doing?
Leave her alone!
Hodor.
No!
Shh, shh, shh.
(WHIMPERING)
Shh.
You've got
pretty hair,
don't you?
Now what is
a pretty little
highborn girl like you
doing out here
in the deep,
dark woods, eh?
You left your daddy's castle
looking for trouble,
didn't you?
No dresses for you.
You like it rough,
don't you?
You like it in the
gutter, don't you?
If you let my sister go,
I can help you.
You can help me?
I can.
And how you
gonna do that?
I have the sight.
I can see things.
That's very helpful.
Things that haven't
happened yet.
What a fine thing.
A fine thing.
Have you seen what I'm
gonna do to your sister?
What they're
going to do?
No.
Don't close your eyes.
I saw you die tonight.
I saw your body burn.
I saw the snow fall
and bury your bones.
MAN: To arms!
They're here,
the Night's Watch.
(MEN SHOUTING)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(MAN SCREAMS)
Rescue party
is here, lads.
Lady.
Is Jon with you?
Aye.
I'll take you to him.
You're Brandon Stark?
(GASPS)
Hodor.
The little crippled lord.
We're going for a ride, boy.
Jon!
Keep talking
and I'll cut
your friends' throats.
Starting with the idiot.
Do you hear?
HODOR: Hodor!
Hodor.
(GRUNTING)
(CHOKING)
(NECK SNAPS)
Hodor.
Hodor, get his knife.
Cut me loose.
Hodor.
Cut me loose, Hodor.
Jojen and Meera,
free them.
Go!
(SWORDS CLANKING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
Jon.
Jon!
If he sees you,
he won't let you
go north.
He's my brother.
And wants to
protect you.
He'll take you back
to Castle Black.
MAN: They're coming
from that way as well!
You have to decide.
Do you want to find
the three-eyed raven?
BRAN: Hodor.
HODOR: Hodor.
We need to free Summer.
And we need to go.
(SHOUTS)
(GROANS)
Lord Snow.
Are you bringing
me back for trial?
We had a good
thing here.
We were free men.
You'll never be free.
You'll never know
what that's like.
You learn how to
fight in a castle?
(GROANS)
Some old man teach
you how to stand,
how to parry?
(GROANS)
How to fight with honor?
You know what's
wrong with honor?
(SPITS)
(GRUNTS)
You.
(WOMAN WHIMPERING)
(GURGLING)
(PANTING)
Are you all right?
Come with me.
Come on.
(GRUNTS)
We lost four brothers?
Five.
What the seven hells
could do that to a man?
I count 10
dead mutineers.
Locke said there
were 11 of them.
Where's Rast?
(WIND HOWLING)
(PANTING)
(CROWS CAWING)
(ROARING)
(RAST SCREAMS)
Here's another.
Jon.
JON: Where in seven hells?
Come here.
I missed you, boy.
What should we
do with this lot?
It's not safe for you
here on your own.
Mance Rayder has
an army heading this way
and there's worse
out there than Mance.
Come with us
to Castle Black.
We can find you work.
Keep you safe.
Meaning all respect,
ser crow,
Craster beat us
and worse.
Your brother crows
beat us and worse.
We'll find our own way.
You want to stay here?
In Craster's Keep?
(SPITS) Burn it
to the ground
and all the dead
with it.