RAMSAY: Tansy!
MYRANDA: Tansy!
(DOGS BARKING)
(GROWLING)
(BARKING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
RAMSAY: Tansy!
(TANSY SCREAMS)
There you are.
(BARKING)
(SCREAMING)
MYRANDA: I can't see her. Tansy!
(PANTING)
MYRANDA: (LAUGHING) Tansy!
(SCREAMS)
If you make it out
of the woods, you win!
Run, Tansy!
(SCREAMS)
(WHIMPERING)
(SOBBING)
RAMSAY: Tansy!
MYRANDA: Where is she?
(BARKING)
(WHIMPERING)
(SCREAMS)
(WAILING)
Good girls. Down.
Well done. You, too.
I only wounded her.
You brought her down.
That's what matters.
A fine shot.
Wasn't it, Reek?
A fine shot, master.
My lady.
TANSY: Please, my lord.
(SOBBING)
It hurts. Please.
Sweet. Don't cry.
It will be over soon.
She thinks she's pretty.
Let me put one
through her face.
RAMSAY: We have to
reward the hounds, love.
They did
all the hard work.
Why? I did whatever
you asked.
RAMSAY: But you made
Myranda feel jealous.
Me, jealous of her?
My lord, please.
You can see that
your presence has
become a bit of a problem.
(SOBBING)
(DOGS SNARLING)
Rip her!
(TANSY SCREAMING)
(DOGS BITING)
Not so pretty now.
TYRION: Your new hand,
it's nicer than the old one.
Wouldn't you agree, Pod?
Is it solid gold?
TYRION: Gilded steel.
You're not eating.
Why is no one eating?
My wife wastes away
and my brother
starves himself.
I'm not hungry.
You lost a hand,
not a stomach.
Try the boar.
Cersei can't get enough
of it since one
killed Robert for her.
A toast.
To the proud
Lannister children.
The dwarf, the cripple,
and the mother of madness.
I'll clean it up.
No, I'll do it.
Leave us.
It's only wine.
(DOOR CLOSES)
I can't fight anymore.
What about your left?
I can hold a sword,
but all my instincts
are wrong.
How can I protect the King
when I can hardly
wipe my own ass?
You're the
Lord Commander now.
Command. Let others
do the fighting.
When was the last time
Father used a sword?
I'm not Father.
I'm the Kingslayer.
When people find out
I can't slay a pigeon...
Train, then.
Learn to fight
with your other hand.
With whom? You?
Men talk.
As soon as someone
discovers I can't fight,
he'll tell everyone.
You need a proper,
discreet swordsman.
I have just the one.
My brother tells me
you can keep
your mouth shut.
Unusual talent
for a sellsword.
He tells me you shit gold,
just like your father.
Is this place safe?
There's this knight,
Leygood. Got
thunderbolts on his shield.
Uh-huh.
Right here is
where I fuck his wife.
She's a screamer, that one.
If they don't hear her,
they won't hear us.
(WHISTLES) I've
never seen Valyrian steel
before. She's a beauty.
Problem is,
if you fight with
an edged blade,
I'll have to.
And if I fight
with an edged blade,
I'll have no one
left to pay me.
(BLADE CLATTERS)
I haven't used
a sparring sword
since I was nine.
BRONN: Mmm-mmm.
(GROANS)
Bold warrior you are,
attacking a man
when his guard's down.
Best time to attack a man.
Mind yourself.
If I still had
my right hand...
Plan on growing it back?
(PANTING)
Come on, then.
MAN: Open the gates!
Riders coming in!
(HORSE WHINNIES)
MAN: Let's get
these horses seen to!
Father. Welcome home.
Walda, this is
Ramsay Snow,
my bastard.
A pleasure, Mother.
Hello.
BOLTON: See that
the horses are fed,
watered, and rubbed down.
And take Lady Walda
to her chambers.
WOMAN: This way, my lady.
Where is your prize?
With the hounds.
I'll have a look at him.
I hear you took a hand
from the Kingslayer.
Word travels.
How he screamed.
You would have loved it.
(LAUGHS)
Father.
(THEON GRUNTS)
What did you do to him?
I trained him.
He was a slow learner,
but he learned.
You flayed him.
Peeled a few bits.
Removed a few others.
This was Balon Greyjoy's
son and heir.
We've been flaying our
enemies for 1,000 years.
The flayed man
is on our banners.
My banners, not yours.
You're not a Bolton.
You're a Snow.
Tywin Lannister has
given me the North.
But he won't lift a finger
to help me take it.
As long as the ironborn
hold Moat Cailin,
our armies are
trapped south of the Neck.
Theon was a valuable hostage,
not your plaything.
I wanted to trade him
for Moat Cailin.
I already asked.
Lord Greyjoy refused.
Savages have no...
You sent terms
to Balon Greyjoy
without my consent?
You made me acting
Lord of the Dreadfort.
I acted.
I had to smuggle
myself into my own lands,
thanks to the Greyjoys.
I needed Theon whole.
Theon was our enemy.
But Reek
will never betray us.
I placed far too
much trust in you.
Reek,
how could you let me stand
before my father unshaven?
It's disrespectful.
Sorry, my lord.
Give him the razor.
I'm not a Bolton, Father.
What does it matter?
Go on, Reek.
A nice close shave.
Reek,
tell Father,
where are Bran
and Rickon Stark?
I don't know, my lord.
You murdered them
and displayed their
corpses at Winterfell.
RAMSAY: Reek,
did you murder
the Stark boys?
No, my lord.
Just two farm boys.
RAMSAY: And crisped them
so no one would know?
THEON: Yes, my lord.
The Starks have
always ruled the North.
If Bran and Rickon are alive,
the country will
rally to their side,
now that Robb Stark is gone.
Oh, that's right, Reek.
Robb Stark is dead.
Sorry.
I know he was like
a brother to you.
But my father put
a knife through his heart.
How do you feel about that?
(WHIMPERING)
You ready for a hunt?
Always.
Find those boys
and I'll give you
1,000 acres and a holdfast.
Your pet rat have any
thoughts on which way
they went after Winterfell?
Jon Snow is at Castle Black.
Who the fuck is Jon Snow?
Their bastard brother.
He could be sheltering them.
He may know where they are.
Even if he doesn't,
he's half Stark himself.
Could be a threat.
You want to prove
yourself a Bolton?
Gather whatever men you can
and ride for Moat Cailin.
Bring this creature of yours.
Maybe he'll be of some use.
Take the Moat for the family,
for our family,
and I'll reconsider
your position.
Lord Varys.
Breakfasting
with the King?
I'm afraid foreigners
aren't welcome at
such exclusive affairs.
Oh, to be foreign.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Shae has been noticed.
Sansa's maid saw you
with her. She already
told your sister.
It's only a matter of time
before your father hears.
So I'm guilty of
being seen with
my own wife's handmaiden.
My father will ask you
if there's anything more,
and you'll tell him
some clever lie.
No, I will not.
How long do you imagine
your father and sister
would let me live
if they suspected me
of lying?
I have no pet sellsword
to protect me.
No legendary brother
to avenge me.
Only little birds
who whisper in my ear.
Forgive me
if I don't weep for you.
No one weeps for spiders,
or whores.
I have friends
across the sea
who could help her.
She won't leave.
I've told her
this is a dangerous place
so many times,
she no longer believes it.
Your father has
promised to hang
the next whore
he finds you with.
Have you ever
known your father
to make an idle threat?
MACE: From House Tyrell
and the people of the Reach,
Your Grace, it is my honor
to present you
with this wedding cup.
May you and
my daughter Margaery
drink deep and live long.
A handsome goblet,
my lord.
Or shall I call
you Father?
I should be honored,
Your Grace.
She's the whore
I told you about.
The dark-haired one.
Have her brought to
the Tower of the Hand
before the wedding.
Hmm.
A book?
The Lives of Four Kings.
Grand Maester Kaeth's
history of
the reigns of
Daeron the Young Dragon,
Baelor the Blessed,
Aegon the Unworthy,
and Daeron the Good.
A book every king
should read.
Now that the war is won,
we should all
find time for wisdom.
Thank you, Uncle.
One of only two
Valyrian steel swords
in the capital, Your Grace,
freshly forged
in your honor.
PYCELLE: Careful,
Your Grace.
Nothing cuts
like Valyrian steel.
So they say.
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
Such a great sword
should have a name.
What shall I call her?
MAN 1: Stormbringer.
MAN 2: Terminus.
MAN 3: Widow's Wail.
MAN 4: Wolfsbane.
Widow's Wail.
I like that.
(CHUCKLES)
Every time I use it,
it'll be like cutting
off Ned Stark's head
all over again.
(DOOR OPENS)
Don't.
You want me on the desk?
What's wrong, my lion?
Don't call me that.
What should I call you?
I'm afraid our
friendship can't continue.
Our friendship?
There's a ship
waiting in the harbor
bound for Pentos.
What?
You'll have your own cabin,
and across the Narrow Sea
a house, servants.
What is this?
I'm a married man.
My wife has
suffered a great deal,
as you well know.
I don't want her
to suffer anymore
on my account.
I need to uphold my vows.
She doesn't want you.
I need to do right by her.
You don't want her.
By our children.
What are you afraid of?
I'm not afraid.
You are.
You are afraid of your
father and your sister.
You're going to run
from them all your life?
I need you to leave.
I'm not afraid of them.
I'm not going
to run from them.
Shae.
We will fight them together.
It's like you said,
I am yours and you are mine.
You're a whore!
Sansa is fit to bear
my children, and you are not.
I can't be in
love with a whore.
I can't have children
with a whore.
How many men have
you been with? 500? 5,000?
How many whores
have you been with?
I have enjoyed
my time with all of them,
and I have enjoyed my time
with you most of all.
But now that time is over.
(SHAE SOBBING)
You'll have
a comfortable life
in Pentos.
Bronn will escort you
to your ship.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
MELISANDRE: Hear us now.
Accept these tokens
of our faith, my lord,
and lead us from the darkness.
(WAILING)
Sire, I served you well.
CROWD: (CHANTING)
Lord of Light,
show us the way.
Lead us from the darkness.
Selyse, you're my sister!
Yours are
the stars that guide us.
Tell him!
MELISANDRE:
Lord of Light, protect us,
for the night is dark
and full of terrors.
(SCREAMING)
SELYSE: Did you see?
Their souls.
It was their souls.
Our lord took them.
Did you see?
DAVOS: Lord Florent
was your brother by law.
STANNIS: He was an infidel.
DAVOS: He worshipped the
gods of his fathers and
their fathers before him.
They were the gods
of your fathers, too.
I ordered him to
tear down his idols.
He disobeyed.
How many ships did he
bring to your cause?
How many men?
A good deal more than you.
Did you see, Ser Davos?
They're with our lord now.
Their sins all burned away.
I'm sure they're more
than grateful, My Queen.
(SNIFFS)
Meat's off.
Our larders
are almost empty.
Serve fish, then.
We're on an island.
You hate fish.
I hate a good many things,
but I suffer them
all the same.
When Storm's End
was under siege
and I was starving,
Stannis boiled soup
for me from books.
The binding glue
is made from horses.
One morning,
he shot two seagulls
on the beach.
I've never tasted anything
as good as grilled seagull.
Do you remember?
Of course.
Have you ever known
true hunger, my lady?
That's all I knew
when I was a child.
Until you found
the Lord of Light?
Until he found me.
I fear for our
daughter's soul.
MELISANDRE: Every mother
should fear for
her child's soul.
SELYSE: She's
a stubborn little beast.
She's a child.
You barely know her.
You think she's sweet
because she smiles
when you visit.
She's sullen and
stubborn and sinful.
Why else would
the Lord of Light
have seen fit
to mark her face?
She needs the rod.
She's my daughter.
You will not strike her.
As you command.
Perhaps the Lady Melisandre
could speak with her.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
Come in.
Were you sleeping, Princess?
Did you watch
the ceremony on the beach?
I heard it.
And it frightened you?
Ser Axell was my uncle.
He was always kind to me.
They're in a better
place now, Princess.
The fire cleansed them
of the sins of the world.
But they screamed.
Women scream when
they give birth.
Afterward they
are filled with joy.
aren't ash and bone.
You have so many questions,
don't you?
So did I
when I was a child.
I was much like you.
Only I wasn't a princess.
And you didn't have this.
No.
But I suffered in
other ways, sweet girl,
believe me.
What do you know of the gods?
I read
The Seven-Pointed Star.
Lies and fables.
Septons speak of seven gods.
There are but two.
A god of light
and love and joy,
and a god of darkness,
evil, and fear.
Eternally at war.
Then there are
no seven heavens
and no seven hells?
There's only one hell,
Princess.
The one we live in now.
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(SUMMER GROWLING)
HODOR: Hodor.
(PANTING)
Why did you wake me?
You've been
gone for hours.
I was hungry.
We're all hungry.
I was just eating.
Summer was eating.
Your body can't
live on the food
your wolf consumes.
Spending too much
time in Summer's skin
is dangerous.
You're not a direwolf, Bran.
Must be glorious, though.
To run, to leap, to hunt.
To be whole.
I know it's tempting,
but if you're trapped
in Summer for too long,
you'll forget what
it was to be human.
You'd forget us, Bran.
You'd forget your
mother and father,
your brothers and sisters,
Winterfell.
You'd forget you.
And if we lose you,
we lose everything.
(SUMMER BARKING)
Hodor, take me to the tree.
(CAWS)
MALE VOICE: Look for me
(CAWING)
beneath the tree.
CERSEI: He saw us!
(SCREAMING)
(DRAGON ROARING)
MALE VOICE: North.
(GASPING)
I know where we have to go.
(BELLS TOLLING)
Let it be known that
Margaery of House Tyrell
and Joffrey of the Houses
Lannister and Baratheon
are one heart,
one flesh, one soul.
Cursed be he
who would seek to
tear them asunder.
With this kiss,
I pledge my love.
We have a new queen.
Better her than you.
Bit much,
wouldn't you say?
It feels proportionate.
Proportionate to what?
The expected extravagance.
People who spend
their money on
this sort of nonsense
tend not to have
it for long.
You ought to try
enjoying something
before you die.
You might find
it suits you.
Not now, Mace.
Lord Tywin and I
are speaking.
Anyway, I don't know
what you're
complaining about.
I'm paying my share.
Shall we stick golden roses
on half the meat pies
to commemorate
your generosity?
No, your heartfelt
"Thank you" is
its own reward.
I would imagine
I'll be hearing it
again before long.
Wars are rather expensive.
"The Iron Bank
will have its due."
How they love to
remind everyone.
Almost as much as
you Lannisters
with your debts.
I'm not worried
about the Iron Bank.
We both know you're
smarter than that.
Come, Tywin, let us
celebrate young love.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
All taken care of.
You saw her
board the ship?
Aye, she's on it.
And you saw
the ship sail away?
No one knows she's there
but you, me, and Varys.
How do you know?
Because if someone follows me
without an invitation,
I'm the last person
they ever follow.
Was someone following you?
She's gone.
I know you don't want to
believe it, but she is.
Now,
go drink until it feels like
you did the right thing.
OBERYN: Hello.
Hello.
Not you.
OLENNA: You look
exquisite, child.
The wind has
been at you, though.
I haven't had
the opportunity to tell you
how sorry I was to
hear about your brother.
War is war,
but killing a man
at a wedding,
horrid.
What sort of monster
would do such a thing?
As if men need more
reasons to fear marriage.
My lady.
Lord Tyrion, you see?
Not as bad as all that.
Perhaps if your
pauper husband
were to sell his mule
and his last pair of shoes,
he might be able to
afford to bring you
to Highgarden for a visit.
Now that peace has come
and all is right
with the world,
it would do you good
to see some of it.
You must excuse me.
It's time I ate some
of this food I paid for.
♪ A coat of gold
♪ A coat of red
♪ A lion still has claws
♪ And mine are long... ♪
Very good. Off you go.
(COINS CLATTER)
(CROWD LAUGHS)
My love,
why don't we make
the announcement?
(GOBLET CLINKING)
JOFFREY: Everyone.
The Queen would like
to say a few words.
(APPLAUSE)
We are so fortunate
to enjoy this
marvelous food and drink.
Not all among us
are so lucky.
To thank the gods
for bringing the
recent war to a just end,
King Joffrey has
decreed that the leftovers
from our feast
be given to
the poorest in his city.
(THE BEAR AND
THE MAIDEN FAIR PLAYING)
You're an example to us all.
Ser Jaime, I'm very sorry.
Ser Loras,
it's quite all right.
Your sister
looks very beautiful.
LORAS: As does yours.
So, are you looking
forward to your wedding?
Yes, very much.
Our fathers are
both rather keen
on the prospect.
They certainly are.
Perhaps they
should get married.
If you were to marry
Cersei, she'd murder
you in your sleep.
If you somehow managed
to put a child in her first,
she'd murder him, too,
long before he
drew his first breath.
Luckily for you,
none of this will happen
because you'll
never marry her.
And neither will you.
Your Grace. My King.
My Queen.
Lady Brienne.
So good of you to come.
I'm no lady, Your Grace.
CERSEI: Did you just bow?
Apologies, Your Grace.
I never did
master the curtsy.
You're the one who put a sword
through Renly Baratheon.
That's not true, my love.
Brienne had
nothing to do with it.
A shame.
I'd knight the man
that put an end to
that deviant's life.
I just wanted to
congratulate you both
and wish you good fortune.
The country has
been at war too long.
I hope your reign
is long and peaceful.
Yes.
Thank you.
I hope we see more of you.
Lady Brienne.
You're Lord Selwyn
Tarth's daughter.
That makes you a lady
whether you want
to be or not.
As you say, Your Grace.
I owe you my gratitude.
You returned
my brother safely
to King's Landing.
In truth,
he rescued me, Your Grace.
More than once.
Did he?
Haven't heard
that story before.
Not such
a fascinating story.
I'm sure you have many.
Sworn to Renly Baratheon,
Catelyn Stark,
and now my brother.
Must be exciting to flit
from one camp to the next,
serving whichever
lord or lady you fancy.
I don't serve your brother,
Your Grace.
But you love him.
No, come to my chambers
and I will
examine you personally.
She'll do no such thing.
Oh, Your Grace.
This young lady
sought my advice...
You should see Qyburn.
He's quite good.
Your Grace.
Qyburn? Deplorable man.
Brought shame on
the Citadel with his
repugnant experiments.
More repugnant than
your gnarled fingers
on that girl's thighs?
Your Grace,
I am a man of learning.
My little brother
had you sent to
the Black Cells
when you annoyed him.
What do you think
I could do to you?
I never meant
to annoy anyone.
But you are.
You're annoying me right now.
Every breath you
draw in my presence
annoys me.
So here's what
I want you to do.
Leave my presence.
Leave this wedding right now.
Go to the kitchens
and instruct them that
all the leftovers
from the feast
will be brought
to the kennels.
Your Grace,
Queen Margaery...
The Queen is telling you
the leftovers
will feed the dogs,
or you will.
A gold dragon to
whoever knocks
my fool's hat off.
(CROWD LAUGHING)
TYWIN: You're in
rather a good mood.
I suppose I am.
I won't ask why.
Small pleasures.
Your Grace. Lord Tywin.
Prince Oberyn.
I don't believe
you have met Ellaria.
This is the Lord
Hand Tywin Lannister,
and Cersei Lannister,
the Queen Regent.
I suppose it is
former Queen Regent now.
Lord Hand and Lady Cersei,
Ellaria Sand.
My lord. My lady.
Charmed.
Can't say I've ever
met a Sand before.
We are everywhere
in Dorne. I have 10,000
brothers and sisters.
Bastards are born of
passion, aren't they?
We don't despise them
in Dorne.
No? How tolerant of you.
I expect it is a relief,
Lady Cersei,
giving up your
regal responsibilities.
Wearing the crown
for so many years
must have left your
neck a bit crooked.
I suppose you'll
never know, Prince Oberyn.
It's a shame
your older brother
couldn't attend the wedding.
Please give him
our regards.
With any luck,
the gout will
abate with time
and he will be
able to walk again.
They call it
the rich man's disease.
A wonder you don't have it.
Noblemen in my
part of the country
don't enjoy the same
lifestyle as our
counterparts in Dorne.
People everywhere
have their differences.
In some places,
the highborn frown
upon those of low birth.
In other places,
the rape and murder
of women and children
is considered distasteful.
What a fortunate
thing for you,
former Queen Regent,
that your daughter
Myrcella has been sent
to live in
the latter sort of place.
(GOBLET CLINKING)
Everyone, silence!
Clear the floor.
There's been
too much amusement
here today.
A royal wedding is
not an amusement.
A royal wedding is history.
Time has come for all of us
to contemplate our history.
My lords,
my ladies,
I give you
King Joffrey,
(SHOUTING)
Renly, Stannis,
Robb Stark, Balon Greyjoy!
The War of the Five Kings!
(CROWD CHEERING)
I'm the rightful king.
King in the North!
Yes!
ACTOR 1: Traitor.
ACTOR 2: You're a traitor.
(LAUGHING)
ACTOR 3: I'm the King
of the Seven Kingdoms!
Let the war begin.
(LAUGHING)
(HOWLS)
Renly, you're no king.
Away, degenerate.
Careful.
(SQUEALS)
Go on.
I want you to
be my prince.
(LAUGHING)
Stannis!
Who's got the
gold now, Stark?
I am
the rightful king.
Challenge me, kraken.
Take that.
I'm drowning!
I am the King in the North!
Not wildfire!
(WHIMPERING)
Pay each of them
20 gold when this is done.
PODRICK: Yes, my lord.
We'll have to
find another way
to thank the King.
Charge!
Ready? Again.
I am the King in the North!
Charge!
Yes!
(CROWD CHEERING)
Your head!
(LAUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
Fine gentlemen.
JOFFREY: Well fought.
Here you are.
Champion's purse.
Though you're not
the champion yet, are you?
A true champion defeats
all the challengers.
Surely there are
others out there
who still dare to
challenge my reign.
Uncle.
How about you?
I'm sure they
have a spare costume.
One taste of combat
was enough for me,
Your Grace.
I would like to keep
what remains of my face.
I think you
should fight him.
This was but a poor imitation
of your own bravery
on the field of battle.
I speak as
a firsthand witness.
Climb down from
the high table with
your new Valyrian sword
and show everyone
how a true king
wins his throne.
Be careful, though.
This one is
clearly mad with lust.
It would be a tragedy for
the King to lose his virtue
hours before
his wedding night.
(CROWD LAUGHS LIGHTLY)
A fine vintage.
Shame that it spilled.
It did not spill.
My love, come back to me.
It's time for
my father's toast.
(SCATTERED APPLAUSE)
JOFFREY: How does
he expect me to
toast without wine?
Uncle, you can be
my cupbearer
seeing as you're
too cowardly to fight.
Your Grace does me
a great honor.
It's not meant as an honor.
Bring me my goblet.
What good is an empty cup?
Fill it.
Kneel.
Kneel before your king.
I said kneel!
Look, the pie.
(APPLAUSE)
My Queen.
(GASPS)
MARGAERY: Wonderful.
My hero.
Can we leave now?
Let's find out.
Uncle.
Where are you going?
You're my cupbearer,
remember?
I thought I might
change out of these
wet clothes, Your Grace.
No, you're perfect
the way you are.
Serve me my wine.
Hurry up.
This pie is dry.
Mmm, good.
Needs washing down.
If it please Your Grace,
Lady Sansa is very tired.
No. (COUGHS)
No, you'll wait here...
(COUGHING)
(STAMMERS)
Your Grace?
(CONTINUES COUGHING)
It's nothing.
(GASPING)
He's choking!
Help the poor boy.
(GASPING)
Idiots, help your king.
Move away!
(CHOKING)
Joffrey!
CERSEI: Help him!
Someone help him!
Joffrey!
(GAGGING)
Come with me now.
CERSEI: Joffrey!
If you want to live,
we have to leave.
Don't touch him!
(GURGLING)
Joffrey.
(GASPING)
Please, Joffrey.
Joffrey, what is it?
Help him!
(SOBBING) My son.
He did this.
He poisoned my son,
your king.
Take him!
(CROWD CLAMORING)