(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CAWING)
(DOGS BARKING)
You're wearing
a black cloak again.
I've been sent to
negotiate with you.
It appears my trusting nature
got the better of me.
It's happened before.
I was hoping your
loyalty was real
when you pledged
yourself to us, Jon Snow.
Truly, I was.
The Halfhand ordered
me to join your army
and bring back
whatever information
I could to Castle Black.
He made me kill him
so you'd trust me.
I was loyal
to him and to my
Night's Watch vows.
All your vows?
She wasn't enough
to turn you, eh?
Were you enough
to turn her?
She put three arrows
in me when I escaped.
Did you see her
again at Castle Black?
Yes.
And?
She's dead.
Your doing?
No.
We'll drink to her.
Of all the ways I'd kill you,
poison would be the last.
Ygritte.
(COUGHING)
That's not wine.
No, it's a proper
northern drink, Jon Snow.
You did well. Fought hard.
Killed some of
our strongest men.
One of our giants
went into your tunnel
and never came out again.
Mag the Mighty.
He's dead.
He killed my friend Grenn.
MANCE: He was their king.
The last of a bloodline
that stretches back
before the First Men.
Grenn came from a farm.
Mag and Grenn.
Grenn and Mag.
MANCE:
Kullback, could I trouble you
for something to eat?
I don't imagine our
guest has eaten anything
for quite some time.
So, you're here to
strike a bargain?
Turn your army
around and go home.
MANCE: You know I know
you're low on arrows,
you're low on oil,
you're low on men.
How many are left, 50?
I told Tormund and Orell.
We have more than 1,000 men.
I showed you everything I had.
The whole army,
100,000 strong.
And what did you do?
You fired on us with
everything you had.
It wasn't much.
As soon as I saw that,
I sent 400 men
to climb the Wall,
an unmanned stretch
five miles west of here.
A lot of them
will die climbing,
but most of them will be over
by the end of the day.
It's me being honest
with you, Jon Snow,
which is more than
you've ever done for me.
My people have bled enough.
We're not here to conquer.
We're here to hide
behind your Wall.
Just like you.
We need your tunnel.
Now we both know
that winter is coming.
And if my people
aren't south of the Wall
when it comes in earnest,
we'll all end up
worse than dead.
You want to strike
a bargain with me?
Here's the bargain.
You go back,
you open the gates to us,
and I swear to you
that no one else will die.
Refuse,
and we'll kill every
last man at Castle Black.
(UNSHEATHING)
Ah!
Oh...
That's why you're here.
I reckon you could do it
before any of
them could stop you.
They'd kill you, of course.
They'd kill you slow.
But you knew that
when you came in here.
Are you capable
of that, Jon Snow?
Killing a man in his own tent
when he's just
offered you peace?
Is that what
the Night's Watch is?
Is that what you are?
(HORN BLOWS)
MAN: Riders coming!
Are you attacking us?
No.
It's like you said,
we don't have the men.
(HORN BLOWING)
(DOGS BARKING)
(MEN YELLING)
Hold! To me! To me!
(YELLING)
(CHAOTIC SHOUTING)
(SCREAMING)
Stand down!
I said my people
have bled enough,
and I meant it.
(MEN SCREAMING)
(SHOUTING)
MAN: Round them up.
Stay with the horses.
You're the
King-beyond-the-Wall?
Do you know who I am?
Never had the pleasure.
This is Stannis Baratheon,
the one true king of
the Seven Kingdoms.
We're not in
the Seven Kingdoms,
and you're not
dressed for this weather.
It is customary to kneel
when surrendering to a king.
We do not kneel.
I'll have
thousands of your men
in chains by nightfall,
have nowhere to put them,
have nothing to feed them.
I'm not here to
slaughter beat dogs.
Their fate
depends on their king.
All the same,
we do not kneel.
Take these men away.
What's a man of
the Night's Watch
doing in a wildling camp?
I was sent to discuss terms
with the King-beyond-the-Wall.
You're speaking to
the one true king, boy.
You will address
him as "Your Grace."
I know he's the king.
My father died for him.
My name is Jon Snow,
Your Grace.
I'm Ned Stark's son.
Your father was
an honorable man.
He was, Your Grace.
What do you think
he'd have done with him?
I was this man's
prisoner once.
He could have tortured me.
He could have killed me.
But he spared my life.
I think my father would
have taken him prisoner,
listened to
what he had to say.
Very well, then.
Take him.
Your Grace.
If my father had seen
the things that I've seen,
he'd also tell you to
burn the dead
before nightfall.
All of them.
(FLIES BUZZING)
I would suggest
milk of the poppy
to ease his pain,
but he is
completely insensate.
Bloody Martells.
PYCELLE: The cause
appears to be manticore venom.
It is.
The Death's Head manticore.
I've read
a great deal about it.
It's a horrible poison.
Usually Mantari in origin.
(SQUISHING)
Oh!
There's nothing to be done.
Yes, there is.
May I ask what you
think you're doing?
Saving him.
PYCELLE:
Your Grace, I wish it
were otherwise,
but Ser Gregor
is beyond saving.
Well, well beyond.
This man is not
even a maester,
let alone grand maester.
That's for the best.
No maester knows
how to save him.
That is exactly
the sort of arrogance
that had him expelled
from the Citadel, Your Grace.
His curiosity was deemed
dangerous and unnatural.
Rightly so, in my opinion.
You're dismissed,
Grand Maester.
(STAMMERING)
But, Your Grace,
this is my laboratory.
Not anymore.
PYCELLE: But...
(SCOFFS)
(DOOR OPENS)
You can save him?
Difficult to say,
Your Grace.
But if my past
work is any guide...
(DOOR SLAMS)
...we stand a chance.
Do everything you can.
Come to me for
anything you need.
Thank you, Your Grace.
You should know,
the process may change him
somewhat.
Will it weaken him?
Oh, no.
Very well, then.
TYWIN: Not another word.
We've been over this.
The matter's closed.
I'm opening it again.
You were betrothed
to Loras Tyrell.
You're still betrothed
And you will
marry Loras Tyrell
as soon as Tommen
marries Margaery.
I will not.
Jaime cannot marry
or inherit lands.
Tyrion's sentence
will be carried out tomorrow.
You have on
several occasions
made great claims
about your commitment
to this family's future.
Your role in that future
is more vital now
than it ever was.
I don't care.
I will stay in King's Landing
where I belong
with my son, the king.
When you were nine years old,
I was called to the capital.
I decided to take
your brother with me
and not you.
You insisted that
you would not be left
at Casterly Rock
under any circumstances.
If you recall...
I'm not interested
in hearing
another one of
your smug stories
about the time you won.
This isn't going to
be one of those times.
Do you think you'll
be the first person
dragged into a Sept
to be married
against her will?
When you marched
into the throne room
to tell me
we'd won
the Battle of Blackwater,
do you remember?
I was sitting on
the Iron Throne
with Tommen.
I was about to give him
essence of nightshade.
That's how far I
was willing to go
when I thought someone awful
had come to take my son away.
Someone awful is
coming to take him away.
No.
Joffrey is dead.
Myrcella's been
sold like livestock.
And now you
want to ship me off
to Highgarden
and steal my boy.
My last boy.
Margaery will
dig her claws in,
you will dig your claws in,
and you'll fight
over him like beasts
until you rip him apart.
I will burn our
house to the ground
before I let that happen.
And how will you do that?
I'll tell everyone
the truth.
What truth
would that be?
You don't know, do you?
You never believed it.
How is that possible?
What am I saying?
Of course it's possible.
How can someone so consumed
by the idea of his family
have any conception
what his actual
family was doing?
We were right
there in front of you,
and you didn't see us.
One real look in
the past 20 years
at your own children
and you would have known.
Known what?
Everything they say
is true
about Jaime and me.
No.
Your legacy is a lie.
No, no, no, no.
I don't believe you.
Yes, you do.
CERSEI: Jaime.
You won.
One fewer brother.
Must be proud of yourself.
There's really nothing
you wouldn't do, is there?
For my family,
no, nothing.
I would do
things for my family
you couldn't imagine.
Tyrion is your family.
He's not.
You don't get to choose.
I do. So do you.
You can choose
the creature that
killed our mother to
come into this world...
Are you really mad enough
to blame him for that?
He didn't
decide to kill her.
He was an infant.
A disease doesn't
decide to kill you.
All the same, you cut
it out before it does.
What do you decide?
What do you choose?
The things I did
to get back to you,
to endure all that,
only to find you...
I choose you.
Those are words.
Yes.
Like the ones I
just said to Father.
I told him.
Told him what?
I told him about us.
You told him?
I told him I won't
marry Loras Tyrell.
I told him I'm
staying right here
with Tommen, with you.
You think he'll
just accept that?
Go and ask him.
What did you say?
I don't want to talk
about Tywin Lannister.
I don't choose
Tywin Lannister.
I don't love
I love my brother.
I love my lover.
People will whisper,
they'll make their jokes.
Let them.
They're all so small,
I can't even see them.
I only see what matters.
Someone will walk in.
I don't care.
(MISSANDEI SPEAKING)
(MAN SPEAKING)
I can speak
the Common Tongue,
if you wish.
You speak it very well.
Before you freed me,
I belonged to
Master Mighdal.
I was tutor to his children.
I taught them
languages and history.
They know a great deal
about your family
because of me.
Little Calla is only seven,
but she admires
you very much.
I hope I can prove
worthy of her admiration.
What can I do for you?
When you took the city,
the children
begged me not to
leave the house.
But Master Mighdal and
I agreed that I must.
So I lost my home.
Now I live
on the streets.
I have outfitted mess halls
to feed all former slaves
and barracks to shelter them.
I do not mean to offend,
Your Grace.
I went to one
of these places.
The young
prey on the old,
take what they want
and beat us if we resist.
My Unsullied will
make them safe again
in short order, my friend,
this I promise you.
Even if they are safe,
who would I be there?
What purpose
would I serve?
With my master,
I was a teacher.
I had the respect and
love of his children.
What is it that
you want from me?
Your Grace,
I ask you to
let me sell myself
back to Master Mighdal.
You want to return
to a man who owned you
like a goat or a chair?
Please, Your Grace.
The young may
rejoice in the new world
you have built for them,
but for those of us
too old to change,
there is only
fear and squalor.
I am not alone.
There are many outside
waiting to beg
the same of you.
I did not take this
city to preside over
the injustice I
fought to destroy.
I took it to
bring people freedom.
But freedom means
making your own choices.
I will allow you
to sign a contract
with your former master.
It may not cover a period
lasting longer than a year.
Thank you, Your Grace.
Thank you.
The masters
will take advantage
of this situation.
The men serving them
will be slaves
in all but name.
Approach, my friend.
(SOBBING)
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
MISSANDEI: (TRANSLATING)
I have brought you...
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
He came from the sky.
MISSANDEI: The black one.
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
The winged shadow.
MISSANDEI:
He came from the sky and...
(MAN SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
MISSANDEI: My girl.
My little girl.
(SOBBING)
DAENERYS: What was her name?
MISSANDEI: Zala, Your Grace.
How old was she?
Three.
(GREY WORM SPEAKING)
(SCREECHING)
(SCREECHES)
AEMON: They came to us
from White Harbor
and Barrowton,
from Fairmarket
and King's Landing,
from north and south,
from east and west.
They died
protecting men,
women, and children
who will never
know their names.
It is for us
to remember them.
Our brothers,
we shall never see
their like again.
ALL:
And now their
watch is ended.
AEMON:
And now their
watch is ended.
(FIRE CRACKLING)
Your old blind
man patched me up.
Why?
He's sworn to treat
all wounded men,
friend or foe.
You want me alive so
you can torture me?
No one's gonna
torture you.
So how do we die?
Hanging? Beheading?
Drop us from
the top of the Wall?
I don't know what
happens to the prisoners.
Who decides?
I suppose Stannis does.
He your king now?
I don't have a king.
You spent too much
time with us, Jon Snow.
You can never be
a kneeler again.
We're gonna burn
the bodies of your dead.
Do you want to say
any words over them?
Words? What kind of words?
Funeral words.
I don't know how
the free folk do it.
TORMUND: Do what?
Say farewell.
The dead can't
hear us, boy.
Snow.
Did you love her?
She loved you.
She told you?
TORMUND: No.
All she ever talked
about was killing you.
That's how I know.
She belongs in the North.
The real North.
You understand me?
(WIND HOWLING)
(GROANING)
We can stop.
We can rest.
We'll rest with
the three-eyed raven.
(GROANS)
We're not going
to make it.
We're already here.
BRAN: Jojen.
Jojen.
Look, Jojen.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
MEERA: Jojen! Come on!
Help them! Now!
MEERA: Hold on to me!
(GRUNTING)
Hang on!
Hodor. Hodor.
Help them!
Hodor.
(GROWLING)
Hodor!
(SNARLS)
(GRUNTS)
Hodor!
(GROWLING)
HODOR: Hodor.
(WHIMPERING)
Hodor!
JOJEN: Bran!
Save yourself, now!
(GRUNTING)
(SHOUTS)
GIRL:
Come with me,
Brandon Stark.
(GASPING)
He is lost.
Come with me
or die with him.
Go with them.
(ICE BREAKING)
(SLICES)
(GROWLING)
(SOBS)
GIRL: They cannot follow us.
The power that moves
them is powerless here.
Who are you?
The First Men
called us the Children,
but we were born
long before them.
Come, he waits for you.
(RUSTLING)
(CROW CAWS)
(CAWS)
You're the three-eyed raven?
I've been many things.
Now I am what you see.
My brother, he led us
to you and now he...
He knew what would happen.
From the moment he left,
he knew and
he went anyway.
How do you know?
I've been watching you.
All of you.
All of your lives.
With 1,000 eyes and one.
Now you've come
to me at last,
Brandon Stark.
Though the hour is late.
I didn't want
anyone to die for me.
He died so you could
find what you have lost.
You're going to
help me walk again?
You will never
walk again.
But you will fly.
Podrick.
Where are the horses?
I hobbled them last night.
What sort of hobble?
A figure eight,
like you taught me.
If you did it
like I taught you,
then the horses would be here.
Thieves, maybe?
It's at least 30 miles
to the Eyrie from here.
You're carrying
the saddlebags.
(ARYA GRUNTING)
People coming.
You can shit later.
There's people coming.
Morning.
I like your sword.
Are we getting close
to the Bloody Gate?
About 10 more miles.
Did you hear that,
Podrick?
Only 10 more miles
to the Bloody Gate.
Are you a knight?
No.
But you know how
to use that sword?
I do.
Does it have a name?
Oathkeeper.
Mine's Needle.
Good name.
Who taught you
how to fight?
My father.
Mine never wanted to.
Said fighting
was for boys.
Mine said the same.
But I kept fighting
the boys anyway.
Kept losing.
Finally my father said,
"If you're going to do it,
you might as well
do it right."
Seven blessings.
I'm Brienne of Tarth.
This is Podrick Payne.
You want something?
That's Sandor Clegane.
The Hound.
You're Arya Stark.
I asked if you
wanted something.
I swore to your mother
I would bring you home to her.
My mother's dead.
BRIENNE: I know.
I wish I could have
been there to protect her.
You're not a Northerner.
No, but I swore
a sacred vow to protect her.
Why didn't you?
She commanded me to bring
Jaime Lannister
back to King's Landing.
You're paid by
the Lannisters.
You're here for
the bounty on me.
I'm not paid by
the Lannisters.
No?
Fancy sword
you've got there.
Where'd you get it?
I've been looking at
Lannister gold
all my life.
Go on,
Brienne of
fucking Tarth.
Tell me that's
not Lannister gold.
Jaime Lannister
gave me this sword.
The Bloody Gate
is 10 miles.
I swore to your mother
by the old gods and the new.
I don't care
what you swore.
Arya!
HOUND:
You heard the girl.
She's not
coming with you.
She is.
You're not
a good listener.
Valyrian steel?
I always wanted
some Valyrian steel.
Come with me, Arya.
I'll take you to safety.
Safety?
Where the fuck's that?
Her aunt
in the Eyrie is dead.
Her mother's dead.
Her father's dead.
Her brother's dead.
Winterfell is
a pile of rubble.
There is no safety,
you dumb bitch.
You don't know that by now,
you're the wrong
one to watch over her.
And that's what you're doing?
Watching over her?
Aye, that's what I'm doing.
(GRUNTS)
(BRIENNE PANTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
I have no wish
to kill you, Ser.
I'm not a knight.
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
(SCREAMING)
(HOUND SCREAMS)
Arya!
Where is she?
PODRICK: She was just here.
Why weren't you watching her?
I was watching you.
I thought you
might need some help.
Which way, Pod?
Which way did she go?
PODRICK: I think that way.
BRIENNE: Arya!
Arya!
(HOUND PANTING)
You still here?
(COUGHS)
Big bitch saved you.
I don't need saving.
No, not you.
You're a real killer.
With your water dancing
and your Needle.
You gonna die?
Unless there's a maester
hiding behind that rock,
aye,
I'm done.
I'd skin you alive
for wine.
Fuck water.
Killed by a woman.
(CHUCKLES)
I bet you like that.
Go on,
go after her.
She'll help you.
Going it alone,
you won't last
a day out there.
I'll last longer
than you.
You remember
where the heart is?
Fuck it. I'm ready.
Go on, girl.
Another name
off your list.
You kept promising me.
I cut down your
butcher's boy.
The ginger.
He was begging
for mercy.
"Please, Ser.
Please don't kill me.
"Please, please."
Bled all over
my horse.
Saddle stunk of
butcher's boy
for weeks.
And your sister.
Your pretty sister.
I should have
taken her.
That night
the Blackwater burned.
I should have
fucked her bloody.
At least I'd have
one happy memory.
Do I have to beg you?
Do it.
Kill me.
Kill me!
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Oh, get on with it,
you son of a whore.
Is that any way to
speak about our mother?
What are you doing?
What do you
think I'm doing?
A galley's waiting in the bay
bound for the Free Cities.
Who's helping you?
Varys.
Varys?
You have more
friends than you thought.
There's a locked door
at the top of the stairs.
Knock on it twice,
then twice again.
Varys will open.
I suppose this
is goodbye, then.
Farewell, little brother.
Jaime.
Thank you.
For my life.
Quickly now.
WOMAN: Tywin?
My lion.
(SHAE GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
(WHIMPERS)
I'm sorry.
(CROSSBOW LEVER DRAGGING)
(DOOR CREAKS)
Tyrion.
Put down the crossbow.
Who released you?
Your brother, I expect.
He always had
a soft spot for you.
Come, we'll go and
talk in my chambers.
This is how you want
to speak to me, hmm?
Shaming your father has
always given you pleasure...
All my life
you've wanted me dead.
Yes.
But you refused to die.
I respect that.
Even admire it.
You fight for
what's yours.
I'd never let
them execute you.
Is that what you fear?
I'll never let
Ilyn Payne take
your head.
You're a Lannister.
You're my son.
I loved her.
Who?
Shae.
Oh, Tyrion.
Put down that crossbow.
I murdered her.
With my own hands.
It doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter?
She was a whore.
Say that word again...
And what?
You'll kill your own
father in the privy?
No.
You're my son.
Now, enough of
this nonsense.
I am your son,
and you sentenced
me to die.
You knew I
didn't poison Joffrey,
but you sentenced
me all the same.
Why?
Enough.
We'll go back to my chambers
and speak with some dignity.
I can't go back there.
She's in there.
You're afraid of
a dead whore?
(GROANS)
You shot me.
You're no son of mine.
I am your son.
I have always
been your son.
(GROANS)
What have you done?
Quickly.
Trust me, my friend.
I've brought you this far.
(BELLS TOLLING)
I want to see
the captain.
You're seeing him.
I want to go north,
to the Wall.
No, you don't.
I can pay.
There is nothing in the North
but ice and war and pirates.
I wouldn't need a cabin.
Please.
I could work
scrubbing the floors...
I'm not going north, child.
I'm going home.
Where's home?
The Free City
of Braavos.
Wait. I have
something else.
More silver won't
make a difference.
It's not silver.
It's iron.
This...
How did you...
Valar Morghulis.
Valar Dohaeris.
Of course,
you shall have a cabin.