You did this!
We have to leave.
CERSEI: Take him!
Where is his wife?
Where's Sansa?
Find her.
Bar the gates of the city.
Seize every ship
in the harbor.
Where is she?
No one leaves the capital!
(BELLS TOLLING)
(SANSA PANTING)
Get in.
Where are we going?
Somewhere safe.
Up you go, my lady.
You'll be fine.
You're stronger
than you know.
(GASPS)
Lord Baelish?
Petyr.
Are you hurt, my lady?
Good.
I'm sure you've had
quite a fright. Rest easy.
The worst is past.
DONTOS: Lord Baelish.
I promised I'd get
her to you safely.
Softly, my friend.
Voices carry over water.
I should get back
before someone thinks
to look for me.
First you'll want your pay.
Ten thousand, was it?
Ten thousand.
(SNAPS FINGERS)
Wait!
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
LITTLEFINGER: Shh.
You don't want
the Queen to hear,
do you?
A thousand gold cloaks
are searching for you.
And if they found you,
how do you think
they would punish
the girl who
murdered the King?
I didn't murder anyone.
I know. But you must admit,
it looks suspicious.
The King who
executed your father,
who tormented you for years,
and you fled
the scene of his murder.
Why did you kill him?
Because he was
a drunk and a fool,
and I don't trust
drunk fools.
He saved me.
Saved you? My lady,
he followed my orders.
Every one of them.
And he did it all for gold.
Money buys a man's
silence for a time.
A bolt in the heart
buys it forever.
He was helping me
because I saved his life.
Yes, and he gave you
a priceless necklace
that once belonged
to his grandmother.
The last legacy
of House Hollard.
I had it made
a few weeks ago.
What did I once tell
you about the capital?
"We're all liars here."
Come, my lady.
I know you've had
a difficult day.
But you're safe now.
I promise you that.
You're safe with me,
sailing home.
So am I the queen?
More than
you were with Renly.
Less than
you would have been
if Joffrey had
done you the courtesy
of consummating
the marriage before dying.
This would not be
an opportune moment
to press the issue.
Clawing at his own throat,
looking to his mother
to make it stop...
It was horrible.
The world is overflowing
with horrible things.
But they're all a tray
of cakes next to death.
They brought me
your grandfather's body
when he died.
Made me look at it.
What was it like?
They took me to
the Great Hall.
There he was.
The man I'd married
and suffered to
father my children.
A great doughy lump
I'd sat next to
at endless dinners
and tedious gatherings.
There he was,
lying on a table.
One of my husbands
preferred the company of men
and was stabbed
through the heart.
Another was
happiest torturing animals
and was poisoned at
our wedding feast.
I must be cursed.
Nonsense.
Your circumstances
have improved markedly.
You may not have
enjoyed watching him die,
but you enjoyed it more
than you would have enjoyed
being married to him,
I can promise you that.
But I would have
been the queen.
Our alliance
with the Lannisters
remains every bit
as necessary to them
as it is unpleasant for us.
You did wonderful
work on Joffrey.
The next one
should be easier.
TYWIN: Your brother is dead.
Do you know
what that means?
I'm not trying
to trick you.
It means I'll become king.
Yes, you will
become king.
What kind of king do
you think you'll be?
A good king?
TYWIN: Mmm.
I think so as well.
You've got the right
temperament for it.
But what makes
a good king? Hmm?
What is a good king's
single most
important quality?
This is hardly
the place or the time.
Holiness?
Hmm.
Baelor the Blessed
was holy.
And pious.
He built this Sept.
He also named
a 6-year-old boy High Septon
because he thought
the boy could work miracles.
He ended up
fasting himself
into an early grave
because food was
of this world and
this world was sinful.
Hmm.
Justice.
Mmm.
A good king must be just.
Orys I was just.
Everyone
applauded his reforms,
nobles and commoners alike.
But he wasn't just for long.
He was murdered in his sleep
after less than a year
by his own brother.
Was that truly
just of him?
To abandon his subjects
to an evil that
he was too
gullible to recognize?
No.
What about strength?
Yes.
Strength.
King Robert was strong.
He won the rebellion
and crushed
the Targaryen dynasty.
And he attended
three Small Council
meetings in 17 years.
He spent his time
whoring and hunting
and drinking
until the last two
killed him.
So, we have a man
who starves
himself to death,
a man who lets his
own brother murder him,
and a man who thinks
that winning and ruling
are the same thing.
What do they all lack?
Wisdom.
Yes!
Wisdom is what
makes a good king.
Yes.
But what is wisdom? Hmm?
A house with great
wealth and fertile lands
asks you for your protection
against another house
with a strong navy that
could one day oppose you.
How do you know
which choice is wise
and which isn't?
You've any experience
of treasuries and granaries
or shipyards and soldiers?
No.
TYWIN: Of course not.
A wise king
knows what he knows
and what he doesn't.
You're young.
A wise young king
listens to his counselors
and heeds their advice
until he comes of age.
And the wisest kings
continue to listen to
them long afterwards.
Your brother was
not a wise king.
not a good king.
If he had been,
perhaps
he'd still be alive.
Now, as the king,
you will have to marry.
Do you understand why?
TOMMEN: A king needs a queen.
TYWIN: Yes, but why?
To further
the family line.
Do you know
how that happens?
TOMMEN: Yes.
TYWIN: But has anyone
explained the details
to you?
TOMMEN: I don't think so.
It's all relatively
straightforward.
How are you?
I'm all right.
You are. You will be.
I'll see to that.
Please give
the Queen a moment
alone with her son.
Yes, my lord.
All of you.
(SNAPS FINGERS)
(SOBS)
It was Tyrion.
He killed him.
He told me he would.
"A day will come when you
think you are safe and happy,
"and your joy
will turn to ashes
in your mouth."
That's what he said to me.
You saw it.
You saw Joff point at
him just before he...
I don't know what I saw.
Avenge him.
Avenge our son.
Kill Tyrion.
Tyrion's my brother.
Our brother.
There'll be a trial.
We'll get to the
truth of what happened.
I don't want a trial.
He'll squirm
his way to freedom
given the chance.
I want him dead.
(SOBBING) Please, Jaime.
You have to.
He was our son.
(SNIFFLING)
Our baby boy.
(GASPS)
You're a hateful woman.
Why have the gods made me
love a hateful woman?
Jaime, not here, please.
Please.
(FABRIC RIPS)
Stop it.
No.
Stop.
Stop. It's not right.
(GRUNTS)
It's not right.
I don't care.
(SOBBING)
Don't.
I don't care.
Jaime, don't.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
ARYA: Gonna rain soon.
(URINATING)
Where are we?
Near Fairmarket, I think.
You think?
You don't have a map?
No.
Maybe we should get one.
Just point out the next
map shop you see,
and I'll buy you one.
How far is it to the Eyrie?
Far.
And you're sure we're
going the right way?
Believe me, girl,
I want you there
as soon as I can.
Get my gold, be on my way.
Where?
Why do you care?
Might book passage
across the Narrow Sea.
Fight as a sellsword.
Second Sons, could be.
Seems like a good fit for me.
I'd like to see
Braavos one day.
Why Braavos?
I have friends there.
(BLOWS NOSE) I doubt it.
MAN: Seven blessings to you.
What do you want?
This is my land.
If I'm standing on it,
it's my land.
We were just
watering the horses.
We'll be on our way.
Forgive my father.
He was wounded
fighting in the war.
Our cottage burned
down while he was gone,
and my mother with it.
He's never been the same.
Which house
did he fight for?
The Tullys of Riverrun.
There's a storm coming.
You'll be wanting
a roof tonight.
There's fresh hay
in the barn.
And Sally here makes
rabbit stew just
like her mom used to do.
We don't have much,
but any man that
bled for House Tully
is welcome to it.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(RAIN PATTERING)
MAN: We ask the Father
to judge us with mercy,
accepting our human frailty.
We ask the Mother
to bless our crops,
so we may feed ourselves
and all who come to our door.
We ask the Warrior
to give us courage
in these days of
strife and turmoil.
We ask the Maiden to
protect Sally's virtue
and keep her from
the clutches of depravity.
You going to do all
seven of the fuckers?
ARYA: Father!
We ask the Smith to
strengthen our hands
and our backs,
so we may finish
the work required of us.
We ask the Crone to
guide us on our journey
from darkness to darkness.
And we ask the Stranger
not to kill us
in our beds tonight
for no damn reason at all.
I'm so sorry.
(SLURPING LOUDLY)
Really good.
MAN: Did you fight
at the Twins?
Call that a fight?
Slaughtering
livestock more like.
The Red Wedding,
they're calling it.
Walder Frey committed
sacrilege that day.
He shared bread and
salt with the Starks.
He offered them guest right.
HOUND: Guest right
don't mean much anymore.
It means something to me.
The gods will
have their vengeance.
Frey will burn in
the seventh hell
for what he did.
Things were different
when Hoster Tully
ruled the Riverlands.
We had good years
and bad years,
same as anyone,
but we were safe.
Now with the Freys,
raiders come plundering,
steal our food,
steal our silver.
I was gonna send Sally north
to stay with my brother,
but the North's
no better. The whole
country's gone sour.
You got any ale?
Afraid not.
How can a man not
keep ale in his home?
You look like
you could really
swing that sword.
A real warrior
with proper training.
Those raiders wouldn't
stand a chance against you.
How would it be
if you stayed on
till the new moon?
I could use a man to
help with the farm work.
Sally does what she can,
but she can't
lift a bale of hay.
And if any thieves came
looking for easy pickings,
one look at you,
I bet they'd
run the other way.
Meaning no offense.
What'll you pay?
I don't have much.
But I have
hidden a bit of silver
from the bandits.
Fair wages for fair work?
Fair wages for fair work.
(CHICKENS CLUCKING)
(MEN ARGUING INDISTINCTLY)
(PUNCH LANDS)
MAN: Ahhh!
(SALLY SCREAMS)
(MAN GROANING)
ARYA: What did you do?
HOUND: Get your horse
saddled.
You told me you
weren't a thief.
I wasn't.
He took us in.
He fed us and you...
Aye, he took us in.
He's a good man,
and his daughter
makes a nice stew.
And they'll both
be dead come winter.
You don't know that.
I do.
He's weak.
He can't protect himself.
They'll both be
dead come winter.
Dead men
don't need silver.
You're the worst shit
in the Seven Kingdoms.
There's plenty
worse than me.
I just understand
the way things are.
How many Starks
they got to behead
before you figure it out?
RANGER: Raper.
Horse thief.
Ninth-born son.
Raper. Thief.
Thief and raper.
ALLISER: There he is,
Sam the Slayer.
JANOS: Going to visit
your wildling whore?
She's not a whore.
No?
Maybe I'll give
her a copper tonight
and find out.
SAMWELL: They all
think I'm lying.
About what?
Killing the White Walker.
You're not lying.
I'll never forget
the way it screamed.
But you're the only one
that saw it.
And they all think
you're just a...
A what?
A wildling.
GILLY: My father
hated that word.
It's not a very nice word.
I don't know.
It makes me sound
a bit dangerous,
doesn't it?
(BABY COOING)
So, are you all right?
No one bothering you?
I get a lot of looks.
I hear them
making their jokes.
But no one's touched me,
if that's what you mean.
I worry about it
sometimes.
All the time.
Why do you worry about it?
One hundred men,
one woman.
They've got other
things to think about.
That's the only thing
they think about.
You're being silly.
I'm not being silly.
There's 100 men
lying awake at night,
picturing you.
What about you?
What about me?
Gilly?
I worry about you.
Thank you.
For what?
For worrying about me.
I don't know
if you're safe here.
They're my brothers,
but some of them
were thieves before
they came here.
Some of them were rapers.
You saw what they did
at your father's keep.
So what are you saying?
Maybe you'd be
safer in Mole's Town.
Are you bored of me?
Bored of you?
I...
I want to protect you.
I'll get these to Hobb.
Keep an eye on little Sam.
(MEN YELLING DISTANTLY)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Your Grace.
You're a literary man now.
What do you make of that?
(INAUDIBLE)
Joffrey?
"The usurper,
Joffrey Baratheon."
I said those words
when I tossed
a leech into the fire,
filled with bastard blood.
A bastard you set free.
I am now faced with
a great opportunity,
and I am powerless to
take advantage of it.
I will find you an army,
Your Grace.
I've been working
day and night...
What progress have you made?
I've rallied House Peasebury
to your cause.
House Peasebury.
House Musgood.
And House Haigh.
House Haigh.
(PIECES CLATTER)
They don't have
enough men between them
to raid a pantry.
Westeros is not the world,
Your Grace.
We need to look east
for ships and men.
10,000 skilled soldiers
fight for the Golden Company.
The Golden Company?
They've never
broken a contract.
They're sellswords.
We're willing to
use blood magic
to put you on the throne,
but we're not willing
to pay men to fight?
Now the Red Woman's
magic is real.
Her visions and
prophecies may be, too,
but I've never heard of
visions and prophecies
winning a war.
Soldiers win wars.
Soldiers on the ground.
It's dirty on the ground.
We don't have any gold.
Not yet.
If I do not press my claim,
my claim will be forgotten.
I will not become
a page in someone
else's history book.
I'm running out
of time, Ser Davos.
Which means you're
running out of time.
(KNOCKING)
You're late.
DAVOS: I'm sorry, Princess.
I thought
you weren't coming.
The Hand of the King
doesn't have
much leisure time.
You won't be
a very good Hand if you
see the word knight
and say "ka-nigit."
That happened once,
weeks ago.
You're your father's
daughter, no mistake.
Bloody relentless,
the both of you.
It's a new one today.
Lots of tricky words.
But I think you can manage.
You'll never read well
if you move your lips.
That's how children do it.
(SIGHS)
"The Life and Adventures
of Elyo Grivas
"First Sword of Braavos."
Thank you very much.
I like this one.
It's full of
swordfights and pirates.
You were a pirate once.
No, I was a smuggler.
What's the difference?
If you're a famous smuggler,
you're not doing it right.
My father says
a criminal is a criminal.
Your father
lacks an appreciation
of the finer points
of bad behavior.
So do the Braavosi.
You've sailed to Braavos?
Of course.
Almost got beheaded by
a First Sword of Braavos.
I tried to explain to him
the difference between
pirates and smugglers,
but he didn't seem
any more interested
in the distinction
than your father.
I suppose if you work
for the Iron Bank of Braavos
and each one of
your gold barges
is worth half a kingdom,
you tend not to
be overly concerned
with the kind
of distinction...
What was that for?
I need you to
write a message.
You should write
it yourself.
It's good practice.
It's too important for me.
I need a smart person
to do it. Go on.
To the offices of
the Iron Bank of Braavos,
from Stannis Baratheon,
the one true king
of Westeros.
But that's not you.
I need to
get their attention.
Go. Write.
(BABY COOING)
He's seen some adventures,
hasn't he?
(BABY CRYING)
(PEOPLE TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Precious little thing.
Thank you.
What's his name?
Sam.
Lovely.
That the daddy?
No.
Where's the daddy?
He's dead.
Where you from?
North of here.
North of here?
You a fucking wildling?
WOMAN: Only room and board?
That's right.
She'll clean and cook
and look after
the other girls' babies.
Could find other
work for her, too.
No other work.
WOMAN: There'd be money.
Give you a piece of it.
No other work.
I promise to come
back and visit
whenever I can.
You'll be safer here.
Who's gonna protect you
at Castle Black? Me?
You protected me
north of the Wall.
This is different.
They're brothers of
the Night's Watch,
and I can't just
stab them in the back.
And I can't run away,
which is what
we did at Craster's.
(BABY CRYING)
You have to trust me.
It's for the best.
Best for you.
Oh, Gilly.
Please don't...
(BABY CRYING)
(PEOPLE MOANING)
Greedy.
No?
I'm sorry. You're
lovely, I just never
acquired the taste.
You're calling my beauty
an acquired taste?
That's quite all right,
lover. There's
more for you.
Your loss.
You like them both the same?
Boys and girls?
Does that surprise you?
Everyone has a preference.
Then everyone is missing
half the world's pleasure.
The gods made that,
and it delights me.
The gods made this,
When it comes to war,
I fight for Dorne.
When it comes to love,
I don't choose sides.
I hope I have
as much stamina
when I'm your age.
What are you, 25?
Children.
(CHUCKLES)
Someday, if you're lucky,
you will wake up and
realize you are old.
That pretty ass
of yours will sag,
your belly will grow soft,
and your back will
ache in the night,
and gray hairs will
sprout from your ears.
No one will
want you anymore.
Make sure you've
fucked your fill
before that day.
Did you?
He is a prince of Dorne.
Girls and boys will
line up to fuck him
till the day he dies.
They will all have
to line up behind you.
(DOOR OPENS)
TYWIN: Prince Oberyn.
Lord Tywin.
May we have the room?
Call my name
if you need me, lover.
Would you like to sit?
No, thank you.
Some wine?
(DOOR CLOSES)
I'm sorry about
your grandson.
Are you?
I don't believe that
a child is responsible
for the sins of his father.
Or his grandfather.
An awful way to die.
Which way is that?
Are you interrogating me,
Lord Tywin?
Some believe the King choked.
Some believe
the sky is blue because
we live inside the eye
of a blue-eyed giant.
The King was poisoned.
I hear you studied
poisons at the Citadel.
I did. This is why I know.
Your hatred for my family
is rather well-known.
You arrive at the capital,
an expert in poisoning,
some days later
my grandson dies
of poisoning.
Rather suspicious.
Why haven't you
thrown me in a dungeon?
You spoke with Tyrion
in this very brothel
on the day that you arrived.
What did you discuss?
You think
we conspired together?
What did you discuss?
The death of my sister.
For which you blame me.
She was raped and murdered
by the Mountain.
The Mountain
follows your orders.
Of course I blame you.
Here I stand unarmed,
unguarded.
Should I be concerned?
You are unarmed and
unguarded because you
know me better than that.
I am a man of reason.
If I cut your throat today,
I will be drawn and
quartered tomorrow.
Men at war commit
all kinds of crimes
without their
superiors' knowledge.
So you deny involvement
in Elia's murder?
Categorically.
I would like to
speak with the Mountain.
I'm sure he would
enjoy speaking with you.
He might not enjoy it
as much as
he thinks he would.
I could arrange
for this meeting.
But you want
something in return.
There will be
a trial for my son
and, as custom dictates,
three judges will
render a verdict.
I will preside.
Mace Tyrell will serve
as the second judge.
I would like you
to be the third.
Why?
Not long ago,
the Tyrells sided
with Renly Baratheon.
Declared themselves
enemies of the throne.
Now they are
our strongest allies.
Well, you made
the Tyrell girl a queen.
Asking me to judge
at your son's trial
isn't quite as tempting.
I would also invite you
to sit on the Small Council
to serve as one of
the new king's
principal advisors.
I never realized
you had such respect
for Dorne, Lord Tywin.
We are not the Seven
Kingdoms until Dorne
returns to the fold.
The King is dead.
The Greyjoys are
in open rebellion.
A wildling army
marches on the Wall.
And in the east,
a Targaryen girl
has three dragons.
Before long,
she will turn her
eyes to Westeros.
Only the Dornish
managed to resist
Aegon Targaryen
and his dragons.
You're saying you need us?
That must be hard
for you to admit.
We need each other.
You help me serve justice
to the King's assassins,
and I will help you
serve justice to Elia's.
(DOOR UNLOCKS)
Podrick.
Apologies for the stench.
I brought you
some wine, my lord,
but they took it from me.
A noble effort.
They didn't find
the candles, though.
A quill, some parchment,
duck sausage, almonds,
and some hard cheese.
You're a good lad.
Any word of Shae?
I've heard nothing, my lord.
I suppose
that's a good thing.
What are they saying
about me out there?
You're to stand
trial in a fortnight
for murdering the King.
Do you believe
I murdered Joffrey?
No, my lord.
You didn't?
Gods, no.
The world is
a better place without him,
but I had
nothing to do with it.
I would like to think
if I were arranging
a royal assassination,
I'd plan it in such
a way that I wouldn't
be standing there,
gawking like a fool
when the King died.
Trial in a fortnight.
Have they announced
the judges yet?
Your father.
Of course.
Mace Tyrell.
Who will vote exactly
as my father
tells him to vote.
And Prince Oberyn of Dorne.
Oberyn?
(TYRION SCOFFS)
Give it to my father.
He never fails
to take advantage
of a family tragedy.
I'm supposed to get
a list of names from you,
my lord.
Anyone who might
testify on your behalf.
Oh, I can call
my own witnesses?
How generous of them.
Very well, my wife. Sansa.
My lord, she's gone.
Gone?
No one's seen her
since the wedding.
You don't think she...
No one had more
cause to kill Joffrey
than Sansa,
but the girl
is no assassin.
Whoever killed the King
wanted me to
lose my head for it.
And with my
wife's disappearance,
it makes me seem
that much more guilty.
Podrick.
Yes, my lord?
They'll be following you now.
Who will?
I don't know.
They. The ominous they.
The man pulling the strings.
Or woman. My father.
Maybe Joffrey was
too much work for him.
Sweet Tommen will be
so much easier to handle.
Whenever something
bad happens to me,
I assume it's my sister
that had a hand in it.
But say what you
will of Cersei,
she loves her children.
She is the only one
I'm certain
had nothing to do
with this murder.
Which makes it unique
as King's Landing
murders go.
Any other witnesses,
my lord?
Varys could vouch
for me, if he dared.
He's already been called
as a witness for the Queen.
Of course. Fetch Bronn.
I have a job for him.
I've already asked, my lord.
They won't let him see you.
Why not?
They say he's
a known cutthroat
and your close associate.
He's under
investigation himself.
And my brother?
Will they at least
allow me to see Jaime?
I'll ask, my lord.
There's something else,
my lord.
A man,
I didn't know his face,
he came to ask if I'd
testify against you.
Said I'd be named
Ser Podrick Payne
if I told the judges
you'd bought a poison
called the strangler.
Ser Podrick Payne?
Has a nice ring to it.
What did you tell him?
I didn't tell them
anything, my lord.
Are you going to
accept their offer?
My lord.
Testifying against me
wasn't a suggestion.
If they can't
tempt you with honey,
they'll choose
something less sweet.
You've been good
to me, my lord.
Pod, the trial's
in a fortnight.
They'll want
an answer before that.
I already gave them
an answer, my lord.
I will not have you
dying on my behalf.
Do you hear me?
If I have to take
that long walk to
the executioner's block,
I don't want to see
your head already mounted.
My lord.
Pod, I am giving
you an order.
Go and find my brother.
Tell him I need him.
And get yourself
out of King's Landing
before it's too late.
Pod!
This is farewell.
Farewell, my lord.
(DOOR OPENS)
Pod.
There has never lived
a more loyal squire.
(DOOR CLOSES)
BOY: Mother says
it's time to eat.
What's she got boiling?
Wait. Let me guess.
BOTH: Potatoes.
No one boils a potato
better than your mom.
She got...
MAN: The wildlings!
Guymon!
Hide.
Hide!
MAN: Run!
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING)
(CHAOTIC HUBBUB)
(GRUNTS)
You know how to
get to Castle Black?
Yes.
Those your parents?
Open your eyes.
I'm going to eat them.
Do you hear me?
I'm going to
eat your dead mama
and your dead papa.
Go tell the crows
at Castle Black.
YARWYCK: We need to
teach them a lesson
about the way
we deal with their kind.
MEN: Aye! Aye!
YARWYCK: Three dozen
bodies with
slit throats tossed
off the top of the Wall.
Seems like that
would be a good lesson.
ALL: Aye!
If we go after them,
we'll be giving them
what they want.
They want to draw us out,
pick us off a few at a time.
We have just
over 100 men.
And that's including
stewards and builders.
And me. We can't afford
to lose a single man.
We must remember
our first responsibility.
We are
the watchers on the Wall.
There's got to be
a way to protect them.
You're a champion
of the common people,
Lord Snow.
What do you say
to Brother Pyp's
proposition?
Mance Rayder is coming.
If the wildlings
breach the Wall,
they'll roll over everything
and everyone for 1,000 miles
before they reach
an army that can stop them.
We need to shore
up Castle Black
and defend the Wall.
That is our job.
(HORN BLOWS)
Rangers returning.
MAN: Help him.
Thought you'd have
blue eyes by now.
ALLISER:
What took you so long?
We were held up.
By what?
Chains.
We were guests
of the mutineers
at Craster's Keep.
And the mutineers stayed?
They're not going anywhere.
They've got Craster's
food and his wives.
DOLOROUS EDD: Poor girls.
Never thought
they'd miss their daddy.
Karl's running things now.
He's the one who put a knife
through Craster's mouth.
We need to ride north
and kill them all.
We just went over this, boy.
Justice can wait.
It's not about justice.
I told the wildlings
we had over 1,000 men
at Castle Black alone.
Karl and the others
know the truth
as well as we do.
How long do you think
they'll keep that
information to themselves
when the wildlings
are peeling
their fingernails off?
Mance has all he needs
to crush us, he just
doesn't know it yet.
As soon as he gets
his hands on them,
he will.
Then he'll throw
his full strength at us.
And even if every one of us
kills 100 wildlings,
there's still not a thing
we can do to stop them.
I don't think I can
kill 100 wildlings.
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
DAENERYS: Are they attacking?
JORAH: A single rider.
A champion of Meereen.
They want you to
send your own champion
against him.
(CHEERING)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(SPEAKS VALYRIAN)
What is he doing?
I believe he means to...
(CROWD CHEERING)
(SIGHS)
(LAUGHING)
He says that
we're an army of men
without man parts.
He claims you are
no woman at all,
but a man who
hides his cock in
his own arsehole.
Ignore him, Your Grace.
These are
meaningless words.
They're not
meaningless
if half the city
you intend to take
is listening to them.
(MAN CONTINUES
SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
I have something to say
to the people of Meereen.
First, I will need
this one to be quiet.
Do I have a champion?
Your Grace, I've won
more single combats
than any man alive.
Which is why you
must remain by my side.
I've been by your side
longer than any
of them, Khaleesi.
Let me stand for
you today as well.
You are my most
trusted advisor,
my most valued general,
and my dearest friend.
I will not
gamble with your life.
DAARIO: I was
the last to join your army.
I'm not your general
or a member of
your Queensguard
or the commander
of your Unsullied.
My mother was a whore.
I come from nothing.
I will return to nothing.
Let me kill
this man for you.
Very well.
You have quite an audience.
Make it worth their while.
He is very brave,
Your Grace.
Yes, win or lose,
as long as the whole
city is watching.
You sure you
don't want a horse?
DAARIO: Why would
I want a horse?
Horses are faster than men.
Horses are
dumber than men.
(WHINNIES)
(CHEERING)
(GRUNTS)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(SHOUTING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)