A cripple?
You let a cripple escape?
The boy can't walk,
but somehow he
slipped past you?
The giant must have took him.
The giant?
Hodor?
Oh, that's all right, then.
You let a halfwit
escape with a cripple.
And Rickon, too?
The little one?
Gone, along with
the wildling woman.
The one you were fucking.
(GRUNTING)
(MAN GROANING)
(PANTING)
Right.
Get the horses
and the hounds.
(DOGS BARKING)
Come on, find the scent.
Where they going?
Halt!
Enjoying your first hunt?
So far, hunting seems
very similar to riding,
my lord.
With hunting,
there's blood at the end.
They're little boys.
I was a little boy
when I was torn away
from my home and brought here.
So I kept my word.
I never ran away.
If I find them soon enough,
I won't hurt them.
Well, I'll hurt them,
but I won't kill them.
Those boys are
of far more value
to you alive than dead.
They have no
value to me missing.
Robb will have sent a force
to retake Winterfell by now.
Robb's in the Riverlands.
My sister's in Deepwood Motte.
She'll get here
long before they do.
And Ned Stark always said
500 men could hold
Winterfell against 10,000.
(DOG BARKING)
MAN: We have a scent!
The hounds have the scent.
Come, Maester,
don't look so grim.
It's all just a game.
OSHA: We should
have took more food.
We couldn't risk
going to the kitchens.
Those people all love you.
They would have
given you whatever you needed.
And if Theon found out,
he'd hang them.
The boy can't
survive on walnuts.
I'm fine.
We've been walking
since before sunrise.
Even Hodor will tire.
Hodor.
Even you,
sweet giant.
(CHUCKLES) Hodor.
(CHILDREN SHOUTING)
Wait, I know that farm.
I sent those two
Winterfell orphans there.
Jack and Billy.
They'll give us some food.
We can't risk it.
If Theon tracks us here,
he'll torture them
until he finds
out where we are.
Billy climbs a tree
better than anyone.
You've never seen me
climb a tree, little man.
They'll be after
us with hounds.
We got a good start on them,
but we can't
outrun hounds forever.
Did you pull a knife
on me in the night?
What's the matter?
Can't be the first
time you pressed your bone
against a woman's arse.
Let's move.
It is the first time.
How old are you, boy?
I'm a man of
the Night's Watch.
You're a boy who's
never been with a girl.
Don't your
stones start to hurt
if your bone never gets...
Don't call them that.
What, stones?
Or bone?
Neither.
Both.
Move!
I heard they get all
swollen and bruised
if you don't use them.
Of course, maybe that's
just what the lads say
when they want me
feeling sorry for them.
As if I'd feel sorry for them.
Are there no girl crows?
There are no women of
the Night's Watch, no.
So the lads just do
it with each other?
No.
Never?
Never.
We swore an oath.
You have sheep at the Wall?
With your hands, then?
No wonder you're
all so miserable.
Would you please shut up?
You think you're
better than me, crow.
I'm a free woman.
You're a free woman?
I might be your prisoner,
but I'm a free woman.
If you're my prisoner,
you're not
a free woman.
That's what "prisoner" means.
And you think you're free?
You swore some stupid oath
and now you can
never touch a girl.
It was my choice
to say the words.
So you don't like girls?
Of course I like girls.
But you chose
never to touch them.
That's the price you pay
if you want to be
a man of the Night's Watch.
So instead of
getting naked with a girl,
you'd prefer to
invade our lands...
Invade your lands?
Wildlings raid our
lands all the time.
Some of them tried to
kill my little brother,
a crippled boy!
They're not your lands!
We've been here
the whole time.
You lot came along and
just put up a big wall
and said it was yours.
My father was Ned Stark.
I have the blood
of the First Men.
My ancestors lived here,
same as yours.
So why are you fighting us?
Go on.
MAN: Now I want you to tell me
what happened.
GUARD: Come on, this way.
(MAN SCREAMING)
MAN: Come on, speak up.
Speak up.
(SNIFFS)
Wolfsbane.
A rare substance.
This is no common assassin.
We hanged 20 men last night.
I don't care if
you hanged 100.
A man tried to kill me.
I want his name
and I want his head.
We think it was
an infiltrator from
the Brotherhood
Without Banners.
Pretentious name
for a band of outlaws.
We can't allow
rebels behind our lines
to harass us with impunity.
We look like fools and
they look like heroes.
That's how kings fall.
I want them dead, every one.
Killing them
isn't the problem.
It's finding them.
Have you gone soft, Clegane?
I always thought you
had a talent for violence.
Burn the villages,
burn the farms.
Let them know what it means
to choose the wrong side.
Mmm.
Is that mutton?
Yes, my lord.
(DOOR CLOSING)
Don't like mutton.
I'll bring something else.
Leave it.
Are you hungry?
No.
Of course you are.
Eat.
I'll eat in the kitchen later.
It's bad manners to
refuse a lord's offer.
Sit.
Eat.
You're small for your age.
I suppose you've been underfed
your whole life.
I eat a lot.
I just don't grow.
Mmm.
This will be my last war.
Win or lose.
Have you ever lost before?
Do you think I'd
be in my position
if I had lost a war?
But this is the one
I'll be remembered for.
The War of Five Kings,
they're calling it.
My legacy will be determined
in the coming months.
Do you know what legacy means?
It's what you pass
down to your children
and your children's children.
It's what remains of
you when you're gone.
Harren the Black thought
this castle
would be his legacy.
The greatest
fortress ever built.
The tallest towers,
the strongest walls.
The Great Hall had
35 hearths.
Thirty-five.
Can you imagine?
Look at it now.
A blasted ruin.
Do you know what happened?
Dragons?
Yes.
Dragons happened.
Harrenhal was
built to withstand
an attack from the land.
A million men could have
marched on these walls,
and a million men
would have been repelled.
But an attack from
the air with dragon fire...
Mmm-mmm.
Harren and all his sons
roasted alive
within these walls.
Aegon Targaryen
changed the rules.
That's why every child alive
still knows his name
300 years after his death.
Aegon and his sisters.
Mmm?
It wasn't just
Aegon riding his dragon.
It was Rhaenys
and Visenya, too.
Correct.
A student of history,
are you?
Rhaenys rode Meraxes.
Visenya rode Vhagar.
I'm sure I knew
that when I was a boy.
Visenya Targaryen
was a great warrior.
She had a Valyrian steel sword
she called Dark Sister.
Hmm.
She's a heroine of yours,
I take it?
Aren't most
girls more interested
in the pretty
maidens from the songs?
Jonquil with
the flowers in her hair?
Most girls are idiots.
(LAUGHS)
You remind me of my daughter.
Where did you learn
all this stuff about
Visenya and her
Valyrian steel sword?
From my father.
He was a well-read stonemason.
Can't say I've ever met
a literate stonemason.
Have you met many stonemasons,
my lord?
Careful now, girl.
I enjoy you,
but be careful.
Take that back
to the kitchen.
Eat what you want.
And, girl.
"M'lord."
Lowborn girls say "m'lord,"
not "my lord."
If you're going to
pose as a commoner,
you should do it properly.
My mother served Lady Dustin
for many years, my lord.
She taught me how
to speak proper...
Properly.
You're too smart
for your own good.
Has anyone told you that?
Yes.
Go on.
I beg pardon, ser.
I should have
come to you after
to thank you for saving me.
You were so brave.
Brave?
A dog doesn't need
courage to chase off rats.
Does it give you
joy to scare people?
No, it gives me
joy to kill people.
Spare me. You can't tell me
Lord Eddard
Stark of Winterfell
never killed a man.
It was his duty.
He never liked it.
Is that what he told you?
He lied.
Killing is
the sweetest thing there is.
Why are you always so hateful?
You'll be glad of
the hateful things I do
someday when you're queen
and I'm all that
stands between you
and your beloved king.
I've demanded
a meeting of the Thirteen.
One of them did this
or knows who did.
You are one of the Thirteen.
If I wanted your dragons,
I would have taken them.
They mean nothing
to me on their own.
Nothing?
They're more valuable
than anything in the world.
Shall we look inside my vault
and see what
selling your dragons
would buy me I
cannot buy already?
We will get them back.
There is no we,
so why would you
help me get them back?
I took you under my protection
in front of
the rulers of my city.
A man is what others
say he is and no more.
If they say that Xaro
Xhoan Daxos is a liar,
my word is worth nothing.
I cannot let this
thing happen to you
under my roof.
But it did happen
under your roof.
Khaleesi, many times in
my life, I have been...
I don't care
where you've been.
You think we're savages
because we don't
live in stone castles.
We can't make
steel as good as yours,
it's true, but...
We're free.
If someone tried to tell us
we couldn't lie
down as man and woman,
we'd shove
a spear up his arse.
We don't go
serving some shit king
who's only king
because his father was.
No.
No, you serve Mance Rayder,
the King beyond the Wall.
We chose Mance Rayder
to lead us.
He was a crow, same as you,
but he wanted to be free.
You could be free, too.
You don't need to
live your whole life
taking commands from old men.
Wake up when you
want to wake up.
I could show you
the streams to fish,
the woods to hunt.
Build yourself a cabin
and find a woman to lie
with in the night.
You're a pretty lad.
The girls would claw
each other's eyes out
to get naked with you.
Walk.
I could teach you
how to do it.
I know how to do it.
You know nothing, Jon Snow.
And what did she say?
She admired your spirit,
Your Grace.
And what then?
She...
If every man were
held accountable for the
actions of every
distant relative, Ser Alton,
we'd all hang.
She tore the paper
in half, Your Grace.
You've acted with honor.
I thank you for it.
Lord Karstark,
see that Ser Alton's
pen is clean,
and give him a hot supper.
Ser Alton's pen is occupied,
Your Grace.
The prisoners
from the Yellow Fork.
Too many prisoners.
Is there room for Ser Alton?
Does he need to lie down?
Have the men
build him a new pen.
Put him in with
the Kingslayer for now.
Have your boy watch over them.
Torrhen.
That will be all.
Your Grace.
A minute of your time?
I've been treating
your wounded men.
And my enemies,
as some of my bannermen
are fond of mentioning.
They're not my enemies.
That's what I tell
my bannermen.
I've already run
through the supplies
I brought with me.
Some are easily replaced.
Egg yolks, turpentine,
oil of roses.
But some are not.
I need silk for stitching.
I need fennel root
for those with fever,
willow bark. Mostly I
need milk of the poppy.
You saw what it was like
to amputate
a foot without any.
I assume there will
be more loss of limb
before this war is over.
If you need help
finding these...
I know where to find them.
I'm sorry,
I shouldn't interrupt you.
Continue, my lady.
You're riding to the Crag
to negotiate a surrender?
Yes.
The Crag will have a maester
and he will have what I need.
I expect he will.
If I could write a list.
Come with me to the Crag.
I don't think that will be...
Let the maester
show you his stores.
I want the wounded men
to be treated well,
all the wounded men.
(DOGS BARKING)
WOMAN:
Children, come inside, quick.
CHILD: Come on.
Hurry up!
MAN: Can't find anything, ser.
They've lost the scent.
Try again.
We've circled
this farmhouse twice.
There's no sign of them.
We could start
the search fresh
in the morning, my lord.
I'm looking at spending
the rest of my life
being treated like
a fool and a eunuch
by my own people.
Ask yourself, is there
anything I wouldn't do
to stop that from happening?
The hounds will
find the scent again.
I'll beat them until they do.
I'll whip every man here
until I have both
those boys in hand.
And once I've got them,
the pampered little shits...
It's better to be
cruel than weak.
Prince Theon.
Where are they?
Who, m'lord?
The Stark boys.
Where are they?
I don't know. I seen no one.
(GROANS)
Think harder.
I swear, m'lord. I don't know.
My lord, over here.
I think I've found
what we're looking for.
Send the old man home.
Go back to Winterfell.
Take him back.
Theon, don't do this.
You came back.
As soon as I heard.
Do you know anything?
Irri is dead.
I know.
She was a good...
She's dead.
She died alone.
She died for me and I
couldn't protect her.
Doreah?
We can't find her.
She must be dead, too.
I led my people
out of the Red Waste
and into the slaughterhouse.
I should have been here.
You went to find me a ship.
My place is by your side.
I shouldn't
have left you alone
with these people.
"These people"?
They are not to be trusted.
And who is to be trusted?
Who are my people?
The Targaryens?
I only knew one, my brother,
and he would have
let a thousand men
rape me if it had
got him the crown.
The Dothraki?
Most of them
turned on me the day
that Khal Drogo
fell from his horse.
Your people are in Westeros.
The people in Westeros
don't know I'm alive.
They will soon enough.
And then what?
They'll pray for my return?
They'll wave dragon banners
and shout my name?
That's what my
brother believed
and he was a fool.
You are not your brother.
Trust me, Khaleesi.
There it is.
"Trust me."
And it's you I
should trust, Ser Jorah?
Only you?
I don't need trust any longer.
I don't want it and I
don't have room for it.
You are too young to be so...
And you are too familiar.
Forgive me, Khaleesi.
No one can
survive in this world
without help. No one.
Let me help you, please.
Tell me how.
Find my dragons.
YGRITTE: How long till we
get back to your crows?
We're close.
What, a day? A half-day?
You don't know, do you?
Do you even know
where they are?
We're close.
What do you think they'll say
when they hear
about you and me?
Nothing happened
between you and me.
"I swear it,
Old Master King Crow, ser,
"we were only close
together for warmth.
"And then I felt it,
right up against me
backside like a club.
"I can show you
the bruise on me tailbone.
"And before I knew
what was where,
his... his...
"Well,
it was all out in the open,
all angry as you like.
"And I didn't want to
want it, but oh, I did!
"And he spread me
legs and ruined.
"The shame of it.
"Now I can never
marry a perfumed lord.
"What will me poor
savage father say?"
Turn back around.
"And I thought
that we were done,
but he said,
(IN DEEP VOICE)
"'Turn back around.'"
(NORMAL VOICE) I'll
tell you what, Jon Snow.
Since it's gonna be
your word against mine,
and since you can't
talk about it
without blushing,
we may as well just...
What, right here in the muck?
I'll keep you warm enough.
Are you that afraid of it?
That's enough.
It's nice
and wet
and warm.
Enough!
It don't have teeth.
All right!
All right.
Gods, you're dull.
(GRUNTING)
(UNSHEATHING SWORD)
(YGRITTE WHISTLES)
Should have took me
while you had the chance.
(SANSA CRYING)
No, no!
(SCREAMS)
(LAUGHS)
(GASPS)
No. Oh, no.
(WHIMPERING)
It's all right.
Give me that.
If the Queen sees,
I can have
Joffrey's children now.
Help me flip it over.
Where are you going?
To tell Her Grace.
You'll say nothing to anyone.
Do you understand?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Your mother might
have prepared you.
You flowered, my dear.
No more.
My mother told me,
but I thought it
would be different.
In what way?
I thought it would be less...
Less messy.
Wait until you birth
a child.
You're a woman now.
Do you have any
idea what that means?
I'm fit to bear
children for the king?
A prospect that
once delighted you,
bringing little
princes and princesses
into the world,
the greatest honor
for a queen.
Joffrey has
always been difficult.
Even his birth,
I labored a day and a half
to bring him into this world.
You cannot imagine the pain.
I screamed so loudly,
I was sure
Robert would hear
me in the Kingswood.
His Grace was not with you?
Robert was hunting.
That was his custom.
Whenever my time was near,
my royal husband
would flee to the trees
with his huntsmen
and his hounds.
And when he returned,
he would present me
with some pelts
or a stag's head,
and I would
present him with a baby.
Not that I wanted
him there, mind you.
I had Grand Maester Pycelle,
an army of midwives,
and I had my brother.
When they told Jaime
he wasn't allowed
in the birthing room,
he smiled
and asked which one of them
proposed to keep him out.
Joffrey will show
you no such devotion.
You may never love the king,
but you will
love his children.
I love His Grace
with all my heart.
That's so very
touching to hear.
Permit me to share
some womanly wisdom
with you on this
very special day.
The more people you love,
the weaker you are.
You'll do things for them
that you know
you shouldn't do.
You'll act the fool
to make them happy,
to keep them safe.
Love no one but your children.
On that front,
a mother has no choice.
But shouldn't I love Joffrey,
Your Grace?
You can try,
little dove.
(MEN CHATTING)
Who did you say
your mother was again?
Cinda Lannister.
Is she the fat one?
Well, perhaps she's
gotten a little
larger than she...
No, no. There's
only one fat Lannister.
If she was your mother,
you'd know it.
I squired for
you once, you know.
When?
The tournament,
the day of
Willem Frey's wedding.
I went to
Willem Frey's wedding?
You did.
Your squire had
gotten so drunk
the night before
that he threw up.
He threw up on his
horse on the way to
the tourney grounds.
What was his name?
Bryan.
(CHUCKLES)
Poor lad.
That was my brother's doing,
I seem to recall.
I remember you.
You'd never squired
for anyone before.
That's right.
I ran up and volunteered.
"Let me, my lord. Let me."
My father was furious.
Afraid I'd
embarrass our family
in front of the Family.
You didn't, though.
You really remember?
You knew when you were needed
and when to go away.
It's a rare talent.
Most of my squires,
they mean well,
but young men with big jobs,
they tend to overdo them.
When I think
back to that day...
Shh!
You were saying?
I...
Never mind. It's embarrassing.
More embarrassing
than being chained
to a post covered
in your own shit?
I remember
everything about that day,
your helmet, your horse,
the rake lines in
the dirt along the list,
where the sun was
in the sky when
you knocked Balon Swann
from his horse,
and the dent in your shield
when you handed it back to me.
I'll remember it
all until I die.
That was the best day
of my life.
And I remember
being on the field
after it was over.
All the competitors were done.
I was the last one out there.
And I couldn't leave.
I couldn't bring myself
to go and sit with my family
at a table so far
on the edge of the feast
you could barely
even see the bride.
And I couldn't
bear to tell them
what it had been
like squiring for you,
when I knew that
they could never have
the faintest idea
what I was talking about.
I understand completely.
How could you?
Sorry, I...
I didn't mean to doubt you.
It's just that I...
I was 16 once.
I also had to
replace someone's squire
on short notice.
Which knight was it?
Barristan Selmy.
The fight against
the Kingswood Outlaws.
Before your time.
What was he like?
(SIGHS)
He was...
A painter.
A painter who only used red.
I couldn't imagine being
able to fight like that,
not back then.
And to help him do that,
to be a part of
something that perfect.
I don't need to
explain how that felt,
not to you.
It's hard to put into words.
It's like
stepping into a dream
you've been dreaming
for as long as
you can remember,
and finding out that the dream
is more real than your life.
Leaving that battlefield was
like being
dragged off to prison.
Did you squire for him again?
No.
I didn't have your gift.
He couldn't take a step
without stepping on me.
I was awful,
a complete liability.
Until one of
the outlaws decided
to take on
a 16-year-old squire.
It's a good thing
I am who I am.
I'd have been useless
at anything else.
I'm not well-suited
for imprisonment.
Shocking, I know.
Some men are.
Ned Stark,
I imagine he made
an excellent prisoner
right up until the end.
Not me, though.
My life has left me
uniquely unfit for constraint.
And have you thought about...
Of course. Every day.
And?
Good prisoners
breed good jailers,
apparently.
The Starks are very careful.
But there is a way, I think.
It wasn't possible until now.
What is it?
It's actually quite simple.
Well, let me help you.
You'll only have
to do one thing.
Tell me.
You'll have to die.
(CHOKING)
(BONE CRACKING)
Jorah the Andal.
This man must sail
past old Valyria.
All who travel too
close to the doom
must have protection.
I didn't come
here for lessons.
No, you came for the dragons.
You have them?
Where are they?
Draw your sword.
See what your steel is worth.
You want to please
the Mother of Dragons.
You love her.
Where are the dragons?
Will you betray her again,
Jorah the Andal?
Will you betray her again?
Never.
The thief you seek
is with her now.
I did not leave
the comfort of my home
to come to yours
and be called a thief.
No one is calling you a thief.
Who is she to accuse us?
Please, they're my children.
I'm begging you.
Begging us?
It wasn't very long ago
you were threatening us.
Without me,
the dragons will die.
It will be for the best.
Your dragons
will bring the world
nothing but death
and misery, my dear.
If I knew where they were,
I would not tell you.
PYAT PREE:
You are cruel, my friend.
The Mother of Dragons
is in the right.
She must be
reunited with her babies.
I will help you, Khaleesi.
How?
I will take you to
the House of the Undying
where I have put them.
You have my dragons?
When I learned you
were coming to our city,
I made an arrangement
with the King of Qarth.
(LAUGHING)
He procured them for me.
But there is no King of Qarth.
There is now.
That was the other
half of the arrangement.
You would keep your
gates and your minds
closed to everything
outside your walls,
but Qarth cannot
remain the greatest city
that ever was if it
refuses to change.
I will open Qarth to the world
as I have forced it
to open itself to me.
Your ambition is
an inspiration.
But like all upstarts,
you overreach.
Three dragons the size of cats
and an alliance
with a charlatan
do not make you a king.
An upstart and a charlatan?
Empires have
been built by less.
Those on the margins
often come to
control the center,
and those in
the center make room for them,
willingly or otherwise.
The Mother of Dragons
will be with her babies.
She will give them her love
and they will
thrive by her side,
forever.
(GURGLING)
(GASPS)
(GROANING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
A mother should be
with her children.
Where will you run to,
Daenerys Stormborn?
Your dragons wait for you
in the House of the Undying.
Come see them.
Lady Stark!
No farther.
Keep your hands off me, woman.
Don't enter without
an invitation, man.
Forgive me. Lady Stark.
CATELYN: What is it?
They caught the Kingslayer.
(MEN SHOUTING)
Kingslayer!
Kill the fucking Kingslayer!
Hang him!
(MEN SHOUTING)
You'll die today.
Justice for the Karstark.
Gut him!
Get back!
I want his head!
Any man who stands
between a father
and his vengeance
asks for death.
Lord Karstark,
this man is our prisoner.
This monster killed my son.
And crippled mine.
He will answer for his crimes,
I promise you, but not here.
I will have his head.
And if you try and stop me...
You will strike me down?
Have you forgotten me, ser?
I am the widow of your liege,
Lord Eddard Stark.
I am the mother of your king!
And where is our king now?
You know very well.
He has gone to the Crag
to accept the surrender.
Aye, gone to the Crag,
but not to negotiate.
He brought that
foreign bitch with him.
How dare you!
Threatening my lady
is an act of treason.
Treason?
How can it be treason
to kill Lannisters?
I understand
your grief, my lord,
better than most,
I understand it.
But in the name of my son,
the King in the North,
stand down.
When your son returns,
I will demand
this murderer's head.
Wise men do not
make demands of kings.
Fathers who
love their sons do.
I will have his head.
Thank you for
fighting on my behalf,
Lady Stark.
I would have come to
your defense, but...
Take him to the stockades.
Bind him with every
chain you can find!
You've become a real she-wolf
in your later years.
There's not much
fish left in you.
And gag him!
Since when do you
light your own candles?
Since I decided that I
can't stand to look at
any of my handmaidens
for another instant.
How many times
can you read one raven scroll?
Stannis Baratheon's
fleet has been spotted
sailing north past Tarth,
200 ships.
More than we have.
Yes, that's more than we have.
He'll be at our
gates within five days,
four if he has the wind.
We have strong, high walls.
We'll rain fire down
on them from above.
"Rain fire on them
from above."
You're quoting Father,
aren't you?
Why not?
He has a good mind for
strategy, doesn't he?
Call it tactics, not strategy.
But, yes, he does
have a good mind for it.
The best mind, some would say.
Sadly, he's not here.
It's just you, me and Joffrey,
the Lord of the Seven Kingdoms
and Protector of the Realm.
I'm sure you'll make
a point eventually.
He needs to start
acting like a king.
This war you started
is coming to our doorstep.
And if the entire city
wants Joffrey dead...
I'm not the one
giving the boy
whores to abuse.
I thought the girls
might help him.
Did you?
I was wrong.
If we can't control him...
Do you think I haven't tried?
He doesn't listen to me.
It's hard to put
a leash on a dog
once you've put
a crown on its head.
I always hoped
he'd be like Jaime.
He looks like him.
In a certain light.
The boy is more Robert
than Jaime.
Robert was a drunken fool,
but he didn't enjoy cruelty.
Sometimes I wonder.
What?
If this is the price
for what we've done,
for our sins.
Sins?
The Targaryens...
Wed brother and sister
for hundreds of years, I know.
That's what
Jaime and I would say
to each other in
our moments of doubt.
It's what I told Ned Stark
when he was stupid
enough to confront me.
Half the Targaryens
went mad, didn't they?
What's the saying?
"Every time
a Targaryen is born,
the Gods flip a coin."
You've beaten the odds.
Tommen and Myrcella are good,
decent children, both of them.
(SOBS)
MAN 1: Then why wait?
MAN 2:
We're sworn to the king.
There's not a king.
That's treason.
MAN 1: So is
saving Lannisters, yeah?
Back off, you.
No, I won't.
Your son returns
at dawn, my lady?
So they say.
BRIENNE: The Kingslayer
won't last the night.
The more they drink,
the angrier they'll get.
And when the Karstarks
draw their swords...
Who wants to die
defending a Lannister?
Come.
MAN: He'll not be
making it through the night.
I need to be alone with him.
My lady, our orders...
Your orders,
which I just gave you,
are to leave me
alone with him.
Come to say goodbye,
Lady Stark?
I believe it's my
last night in this world.
Is that a woman?
Do you hear them out there?
They want your head.
Old Lord Karstark
doesn't seem to like me.
You strangled his son
with your chains.
Oh. Oh.
Was he the one
on guard duty?
He was in my way.
Any knight would
have done the same.
You are no knight.
You have forsaken
every vow you ever took.
So many vows.
They make you swear and swear.
Defend the king,
obey the king,
obey your father,
protect the innocent,
defend the weak.
But what if your
father despises the king?
What if the king
massacres the innocent?
It's too much.
No matter what you do,
you're forsaking
one vow or another.
Where did you find this beast?
She is a truer knight
than you will ever be,
Kingslayer.
What a king he was.
Here's to Aerys Targaryen,
the Second of His Name,
Lord of the Seven Kingdoms,
Protector of the Realm,
and to the sword
I shoved in his back.
You are a man without honor.
Do you know,
I've never been with
any woman but Cersei.
So in my own way,
I have more honor than
poor old dead Ned.
What was the name of
that bastard he fathered?
Brienne.
No, that wasn't it.
Snow,
a bastard from the North.
Now, when... When good old Ned
came home with
some whore's baby,
did you pretend to love it?
No.
You're not very
good at pretending.
You're an honest woman.
You hated that boy,
didn't you?
How could you not hate him?
The walking,
talking reminder
that the honorable
Lord Eddard Stark
fucked another woman.
Your sword.
(SIGHS)
I told you what would happen.
All of you.
I told you what would happen
if you served me loyally.
And what would
happen if you did not.
What are you doing?
What have you done?
If there are any
who still question
whether your new lord
means what he says,
here is the answer
to your question.
(CROWD GASPING)
No!