(URINATING)
(BIRDS CHITTERING)
(RUSTLING)
(URINATING STOPS)
(MEN CHATTERING)
(HORSE NEIGHS)
MAN: Gotta be
ready before nightfall.
MAN 2: Now keep it moving.
MAN: Put a watch on the ridge
and the tree lines.
JAQEN: Boy.
Lovely boy.
ARYA: What do you want?
A man has a thirst.
A man does not drink
for a day and a night.
A boy could make a friend.
I have friends.
Give us beer
before I skin you.
JAQEN:
A man does not
choose his companions.
These two,
they have no courtesy.
A man must ask forgiveness.
You're called Arry?
This man has the honor
to be Jaqen H'ghar,
once of the Free
City of Lorath...
Beer, you little shit.
Get us beer!
You should have asked nicely.
Aah!
Come closer...
and I'll shove that
stick up your bunghole
and fuck you bloody.
That boy has more
courage than sense.
Come here!
Yoren said none of us were
to go near those three.
Come here!
They don't scare me.
Hmm? Then you're stupid.
They scare me.
(HORSE NEIGHS)
What are gold cloaks
doing so far
from King's Landing?
What are you doing?
They're looking for me.
MAN: You in command here?
You're a long way from home.
MAN: I asked you a question.
Aye, you did.
You asked without manners
and I chose not to answer.
I have a royal warrant
for one of these gutter rats
you're transporting.
Well, the thing is...
these gutter rats belong
to the Night's Watch now.
That puts them
beyond the reach
of kings and queens.
Does it?
YOREN: It's a funny thing,
people worry so much
about their throats
that they forget
about what's down low.
Now, I sharpened this
blade before breakfast.
I could shave a spider's
arse if I wanted to.
Or...I could nick
this artery in your leg.
And once it's nicked,
there's no one around here
who knows how to un-nick it.
We'll just keep that.
Good steel is always
needed on the Wall.
Seems you have a choice,
you can die here
at this crossroads
a long way from home,
or you can go
back to your city
and tell your masters
you didn't find what
you were looking for.
We're looking for
a boy named Gendry.
He carries
a bull's head helmet.
Anyone turning him over
will earn the King's reward.
We'll be back with more men
and I'll be
taking your head home
along with that bastard boy.
(HORSE NEIGHS)
(MEN MURMURING)
(WHISTLING)
(DISTANT SEAGULLS SCREECHING)
(SHAE LAUGHING)
VARYS: My lord.
You make me wait
a long time,
but your friend
keeps me company.
VARYS:
We were just speaking
of your bravery
in the victory against
the Stark auxiliary forces.
It was quite a battle.
I heard you suffered
a terrible head wound.
The northerners are
such fearsome warriors.
And I tell him
the story of how we meet.
To find so lovely a creature
working in your
father's kitchens...
It almost beggars belief.
Strange things do happen.
You should taste her fish pie.
I don't think Lord Varys
likes fish pie.
How can you tell?
I can always tell.
Men like Lord Varys
and I can't let
our disadvantages
get the best of us.
We'll make
a fisherman of him yet.
I am glad your new friend
was able to
accompany you to the capital.
Friends are such
an important part of life.
Unfortunate that your father
didn't want her to come.
But rest easy, my lord.
I am very good
at keeping secrets
for my good friends.
Your discretion
is legendary...
Where your friends
are concerned.
How unspeakable of me
to go on and on
when all you
want to do is rest.
I will leave you.
Welcome to King's Landing,
my dear.
This city is made brighter
by your presence.
We have a council meeting,
my lord.
TYRION: I don't like threats.
Who threatened you?
I'm not Ned Stark.
I understand the way
this game is played.
Ned Stark was a man of honor.
And I am not.
Threaten me again
and I'll have you
thrown into the sea.
You might be
disappointed in the results.
Storms come and go,
the big fish eat
the little fish,
and I keep on paddling.
Come, my lord.
We shouldn't keep
the queen waiting.
CERSEI: "From this time
until the end of time,
"we are not
part of your realm,
"but a free and independent
Kingdom of the North."
He has more
spirit than his father,
I'll give him that.
You've perfected
the art of tearing up papers.
We can give him his
father's bones back,
at least,
as a gesture of good faith.
You'll give
the Starks our reply, cousin?
I will, Your Grace.
Did you see my brother
when you were
the Starks' guest?
ALTON: I did.
They have not broken
his spirit, Your Grace.
If you speak with him,
tell him he's
not been forgotten.
ALTON: I will, Your Grace.
Safe travels, cousin.
You have a deft hand
with diplomacy.
If that's everything...
A raven flew in this morning
from Castle Black.
Trouble with the wildlings.
That's why they're
called "wildlings."
Somewhat less wild these days.
Seems they've stopped
killing each other
and started following
this king-beyond-the-Wall.
Another king?
How many is that now?
Five?
(LAUGHS) I've lost count.
The Lord Commander asks
that we send more
men to man the Wall.
Perhaps he's forgotten
we're fighting a war.
We have no men to spare.
"The cold winds are rising
and the dead rise with them."
The northerners are
a superstitious people.
According to the Commander,
one of these dead men
attacked him in his chambers.
Mormont doesn't lie.
VARYS:
How do you kill a dead man?
Apparently you burn him.
One trip to the Wall
and you come back
believing in
grumpkins and snarks.
I don't know what I believe,
but here's a fact for you:
the Night's Watch
is the only thing
that separates us from
what lies beyond the Wall.
I have every confidence
that the brave men
of the Night's Watch
will protect us all.
DOLOROUS EDD: And I said,
"If the gods wanted
us to have dignity,
"they wouldn't make
us fart when we died."
GRENN: We fart when we die?
DOLOROUS EDD:
My blessed mother,
I was holding her hand
when she left this world.
She farted so hard,
the whole bed shook.
(BLOWING RASPBERRY)
Seems a bit greedy for one man
to have so many wives.
Wouldn't two or three
be enough for him?
We were having
a serious discussion.
Would you look at that?
Nothing like the sight
of a woman walking away.
I prefer watching them
come towards me.
I'm sure that's nice, too.
Yeah, well, there was
a milkmaid named Violet
on the next farm over
from where I grew up.
We were wrestling together
from the time we
were six years old.
And then we got older
and the wrestling...
changed.
SAMWELL: You were with her?
How many times?
Well,
as many times as I could.
I wish I grew up on a farm.
We need more potatoes.
Get another sack
from the sledge.
Get the turnips, too.
(DOG BARKING)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
No. Ghost, no.
No!
Ghost, away. Shoo. Shoo!
You all right?
Did he frighten you?
You shouldn't touch me.
Oh.
Oh, right.
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to make
sure you weren't hurt.
You're very brave.
What are you doing?
This is Gilly.
She's one of
Craster's daughters.
Hello, Gilly.
What are you doing?
Sam said you could help.
I'm sorry, but Sam knows
we're not supposed...
She's pregnant.
We have to take her
with us when we leave.
What?
What would that...
SAMWELL:
I know it sounds a bit mad.
No,
it doesn't sound a bit mad,
it's impossible.
The Lord Commander
ordered us to...
We are sworn to protect.
Sam, we can't take...
Please, sir, please.
I can still run
if I have to.
It's just not possible.
I'm going to have a baby.
If it's a boy...
If it's a boy, what?
You want us to
risk our lives for you
and you won't
even tell us why?
Why'd you do that?
Do what?
Ask her a question?
You were cruel.
Cruel?
Sam, are you in such
a hurry to lose a hand?
I didn't touch her.
No,
you just want to steal her.
What do you think
Craster cuts off for that?
I can't steal her.
She's a person, not a goat.
We're heading
deeper and deeper
into wildling territory.
We can't take a girl with us.
Mormont wouldn't have it.
And even if he would,
what would we do with her?
Who's going to
deliver a baby, you?
I could try.
What? I've read about it.
A bit.
I'm sorry, Sam.
We can't help her.
(SIGHS)
(INSECTS CHITTERING, BUZZING)
(HOOFBEATS APPROACHING)
Khaleesi.
(HORSE NEIGHS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(FLIES BUZZING)
You don't need to see this.
He is blood of my blood.
Who did this?
Khal Pono, perhaps.
Khal Jhaqo.
They don't like
the idea of a woman
leading a khalasar.
They will like it far less
when I am done with them.
(WEEPING)
(IRRI WAILING)
(SEAGULLS SCREECHING)
Is it as you remember,
my lord?
It looks smaller.
Everything looks
bigger when you're a child.
I remember my father's cabin
felt like a palace
when I was little.
Now look at it. (GIGGLES)
They'll be waiting
for me on the docks.
Who will?
Anyone who matters.
This is a big day for them.
They haven't had much to get
excited about since I left.
It's a hard place,
the Iron Islands.
Always has been.
It's cold and it's wet.
Oh, I love the cold and wet.
They say hard
places breed hard men.
And hard men rule the world.
Then you'll be
king before long.
Try smiling with
your lips closed.
Better.
My father doesn't
trust you Iron Islanders.
I don't blame him.
He says that you're
all reavers and rapers
and that no matter
how many women you have,
you'll never be sat...
(GRUNTS)
Quit talking
about your father.
(MOANS)
But he's right about us.
Our wives from
the Iron Islands,
they're for breeding.
That's not enough for us.
That's why we take salt wives,
the women we capture.
Capture me.
Take me with you
when you go ashore.
Make me your salt wife.
Your place is on this ship.
Not after you leave.
Father will punish me.
He'll call me a whore.
I haven't paid you.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(MOANING) Oh, yeah.
(JEWELRY JANGLING)
(DOOR OPENS)
MAN: I paid good money...
(DOOR SLAMS)
(MAN GRUMBLING)
I'm not going to
stand for this.
I barely touched her.
(WOMAN CRYING)
Now, you charge twice as much
as every other brothel
and this is
what I get, crying.
One moment, my friend.
A moment.
(SNAPS FINGERS)
Please accept my
sincerest apologies.
Aremca will take
good care of you.
(CRYING CONTINUES)
I'm sorry, my lord.
(SHUSHING)
Did he hurt you?
No, my lord.
(SNIFFLES)
It's Mhaegen.
Who?
She works for you.
She's the one...
The gold cloaks,
they killed her baby.
Ah, yes.
That was...
poorly handled.
Sometimes those
with the most power
have the least grace.
I can't stop
thinking about it.
I can't sleep.
Her poor little baby.
You know, you remind
me of another girl,
a lovely thing I once acquired
from a Lysene pleasure house.
Beautiful, like yourself,
and intelligent,
like yourself.
But she wasn't happy.
She cried often.
I asked her why,
but we didn't have
the kind of rapport
that you and I have.
Yes, it was quite sad.
Girls from
the Lysene pleasure houses
are expensive,
extremely expensive.
And this one wasn't
making me any money.
I hate bad investments.
Really, I do.
They haunt me.
I had no idea how
to make her happy,
no idea how to
mitigate my losses.
A very wealthy patron,
he offered me
a tremendous amount of money
to let him transform
this lovely, sad girl.
To use her in ways
that would never
occur to most men.
But you know what
occurs to most men.
I would not say he succeeded
in making her happy,
but my losses were
definitely mitigated.
Take tonight off to
mourn Mhaegen's child.
I'll see you tomorrow.
And you'll be happy?
That makes me happy.
(CRYING)
TYRION: More wine?
JANOS: Damn it, boy!
PODRICK: Apologies, my lord.
TYRION: Leave us, Podrick.
I believe we know how
to pour our own wine.
That's your new squire?
I could've found
you a proper lad.
Myself,
I prefer the improper ones.
That's a good red. Dornish?
You know your wines, my lord.
That I do.
(SIGHS) A fine dinner,
my lord.
Call me Tyrion, please.
I'm sure you're
getting used to fine dinners,
now that you're a lord.
Maybe I'll hire
this cook of yours.
Wars have been
started for less.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
I heard there was some trouble
in Littlefinger's
brothel the other night.
Mmm.
Nasty business.
Had to be done.
Yes, of course.
The City Watch
must keep the peace.
Only, I hadn't realized
peace depended
on killing babies.
Orders are orders.
Quite right.
Especially the Queen's orders.
I never said they
were the Queen's orders.
No, but who else would
want to murder King
Robert's bastards?
She's always been
a jealous woman.
You know your sister
better than I do.
You've heard the awful rumors
about my brother and sister?
I don't listen to filth.
That's good of you,
but you have heard them.
I suppose people who
do believe that filth
consider Robert's bastards
to be better
claimants to the throne
than Cersei's children.
Joffrey is my king.
The rest doesn't interest me.
I appreciate your loyalty.
Tell me, when your men
slaughtered Ned Stark's men
in the throne room,
did you give the order?
I did.
And I would again.
The man was a traitor.
He tried to buy my loyalty.
The fool.
He had no idea you
were already bought.
Are you drunk?
I'll not have my honor
questioned by an imp!
I'm not questioning
your honor, Lord Janos.
I'm denying its existence.
If you think I'll stand here
and take this
from you, dwarf...
Dwarf? You should
have stopped at imp.
And, yes, you will stand here
and take it from me,
unless you'd like to take it
from my friend here.
I intend to serve
as Hand of the King
until my father
returns from the war.
And seeing as you betrayed
the last Hand of the King,
well,
I just wouldn't feel safe
with you lurking about.
What are you...
My friends at court
will not allow this!
The Queen
herself has granted...
The Queen Regent.
And you're a fool to
believe she is your friend.
We shall hear what Joffrey
has to say about this.
No, we shan't.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACH)
(DOORS OPEN)
There's a ship leaving for
Eastwatch-by-the-Sea tonight.
From there, I'm afraid,
it's rather a long
walk to Castle Black.
I hope you enjoy the Wall.
I found it
surprisingly beautiful...
in a brutal,
horribly uncomfortable
sort of way.
The lads will escort you.
The streets aren't
safe at night, my lord.
These men are
under my command!
I command you to
arrest this cutthroat.
His name is Bronn,
and he is the new commander
of the City Watch.
Boys.
(JANOS GRUNTING)
I have friends at court,
powerful friends!
The king himself
made me a lord!
(SIGHS)
To the new commander.
If I told you to
murder an infant girl, say,
still at her mother's breast,
would you do it
without question?
Without question? No.
I'd ask, "How much?"
(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(HORSE NEIGHS)
If they come back,
I say we yield.
Gendry's the one they want.
Don't want to get caught
in the middle of a battle.
I ain't afraid
of no battles.
If you got within
a mile of a battle,
you'd fill your pants.
I've seen
lots of battles.
I saw...
Liar.
I saw a man
kill another man
just outside a tavern
in Flea Bottom.
Stabbed him
right in the neck.
Two men fighting
isn't a battle.
They had armor on.
So?
So, if they've got
armor on, it's a battle.
No, it isn't.
What does a dyer's apprentice
know about battles anyway?
Gendry's
an armorer's apprentice.
Hot Pie, tell Gendry
what makes
a fight into a battle.
It's when
they've got armor on.
GENDRY: Who told you that?
A knight.
How'd you know
he was a knight?
Well, it was 'cause
he'd got armor on.
You don't have to be
a knight to have armor.
Any idiot can buy armor.
HOT PIE: How do you know?
'Cause I sold armor.
What do the gold cloaks
want with you?
No idea.
You're a liar.
You know, you shouldn't
insult people that
are bigger than you.
Then I wouldn't
get to insult anyone.
I don't care what
any of them want.
No good's ever come
of their questions.
No good's ever come?
Who asked questions before?
How can someone so small
be such a huge
pain in my arse?
Who asked questions?
(SIGHS) The Hand of the King.
Hands of the King.
Lord Arryn came first
a few weeks before he died,
and then Lord Stark came
a few weeks before he died.
Lord Stark?
See? Asking me
questions is bad luck.
You'll probably be dead soon.
What did they ask about?
My mum.
Who's your mum?
Just my mum,
worked in a tavern,
died when I was little.
And who was your father?
Could've been one of those
gold-hatted bastards,
for all I know.
What about you anyway?
You thought
they were after you.
Why?
Did you kill someone
or is it just
because you're a girl?
I'm not a girl.
Yes, you are.
Do you think I'm as stupid
as the rest of them?
Stupider.
The Night's Watch
doesn't take girls,
everyone knows that.
Yeah, that's true,
but you're still a girl.
I am not!
Yeah? Well, pull your cock out
and take a piss, then.
I don't need to take a piss.
Lommy and Hot Pie can't know.
No one can know.
Well, they won't.
Not from me.
My name's not Arry.
It's Arya, of House Stark.
Yoren is taking me
home to Winterfell.
He was your father,
the Hand, the traitor.
He was never a traitor.
Joffrey is a liar.
So you're a highborn, then.
You're a lady.
No. I mean, yes.
My mother was
a lady and my sister...
Yeah, but you were
a lord's daughter,
and you lived in
a castle and you...
Look, all that about cocks,
I should never have said...
And I've been pissing
in front of you
and everything.
I should be
calling you "my lady."
Do not call me "my lady."
As my lady commands.
Well, that was unladylike.
Oh!
(LAUGHS)
What's she carrying?
Myrish oranges,
wine from the Arbor...
and the heir to Pyke
and the Iron Islands.
The only living
son of Balon Greyjoy.
Me.
I don't like wine.
Woman's drink.
I need to get to Pyke.
I'll find you a horse.
I'm heading that way.
I can take you there.
I bet you can.
Have you been at sea long?
Or were there just no women
where you came from?
None like you.
You don't know
what I'm like.
Maybe you don't
know what you're like.
Maybe you need
someone to teach you.
Do you know who I am?
You think I offer free rides
to every man in jewelry,
Lord Greyjoy?
Have my things
sent up to the castle.
You should give me the reins.
I'm a better rider than you.
I've been on horseback
for the past nine years.
Nine years?
Do you still know
your way around a ship?
Have these hands
ever touched a rope?
Don't you worry
about my hands.
The sea is in my blood.
Your blood will be in the sea
if I don't watch
where I'm going.
I have a proposal
for my father,
one that will
make him king again,
and me after him.
You may get to stay
in a castle tonight
if you're lucky.
Is that an offer
from my future king?
An order from
your future king.
You can tell
your grandchildren
about this night.
I don't imagine it will be
a story fit for children.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
THEON: Father.
BALON: Nine years, is it?
They took a frightened boy.
What have they given back?
A man.
Your blood and your heir.
We shall see.
Stark had you
longer than I did.
Lord Stark is gone.
And how do you
feel about that?
What's done is done.
I've brought you
a proposal from Robb Stark.
Who gave you those clothes?
Was it Ned Stark's pleasure
to make you his daughter?
If my clothes offend you,
I will change them.
You will.
That bauble round your neck,
did you pay the iron
price for it, or the gold?
I asked a question.
Did you pull it from the neck
of a corpse you made
or did you buy it to
match your fine clothes?
Iron or gold?
Gold.
I'll not have my son
dressed as a whore.
My fears have come true,
the Starks have
made you theirs.
My blood is salt and iron.
Yet the Stark
boy sends you to me
like a trained raven
clutching his message.
The offer he makes
is one I proposed.
He heeds your counsel?
I've lived with him,
hunted with him,
fought at his side.
He thinks of me as a brother.
No, not here,
not in my hearing.
You will not name him brother,
this son of the man
who put your true
brothers to the sword.
Or have you
forgotten your own blood?
I forget nothing.
I remember my brothers.
And I remember when
my father was a king.
I see.
I destroy Robb Stark's
enemies for him
and he will make me
king of the Iron
Islands once again.
I will lead the attack myself.
Oh, you will?
I'm your son,
your only living heir.
Who else?
(DOOR OPENS)
I told you to wait outside.
How did you get
past the guards?
Anything with a cock
is easy to fool.
My dear.
Yara?
So good to see you, brother.
This is a homecoming
I'll tell my
grandchildren about.
She can't lead an attack!
BALON: And why not?
You're a woman!
You're the one in skirts.
This isn't Winterfell, boy.
Your sister took over command
of your eldest brother's ship
after your new
father killed him.
What's dead may never die.
...dead may never die.
The only nights she's
spent off these islands
have been spent on the sea.
She's commanded men.
She's killed men.
She knows who she is.
No man gives me a crown.
I pay the iron price.
I will take my crown,
for that is who I am.
That is who we
have always been.
You won't stand a chance
against
the Lannisters on your own.
Who said anything
about the Lannisters?
DAVOS: You'll have your gold
when we take the treasury
at King's Landing.
SALLADHOR:
All these kings
fighting for the throne,
and this Stannis
has the smallest army.
Why would I bet on the man
with the worst chance?
Because you're
a smart gambler.
Stannis has proved
himself in war twice.
His baby brother
has never set foot
on a battlefield.
Neither has
the false King Joffrey.
And yet they both
have larger armies.
Stannis has just
begun the fight.
His bannermen will
rally to his cause.
There's no man in
the Seven Kingdoms
more honorable
than Stannis Baratheon
or more worthy of loyalty.
What is the world coming to
when smugglers must vouch
for the honor of kings?
Mind your words, pirate.
Matthos.
You think I'm insulted?
I am a pirate.
I'm an excellent pirate.
I don't sail for promises.
Of course you do.
Every time you leave harbor,
you're leaving on a promise,
a promise that
somewhere on the sea,
somebody's got some gold
and you can take it from him.
That's a promise
that always comes true.
As is mine.
You're not
a young man, Salladhor.
And correct me if I'm wrong,
most pirates don't grow old.
Only the clever ones.
You want to spend
your last few years on the sea
stealing from
Pentoshi cheesemongers
and Myrenese silk merchants,
then go.
They're out there
waiting for you.
That's easy.
What I'm offering you is hard.
Come with me and plunder
the greatest city in Westeros.
You'll be
the richest man in Lys,
and the most famous.
They'll be
singing songs about you
as long as men
have voices to sing.
"Salladhor Saan" is
a good name for songs.
It is.
One thing, I want the queen.
The queen?
Cersei, I want her.
I'll sail with your fleet,
all 30 of my ships.
And if we don't
drown at the bottom
of Blackwater Bay,
I will fuck this blonde queen
and I'll fuck her well.
MATTHOS:
This war isn't about you.
We're not
attacking King's Landing
so that you can
rape the queen.
I'm not going to rape her.
I'm going to fuck her.
As if she would just let you.
You don't know
how persuasive I am.
I've never tried to fuck you.
Stannis is the rightful king
and the Lord of Light,
the one true god...
I've been all over the world,
my boy,
and everywhere I go,
people tell me
about the true gods.
They all think they
found the right one.
The one true god
is what's
between a woman's legs,
and better yet,
a queen's legs.
I never thought you'd have
a true believer for a son.
He's young yet.
I promise you the gold.
I promise you the glory.
I cannot
promise you the queen.
You believe your king can win?
He is the one true king.
You Westerosi
are funny people.
A man chops off your fingers
and you fall in love with him.
I'll sail with you,
Davos Seaworth.
You're the most
honest smuggler I ever met.
Make me rich.
Get me to the gates
of King's Landing and I will.
MATTHOS: When will
the king have us sail?
As soon as his god
wills it.
He's my god, too, and yours,
but you are too blind to see.
Let me teach you how to read.
Oh, you and your mother.
It won't take long.
You already know the letters.
The holy books are
much more
persuasive than I can be.
I wish I had a god, truly.
I'm not mocking you,
but I've seen men pray
to every god there is,
pray for wind,
pray for rain,
pray for home.
None of it works.
But you always came home.
I wasn't praying.
But I was.
Every night that
you were at sea,
I lit a candle and
I prayed for you.
You want me to have a god?
Fine.
King Stannis is my god.
He raised me up
and blessed me with his trust.
He gave you a future
I could never have imagined.
You know how to read.
You'll be a knight someday.
You think a fire god
commanded all that?
It was Stannis,
only Stannis.
Stannis is my king,
but he's only a man.
Don't tell him that. (LAUGHS)
CERSEI: Lord Janos Slynt
was commander of
the City Watch.
You had no right
to exile him.
I have every right.
I am the King's Hand.
You're serving
as the King's Hand
till Father gets here.
I am Queen Regent.
Listen to me, Queen Regent.
You're losing the people.
Do you hear me?
(LAUGHS) The people.
You think I care?
You might find it difficult
to rule over
millions who want you dead.
Half the city will
starve when winter comes.
The other half will
plot to overthrow you.
And your gold-plated thugs
just gave them
their rallying cry,
"The Queen slaughters babies."
You don't even have
the decency to deny it.
It wasn't you who
gave the order, was it?
Joffrey didn't even tell you.
Did he tell you?
I imagine that
would be even worse.
He did what needed to be done.
You want to be
Hand of the King?
You want to rule?
This is what ruling is,
lying on a bed of weeds,
ripping them out by the root,
one by one,
before they
strangle you in your sleep.
I'm no king,
but I think there's
more to ruling than that.
I don't care what you think!
You've never
taken it seriously.
You haven't, Jaime hasn't.
It's all fallen on me.
As has Jaime, repeatedly,
according to
Stannis Baratheon.
You're funny.
You've always been funny...
but none of your
jokes will ever match
the first one, will they?
You remember?
Back when you
ripped my mother open
on your way out of her
and she bled to death?
She was my mother, too.
Mother gone...
for the sake of you.
There's no bigger joke
in the world than that.
(DOOR OPENS)
Your Grace.
STANNIS: How did you
fare with your pirate?
Salladhor Saan will
join our fleet, 30 ships.
His men know how to fight.
In my experience,
pirates prefer
fighting unarmed men.
It does seem
the wiser choice.
There won't be
a choice this time.
Do you trust him?
Salladhor Saan
is an old friend.
I've known him 30 years.
I've never trusted him.
Now, once he gets
the smell of gold
he never stops.
Well, if he does his job,
he'll have his share.
Leave us.
At once, Your Grace.
The Lord of Light
shines through you,
young warrior.
(WHISPERING)
Come.
What did you say to him?
I told him death by fire
is the purest death.
Why?
Because it is true.
You're troubled, my king.
Yeah.
These armies are toys
for the Lord of Light.
Tell your lord to
burn them, then.
I tell him nothing.
I pray for his
commands and I obey.
My little brother
has 100,000 men,
according to the scouts,
men whose allegiance
rightly belongs to me.
You must have faith.
Faith?
In a real war, the side with
the greater number wins,
nine times out of ten.
Then we must be the 10th.
I cannot defeat my
brother in the field.
And I can't
take King's Landing
without the men he's stolen.
I have seen the path to
victory in the flames.
But first,
you must give yourself
to the Lord of Light.
I've said the words, damn you.
I burned the idols.
You must give all of yourself.
I have a wife.
I took a vow.
She's sickly, weak...
Shut away in a tower.
She disgusts you.
And she's given you nothing,
no sons, only stillborns,
only death.
(WHISPERING) I will
give you a son, my king.
A son?
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
(WIND HOWLING)
(FOOTSTEPS)
(BABY COOING)
(WINGS FLAPPING)
(CROW CAWS)
(SCRAPING)
(JANGLING)
(CREATURE SNARLS)
(GASPS)
(BABY CRYING)
(CREATURE CHITTERING)
(CREATURE SNARLING)
(BABY CONTINUES CRYING)
(CRYING)
(GUTTURAL CLICKING)
(GASPS)