You swear it?
CATELYN: By the mother.
My son has no interest
in the Iron Throne.
Then I see no reason
for hostility between us.
Your son can go on
calling himself
King in the North.
The Starks will have dominion
over all lands
north of Moat Cailin,
provided he swears me
an oath of fealty.
And the wording
of this oath?
The same Ned Stark swore
to Robert 18 years ago.
Cat, their friendship held
the kingdoms together.
And in return for
my son's loyalty?
In the morning, I'll
destroy my brother's army.
When that's done,
Baratheon and Stark will fight
their common enemy together,
as they have done
many times before.
Our two houses have
always been close,
which is why I am begging you
to reconsider this battle.
Negotiate a peace
with your brother.
Negotiate with Stannis?
(CHUCKLES)
You heard him out there.
I'd have better luck
debating the wind.
Please bring my
terms to your son.
I believe we are
natural allies.
I hope he feels the same.
Together we could end
this war in a fortnight.
(WIND HOWLING)
(HISSING)
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
(HISSES)
No!
No.
MAN: Follow me!
You'll die for this.
No, wait, it wasn't her!
(SOBBING)
We've got to leave.
They'll hang you
for this.
Now.
I won't leave him.
You can't avenge him
if you're dead.
MAN: Over there, go!
Not that way.
(MEN SHOUTING)
We need to go home.
Loras.
LITTLEFINGER:
My lord, my lady.
Get out.
Stannis will be
here in an hour.
When he arrives,
Renly's bannermen
will flock to him.
Your former companions
will fight for the privilege
of selling you
to their new king.
And you want that
privilege for yourself.
You will note that
I am standing here
talking to you,
not Stannis.
There's no time for this.
Ride back to Highgarden,
sister.
I'm not running
from Stannis.
Brienne of Tarth
murdered Renly.
I don't believe that.
You don't believe that.
Who gained the most
from our king's death?
Stannis.
I will put a sword
through his righteous face.
You can't stay here.
He would have
been a true king,
a good king.
LITTLEFINGER:
Tell me, Ser Loras,
what do you desire
most in this world?
Revenge.
I have always found that
to be the purest
of motivations,
but you won't have a chance
to put your sword
through Stannis,
not today.
You'll be cut to pieces
before he sets foot
on solid ground.
If it is justice
that you want,
be smart about it.
You can't avenge him
from the grave.
Bring the horses.
Please.
He was very handsome.
He was, Your Grace.
"Your Grace."
Calling yourself king
doesn't make you one.
And if Renly wasn't a king,
I wasn't a queen.
Do you want to be a queen?
No.
I want to be the queen.
(LAUGHING)
Killed? By whom?
TYRION: Accounts differ.
Most seem to
implicate Catelyn Stark
in some way.
Really?
Who'd have thought?
Some say it was one
of his own Kingsguard,
while still others say
it was Stannis himself
who did it
after negotiations
went sour.
Whomever did it,
I say well done.
It's not what Varys says.
He says Renly's army
is flocking to
support Stannis,
which would give Stannis
superiority over us
on both land and sea.
Littlefinger says we can
outspend him three to one.
And I say Father raised you
to have too much respect
for money.
Stannis Baratheon
is coming for us,
sooner rather than later.
Aren't there other things
you should be doing,
like sealing my
daughter in a crate
so you can ship her away?
She'll be safer in Dorne.
Yes, I know
how concerned you are
for her safety.
It so happens that I am.
Myrcella is a sweet,
innocent girl
and I don't blame her
at all for you.
So clever.
Aren't you always
so clever with your
schemes and your plots?
Schemes and plots
are the same thing.
They are going to attack us.
We need to be ready.
No need to concern
yourself over it.
The king is
taking personal charge
of siege preparations.
May I ask specifically
what the king has in mind?
You may, specifically,
or you may ask vaguely.
The answer will be the same.
It's important that
we talk about this.
It's the king's
royal prerogative
to withhold
sensitive information
from his councilors.
(DOOR CLOSES)
LANCEL: It's wildfire.
Wildfire?
You wouldn't lie to me,
would you, cousin?
No.
That's a lie right there.
It is not a lie.
Why would I lie?
Tell me,
if the vile allegations
against my brother
and sister are true,
do you think it
will make Jaime
more likely to kill you
or less likely?
When I tell him
you're fucking her, I mean.
I'm telling you the truth.
The smart money
would be on more likely.
She's making wildfire.
But then perhaps his
own unnatural urges
will give him
sympathy for yours.
The Alchemists' Guild
is being commissioned.
I suppose there's
only one way to find out.
They have thousands of pots
already stored
in their vaults.
They are planning to launch it
from the city walls
into Stannis'
ships and armies.
Please.
When did she tell you this?
I heard her talking
with the pyromancer.
And the other night,
after I left her,
she went to meet him.
I swear to you.
Swear to me on what?
On my life.
But I don't care
about your life.
In the light of the Seven,
by all that is holy and right,
I, Lancel Lannister,
do solemnly vow...
All right, all right. Enough.
Even torturing you is boring.
Just get out.
(GRUNTS)
Oh, Lancel,
tell my friend Bronn
to please kill you
if anything
should happen to me.
Please kill me if anything
should happen to Lord Tyrion.
It will be
my pleasure.
Your Grace.
What is it?
I'm sorry
about your brother,
Your Grace.
I wanted to let you know
that people grieve for him.
Fools love a fool.
I grieve for him as well,
for the boy he was,
not the man he grew to be.
I need to speak to you
about what I saw
in that cave.
I thought I made
it clear to you
there'd be no
need to speak to me
on this matter.
Your Grace, I...
I've never known you to need
to hear a thing twice.
And I've never known you
to hide from the truth.
You've come to
lecture me on truth?
I've come to tell
you that what I saw...
All my brother's bannermen
have come to my side.
Except the Tyrells,
who fled like cowards.
They won't be able
to resist us now.
Soon I shall be
sitting on the Iron Throne.
Nothing is worth
what this will cost you,
not even the Iron...
I'll hear no more about it.
MAN: Take a company of men,
secure the perimeter.
When do we sail
for King's Landing?
As soon as I've
consolidated my troops.
We'll make short work
of the Lannisters' fleet.
Once Blackwater Bay
is cleared,
we'll deliver our
troops to their doorstep
and take the city.
And will you bring
Lady Melisandre with you?
That's not your concern.
If you take King's Landing
with her by your side,
the victory will be hers.
I never thought
I'd have reason
to doubt your loyalty.
Was I wrong?
Loyal service means
telling hard truths.
Oh, truth again.
All right,
what's the truth?
The hard truth?
She's a foreigner
preaching her
foreign religion.
Some believe she whispers
orders in your ear
and you obey.
What do you believe?
You won those
bannermen from Renly.
Don't lose them to her.
We set out for King's Landing
without Lady Melisandre.
And you lead the fleet
into Blackwater Bay.
Your Grace, I'm honored,
but my time on the sea
was spent evading ships,
not attacking them.
The other lords
won't be happy.
Most of those lords
should consider
themselves lucky
I don't hang them
for treason.
Hard truths cut
both ways, Ser Davos.
GIRL: I've got it!
I've got it!
MAN: So it's that
one there at the top,
on the right.
Buy my fruit, my lord.
Fresh fruit.
Stannis has more infantry,
more ships, more horses.
What do we have?
There's that mind of yours
you keep going on about.
Well, I've never actually
been able to kill people
with it.
Good thing.
I'd be out of a job.
What about your father?
He hasn't sent
a raven in weeks.
He's very busy.
Being repeatedly
humiliated by Robb Stark
is time-consuming.
We won't be able
to hold the city
against Stannis,
not the way Joffrey's
planning on holding it.
MAN: Corruption.
CROWD: Yes!
We are swollen,
bloated, foul.
Brother fornicates with sister
in the bed of kings
and we're surprised
when the fruit of
their incest is rotten?
(CHEERING)
Yes, a rotten king.
It's hard to argue
with his assessment.
Not after what he did
to your birthday present.
The king is a lost cause.
It's the rest of us
I'm worried about now.
A dancing king,
prancing down his
bloodstained halls
to the tune of
a twisted demon monkey.
(LAUGHING)
You have to admire
his imagination.
He's talking about you.
What? Demon monkey?
People think you're
pulling the king's strings.
They blame you
for the city's ills.
Blame me?
I'm trying to save them.
You don't need
to convince me.
Demon monkey.
(MEN LAUGHING)
Yeah, come on.
THEON: You're
the crew of the Sea Bitch?
I'm your commander. Welcome.
Stop.
Stop!
Your captain
commands you to stop!
Where are we headed,
Captain?
The Stony Shore,
to raid their villages.
There'll be spoils in
it for you, and women,
if you do your jobs well.
And who decides if
we've done our jobs well?
I do.
Your captain.
(ALL LAUGHING)
I have been reaving and raping
since before you left
Balon's balls, Captain.
Don't reckon I've got
much use for your ideas
on how to do it.
Don't reckon I've got much use
for a captain at all.
I'm thinking I can
do the job of captain
real well myself.
All I need is a ship.
You wouldn't know
where I could find myself
a ship now, would you?
You could do that,
take the ship,
head out on your own.
And I will hunt you down,
drag you back here in chains
and hang you
for a traitor.
Stop. We yield.
Congratulations on
your first command.
Thank you. Kind of
you to come see me off.
Oh, I'm not here for you.
I was just on my
way to Red Harbor.
I've got 30 ships.
There's nowhere
to put them here.
Too narrow.
You'd better get out there.
Wouldn't want her to
set sail without you.
That would never happen.
My crew would wait on deck
for a year if I asked them to.
This lot, though...
Enjoy the Stony Shore.
Come on, I'll take you out.
Who are you?
Dagmer, your first mate.
Why aren't you
with the rest of them?
Or did they send
you to row me out
and dump me
halfway in the sea?
That would be
good for a laugh.
They're not gonna respect you
until you prove yourself.
And how am I supposed
to prove myself
by pillaging
piss-poor fishing villages?
You're not.
And yet that's the task
my father has given me
to prove that I'm
a true Iron Islander.
They're all
Iron Islanders.
Do they do as they're told
or do they do as they like?
THEON:
The Stony Shore's not far
from Torrhen's Square.
The seat of
the House of Tallhart,
a more impressive prize
than a few fishermen's
daughters.
What, you don't
think we could take it?
No, we could.
We could never hold it
for more than a few days.
As soon as Winterfell got
word that we'd taken
Torrhen's Square,
the Starks
would send their men
to take it back.
And then...
Take me to my ship.
The Starks have
overextended their lines.
Now that summer's over,
they'll have a hard time
keeping their
men and horses fed.
The Starks understand winter
better than we ever will.
The cold won't beat them.
Our spies report
growing discontent
among the Northern lords.
They want to return home
and gather the harvest
before the crops turn.
And I'm sure if
those same spies
snuck into our
own encampments,
they would report
growing discontent
amongst the Southern lords.
This is war,
no one's content.
We've underestimated
the Stark boy for too long.
He has a good
mind for warfare,
his men worship him.
And as long as he
keeps winning battles,
they'll keep believing
he is King in the North.
You've been waiting
for him to fail.
He is not going to fail,
not without our help.
So how do we stop him?
REGINALD: We've worked
through the night, my lord.
Perhaps we'd profit
from some sleep.
Yes, I think
you would, Reginald.
And because you're my cousin,
I might even let you
wake from that sleep.
Go, I'm sure your
wife must miss you.
My wife's in Lannisport.
Well, then you'd
better start riding.
Go, before I change my mind
and send her your head.
If your name
wasn't Lannister,
you'd be scrubbing out pots
in the cook's tent. Go!
Not wine, water.
We'll be here for some time.
Girl.
Where are you from?
Maidenpool, my lord.
And who are
the Lords of Maidenpool?
Remind me.
House Mooton, my lord.
And what is their sigil?
A red salmon.
I think a Maidenpool girl
would remember that.
You're a Northerner,
aren't you?
Good. One more time,
where are you from?
Barrowton, my lord.
House Dustin.
Two crossed longaxes
beneath a black crown.
And what do they say
of Robb Stark in the North?
They call him
the Young Wolf.
And?
They say he rides
into battle on the back
of a giant direwolf.
They say he can turn into
a wolf himself when he wants.
They say
he can't be killed.
And do you believe them?
No, my lord.
Anyone can be killed.
Fetch that water.
A girl says nothing.
A girl keeps
her mouth closed.
No one hears,
and friends may
talk in secret, yes?
A boy becomes a girl.
I was always a girl.
And I was always aware.
But the girl keeps secrets.
It is not for
a man to spoil them.
You're one of them now.
I should have let you burn.
And you fetch water
for one of them now.
Why is this right for you
and wrong for me?
I didn't have a choice.
You did.
I did.
And here we are.
A man pays his debts.
A man owes three.
Three what?
The Red God takes
what is his, lovely girl.
And only death
may pay for life.
You saved me and
the two I was with.
You stole three deaths
from the Red God.
We have to give them back.
Speak three names
and the man will do the rest.
Three lives I will give you,
no more, no less,
and we're done.
I can name anyone
and you'll kill him?
A man has said.
The one who
tortures everyone.
A man needs a name.
I don't know his name.
They call him the Tickler.
That is enough.
Go now, girl.
Your master is thirsty.
MORMONT: He's not here yet.
He'd have seen us,
blown the horn.
JON: When will he come?
The Halfhand does things
in his own time.
My uncle told me
stories about him.
Most of them are true.
I heard the Halfhand
spent half of last winter
beyond the Wall.
The whole winter.
He was north of
the Skirling Pass
when the snows came.
Had to wait for the thaw.
So it is possible for
someone to survive out
here on their own.
Well, possible
for the Halfhand.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Gilly would love it here.
There's nothing more sickening
than a man in love.
(MAN CHATTERING)
MAN: About time
you did something.
At least
you'll keep warm.
The Fist of
the First Men.
Think of how old
this place is.
Before the Targaryens
defeated the Andals,
before the Andals
took Westeros from
the First Men.
Before I die,
please, stop talking.
Thousands and
thousands of years ago,
the First Men stood here
where we're standing
all through the long night.
What do you
think they were like,
the First Men?
Stupid.
Smart people
don't find themselves
in places like this.
I think
they were afraid.
I think they came here
to get away from something.
And I don't think
it worked.
(HORN SOUNDING)
Wildlings?
JON: One blast is
for rangers returning.
Wildlings is two blasts.
So you got to
stand there waiting,
wondering.
One blast for friends,
two for foes.
And three
for White Walkers.
It's been a thousand years,
but that's the only time
they blow the horn
three times.
But if it's been
a thousand years,
how do you know?
Well...
BOTH: I read it in a book.
Look.
It's Qhorin Halfhand.
Aye, we'll live another day.
Hurrah.
Take care, my lord.
I remember reading
an old sailors' proverb,
"Piss on wildfire and
your cock burns off."
Oh, I have not
conducted this experiment.
It could well be true.
The substance burns so hot,
it melts wood, stone,
even steel,
and, of course, flesh.
The substance burns so hot,
it melts flesh like tallow.
After the dragons died,
wildfire was the key
to the Targaryen power.
(BRONN SCOFFS)
My companion takes issue.
If I could tell you
how many crazy old men
I've seen pushing carts
around army camps
making grand claims
about jars full of pig shit.
No offense meant.
Our order does not
deal in pig shit.
The substance is
fire given form.
And we have been perfecting it
since the days of Maegor.
To do what?
The jars are put in catapults
and flung at the enemy.
How much do you have?
If you could get real soldiers
to man the catapults,
then maybe you'd hit
your target one time in ten,
but all the real soldiers
are in the Riverlands
with your father.
My lord,
this man is insulting.
I don't know if
you've ever seen a battle,
old man,
but things can
get a bit messy.
'Cause when we're
flinging things at Stannis,
he's flinging them
right back at us.
Men die,
men shit themselves,
men run,
which means pots falling,
which means fire
inside the walls,
which means
the poor cunts trying
to defend the city
end up
burning it down.
My friend
remains unconvinced.
He would not dare
insult my order whilst
Aerys Targaryen lived.
Well, he's not
living anymore.
And all his pots of wildfire
didn't help him, did they?
Men win wars,
not magic tricks.
We have been
working tirelessly,
day and night,
ever since your royal sister
commanded us to do so.
Our present count
stands at 7,811.
Enough to burn
Stannis Baratheon's fleet
and armies both.
This is a shit idea.
I'm afraid I have to concur
with my advisor,
Wisdom Hallyne.
The contents of this room
could lay King's Landing low.
You won't be making wildfire
for my sister any longer.
You'll be making it for me.
(DRAGON CHITTERS)
(SPEAKING HIGH VALYRIAN)
(SQUEAKS)
(HISSES)
(SCREECHES)
(CHUCKLES)
He'll be able to feed
himself from now on.
Let him sleep, Doreah.
Yes, Khaleesi.
He loves you.
Thank you, my friend.
Did you see the dress
Xaro had made for you?
They say he's
the wealthiest man in Qarth.
It is known.
And if Qarth is the wealthiest
city in Essos...
The last time a rich
man gave me a dress,
he was selling me
to Khal Drogo.
Xaro is our host,
but we know nothing
about him.
Men like to talk
about other men
when they're happy.
You would look
like a real princess
in Xaro's...
She's not a princess.
She's a Khaleesi.
You should wear it,
Khaleesi.
You are their guest.
It would be rude not to.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(PEOPLE CHATTING)
(BIRDS SQUAWKING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(WOMAN LAUGHING)
And you must visit
the night market.
The Qartheen night market
is like no night market
you've ever seen.
It sounds wonderful.
The Meereenis think
they have a night market.
I will take
you there myself.
Please excuse me
for a moment.
(MEN SPEAKING DOTHRAKI)
What are they doing?
Malakko says the statue
is too heavy to carry.
Kovarro says that
Malakko is an idiot.
They can pry out the gems,
the rest is pure gold.
Very soft.
He can chop off as
much as we can carry.
My brother used to say
the only thing
the Dothraki knew how to do
was steal things
better men have built.
It's not the only thing.
They're quite good at
killing the better men.
That's not the kind of
queen I'm going to be.
PYAT PREE: Mother of Dragons.
On behalf of
the warlocks of Qarth,
I welcome you.
A demonstration?
Take this gem.
Look at it.
Into its depths.
So many facets.
Look closely enough
and you can see
yourself in them.
Often more than once.
Should you grow tired
of Xaro's baubles
and trinkets,
it would be an honor
to host you at
the House of the Undying.
You are always welcome,
Mother of Dragons.
(GUESTS APPLAUDING)
My apologies.
Pyat Pree is one
of the Thirteen.
It was customary for me
to extend him an invitation.
Customs die slow
deaths in Qarth.
What is
the House of the Undying?
It is where the warlocks go
to squint at dusty books
and drink shade
of the evening.
It turns their lips blue
and their minds soft.
So soft, they actually believe
their parlor tricks are magic.
WOMAN: You watch over her.
Do I know you?
I know you.
Jorah Mormont
of Bear Island.
Who are you?
I'm no one.
But she is
the Mother of Dragons.
She needs true protectors,
now more than ever.
They shall come day and night
to see the wonder born
into the world again.
And when they see,
they shall lust,
for dragons are
fire made flesh.
And fire is power.
It looked like Stannis.
To me it just
looked like...
A shadow in
the shape of a man.
In the shape of Stannis.
We should reach my
son's camp tomorrow.
Will you stay
there long, my lady?
Only long enough
to tell Robb what I have seen.
After that,
I will leave for Winterfell.
My two youngest need me.
I've been away from
them for far too long.
I never knew my mother.
I'm sorry.
My own mother died
on the birthing bed
when I was very young.
It's a bloody business.
What comes after
is even harder.
Once you're safely back
amongst your own people,
will you give me
leave to go, my lady?
You mean to kill Stannis.
I swore a vow.
But Stannis has
a great army around him.
His own guards are
sworn to keep him safe.
I'm as good
as any of them.
I should never have fled.
Renly's death was
no fault of yours.
You served him bravely.
I only held him that once
as he was dying.
He's gone, Brienne.
You serve nothing and no one
by following him
into the earth.
Renly's enemies are
Robb's enemies as well.
I do not know
your son, my lady.
But I could serve you,
if you would have me.
You have courage.
Not battle courage, perhaps,
but, I don't know,
a woman's kind of courage.
And I think that
when the time comes,
you will not hold me back.
Promise me that you
will not hold me back
from Stannis.
When the time comes,
I will not hold you back.
Then I am yours, my lady.
I will shield your back
and give my life for yours,
if it comes to that.
I swear it by
the Old Gods and the new.
I vow that you shall always
have a place in my home
and at my table
and that I shall ask
no service of you that
might bring you dishonor.
I swear it by
the Old Gods and the new.
(THUDS)
MAN: And it's not
just thieves, my lord.
There's wolves
in them hills now,
more than I ever seen.
They come down in the night
and they kill my sheep.
My three sons is away
fighting for your brother,
my lord.
They'll fight, keep fighting
till they're told to go home.
I have no one to man
my flock now. Only me.
I can't keep watch
all day and all night.
We can send two orphan boys
from Winterstown home with you
to help watch over
your flock
if you can give them
room and board.
My wife always prayed
for more children.
We'll look after them.
Thank you, my lord.
And may the gods
bless you and yours.
Stop it.
If that's everyone,
I'm going to go for
a ride before dark.
Good.
Hodor.
Ah! Lord Stark.
Torrhen's Square
is under siege.
is barely 40
leagues from here.
How can the Lannisters
strike so far north?
Might be a raiding party
led by the mountain.
Might be sellswords
paid by Tywin Lannister.
We have to help them.
Most of the fighting
men are away with Robb,
but I can gather
200 decent men.
Do you need so many?
If we can't protect
our own bannermen,
why should they protect us?
Go, Ser Rodrik.
Take the men you need.
Won't take long, my lord.
Southerners don't
do well up here.
(BIRD SQUAWKS)
BRAN: So,
what does it mean?
Ask your Maester Luwin.
He's the one studying
books all the time.
I did ask him.
He'd never heard of
a three-eyed raven.
Must not mean
anything, then.
You're lying.
You might be a little lord,
but don't you call me a liar.
You know what it means.
I never said I didn't.
You didn't give me
an honest answer.
That's not the same
as being a liar.
Well, it's not far off.
So, you've been dreaming
of a three-eyed raven again?
In the godswood,
you told me you didn't dream.
Now who's a liar?
What did you see
in your dream?
Something bad?
Tell me, boy.
I dreamt that
the sea came to Winterfell.
I saw waves
crashing against the gates
and the water came
flowing over the walls...
It flooded the castle.
Drowned men
were floating here,
in the yard.
Ser Rodrik was one of them.
The sea is
hundreds of miles away.
I know.
It's just a stupid dream.
I've got to get these
potatoes to the kitchen.
Otherwise they'll
put me in chains again.
Osha.
The three-eyed raven,
what do they say about it
north of the Wall?
They say all sorts
of crazy things
north of the Wall.
(WIND HOWLING)
(HORSES NEIGHING)
QHORIN: There.
MORMONT: Where?
On that mountain.
SAMWELL:
I don't see very well.
JON: A fire.
There's a fire.
The people sitting around it
have better eyes
than yours or mine.
When they see us coming,
that fire becomes a signal.
Gives Mance Rayder
plenty of time to throw
a party in our honor.
How many wildlings
have joined him?
From what we can tell,
all of them.
Mance has gathered them all
like deer against the wolves.
They're almost ready
to make their move.
Where?
Somewhere safe.
Somewhere south.
Can't just march
into their midst.
And we can't wait
for them here
with nothing but a pile
of stones to protect us.
You saying we should
fall back to the Wall?
Mance was one of us once.
Now he's one of them.
He's going to teach them
our way of doing things.
They'll hit us in force
and they won't run away
when we hit back.
They're gonna be more
organized than before,
more disciplined,
more like us.
So we need to be
more like them,
do things their way.
Sneak in, kill Mance,
and scatter them
to the winds before they
can march on the Wall.
And to do that...
We need to get rid
of those lookouts.
It's not a job
for 400 men.
I need to move
fast and silent.
Harker,
Stonesnake, Borba.
Lord Commander,
I'd like to join
Lord Qhorin.
I've been called
lots of things,
but that might be
my first Lord Qhorin.
(LAUGHING)
You're a steward,
Snow, not a ranger.
I've fought and
killed a wight.
How many rangers
can say that?
He's the one?
Aye. You killed a wight.
You also let an old
man beat you bloody
and take your sword.
(ALL LAUGHING)
QHORIN: Craster?
In the boy's defense,
that's a tough old goat.
I could take up Jon's duties
while he's gone, my lord.
It would be no trouble.
Well, I hope you
make a better ranger
than you do a steward.
Go on.
XARO: So, tell me,
how long has your manservant
been in love with you?
He's not my manservant
and he's not in love with me.
He's my advisor,
my friend.
Unlikely.
I can almost always tell
what a man wants.
And what about
what a woman wants?
Much more complicated.
You, for example,
what do you want?
To cross the Narrow Sea
and take back the Iron Throne.
Why?
Because I promised
my khalasar I'd protect them
and find them a safe home.
(CHUCKLES)
You want to conquer
the Seven Kingdoms
for the Dothraki?
I want them because
they're mine by right.
The Iron Throne is mine
and I will take it.
Ah, a conqueror.
And how did you
get all of this?
Did someone give it to you?
No. I come from nothing.
I hit the docks
like a piece of cargo,
except someone normally cares
what happens to cargo.
So you wanted
more than you had
and you took it.
You're a conqueror, too.
You're just less ambitious.
(CHUCKLES)
What do you want,
Xaro Xhoan Daxos?
At the gates of the city,
you bled for me.
Why?
I will show you why.
The door and the vault
is made of Valyrian stone.
The hardest steel
does not make a mark.
I offered the greatest
locksmiths in Qarth
their weight in gold if
they could break into it.
I made the same offer
to the greatest thieves.
They all went home
empty-handed.
The only thing that
can open this door
is this key.
And behind the door?
(XARO CHUCKLES)
And it can all be mine?
All? Let us say half.
More than enough
to buy horses,
ships, armies...
Enough to go home.
All I have to do?
Is marry me.
That was
a romantic proposal.
I've already married
once for love,
but the gods
stole her from me.
I come from nothing.
My mother and father
never owned a pair of shoes.
But marry me,
and I will give you
the Seven Kingdoms
and our children
will be princes
and princesses.
See?
I have more ambition
than you thought.
The time is right,
Daenerys Targaryen,
First of Your Name.
Robert Baratheon is dead.
JORAH: If you cross the sea
with an army you bought...
The Seven Kingdoms
are at war with one another.
Four false kings
destroying the country.
To win Westeros,
you need support
from Westeros.
The usurper is dead.
The Starks fight
the Lannisters,
and Baratheons
fight each other.
According to your new friend
who earned your trust
by cutting his hand?
The time to strike is now.
We need to find ships
and an army
or we'll spend
the rest of our lives
rotting away at
the edge of the world.
Rich men do not become rich
by giving more than they get.
They'll give you
ships and soldiers
and they'll own you forever.
Moving carefully
is the hard way,
but it's the right way.
And if I'd
listened to that advice
outside the gates of Qarth,
we'd all be dead by now.
I know the opportunity
before you
seems like the last
you'll ever have,
but you must...
Do not speak to me
like I'm a child.
I only want...
What do you want?
Tell me.
To see you
on the Iron Throne.
Why?
You have a good claim.
A title.
A birthright.
But you have
something more than that.
You may cover it up
and deny it, but you have
a gentle heart.
You would not only be
respected and feared,
you would be loved.
Someone who can rule
and should rule.
Centuries come and go
without a person like that
coming into the world.
There are times
when I look at you
and I still can't
believe you're real.
So what would
you have me do,
as my advisor?
Make your own way.
Find your own ship.
You only need one.
The allies we need are
in Westeros, not Qarth.
And how do I get the ship?
I'll find it for you.
A sound ship
with a good captain.
I look forward
to meeting him.
Khaleesi.
(DRAGONS CHIRPING)
(WATER SIZZLING)
You should stand sideface.
Sideface?
Sideways.
Why?
Smaller target.
Am I fighting someone?
You're practicing
for a fight.
You should practice right.
(LOUD THUD)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
MAN: Guards!
Did you see anything?
Go up there. Go and
see where he fell from.
Go up the battlement.
Move away.
Stand back. He's dead.