(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(HORSE NEIGHS)
MAN:
It's got to be the Mountain.
He's the biggest.
He's the strongest.
Bulls are bigger
than lions.
Doesn't mean I'd
pick a bull in a fight.
If the bull had
fangs and claws, I would.
Right, the Mountain
or our man Jaime.
If he ever gets out.
(THUNDERCLAP)
Loras Tyrell?
Loras Tyrell.
He's prettier
than the Queen.
I don't care about pretty.
He's better with a sword
than any of them.
How good could he be?
He's been stabbing
Renly Baratheon for years,
and Renly ain't dead.
(LAUGHING)
(HORSE WHINNYING)
The horses seem
a little spooked to you?
They're horses.
They get spooked by
their own shadows.
(SHUSHING)
(HORSE SNORTING)
Do you hear that?
No.
There's something out there.
(NEIGHING)
(FARTS)
(GASPS)
(LAUGHING)
Oh.
Oh, you're
a right little prick.
You should see your face.
I swear
you pissed yourself.
"Oh, who goes there? Ahh!"
(LAUGHS)
There is something
out there.
Yeah, don't even try me.
(HORSE NEIGHS)
Rennick.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
Rennick!
(RENNICK SCREAMING)
(HORSES NEIGHING)
COMMANDER: King in the North!
MEN: The King in the North!
(WATER RUNNING)
(MAN GROANS)
(FLIES BUZZING)
(MAN SCREAMING)
(HORSE NEIGHING)
BOLTON: Five Lannisters dead
for every one of ours.
MAN: They're dead.
Take everything they've got.
BOLTON: We've nowhere to keep
all these prisoners.
Barely enough food
to feed our own.
We're not executing prisoners,
Lord Bolton.
Of course, Your Grace.
The officers will
be useful.
Some of them may be privy
to Tywin Lannister's plans.
I doubt it.
BOLTON: Well,
we'll learn soon enough.
In my family, we say,
"A naked man has few secrets.
"A flayed man none."
My father outlawed
flaying in the North.
We're not in the North.
We're not torturing them.
The high road's very pretty,
but you'll have a hard time
marching your army down it.
The Lannisters hold
prisoners of their own.
I won't give them an excuse
to abuse my sisters.
MAN: No, don't!
Don't! Please!
(WOMAN SHUSHING)
(FLIES BUZZING)
The rot's set in.
No, don't! No, don't!
Shh.
Please, don't!
It'll get better.
It doesn't even hurt.
The rot will spread.
If we don't take
the foot now...
No, you can't!
Ser! Please, ser.
I can't lose...
You'll die if she doesn't.
I don't want to be
a cripple, please.
Surely one of our men
needs your attention
more than this cub.
Your men are not
my men, my lord.
Put this in your
mouth and lie down.
You don't want to watch.
No! You can't!
Bite on it.
It's better than
biting your own tongue,
believe me.
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(SAWING)
What's your name?
Talisa.
Your last name?
You want to know what side
my family fights on?
You know my family name.
You have me at
a disadvantage.
That boy lost his foot
on your orders.
They killed my father.
That boy did?
The family he fights for.
Do you think he's friends
with King Joffrey?
He's a fisherman's son
that grew up near Lannisport.
He probably never
held a spear
before they shoved one
in his hands
a few months ago.
I have no hatred
for the lad.
(SIGHS)
That should help
his foot grow back.
You'd have us surrender,
end all this bloodshed.
I understand.
The country would
be at peace
and life would be just
under the righteous hand
of good King Joffrey.
You're going to
kill Joffrey?
If the gods
give me strength.
And then what?
I don't know.
We'll go back
to Winterfell.
I have no desire to
sit on the Iron Throne.
So who will?
I don't know.
You're fighting to
overthrow a king,
and yet you have no plan
for what comes after?
First we have to
win the war.
You never told me
where you're from.
Volantis.
Volantis?
You're far from home.
The boy was lucky
you were here.
He was unlucky
that you were.
You're here to answer
for your brother's
latest treasons.
Your Grace,
whatever my traitor
brother has done,
I had no part.
You know that.
I beg you, please...
Ser Lancel,
tell her of this outrage.
LANCEL:
Using some vile sorcery,
your brother fell
on Stafford Lannister
with an army of wolves.
(CROWD MURMURING)
Thousands of good
men were butchered.
After the slaughter,
the Northmen feasted on
the flesh of the slain.
(CROWD MURMURING)
Killing you
would send your
brother a message.
(CRYING)
But my mother insists
on keeping you alive.
Stand.
So we'll have to send
your brother a message
some other way.
Meryn.
Leave her face.
I like her pretty.
(BLOW LANDS)
(SANSA GASPS)
(GROANS)
Meryn, my lady is
overdressed.
Unburden her.
If you want Robb
Stark to hear us,
we're going to
have to speak louder.
(SOBBING)
TYRION:
What is the meaning of this?
What kind of knight
beats a helpless girl?
The kind who
serves his king, Imp.
Careful, now.
We don't want to get blood
all over your
pretty white cloak.
TYRION: Someone get the girl
something to
cover herself with.
She is to be your queen.
Have you no regard
for her honor?
JOFFREY: I'm punishing her.
TYRION: For what crimes?
She did not fight
her brother's battle,
you half-wit.
You can't talk
to me like that.
The king can do as he likes!
The Mad King did
as he liked.
Has your Uncle
Jaime ever told you
what happened to him?
No one threatens His Grace
in the presence
of the Kingsguard.
I'm not
threatening the king, ser.
I am educating my nephew.
Bronn, the next
time Ser Meryn speaks,
kill him.
That was a threat.
See the difference?
(CROWD WHISPERING)
I apologize for my
nephew's behavior.
(CROWD MURMURING)
Tell me the truth.
Do you want an end
to this engagement?
I am loyal to King Joffrey,
my one true love.
Lady Stark,
you may survive us yet.
The little king's
backed up.
Clogged from balls
to brains.
You think dipping his wick
will cure what ails him?
There's no cure
for being a cunt.
But the boy's
at that age.
And he's got
nothing to do all day
but pick wings off flies.
Couldn't hurt to get
some of the poison out.
What are you
doing here, dog?
Your uncle left
your nameday present
and asked me to
see that you got it.
And?
What is it?
Look inside, Your Grace.
Your Grace.
Happy nameday,
My nameday has passed.
We won't tell
if you won't.
No.
Her.
Touch her.
(WOMEN GIGGLING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Could you hit her?
(LAUGHS)
My uncle sent you?
Yes, Your Grace.
He chose us himself.
Hmm.
(SLAPPING)
(WOMEN LAUGHING)
Use this.
Harder.
(WHIMPERS)
I said harder.
He'd want me to get
his money's worth.
(CRYING)
(SCREAMING)
Your Grace, too much pain
will spoil the pleasure.
(WOMAN WHIMPERING)
Please, Your Grace.
Your Grace,
if your uncle finds out...
Oh, I want him to find out.
You will bring her
to his chambers
when you're finished
and show him
what you've done,
or the same thing
will happen to you.
Begin.
(THUDS)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
Harder!
Well, if it isn't my
favorite whoremonger.
Pray I haven't
kept you waiting long.
Your Grace.
Now you do
the Lannisters' bidding,
is that it?
Tell me, was my
brother's body even cold
before you secured
your newest patron?
I'm a practical man.
Just not a loyal one.
And who would you
have me be loyal to?
Your brother's corpse?
(CHUCKLES)
I don't like you,
Lord Baelish.
I don't like your face.
I don't like the words
that come oozing
out of your mouth.
I don't want you in my tent
one minute more
than necessary.
So tell me,
why are you here?
You can trust Brienne.
Her loyalty comes
without charge.
You still have many friends
at court, Your Grace,
many who believe Ned Stark
erred by not supporting
your claim.
Now I understand.
You know I have the numbers.
You know I'm marching
on King's Landing.
When I take the throne,
you hope to retain
your position.
And your head.
I would give
priority to my head.
I understand that
you don't like me,
and while that
saddens me greatly,
I did not come here today
seeking your affection.
When you march
on King's Landing,
you may find yourself facing
a protracted siege or...
open gates.
Your Grace.
Lord Baelish.
All of these tents
look the same to me.
Would you be so kind...
It would be my pleasure.
It took me weeks
to learn my way
around the camp.
Twice I walked in on officers
in stages of undress.
And the moment I
learn which tent is mine,
we're on the move again.
"Your tent"?
Not "Our tent"?
The king snores, perhaps?
Or simply prefers solitude?
Pressures of command,
no doubt.
Four kings vying
for the throne.
I am not tutored
in warfare,
but basic arithmetic
favors the side with
the greater numbers.
If war were arithmetic,
the mathematicians
would rule the world.
I did notice your brother
entering His Grace's
tent just now.
The place of a Kingsguard
is by the king's side.
And on the night
of your wedding,
who was by
the king's side then?
You seem quite
interested in our marriage.
Your marriage is
quite interesting.
Not only to me,
but to the realm.
The marriage of a wealthy girl
always breeds interest,
if nothing else.
You've never married,
have you?
I've been unlucky in
my affections, sadly.
That is sad.
Though perhaps
it's for the best.
The whole notion of marriage
seems to confuse you,
so allow me to explain.
My husband is my king,
and my king is my husband.
Here is your tent,
Lord Baelish. Good night.
(HOOFBEATS)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
What do you
know of this place?
Only that the desert
around their walls is
called the Garden of Bones.
Every time the Qartheen
shut their gates
on a traveler,
the garden grows.
Go on!
You, keep moving!
(WOMAN CRYING)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
MAN: Bring her about!
What kind of fire
melts stone?
Dragon fire.
There's dragons here?
No, all the dragons
are dead.
What's that smell?
Dead people.
Move.
MAN: Please, please, no, no!
(SCREAMING)
(SOBBING) No.
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(SCREAMING STOPS)
(CHAINS RATTLE)
(HEAVY THUD)
WOMAN: He's dead.
He was my son.
My sister was
three days ago.
My husband,
the day before that.
They take someone
every day?
Does anyone live?
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
ARYA: Joffrey.
Cersei.
Ilyn Payne.
The Hound.
Joffrey.
Cersei.
Ilyn Payne.
The Hound.
Joffrey. Cersei.
Ilyn Payne. The Hound.
How dare you?
You may have
heard false reports.
You betrayed Ned.
Betrayed?
I wanted him to serve
as Protector of the Realm.
I begged him to
seize the moment.
I trusted you.
My husband trusted you.
And you repaid our
faith with treachery.
No, my lady.
Get out!
Cat, I've...
I've loved you
since I was a boy.
It seems to me that fate
has given us this chance...
Have you lost your mind?
Get out!
Do you want to see
your girls again?
Sansa,
more beautiful than ever?
And Arya,
just as wild as ever?
You have Arya, too?
Both girls are
healthy and safe.
For now.
But you know the Queen
and you know Joffrey.
I fear for their longevity
if they remain in the capital.
(KNIFE CLINKS)
What do you want?
The Lannisters will
trade your daughters
for the Kingslayer.
Of course they will.
Jaime Lannister
for two girls?
Robb will never
agree to those terms.
I'm not bringing
these terms to him.
I'm bringing them to you.
You think I keep
secrets from my son?
Robb has surprised them all
with his skills in battle,
but he's not a mother.
Consider it, Cat.
You may not get
another chance.
I've brought you a gift.
I don't want your gifts.
A token of Tyrion
Lannister's goodwill.
He wants you
to understand that this
exchange of prisoners
is offered in good faith.
Good faith?
What's this?
Your husband was
an honorable man.
He should rest
beside his family
in the crypts
beneath Winterfell.
You may not believe...
Get out.
(GROANS)
(MEN SHOUTING)
MAN: Get up, you dogs!
(WOOD BANGING)
That's him,
the one who picks.
The Mountain.
What are you doing?
He told me he
stares at him every day.
That's why he
doesn't get picked.
You.
MAN: Move, boy!
Move!
(LIQUID TRICKLING)
TICKLER:
Is there gold and silver
in the village?
I don't know.
Gems?
I didn't see any.
Where is the Brotherhood?
I don't know.
(RATS SQUEAKING)
TICKLER:
Where is the Brotherhood?
I don't know. Please.
I don't know.
(RAT SQUEAKING)
(WHIMPERING)
Which of the villagers
aided them?
I don't know.
Who?
I...
I never saw.
Who?
Please. Please, stop.
Please, it's starting to...
Who?
I didn't see
anyone help him.
(RAT SHRIEKING)
Take it off!
Who helped him?
Ganes, the butcher,
and his son.
That's better.
You've been very helpful.
No, stop, please!
What are you doing?
Please, stop!
Please, stop! No! No!
I told you everything! No!
No! (SCREAMING)
(RAT CLATTERING)
ARYA: Joffrey.
Cersei.
Ilyn Payne. The Hound.
WOMAN: Please, Polliver.
Some food.
Just a crust of bread.
(WOMAN CRYING)
Polliver.
The Mountain.
STANNIS:
Lady Stark, I had not thought
to find you in the Stormlands.
I had not thought to
be here, Lord Stannis.
Can that truly be you?
Who else might it be?
When I saw your standard,
I couldn't be sure.
Whose banner is that?
My own.
I suppose if we
used the same one,
the battle would be
terribly confusing.
Why is your stag on fire?
The king has
taken for his sigil
the fiery heart of
the Lord of Light.
Ah, you must be
this fire priestess
we hear so much about.
Mmm, brother,
now I understand
why you found religion
in your old age.
Watch yourself, Renly.
RENLY: No, no,
I'm relieved.
I never really believed
you were a fanatic.
Charmless, rigid,
a bore, yes,
but not a godly man.
You should kneel
before your brother.
He's the Lord's chosen,
born amidst salt and smoke.
Born amidst salt and smoke?
Is he a ham?
STANNIS: That's twice
I've warned you.
Listen to yourselves.
If you were sons of mine,
I would knock
your heads together
and lock you in a bedchamber
until you remembered
that you were brothers.
It is strange to find you
beside my brother,
Lady Stark.
Your husband was
a supporter of my claim.
Lord Eddard's integrity
cost him his head.
And you sit
beside this pretender
and chastise me.
We share a common enemy.
The Iron Throne
is mine by right.
All those that
deny that are my foes.
The whole realm denies it,
from Dorne to the Wall.
Old men deny it
with their death rattle
and unborn children deny it
in their mother's wombs.
No one wants you
for their king.
You never wanted
any friends, brother.
But a man without friends
is a man without power.
For the sake of
the mother who bore us,
I will give you this
one night to reconsider.
Strike your banners,
come to me before dawn,
and I will grant you
your old seat in the Council.
I'll even name you my heir
until a son is born to me.
Otherwise I shall
destroy you.
Look across those fields,
brother.
Can you see
all those banners?
You think a few bolts of cloth
will make you king?
RENLY: No.
The men holding
those bolts of cloth
will make me king.
We shall see, Renly.
Come the dawn, we shall see.
Look to your sins,
Lord Renly.
The night is dark
and full of terrors.
Would you believe
I loved him once?
I thought we were welcome.
If you heard a Dothraki horde
was approaching your city,
you might do the same,
Khaleesi.
Horde?
My name is Daenerys...
Daenerys Stormborn of
the house Targaryen.
You know me, my lord?
Only by reputation,
Khaleesi.
And I'm no lord,
merely a humble merchant.
They call you
the Mother of Dragons.
And what should
I call you?
Oh, my name is quite long
and quite impossible
for foreigners to pronounce.
I am simply
a trader of spices.
But we are the Thirteen,
charged with the governance
and protection of Qarth,
the greatest city
that ever was or will be.
The beauty of
Quarth is legendary...
Qarth.
Might we see the dragons?
My friend,
we have traveled very far.
We have no food, no water.
Once I see my people fed,
I would be honored...
Forgive me,
Mother of Dragons,
but no man alive has
seen a living dragon.
Some of my more
skeptical friends
refuse to believe
your children
even exist.
All we ask is the chance
to see for ourselves.
I am not a liar.
Oh, I don't think you are.
But as I've
never met you before,
my opinion on the matter
is of limited value.
Where I come from,
guests are
treated with respect,
not insulted at the gates.
Then perhaps you should
return to where you come from.
We wish you well.
What are you doing?
You promised to receive me.
We have received you.
Here we are,
and here you are.
If you do not let us in,
all of us will die.
Which we shall
deeply regret.
But Qarth did not become
the greatest city
that ever was or will be
by letting Dothraki savages
through its gates.
Khaleesi, please be careful.
Thirteen!
When my dragons are grown,
we will take back
what was stolen from me
and destroy those
who have wronged me.
We will lay waste to armies
and burn cities to the ground.
Turn us away and we
will burn you first.
Ah.
You are a true Targaryen.
Only, as you said
a moment ago,
if we don't let
you into the city,
you will all die.
And so...
Retreating in fear
from a little girl
is unbecoming of
the greatest city
that ever was or will be.
The discussion is over,
Xaro Xhoan Daxos.
The Thirteen have spoken.
I am one of the Thirteen,
and I am still speaking.
The girl threatens
to burn our city
to the ground
and you would invite her in
for a cup of wine?
She is
the Mother of Dragons.
Do you expect her to
watch her people starve
without breathing fire?
I believe we can
allow a few Dothraki
through our gates
without dooming our city.
After all, here I am,
a savage from
the Summer Isles,
and Qarth still stands.
Our decision is final.
Very well.
I invoke soumai.
I will vouch for her,
her people,
and her dragons,
in accordance with the law.
Be it on your head.
Welcome to Qarth,
my lady.
MOUNTAIN: You.
TICKLER:
Is there gold or silver
in the village?
I'm not from the village.
Where is the Brotherhood?
I don't know
what that is.
(SQUEAKING)
(HORSES NEIGH)
MAN: You two.
Take Lord Lannister's
things to his quarters.
What's this?
We weren't expecting you
till tomorrow, Lord Tywin.
(CHUCKLES) Evidently not.
Why are
these prisoners not
in their cells?
MOUNTAIN: Cells are
overflowing, my lord.
POLLIVER:
This lot won't be here long.
Don't need no permanent place.
After we interrogate 'em,
we usually just...
Are we so well-manned
that we can afford to discard
able young bodies
and skilled laborers?
You, do you have a trade?
GENDRY: Smith, my lord.
What are you looking at?
Kneel!
Kneel or I'll carve
your lungs out, boy.
He'll do no such thing.
This one's a girl,
you idiot,
dressed as a boy.
Why?
Safer to travel,
my lord.
Smart.
More than I can
say for this lot.
Get these prisoners to work.
Bring the girl.
I need a new cupbearer.
MOUNTAIN: My lord.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Your visits are
too few, cousin.
Her Grace,
the Queen Regent,
commands you to release
Grand Maester Pycelle.
Here's your warrant.
So it is.
Will you take a cup with me?
I find that mulled
wine helps me sleep.
I am here at
Her Grace's behest,
not to drink with you, Imp.
If my sister was so
concerned for Pycelle,
I would have thought
she'd come herself.
Instead she sends you.
What am I to make of that?
I don't care
what you make of it,
so long as you release
your prisoner immediately.
And you've received
these instructions
directly from Cersei?
As I said several times.
And you've waited this long
to deliver the information?
When the Queen Regent
gives me a command,
I carry it out without delay.
Cersei must have
great trust in you,
allowing you into her chamber
during the hour of the wolf.
The Queen Regent has
a great many responsibilities.
She often works
from dusk till dawn.
She must be very glad
to have you helping her
from dusk till dawn.
Ah.
Lavender oil.
She always loved
lavender oil, even as a girl.
I am a knight!
An anointed knight, yes.
Tell me,
did Cersei have
you knighted
before or after she
took you into her bed?
What? Nothing to say?
No more warnings
for me, ser?
You will withdraw
these filthy accusations.
Have you ever
given any thought
to what King Joffrey
will have to say
when he finds out
you've been bedding
his mother?
It's not my fault!
Did she take you
against your will?
Can you not defend yourself,
knight?
Your own father, Lord Tywin,
when I was named
the King's squire,
he told me to obey
her in everything.
Did he tell you
to fuck her, too?
I only meant I
did as I was bid.
Hated every moment of it,
is that what
you'll have me believe?
A high place in court,
a knighthood,
my sister's legs spreading
open for you at night.
Oh, yes,
it must have been terrible.
Wait here. His Grace
will want to hear this.
Mercy! Mercy,
my lord! I beg you.
Save it for Joffrey.
He loves a good grovel.
My lord, it was
your sister's bidding,
the Queen.
I'll leave the city
at once, I swear.
No, I think not.
My lord?
You heard me.
My father told you
to obey my sister.
Obey her.
Stay close to her side.
Keep her trust.
Pleasure her
whenever she requires.
No one ever need know,
as long as you
keep faith with me.
I want to know
what Cersei is doing,
where she goes, who she sees,
what they talk of, everything.
And you will tell me.
Yes, my lord, I will.
I swear it, as you command.
Oh, rise, rise.
Let us drink to
our understanding.
Oh, you don't have a cup.
Oh, well.
Smile, cousin. My sister
is a beautiful woman,
and it's all for
the good of the realm.
Go back and tell her
that I beg her forgiveness,
that I want no more
conflict between us
and that, henceforth,
I shall do nothing
without her consent.
But her demands?
Oh, I'll give her Pycelle.
You will?
Yes, I'll release him
in the morning.
Cersei can keep him
as a pet, if she wants,
but I will not have
him on the Council.
I could swear
that I had not harmed
a single hair on his head,
but that would not,
strictly speaking, be true.
(WOOD CREAKING)
MAN:
Stay within one table length.
Your Grace.
Do your knucklebones
bring you luck?
Well, life's been good
since you hacked
them off, Your Grace.
And it's four less
fingernails to clean.
Fewer.
Pardon?
Four fewer
fingernails to clean.
Never understood why
you had to wear them.
It reminds me of
where I come from
and where I am now.
It reminds me
of your justice.
It was an honest punishment
and you were good
with the cleaver.
You were a hero
and a smuggler.
A good act does
not wash out the bad,
nor a bad the good.
A lesson I've tried
to teach my son.
Does he listen?
To me?
Gods, no.
But if your red woman
told him to leap
from the crow's nest...
She has a name.
I trust you've not forgotten
your smuggler's tricks.
I've lived within
the law for 17...
I want you to be
a smuggler this time.
Any shore, any night.
What am I bringing ashore?
The red woman.
No one must know
what you do and we'll not
speak of this again.
I am true to Your Grace
and always will be,
but surely there are
other ways, cleaner ways.
Cleaner ways don't
win wars.
Are you afraid,
Onion Knight?
Someone once told me
the night is dark
and full of terrors.
You've carried
more unpleasant
cargo in your time.
Are you a good man,
Ser Davos Seaworth?
I'd say my parts
are mixed, my lady,
good and bad.
If half an onion
is black with rot,
it's a rotten onion.
A man is good
or he is evil.
And which are you?
Oh, good.
I'm a knight myself, of sorts,
a champion of light and life.
Well, that must be
very nice for you.
Do you love your wife?
I do.
Yet you have
known other women.
Don't talk about my wife.
I'm not. I'm talking
about other women.
Like me, Ser Davos.
You want me.
You want to see
what's beneath this robe.
And you will.
Strange that
this Lord of Light
asks you to work
in the shadows.
Shadows cannot live
in the dark, Ser Davos.
They are servants of light,
the children of fire.
And the brighter the flame,
the darker they are.
These weren't here before.
They've barred the passage.
They can't bar
our passage.
Gods protect us.
There's only one god,
Ser Davos,
and he only protects
those who serve him.
(GASPS)
(LAUGHS)
(MOANING)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMING)
(SHRIEKING)
(GROWLS)