MAN: That's it.
(MAN COUGHING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
The tide's against us.
Aye, but we have the wind.
She'll blow us
straight to the gates.
MATTHOS: You're coming home.
DAVOS: King's Landing
hasn't been home
for 20 years.
I spent most of my life
dodging the royal fleet.
And now I'm
sailing right at them.
This is the royal fleet.
And you're not
a smuggler anymore,
you're the high captain.
Of course, there are...
several royal fleets
at the moment.
Not after tonight.
When the sun rises,
Stannis will sit
on the Iron Throne
and you will be his Hand.
Gods be good.
God.
Father, there is only one
and he watches over us.
But not over them?
Over all of us.
The people of
King's Landing did not
choose the false king,
Joffrey Baratheon.
They will be glad to
see his head on a spike.
Well, first,
we have to put it there.
Our ships
outnumber theirs 10-to-1.
Our army
outnumber theirs 5-to-1.
Those walls have
never been breached,
and the men
guarding the walls,
when they see you,
they don't see a liberator,
they see a stranger come
to set their city on fire.
I have faith in
the Lord of Light.
I have faith in our cause.
And I have faith
in my captain.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Are you afraid, my lion?
If the city falls,
Stannis will
burn every Lannister
he can find.
Of course I'm afraid.
I won't let them hurt you.
I'm a Lannister.
I don't have
a choice in all this.
But it's not your war.
It is now.
You can't fuck your way
out of everything.
I have so far.
Do you remember
what you said when
you met me in your tent?
That I should make love
to you like it was your
last day on this earth.
PYCELLE: As you know,
Your Grace,
it is not only
the sworn duty of a maester
to carry out the wishes
of the house he serves,
but also to offer guidance
and counsel
in times of war.
Your words are
always wise and measured.
If you could...
If anything,
a maester's duties
become more urgent
in times of
war and turmoil.
I remember back in
the days of King...
You brought me something?
Yes.
Essence of nightshade
is as dangerous as
it is efficacious.
A single drop
in a cup of wine
suffices to
soothe ragged nerves.
Three drops will bring on
a deep and dreamless sleep.
Ten drops, however...
I know what
ten drops will bring.
Your Grace,
if I may ask...
You may not.
You must have
a lot of work to do.
I'm sure many brave men
will need your wisdom soon.
Yes. A siege is very...
Be careful on the stairs,
Grand Maester.
There are so many.
Your Grace.
MEN: ♪ And so he spoke
♪ That Lord of Castamere
♪ But now the rains
weep o'er his halls
♪ With no one there to hear
♪ Yes, now the rains
weep o'er his halls
♪ And not a soul to hear ♪
Good boys!
Lannisters!
Where'd you learn
the Lannister song?
Drunk Lannisters.
(ALL LAUGHING)
You've got
a pretty voice.
Thank you
very much.
And I like your nose.
How many times
you break it?
Well,
now let's see.
First time,
I was five.
My mam smacked me
with an iron poker.
Oh.
It wasn't me
she was aiming at.
She was trying for
my little brother.
Now he was a real pest.
Second time, I was nine.
Got in a scrap
with a few older boys.
They won.
Third time...
Eh, you don't want
to know about
the third time.
Poor nose.
Don't feel sorry for him.
He'll be halfway
up your arse before
the night's through.
(LAUGHING)
Welcome, friends.
This round's on me.
I don't think he likes me.
You think you're a hard man?
(CHUCKLES)
I know it.
(MEN LAUGHING)
It's warm in here.
We've got
beautiful women
and good brown ale.
Plenty for everyone.
And all you want
is to put one of us
in the cold ground
with no women to
keep us company.
Oh, there's women
in the ground.
I put some there myself.
So have you.
You like fucking
and drinking
and singing.
But killing,
killing's the thing
you love.
You're just like me.
Only smaller.
And quicker.
Eh? (CHUCKLES)
Your Lord Imp's
going to miss you.
Aye...
I expect he will someday.
(BELLS TOLLING)
MAN: Here we are.
(ALL CHATTING)
One more drink
before the war?
Shall we?
I've always hated the bells.
They ring for horror.
A dead king,
a city under siege.
A wedding.
Exactly.
Podrick,
is that it?
"Is that it?"
Nice touch.
As if you don't
know the name of
every boy in town.
I'm not entirely sure
what you're suggesting.
I'm entirely sure
you're entirely sure
what I'm suggesting.
Do you trust him?
Oddly enough, I do.
Good.
The map you asked for.
There must be
20 miles of tunnels
beneath the city.
Closer to 50.
The Targaryens
built this city to
withstand a siege
and to provide
escape if necessary.
I'm not escaping.
Strange as it sounds,
I'm the captain of the ship,
and if the ship goes down,
I go with her.
That is good to hear.
Though I'm sure many
captains say the same
while their ship is afloat.
You look well suited
for battle, my lord.
Well, I'm not.
For all our sakes,
I hope you are wrong.
My little birds tell me
that Stannis Baratheon
has taken up
with a red priestess
from Asshai.
What of it?
You don't believe in
the old powers, my lord?
Blood spells,
curses, shape-shifting.
What do you think?
I think you believe
in what you see
and in what those
you trust have seen.
You probably don't
entirely trust me.
Mmm, don't take it personally.
I don't entirely trust myself.
And yet I have seen things
and heard things,
things you have not,
things I wish I had not.
I don't believe
I've ever told you
how I was cut.
No, I don't believe you have.
One day, I will.
The dark arts have
provided Lord Stannis
with his armies
and paved his path
to our door.
For a man in
service to such powers
to sit on the Iron Throne,
I can think of
nothing worse.
And tonight,
I believe you are
the only man
who can stop him.
(TOLLING CONTINUES)
They're welcoming
the new king.
I've never known bells
to mean surrender.
They want to play
music with us? Let's play.
Drums.
Drums!
(MEN SHOUTING)
TYRION: Remember,
wait till the ships...
BRONN: The ships
are in the bay.
They must be
far enough in...
I know what "in" means.
Do you know
how to use that?
I chopped wood once.
No, I watched my brother
chopping wood.
I saw you kill
a man with a shield.
You'll be unstoppable
with an ax.
Don't get killed.
Nor you, my friend.
Oh, are we friends now?
Of course we are.
Just because I pay you
for your services
doesn't diminish
our friendship.
Enhances it, really.
Oh! "Enhances."
Fancy word for a sellsword.
Been spending time
with fancy folks.
Lady Sansa and Sheila.
Shae.
Shae, yes.
Surely my sister has
asked you to join the
other highborn ladies
in Maegor's holdfast.
She has, my lord,
but King Joffrey sent
for me to see him off.
Sansa.
Always been a great romantic,
my nephew.
JOFFREY: Sansa, come here.
I will pray for your
safe return, my lord.
Will you?
Just as I pray
for the king's.
Stay safe, my lady.
And you, my lion.
Your king rides
forth to battle.
You should see
him off with a kiss.
My new blade.
Hearteater, I've named it.
Kiss it.
You'll kiss it again
when I return
and taste my uncle's blood.
Will you slay him yourself?
If Stannis is fool
enough to come near me.
So you'll be
outside the gates
fighting in the vanguard?
A king doesn't
discuss battle plans
with stupid girls.
I'm sorry, Your Grace.
You're right, I'm stupid.
Of course you'll
be in the vanguard.
They say my brother Robb
always goes
where the fighting
is thickest.
And he is
only a pretender.
Your brother's turn
will come.
Then you can lick his blood
off Hearteater, too.
Some of those boys
will never come back.
Joffrey will.
The worst ones
always live.
Shh.
Come, my lady.
(MEN SHOUTING)
(DISTANT DRUMS BEATING)
Where's our fleet?
On the way.
Why isn't it here now?
They're coming.
Hound, tell the Hand
that his king has
asked him a question.
The king has
asked you a question.
Ser Lancel, tell the Hound
to tell the king
that the Hand is
extremely busy.
LANCEL: The Hand of the King
would like me
to tell you to
tell the king...
If I tell the Hound
to cut you in half,
he'll do it
without a second thought.
That would make me
the quarterman.
It just doesn't have
the same ring to it.
Cut me in half
and I won't be able
to give the signal.
No signal, no plan.
No plan and
Stannis Baratheon
sacks this city,
takes the Iron Throne,
puts your pinched
little head atop
a gate somewhere.
It might be quite amusing,
except that my head
would be up there, too.
I've never much
liked my head,
but I don't want to
see it removed just yet.
Where are their ships?
It was wise to
attack at night.
We took them by surprise.
Lord Varys knows
what you had for breakfast
three days ago.
There are no surprises here.
If it's true there is
dissension in their ranks,
maybe their sailors
have mutinied.
Maybe.
(DRUMMING CONTINUES)
(BABY CRYING)
I don't know why
she wants me here.
She's always
saying how stupid I am.
She hates me.
Maybe she hates you
less than she hates
everyone else.
I doubt it.
Maybe she's
jealous of you.
Why would she be jealous?
Sansa.
I was wondering where
our little dove had flown.
You look pale, child.
Is your red flower
still blooming?
Yes.
Fitting, isn't it?
The men will bleed out there
and you will bleed in here.
Pour Lady Sansa some wine.
I'm not thirsty, Your Grace.
So? I didn't
offer you water.
What's he doing here?
Ser Ilyn?
He's here to defend us.
When the axes
smash down those doors,
you may be glad to have him.
But we have guards
to defend us.
Guards we have paid.
Should the city fall,
they'll be the first
ones out of the doors.
(DOOR OPENING)
The lads caught
a groom and two maids
trying to sneak away
with a stolen horse
and some gold cups.
The battle's first traitors.
Have Ser Ilyn see to them.
Put their heads on spikes
outside the stables
as a warning.
The only way to keep
the small folk loyal
is to make certain
they fear you more
than they do the enemy.
Remember that if you ever
hope to become a queen.
(DOOR CLOSING)
You said he was
here to protect us.
He is.
Traitors are
a danger to us all.
More wine.
(DISTANT DRUMS BEATING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
There they are.
Archers to their marks.
Archers,
to your marks!
Archers!
Nock your arrows!
MAN: Nock arrows!
Hold fast.
MAN 1: Hold fast!
What are you doing?
We need to attack them.
Hold fast.
MAN 2: Boulders ready!
MAN 1: Hold fast!
There's only one ship.
Where are the rest of them?
Archers, stand to!
Man the below!
Nock.
MAN 3: Nock and set!
Draw!
Hold.
MAN 3: Hold.
There's no one on board.
MAN 4: More rocks coming up!
MAN 3: Hold.
Wildfire.
Steer clear! Steer clear!
Matthos! Get down!
(MEN SCREAMING)
(MEN WAILING)
(GROANS)
Prepare to land.
Your Grace.
STANNIS: The dwarf has
played his little trick.
The wildfire.
He can only play it once.
We're too far
from the gates.
The fire,
their archers...
Hundreds will die.
Thousands.
Come with me and
take this city!
(CHEERING)
Sansa, come here,
little dove.
My queen.
What are you doing?
Praying.
You're perfect, aren't you?
What are you praying for?
For the gods to
have mercy on us all.
Oh.
On all of us?
Yes, Your Grace.
Even me?
Of course, Your Grace.
Even Joffrey?
Joffrey is my...
Oh, shut up, you little fool.
Praying to the gods to
have mercy on us all.
The gods have no mercy.
That's why they're gods.
My father told me that
when he caught me praying.
My mother had
just died, you see.
I didn't really understand
the concept of death,
the finality of it.
I thought that
if I prayed very, very hard,
the gods would
return my mother to me.
I was four.
Your father doesn't
believe in the gods?
He believes in them,
he just doesn't
like them very much.
One for her.
Here.
Sit.
Drink.
Not like that. Drink, girl.
I should have been
born a man.
I'd rather face
a thousand swords
than be shut up inside
with this flock
of frightened hens.
They are your guests
under your protection.
You asked them here.
It was expected of me,
as it will be of you
if you ever
become Joffrey's queen.
If my wretched brother
should somehow prevail,
these hens will
return to their cocks
and crow of how
my courage inspired them,
lifted their spirits.
And if the city
should fall?
You'd like that,
wouldn't you?
The Red Keep
should hold for a time,
long enough for me
to go to the walls
and yield to Lord Stannis
in person.
If it were anyone else
outside those gates,
I might have hoped
for a private audience,
but this is Stannis Baratheon.
I'd have a better chance
of seducing his horse.
Have I shocked you,
little dove?
Tears aren't
a woman's only weapon.
The best one's
between your legs.
Learn how to use it. Drink.
Do you have any
notion of what happens
when a city is sacked?
No, you wouldn't,
would you?
If the city falls,
these fine women
should be in for
a bit of a rape.
Half of them
will have bastards
in their bellies
come the morning.
You'll be glad of
your red flower then.
When a man's blood is up,
anything with tits
looks good.
A precious thing like you
will look very, very good.
A slice of cake
just waiting to be eaten.
More pressure!
(MEN GRUNTING)
MAN 4: Pull! Pull!
MAN 5: That's it, men!
Pull! Pull!
He's a serious man,
Stannis Baratheon.
They're coming.
They're coming ashore.
Rain fire on them.
Archers!
There are too many.
Hound, form a welcome party
for any Baratheon troop
that manages to
touch solid ground.
Pod, run to the King's Gate.
Bring any men
guarding it here, now.
Yes, my lord.
Let's go. Stannis is
sending us fresh meat.
You, too.
Any of these
flaming fucking arrows
come near me,
I'll strangle you
with your own guts.
(MEN GRUNTING)
Pull, pull! Go!
Nock!
Draw!
(MEN GRUNTING)
MAN 6: Kill the Lannisters!
Loose!
Draw!
To the Mud Gate, go now!
First and second squads,
to the gate!
To the Mud Gate!
HOUND: Any man dies
with a clean sword,
I'll rape
his fucking corpse.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
CERSEI: When we were young,
Jaime and I,
we looked so much alike
even our father
couldn't tell us apart.
I could never understand why
they treated us differently.
Jaime was taught to
fight with sword
and lance and mace,
and I was
taught to smile
and sing
and please.
He was heir
to Casterly Rock,
and I was sold to some
stranger like a horse
to be ridden
whenever he desired.
You were Robert's queen.
And you will be
Joffrey's. Enjoy.
I don't think
I know this one.
Pretty.
That's the worst curtsy
I've ever seen.
Here, it's not difficult.
I mastered it
when I was four.
Straighten your back
and bend.
Better. You learn fast.
How long have you been
in Lady Sansa's service?
A few weeks, Your Grace.
When did you leave Lorath?
I had a Lorathi
handmaiden once.
But she was
a nobleman's daughter.
You're not.
When did you come
to Westeros?
Ten years ago, Your Grace.
From Lorathi commoner
to the Red Keep
in 10 years,
all without
learning how to curtsy.
I imagine that's
a very interesting story.
What's your name?
Shae, Your Grace.
Tell us a story, Shae.
When I was 13, I...
(DOOR OPENS)
Your Grace!
What news?
The Imp has set
the river afire.
Hundreds of ships
are burning, maybe more.
Stannis' fleet
destroyed, but...
But...
But his troops
have landed
outside the city walls.
Where is Joffrey?
On the battlements
with Lord Tyrion.
Bring him back
inside at once.
Your Grace...
What?
The king's presence
is good for morale.
Bring him back to
his chambers now.
Not here?
With the women and children?
Do you want him to
be mocked as a coward
for the rest of his life?
No, but I...
Now!
When I told you about
Ser Ilyn earlier, I lied.
Do you want to
hear the truth?
You want to know
why he's really here?
He's here for us.
Stannis may take the city,
he may take the throne,
but he will not
take us alive.
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
MAN 7: Help me!
(GROANING)
MAN 8: Fall back!
MAN 9: Fall back!
Get the ladders up!
(GRUNTS)
Faster, you bastards!
Faster!
Come on, kill the scum!
Someone bring me a drink.
Fuck the water.
Bring me wine.
Can I get you
some iced milk
and a nice bowl of
raspberries, too?
Eat shit, dwarf.
You're on the wrong
side of the wall.
I lost half my men.
The Blackwater's on fire.
Dog, I command you to
go back out there and fight.
You're Kingsguard, Clegane.
You must beat them back
or they're going to
take this city.
Your king's city.
Fuck the Kingsguard.
Fuck the city.
Fuck the king.
(MEN SHOUTING)
MAN 10: Loose!
MAN 11:
Put your backs into it!
All right, get up!
MAN 10: Loose!
Clear!
Forward!
(MEN SHOUTING)
MAN 10: Loose!
Forward ladders!
(MEN SHOUTING)
MAN 12: Heave!
(MEN GRUNTING)
Heave!
Your Grace,
the queen has sent me
to bring you back
to the Red Keep.
If you won't
defend your own city,
why should they?
What would you have me do?
Lead.
Get down there
and lead your people
against the invaders
who want to kill them.
What did my mother
say exactly?
Did she have
urgent business with me?
She did not say,
Your Grace.
MAN 10: All men to
the battlements!
Ser Boros,
Ser Mandon,
stay with my uncle
and represent the king
on the field of battle.
MAN 10: Archers,
hold your line
or I'll kill you myself.
Stand fast!
No!
Get up, you fool.
MAN 13: We need more arrows!
Where is the king?
Why isn't he with us?
MAN 14: Who are
we fighting for?
Who leads us?
I'll lead the attack.
I'll lead the attack!
Yes.
What are you talking about?
Pod, my helmet.
Ser Mandon, you will
bear the king's banner.
Men, form up.
Men...
Men!
They say
I'm half a man.
(BANGING ON DOOR)
But what does that
make the lot of you?
The only way out is
through the gates.
And they're
at the gates.
There's another way out.
I'm going to show you.
We'll come out behind them
and fuck them in their arses.
(POUNDING CONTINUES)
MAN 12: Heave!
Heave!
Don't fight for your king
and don't fight
for his kingdoms.
Don't fight for honor.
Don't fight for glory.
Don't fight for riches,
because you won't get any.
This is your city
Stannis means to sack.
That's your gate
he's ramming.
If he gets in, it will
be your houses he burns,
your gold he steals,
your women he will rape.
MAN 12: Heave! Heave!
Heave!
Those are brave men
knocking at our door.
Let's go kill them.
(CHEERING)
LANCEL: The battle
is lost, Your Grace.
Stannis' troops
are at the gates.
When the gold cloaks
saw the king leaving,
they lost all heart.
Where is my son?
I want to escort him
back to the battle.
Why do I care
what you want?
Bring me...
Now listen to me...
(GROANS)
Don't be afraid.
The queen has
raised the drawbridge.
This is the safest place
we can be.
Joffrey's not hurt.
He's fighting bravely.
His knights have
rallied behind him.
They will save the city.
Shall we sing a hymn?
♪ Gentle mother,
font of mercy
♪ Save our sons
from war, we pray ♪
(GASPS)
You must go.
Run to your chamber
and bar your door.
Stannis won't hurt you.
This one will.
Come with me.
I need to say
goodbye to someone.
The queen said
they'd rape everyone.
No one is raping me.
Go. Run.
(SINGING CONTINUES)
(DOOR CLOSING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DISTANT SCREAMS)
The lady is
starting to panic.
(GASPS)
What are you doing here?
Not here for long.
I'm going.
Where?
Someplace
that isn't burning.
North, might be.
Could be.
What about the king?
He can die just
fine on his own.
I can take you with me.
Take you
to Winterfell.
I'll keep you safe.
Do you want to go home?
I'll be safe here.
Stannis won't hurt me.
Look at me.
Stannis is a killer.
The Lannisters are killers.
Your father was a killer.
Your brother is a killer.
Your sons will be
killers someday.
The world is
built by killers.
So you'd better get
used to looking at them.
You won't hurt me.
No, little bird,
I won't hurt you.
MAN 12: Heave!
(MEN GRUNTING)
Come on, you bastards!
Get up those ladders!
(GROANS)
Attack!
Roll it over!
(MEN CHEERING)
(CHANTING) Halfman!
Halfman! Halfman!
Oh, fuck me.
(MEN SHOUTING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Shh!
Be calm, my sweet.
They're still fighting.
No one's going to hurt you.
I'll tell you a story.
You know the one about
the mother lion
and her little cub?
They lived in the woods.
The Kingswood?
Yes, my love.
In the Kingswood,
there lived
a mother and her cub.
She loved him very much.
But there were other things
that lived in the woods.
Evil things.
Like what?
Like stags.
Stags aren't evil.
They only eat grass.
And wolves.
My lord.
CERSEI: He could hear them
howling in the night.
The little cub
was frightened.
His mother said,
"You are a lion, my son.
You mustn't be afraid.
"For one day, all
the beasts will bow to you.
"You will be king.
"All the stags will bow.
All the wolves will bow.
"The bears in the north
and the foxes of the south,
"all the birds in the sky
and the beasts in the sea,
"they will all come
to you, little lion,
"to rest a crown
upon your head."
And the cub said,
"Will I be strong and
fierce like my father?"
"Yes," said his mother.
"You will be strong
and fierce just
like your father."
I will keep you safe,
my love.
I promise you.
(DOOR OPENS)
Back to the boats!
Stand and fight!
Stand and fight,
damn you!
No!
Father.
The battle is over.
We have won.
MAN: ♪ "And who are you,"
the proud lord said
♪ "That I must bow so low?"
♪ "Only a cat of
a different coat
♪ "That's all the truth I know
♪ "In a coat of gold
or a coat of red
♪ "A lion still has claws
♪ "And mine are
long and sharp, my lord
♪ "As long and sharp as yours"
♪ And so he spoke,
and so he spoke
♪ That Lord of Castamere
♪ But now the rains
weep o'er his hall
♪ With no one there to hear
♪ Yes, now the rains
weep o'er his hall
♪ And not a soul to hear ♪