(BIRDS CAWING)
(LABORED BREATHING)
MAN: How many of those
fingers do you think
we could shove up his ass?
LOCKE: Depends if
he's had any practice.
That the sort of thing
you and your sister
go in for?
She loosened you up for us?
(MEN LAUGHING)
He's going to fall.
He's going to fall
off his horse. Help him.
(GROANS)
JAIME: Water.
Water. Please, water.
Water. Water,
please. Please. Please.
(MEN LAUGHING)
If I die,
you won't be getting...
Oh, enough.
Here.
Can't say that
I've ever seen a man
drink horse piss that fast.
(MEN LAUGHING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(MEN CONTINUE LAUGHING)
Stop!
MAN: Far enough.
(GRUNTS)
Do that again and
I'll take your other hand.
MAN 2: Come on, you.
(PANTING)
Oh, Lord Tyrion.
Come in, come in.
I hope we might
speak in confidence.
Oh. Always in confidence.
About the events
of the Blackwater.
Perhaps this is
the wrong time?
Oh, no,
it's a wonderful time.
I thought one of
your little birds might
have knowledge of
my sister's intentions to...
End your life?
I didn't inherit
Littlefinger's spies
along with his position,
I'm afraid.
Which is why
I'm coming to you.
I need proof.
Proof? (SNORTS)
Will there be a trial?
I need to know.
I have no proof,
only whispers.
(GRUNTS)
Before all this nastiness,
I was going to tell you
the story of how I was cut.
Do you want to hear it still?
I don't know. Do I?
As a boy, I traveled
with a troupe of actors
through the Free Cities.
One day in Myr,
a certain man made
my master an offer
too tempting to refuse.
I feared the man
meant to use me
as I'd heard some men
used small boys.
But what he wanted
was far worse.
He gave me a potion
that made me
powerless to move or speak,
yet did nothing
to dull my senses.
With a hooked blade
he sliced me,
root and stem,
chanting all the while.
He burned my parts
in a brazier.
The flames turned blue,
and I heard
a voice answer his call.
I still dream of that night.
Not of the sorcerer,
not of his blade.
I dream of
the voice from the flames.
Was it a god?
A demon? A conjuror's trick?
I don't know.
But the sorcerer called
and a voice answered.
And ever since that day,
I have hated magic and
all those who practice it.
But you can see why
I was eager to aid in your
fight against Stannis
and his red priestess.
A symbolic revenge of sorts.
Yes.
(CLEARS THROAT)
I feel the need for
actual revenge against
the actual person who
tried to have me killed,
which will require
a degree of influence,
which...
You do not possess
at the moment.
But influence is
largely a matter of
patience, I have found.
Once I had served
the sorcerer's purpose,
he threw me out of
his house to die.
I resolved to
live to spite him.
I begged.
I sold what parts of
my body remained to me.
I became an excellent thief,
and soon learned that
the contents of
a man's letters
are more valuable
than the contents
of his purse.
Step by step,
one distasteful
task after another,
I made my way from
the slums of Myr to
the Small Council chamber.
Influence grows like a weed.
I tended mine patiently
until its tendrils
reached from the Red Keep
all the way across to
the far side of the world,
where I managed
to wrap them around
something very special.
Ugh.
The sorcerer.
(WHIMPERING)
Hello, my old friend.
It's been a long time.
I have no doubt
the revenge you want
will be yours in time,
if you have
the stomach for it.
(MUFFLED SCREAMS)
When people talk
about the Night's Watch,
they never
mention the shoveling.
Or the shit.
GRENN: They tell you
about honor,
pardoning crimes,
and protecting the realm,
but shoveling
really is most of it.
And getting attacked
or killed or worse.
And that.
But when you're not
getting attacked or killed,
usually you're shoveling.
Ah, look. More shit.
I was starting to wonder
what to do with
the rest of me day.
We need to
get out of here.
When the Lord Commander
says we go, we go.
The Lord Commander
told us to go to
the Fist of the First Men.
How'd that
turn out for us?
He had no
way of knowing.
We do now.
We know what's out there.
Craster's been
out here surviving.
So he's your
new protector now?
Our good friend Craster?
We're like
the sons he never had.
RAST: Mormont isn't
gonna save you.
This lummox here
isn't gonna save you.
When the Walkers come
calling, Craster will serve
us up like so many pigs.
If we want to live,
we'll have to look
out for ourselves.
(SHUSHING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(BABY CRYING)
You woke him.
I'm sorry.
He's beautiful.
Shh!
(CRYING CONTINUES)
He's beautiful.
Does he have a name?
No.
Are you going to
give him one?
Why?
Here.
Gilly.
You said to hold it for you
until you came back.
You're back.
I wanted you to have it.
I don't want
your stupid thimble.
I want to save
my baby's life.
Can you do that?
Can you?
I don't have time for you.
I don't have time
for anyone but him
because he doesn't
have much time.
(CRYING CONTINUES)
(RAVEN CAWING)
You have to go after him.
How?
You know how.
(GRUNTS)
(RAVEN CAWS)
Brandon.
Mother.
How many times
have I told you?
No climbing.
Mother, I need to find it.
It's here. It's calling me.
I want you to promise me.
No more climbing. Promise me.
Promise me! Promise me!
Mother! Mother!
Promise me, Bran!
(SCREAMS)
Promise me!
(PANTING)
Is he very large?
No larger than usual,
apparently.
And yet,
they said that he was...
Extraordinary.
The most extraordinary
man they've ever had.
And they've had a lot of men.
We're talking
about the same Podrick?
The quiet boy in
Lord Tyrion's service?
Seems a bit simple?
What did he do to them?
I don't know, my lord.
The girls are
usually quite descriptive.
So what did they say?
They said it was
hard to describe.
Huh.
Prodigies appear in
the oddest of places.
And what did
Littlefinger say
about this loss of income?
He was too
preoccupied to notice.
He's leaving for
the Eyrie soon.
I'm helping him
prepare for his journey.
Ah, yes, to pursue
his enduring love of the
Lady Arryn and
the title that
comes with her.
Sad, really.
Is that all it takes
to make our friend
lose interest in
poor Sansa Stark?
He hasn't spoken to her
since the last time,
as far as I know.
Hmm.
But I don't think
he's lost interest.
What makes you say so?
His shipboard inventory.
(GASPS)
You can read.
Rare for a woman
in your profession.
Former profession.
Of course.
I'm missing something obvious
you're about to point out?
Two featherbeds.
He's bringing two
featherbeds for the cabin.
Who is important enough
to Littlefinger
to merit a featherbed,
besides Littlefinger?
Could he be
bringing one of his girls?
He's not interested
in them, my lord.
How do you know?
Because I'm one of his girls.
Prodigies in
odd places indeed.
Rhaenyra Targaryen
was murdered
by her brother,
or rather, his dragon.
It ate her
while her son watched.
(GIGGLES)
What's left of her is
buried in the crypts
right down there.
CERSEI: The ceremony
is traditionally held
in the main sanctum,
which seats
700 comfortably.
OLENNA: There appears
to be a good deal
of room elsewhere
on the premises
for everyone else.
There aren't
more than 700 people
of any importance.
No, the rest are there
to look adoringly
upon the 700
to remind them how
superior they must be
to have the best seats.
Over there, in that urn,
the ashes of
Aerion Targaryen.
Aerion Brightflame,
they called him.
He thought drinking wildfire
would turn him into a dragon.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
JOFFREY: He was wrong.
And, of course,
there's the Mad King,
killed by my uncle.
Would you like to
see where the last
Targaryens are buried?
Are you sure Lady Margaery
doesn't find all this
a bit macabre?
No, it's quite all right,
Your Grace.
I'd love to see
their tombs, really.
It's like taking
a walk through history.
JOFFREY: The tomb's
just up here.
MARGAERY:
This is so exciting.
OLENNA: You were
married here, Your Grace?
CERSEI: Yes.
Must seem like
only yesterday.
Hmm. Seems like
a lifetime ago.
Your husband was
buried here as well?
No, he wanted his remains
returned to Storm's End.
Such a tragedy.
A fairly predictable tragedy.
Hunting and
drinking don't mix.
I should say not.
My son's a hunter.
It helps him forget
he's never been within
a mile of a real battle.
I seem to recall he laid
siege to Storm's End for
the better part of a year.
All he laid siege to
was the banquet table
in the command tent.
(CHUCKLES)
I told him to stay out
of Robert's Rebellion.
He had no business
fighting an actual warrior.
We mothers do what
we can to keep our sons
from the grave.
But they do seem
to yearn for it.
We shower them
with good sense,
and it slides right off,
like rain off a wing.
And yet the world
belongs to them.
(SCOFFS)
A ridiculous arrangement,
to my mind.
(MARGAERY GIGGLES)
The Gods have seen
fit to make it so.
My father didn't
want them here.
He was going to have
their bodies burned and
thrown in the Blackwater,
but the High Septon
convinced him otherwise.
I'm glad he did.
I'm sorry, Your Grace.
I know they did
terrible things at the end,
but their
ancestors built this.
Sometimes severity
is the price we
pay for greatness.
(CHUCKLES)
I couldn't agree more.
(CROWD CLAMORING)
Shall we go
and see them?
If you give them your love,
they will return it
a thousand fold.
I've spoken with them.
I know how they
feel about you.
You led the defense
of King's Landing.
They adore you.
Open the doors.
(DOORS OPENING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
Joffrey.
Wait.
MAN: Lady Margaery!
WOMAN: Lady Margaery!
Bless you, Lady Margaery!
WOMAN 2: Lady Margaery!
WOMAN 3: Lady Margaery!
WOMAN 4: Margaery!
WOMAN 5: Long live
Lady Margaery!
MAN 2: King Joffrey!
WOMAN 6: King Joffrey!
(CROWD CONTINUES CHEERING)
WOMAN 7: King Joffrey!
WOMAN 8: King Joffrey!
MAN 3: King Joffrey!
MAN 4: Gods bless
King Joffrey!
THEON: How far is it
to Deepwood Motte?
BOY: Not far, my lord.
Your sister is
waiting for you there.
She sent you to save me?
Yes.
I served them,
the men who
were torturing you.
I did what they
told and waited.
Why would you risk
your life for me?
I grew up on Saltcliffe,
my lord.
I was only a boy
when they took you away.
My father brought us
up to the bluffs
so we could watch
you carried off.
I remember the look
on my father's face
when he told us,
"That's Balon Greyjoy's
last living son."
And those are the words
I heard over again
when I saw what
they were doing to you.
Those men,
they said my father knew
what they were doing to me.
Did he?
I don't know, my lord.
They...
They never told me much.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
My sister's men
are loyal to her.
We don't need to
hide from them.
Not all those are
your sister's men.
Some of them are
loyal to your father.
(DOOR CLOSES)
THEON: Hmm.
BOY: What is it?
I was just thinking
how jealous I was
when my father told Yara
to take this place.
What did he tell
you to do?
(CHUCKLES) Raid
fishing villages.
He didn't trust me.
Thought I was a Stark.
(LAUGHS) I could
never be a Stark.
Robb Stark always
reminded me of that.
He lorded it over you?
Didn't have to.
All he had to do was be.
Be who he was born to be.
His life fit him
better than his clothes.
How could someone like that
ever be a brother to me?
He's the King in the North.
And me...
My father gave me
a choice and I made it.
I could never be a Stark.
But ironborn, that's
what I was born to be.
I paid the iron
price for Winterfell.
I murdered those boys.
The Stark boys?
Never found them.
Just some poor orphans
living with a farmer.
I let Dagmer slit
their throats and
I let him burn the bodies,
so I could keep Winterfell
and make my father proud.
Maybe it's not too late.
It is.
(SNIFFLES)
My real father lost
his head at King's Landing.
I made a choice,
and I chose wrong.
And now I've
burned everything down.
Not everything, my lord.
She's up here.
Yara.
Shh!
Wait.
I brought him back.
He... He killed the others.
What? No, I didn't.
You can't!
(GROANS)
No! Please, stop!
(THEON YELPING)
No!
(SCREAMS)
Put him back where he belongs.
(SCREAMING)
Eat.
What are you doing?
I'm dying.
You can't die.
You need to live
to take revenge.
I don't care about revenge.
You coward.
A little misfortune
and you're giving up.
Misfor...
Misfortune?
You lost your hand.
My sword hand.
I was that hand.
(SCOFFS)
You have a taste,
one taste of the real world
where people have
important things
taken from them,
and you whine
and cry and quit.
You sound
like a bloody woman.
I know what you did for me.
You told them Tarth
was full of sapphires.
It's called the Sapphire Isle
because of
the blue of its water.
You knew that.
Why did you help me?
(SIGHS)
You wanted to speak to me?
Yes, about Jaime.
What about him?
I wanted to make
sure we're doing
everything we can
to get him back.
When Catelyn Stark
took Tyrion prisoner,
what did I do in response?
You started a war.
And if I would start
a war for that
lecherous little stump,
what do you think I am doing
for my oldest son and heir?
Whatever you can.
Whatever I can.
You're still here.
Yes.
Why?
Did it ever occur to you that
I might be
the one who deserves
your confidence
and your trust,
not your sons?
Not Jaime or Tyrion, but me.
Years and years of lectures
on family and legacy...
(CHUCKLES)
The same lecture, really,
just with tiny,
tedious variations.
Did it ever occur to you
that your daughter
might be the only one
listening to them,
living by them?
That she might have the most
to contribute to your legacy
that you love so much more
than your actual children?
(BLOWS)
All right. Contribute.
The Tyrells are a problem.
The Tyrells helped us
defeat Stannis Baratheon.
The Tyrells saved your life,
your children's lives.
Margaery has
her claws in Joffrey.
She knows how to
manipulate him.
Good. I wish you knew
how to manipulate him.
I don't distrust you
because you're a woman.
I distrust you because
you're not as smart
as you think you are.
You've allowed that boy
to ride roughshod
over you and
everyone else in this city.
Perhaps you should try
stopping him from
doing what he likes.
I will.
GIRL: Do you like it, Nana?
Another golden rose.
How original.
I eat from plates
stamped with roses.
I sleep in sheets
embroidered with roses.
I have a golden rose
painted on my chamber pot,
as if that makes
it smell any better.
Roses are boring, dear.
"Growing strong."
Ha! The dullest
words of any house.
"Winter is coming!"
Now that's memorable.
"We do not sow."
Strong. Strong.
Those are houses
you watch out for.
Direwolves and krakens,
fierce beasts.
But a golden rose
growing strong,
(SCOFFS) that
strikes fear in the heart.
Look, little loves.
A spider in the garden.
Run along now.
Grow strong.
My lady.
I wanted to personally
welcome you to King's Landing.
The city has
been made brighter
by your presence.
The city is made
brighter by my presence?
Is that your usual line,
Lord Varys?
Are you here to seduce me?
A little obvious, perhaps.
Oh, no, please.
Seduce away.
It's been so long.
Though I rather think
it's all for naught.
What happens when
the nonexistent bumps
against the decrepit?
A question for
the philosophers.
But you've come mincing
all this way for something.
So?
Might I sit?
No.
Come, I've heard
you're such a clever man.
I'm curious why
you've sought me out.
You've taken
an interest in Sansa Stark.
Have I?
Because I spoke to her
once in this garden
and one of your little spies
came running to tell you?
Why shouldn't I?
She's an interesting girl.
Is she?
No, not particularly.
But she's had
an interesting childhood.
She has, sadly.
Well, forgive me for
wasting your time, then.
I thought we shared
certain hopes
for her well-being.
(CHUCKLING) Come, come.
You surrender rather easily.
Walk with me.
I know the walls have ears,
but apparently
the shrubbery does, too.
I choose my allies
carefully, and my enemies
more carefully still.
Which is Sansa Stark?
Neither.
A babe in the woods.
I admired her father.
Yes.
Ned Stark had many admirers,
and how many stepped forward
when the executioner
came for his head?
I could not help Lord Stark.
Perhaps I can
help his daughter.
How?
You're not the only one
who has taken
an interest in her.
That's hardly surprising.
She's a beautiful girl
with a famous name.
Indeed.
She'd make a lovely match
for the right suitor.
It almost feels
as if you're about to
arrive at the point.
Littlefinger is not
long for the capital.
A confidant of mine
has told me that
when he goes,
Sansa Stark goes with him.
And why have you come
to me with this matter?
Littlefinger was born
with no lands,
no wealth, no armies.
He has acquired the
first two. How long
before he has the army?
Perhaps you'll laugh,
but I know him
better than most,
and this is the truth.
Littlefinger is one of
the most dangerous
men in Westeros.
If Robb Stark falls,
Sansa Stark is
the key to the North.
And if he marries her,
he'll have
the key in his pocket.
Which seems such a shame.
Why should a man with
such a low reputation
steal away such
a lovely bride?
You must despise him.
You're working so hard
to undermine him.
Actually, I rather enjoy him.
But he would see
this country burn
if he could be
king of the ashes.
You are a clever man,
Lord Varys.
You are too kind.
I believe I have
a possible solution.
One doesn't need to
be clever for that.
It's obvious, isn't it?
(CLEARS THROAT)
I didn't mean
to disturb you.
You haven't.
We'd like some privacy,
please.
If you wouldn't mind
waiting back inside the keep.
Or if you'd be kind enough
to give me your names,
I'll ask the King to
speak with you himself.
What did you pray for?
I can't tell you.
Why not?
I'll tell you
what I prayed for
in the Sept this morning.
Let's see,
for my family's
health and happiness,
for an end to the war,
for a short winter.
Boring and traditional,
I'm afraid. And you?
I'm sorry, I just can't.
MARGAERY: My cousin Alanna
was the most beautiful
girl I'd ever seen.
When I was 12,
I was all elbows and knees,
and Alanna
looked like a goddess
sent to torture me.
"Pig Face," she called me.
(LAUGHS) "Pig Face"?
That's ridiculous.
It had something
to do with my nose.
Whenever she passed me
in the halls, she'd oink.
(OINKS)
(LAUGHS)
So I prayed that
she'd catch
a horrible skin disease.
A week after that,
she came down
with porridge plague.
Porridge plague?
Oh, you don't have it
in the North?
Your skin starts to
look like boiled oats,
and eventually,
your face slides off
and you die in agony.
But that's awful.
(LAUGHS)
You're...
I believed you!
Porridge plague.
I'm an idiot.
Don't say that.
No, you're not.
So what happened
to Alanna?
Oh, she grew up to be
the most beautiful woman
and married a handsome
lord and they have
darling children
and live in
a castle by the sea.
It's all terribly
frustrating.
SANSA: I'm sure
she's jealous of you now.
You'll be married
here in the capital,
and she'll have
to come watch and
pretend to be happy
that you're queen.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
I want us to be friends,
good friends.
That would make me
very happy.
You must see Highgarden.
You'd love it there.
I know you would.
We have a great
masquerade the night
of the harvest moon.
You should see the
costumes. People work
on them for months.
Uh, I don't think
the Queen would let me
leave King's Landing.
The Queen Regent, you mean.
Once I marry Joffrey,
I'll be queen.
And if you were
to marry Loras,
your place would
be at Highgarden,
wouldn't it?
We would be sisters,
you and I.
Would you like that?
His name was Bannen.
He was a good man,
a good ranger.
He came to us from...
Where did he come from?
Down White Harbor way.
He came to us
from White Harbor.
Never failed in his duty.
He kept his vows
the best he could.
He rode far, fought fiercely.
We shall never
see his like again.
ALL: And now
his watch has ended.
And now his watch has ended.
Didn't think a broke
foot could kill a man.
It wasn't his foot
that killed him.
That bastard Craster
starved him to death.
Craster's got his
daughters to feed.
RAST: You on his side?
We can't just show up
and steal all his food.
We're brothers of
the Night's Watch,
not thieves.
The day we leave,
Craster will tap
a barrel of our wine,
and sit down to
a feast of ham
and potatoes
and laugh at us
starving in the snow.
He's a bloody wildling.
Never knew Bannen
could smell so good.
You have one son,
don't you, Mormont?
I had my 99th.
You ever meet
a man with 99 sons?
And more daughters
than I can count.
I'm glad for you.
Are you now?
Me, I'll be glad when
you and yours have gone.
As soon as our wounded
are strong enough.
Ah!
They're as strong
as they're gonna get.
Them that's dying,
why don't you
cut their throats
and be done with it?
Or leave them if
you've not the stomach,
and I'll sort them myself.
(CHUCKLES)
KARL: Whose throat
you gonna cut, old man?
Wait outside.
It's cold outside and
there's nothing to eat.
My wives gave you bread.
There's sawdust
in the bread.
You don't like it,
you go out there
and eat the snow.
I'd rather eat what
you've got hidden away.
I told you to
wait outside.
He's sitting there
drinking our wine, eating
his fill while we die.
I gave you crows enough.
I've got to feed
my women!
You admit you've
got a hidden larder?
How else you make
it through winter?
Enough! Out!
I am a godly man.
You're a stingy bastard!
Bastard?
(GRUNTS) Out with you,
you little thief.
And you! And you!
Go sleep in
the cold on empty bellies.
I'll chop the hands off
the next man
who calls me bastard.
You are a bastard.
A daughter-fucking,
wildling bastard.
(YELLS)
(GURGLING)
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
MORMONT: The Gods
will curse us for this.
By all the laws...
There are no laws
beyond the Wall.
Show us where
he hides the food, or
you'll get the same as him.
Unhand her.
I shall have
your head for this.
(GRUNTS)
(YELLS)
(MEN YELLING)
(GROANS)
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
Quickly. Quickly.
GILLY: What's happening?
I'm not going out there.
No, we have to go. Now!
(BABY CRYING)
GILLY: Follow me.
I know the best way.
Come on.
Run fast, Piggy,
and sleep well!
I'll be cutting your throat
one of these nights.
ARYA: Can I take
this hood off yet?
THOROS: I do apologize,
little lady,
but it's better for you
if you don't see
where we're going.
(HORSE NEIGHING)
MAN: Halt!
What is it?
Blackstrap rum.
Ugh!
Not easy finding
molasses in wartime.
GENDRY: I'd have some.
Let's go home.
GENDRY: What is this place?
Somewhere neither wolves
nor lions come prowling.
You look like
a bunch of swineherds.
ANGUY: Some of us
were swineherds.
And some of us
tanners and masons.
That was before.
You're still swineherds
and tanners and masons.
You think
carrying a crooked spear
makes you a soldier?
MAN: No.
Fighting in a war
makes you a soldier.
Beric Dondarrion?
You've seen better days.
And I won't see them again.
Stark deserters.
Baratheon deserters.
You lot aren't
fighting in a war,
you're running from it.
Last I heard,
you were King Joffrey's
guard dog.
But here you are
1,000 miles from home.
Which of us is running?
Untie these ropes
and we'll find out.
What are you doing
leading a mob of peasants?
Ned Stark ordered me
to execute your brother
in King Robert's name.
Ned Stark is dead.
King Robert is dead.
My brother's alive.
(SPITS)
You're fighting for ghosts.
That's what we are,
ghosts waiting
for you in the dark.
You can't see us,
but we see you.
No matter whose cloak
you wear, Lannister,
Stark, Baratheon,
you prey on the weak,
the Brotherhood
Without Banners
will hunt you down.
You found god? Is that it?
Aye.
I've been reborn
in the light of
the one true god.
As have we all.
As would any man
who's seen
the things we've seen.
If you mean to murder me,
then get on with it.
You'll die soon enough, dog.
But it won't be murder,
only justice.
ANGUY: And a kinder
fate than you deserve.
Lions, you call yourselves.
At the Mummer's Ford,
girls of seven
years were raped,
and babes still on the breast
were cut in two while
their mothers watched.
I wasn't at
the Mummer's Ford.
Dump your dead children
at some other door.
House Clegane was
built upon dead children.
I saw them lay Prince Aegon
and Princess Rhaenys
before the Iron Throne.
Do you take me for
my brother? Is being
born Clegane a crime?
Murder is a crime.
I never touched
the Targaryen babes.
I never saw them,
never smelled them,
never heard them bawling.
You want to cut my throat,
get on with it!
But don't call me murderer
and pretend that you're not.
You murdered Mycah.
The butcher's boy.
My friend.
He was 12 years old.
He was unarmed.
And you rode him down.
You slung him
over your horse like
he was some deer.
Aye, he was a bleeder.
You don't deny
killing this boy?
HOUND: I was Joffrey's
sworn shield.
The boy attacked the prince.
That's a lie!
I hit Joffrey.
Mycah just ran away.
Then I should have
killed you. Not my place
to question princes.
You stand accused
of murder.
But no one here
knows the truth
of the charge, so it is
not for us to judge you.
Only the Lord of Light
may do that now.
I sentence you to
trial by combat.
So, who will it be?
Should we find out
if your fire god really
loves you, priest?
Or you, archer?
What are you worth
with a sword in your hand?
Or is the little girl
the bravest one here?
Aye.
She might be.
But it's me you'll fight.
(KRAZNYS SPEAKING IN VALYRIAN)
The master says
they are untested.
He says you would be wise
to blood them early.
There are many
small cities between
here and there,
cities ripe for sacking.
Should you take captives,
the masters will
buy the healthy ones
and for a good price.
And who knows?
In 10 years, some of
the boys you send them
may be Unsullied
in their turn.
Thus, all shall prosper.
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
(DRAGON HISSING)
(SCREECHING)
Is it done, then?
They belong to me?
(BOTH SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
MISSANDEI: It is done.
(KRAZNYS IN VALYRIAN)
You hold the whip.
(SCREECHING)
(IN VALYRIAN)
(GROANS)
Dracarys.
(SCREAMING)
(THUMPING RHYTHMICALLY)
(DRAGON SCREECHES)