(SPLASHES)
(CLEARS THROAT)
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(EXHALES)
(SCOFFS)
EDMURE: If I may, nephew,
I encountered a situation
with one of my lieutenants
at the Stone Mill which
may have some bearing...
Why don't you shut your mouth
about that damned mill?
And don't call him "nephew."
He is your king.
Robb knows
I meant him no...
You're lucky
I'm not your king.
I wouldn't let you
wave your blunders around
like a victory flag.
My blunder sent
Tywin's mad dog
back to Casterly Rock
with his tail
between his legs.
I think King Robb understands
we won't win this war
if he's the only one
winning any battles.
No, there's glory
enough to go around.
It's not about glory.
Your instructions were to
wait for him to come to you.
I seized an opportunity.
What value was the mill?
The Mountain was garrisoned
across the river from it.
ROBB: Is he there now?
Of course not.
We took the fight to him.
He could not withstand us.
I wanted to
draw the Mountain
into the west,
into our country,
where we could
surround him and kill him.
I wanted him to chase us,
which he would have done
because he is a mad dog
without a strategic
thought in his head.
I could have that head
on a spike by now.
Instead, I have a mill.
We took hostages.
Willem Lannister.
Martyn Lannister.
Willem and Martyn Lannister
are 14 years old.
Martyn is 15,
I believe.
Tywin Lannister
has my sisters.
Have I sued for peace?
No.
Do you think he'll
sue for peace because
we have his father's
brother's great-grandsons?
No.
How many men did you lose?
208.
But for every man we lost,
the Lannisters...
We need our men
more than Tywin needs his!
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
You would have.
Right here today
at this gathering,
if you had been patient.
We seem to be running
short of patience here.
You know who isn't?
Tywin Lannister.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(CHAINS RATTLING)
(CHAIR SQUEAKS)
(CHAIR DRAGGING LOUDLY)
(SIGHS)
Intimate. Lovely table.
Better chairs than
the old Small Council
chamber.
Conveniently close
to your own quarters.
I like it.
What news of Jaime?
20,000 unwashed Northerners
have known about
his escape for weeks.
You control more
spies and informants
than the rest of
the world combined.
Do you mean to tell me
that none of you has
any notion of where he is?
We are trying,
my lord.
Try harder.
What do we have, then?
Robb Stark and
most of his bannermen
are in Riverrun
for the funeral
of his grandfather
Lord Hoster Tully.
In Stark's absence,
Roose Bolton
holds Harrenhal,
which would seem
to make him
Lord of Harrenhal,
in practice,
not in name.
TYWIN: Let him have it.
The name suits our purposes
far more than that
useless pile of rubble.
The Lord of
Harrenhal will make
a worthy suitor
for the widow Arryn.
For which I am
extremely grateful
to you, my lord.
Lady Arryn and I
have known each other
since we were children.
She has always been
positively
predisposed toward me.
A successful
courtship would make
Lord Baelish
acting Lord of the Vale.
Titles do seem
to breed titles.
You'll leave for the Eyrie
as soon as possible
and bring Lysa Arryn
into the fold.
Then the young wolf
can add his own aunt
to the list of people who have
taken up arms against him.
Far be it from me
to hinder true love,
but Lord Baelish's
absence would present
certain problems.
The royal wedding
may end up being
the most expensive
event in living memory.
Summer has ended,
hard days lie ahead.
Not a good time
to leave the crown's
finances unattended.
TYWIN: Fully agreed.
Which is why I'm naming you
new Master of Coin.
(SCOFFS)
Master of Coin?
It would appear to
best suits your talents.
I'm quite good
at spending money,
but a lifetime of
outrageous wealth
hasn't taught me
much about managing it.
I have no doubt
you will prove
equal to this challenge.
Hear, hear.
MAN: ♪ He lifted her
high in the air
♪ He sniffed and roared
and smelled her there
♪ She kicked and wailed,
the maid so fair
♪ But he licked the honey
from her hair
ALL: ♪ From there to here,
from here to there
♪ All black and brown
and covered with hair
♪ He smelled that girl
on the summer air
♪ The bear, the bear,
and the maiden fair ♪
I hope you're pleased.
If I were armed,
they'd never have taken us.
BRIENNE: You were armed
when we were taken.
I was in chains,
if you recall.
Our little match would
have ended quite quick
if my hands weren't bound.
All my life I've been
hearing, "Jaime Lannister,
"what a brilliant swordsman."
You were slower
than I expected.
And more predictable.
I've been sitting
in a muddy pen,
wrapped in chains,
for the past year.
I'm a woman.
I was beating you.
You were not beating me.
Maybe you were as
good as people said...
Once.
Or maybe people just
love to over-praise
a famous name.
When we make camp tonight,
you'll be raped.
More than once.
None of these fellows
have ever been
with a noblewoman.
You'd be wise
not to resist.
Would I?
They'll knock
your teeth out.
You think I care?
No, I don't think you
care about your teeth.
If you fight them,
they will kill you.
Do you understand?
I'm the prisoner
of value, not you.
Let them have
what they want.
What does it matter?
Close your eyes.
Pretend they're Renly.
If you were a woman,
you wouldn't resist?
You'd let them do
what they wanted?
If I was a woman,
I'd make them kill me.
But I'm not, thank the Gods.
If I had a proper forge,
I'd make it good as new.
Doesn't have to look pretty.
It just has to keep
the arrows out of my heart.
Why are you
helping him?
He takes us prisoner,
now he's our friend?
THOROS: You're
not our prisoner.
What am I?
Our guest.
No one's put
any chains on you.
So I can walk away, then?
These woods aren't safe
for Ned Stark's daughter.
You're lucky we found you.
HOUND: You think
you're good with that bow,
you little twat?
ANGUY: Better than
anyone you've met.
HOUND: A coward's weapon.
I like to fight up close.
I like to see a man's face
when I put the steel in him.
Why? So you can kiss him?
You remember the last time
you were here?
Looks like every other
shit inn on the road.
ANGUY: Now, apologies,
but you're one ugly fucker
and I'd rather
not see you no more.
(GROANS)
Watch your head.
(BANGING)
Off we go.
MAN: Walk up!
(HORSE NEIGHING)
What are you doing?
We're about to leave.
I'm staying.
You're what?
I baked brown bread
for the innkeep, she said
she never had better.
Told Thoros she's
keeping me as payment
for all his free meals.
Anyway, it's not me
the Brotherhood wants.
My brother ain't no king.
I'm not a Stark
of Winterhell.
Winterfell.
You sure?
I'm sure.
Well, I made
you something.
What is it?
It's a wolf.
Yes, it is.
ARYA: That's the tail?
Yeah.
Well, be safe.
Yeah, you, too.
Don't get stabbed.
You don't burn your fingers.
Good-bye, Hot Pie.
Good-bye, Arry.
Up you go, little lady.
ARYA: Hey, Hot Pie.
It's really good.
CATELYN: A person
could almost be forgiven
for forgetting we're at war.
It often comforts me
to think that even
in war's darkest days,
in most places in
the world absolutely
nothing is happening.
I've missed you, Uncle.
Father missed you, too,
from the day you left.
Maybe he never said it
in so many words...
Maybe?
Your father was
a stubborn old ox.
I was surprised when
he died. Didn't think
death had the patience.
I'm glad you were
with him. I wish
to the Gods I had been.
Did you make peace
in the end?
After 30 years of fighting,
I don't think he
remembered what started it.
He asked me to stop
calling myself Blackfish.
He said it was an old joke
and it was never
funny to begin with.
I told him people
had been calling me
Blackfish for so long,
they don't
remember my real name.
Every time he would
leave for the capital
or fight in a campaign,
I'd see him off.
"Wait for me, little Cat,"
he'd say.
"Wait for me,
and I'll come back to you."
And I would sit at this
window every day when
the sun came up, waiting.
I wonder,
how many times
did Bran or Rickon
stare across
the moors of Winterfell,
waiting for me to return?
I will never see them
again. (SOBBING)
You mustn't think it.
We don't know the truth.
They could be in hiding.
Robb believes
they're alive.
And he must
go on believing.
He's got to remain strong
if he's to prevail.
And you must
remain strong for him.
(SIGHS)
You're Robb Stark's
wife.
Hold still.
Is it true what
they say about him?
I don't know.
What do they say about him?
That he can turn
into a wolf at night.
True.
And he eats
the flesh of his enemies.
True.
You're a Lannister,
aren't you?
Martyn Lannister.
You've nothing to fear.
My husband
doesn't eat children.
Unless it's a full moon.
It's not a full
moon tonight, is it?
See? Nothing to fear.
(WIND HOWLING)
Always the artists.
It's only horses.
No men.
You said
there was dead crows.
There was.
How many men were here?
About 300.
And you know what
those men are now?
We're all the same to them,
meat for their army.
Do you think
anyone got away?
MANCE: It's not impossible.
You don't go far
betting against Mormont.
But dead or alive,
he took a big
gamble coming north.
And he lost.
His best fighting men
are dead.
And whether
he's Lord Commander
of the Night's Watch
or a blue-eyed corpse,
he's a long way from home.
Tormund. Climb the Wall.
Take Orell and 20 good men.
And take this one.
He knows Castle
Black's defenses
better than any of us.
And if he's useful,
good. If not,
throw him off the Wall.
See if crows can fly.
We're finally going
to war, old friend?
Hide near Castle Black.
When I give the signal,
hit them in the night.
They've got a big old
wall to hide behind,
but it only guards one side.
(CHUCKLES)
We'll meet again.
Aye. If you do your job.
Ah.
How will we
see your signal?
MANCE: Send your eagle
above the Wall every night.
When it's time, I'm going
to light the biggest fire
the North has ever seen.
(MEN COUGHING)
(BABY CRYING)
Ghost?
What have we here?
Frozen crows?
We've come
a long way.
CRASTER: Smaller flock
than you went north with.
We can talk inside.
Oh, can we?
(INHALES)
(WOMAN 1 SCREAMING)
WOMAN 2: They need some water.
Tether it, and I'll be inside.
(WOMAN 1 GROANING)
CRASTER: Keep your
eyes where they belong.
They're not for you.
Bet you feed that pig
better than you feed us.
Aye, pig's got value to me.
You should all
be kissing my feet
for letting you in.
I'd have turned you all away
if I wasn't a godly man.
You are a godly man?
I am. I got no fear
of what's out there.
When the white cold comes,
your swords and cloaks
and bloody fires
won't help you.
The only ones left
will be those who are
right with the Gods.
The real Gods.
(WOMAN 1 CONTINUES GROANING)
Go tell her she can
bite down on a rag
or she can bite
down on my fist.
Women. (CHUCKLES)
That sow right
there gave birth
to a litter of eight.
Barely a grunt.
And she's almost as
fat as this one here.
Now why don't
you dine on him?
Carve off what
you need as you go.
Well, look at him.
He's a walking feast.
(CRASTER IMITATES
PIG SQUEALING)
(CRASTER LAUGHING)
(COUGHING)
(SIGHS)
WOMAN 2: Here we are.
Sharpen these
for me, would ya?
(WOMAN 1 SCREAMING)
I see the head.
Push. That's it.
You're nearly there.
(WHIMPERING)
(PANTING)
One more push should do it.
(SCREAMING IN PAIN)
(BABY CRYING)
(GASPS)
What is it?
(CRYING LOUDLY)
(WATER DRIPPING)
(DOOR OPENING)
(GASPS)
(DOOR CLOSING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WHISPERS) Keep quiet.
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
If you can't ride,
we don't stand a chance.
I can ride.
You're sure?
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
Ride east. Follow
the rising sun. Your
sister's waiting for you.
I'll make you
a Lord of the Iron
Islands for this.
We're not in
the Iron Islands.
Go.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
MAN: Come on back.
STANNIS: You refuse to
tell me where you're going?
MELISANDRE: I don't know yet.
The fires will show me.
STANNIS: How long
will you be gone?
MELISANDRE: (SIGHS)
I don't know.
You're abandoning me.
I will never abandon you.
You are the Son of Fire.
I am sworn to serve you.
Then serve me.
When I return,
you will understand.
My enemies think
they've destroyed me.
They're laughing at me,
the way Renly laughed at me.
I want Joffrey dead.
I want Robb Stark dead.
Make me another son.
I cannot.
(SNIFFS) Why?
You don't have the strength.
It would kill you.
I'm not easily killed.
Men have tried for years.
I want you.
Your fires burn low,
my king.
There is another way.
A better way.
You told me your magic
requires a king's blood.
Yes.
I'm the one true king.
You are.
There are others
with your blood
in their veins.
You will sit on
the Iron Throne,
but first there
must be sacrifices.
The Lord of Light
demands it.
The Walk of Punishment
is a warning, Your Grace.
To whom?
JORAH: To any slave
who contemplates doing
whatever
these slaves did.
Give me your water.
Khaleesi, this man
has been sentenced
to death.
Here, drink.
(INDISTINCT)
BARRISTAN: Leave
this place, Your Grace.
Leave tonight, I beg you.
And what is she
to do for soldiers?
BARRISTAN:
We can find sellswords
in Pentos and Myr.
Is it "we" already,
Ser Barristan?
If you want to
sit on the throne
your ancestors built,
you must win it.
That means blood on
your hands before
the thing is done.
The blood of my enemies,
not the blood of innocents.
JORAH: How many wars
have you fought in,
Ser Barristan?
Three.
Have you ever seen a war
where innocents didn't
die by the thousands?
I was in King's Landing
after the sack, Khaleesi.
You know what I saw?
Butchery.
Babies, children, old men.
More women raped
than you can count.
There's a beast in every man,
and it stirs when you
put a sword in his hand.
But the Unsullied are
not men. They do not rape.
They do not put
cities to the sword
unless they're ordered.
If you buy them,
the only men they'll kill
are those you want dead.
You disagree, Ser Barristan?
When your brother
led his army into
battle at the Trident,
men died for him
because they
believed in him,
because
they loved him,
not because they'd been
bought at an auction.
I fought beside
the last dragon
on that day.
I bled beside him.
Rhaegar fought valiantly,
Rhaegar fought nobly,
and Rhaegar died.
Did you know him well,
Ser Barristan?
I did, Your Grace.
Finest man I ever met.
I wish I had known him.
But he was not
the last dragon.
MISSANDEI: All?
Did this one's ears
mishear, Your Grace?
They did not.
I want to buy
them all.
(BOTH SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
There are 8,000 Unsullied
in Astapor. Is this
what you mean by all?
Yes. 8,000.
And the ones still
in training as well.
(TRANSLATING INTO VALYRIAN)
(GREIZHEN SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
Master Greizhen says
they cannot sell
half-trained boys.
If they fail on
the battlefield,
they will bring shame
upon all of Astapor.
I will have them
all or take none.
Many will fall in battle.
I'll need the boys
to pick up
the swords they drop.
(GROANS)
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN
CONTINUALLY)
Master Kraznys says
you cannot afford this.
Your ship will buy
you 100 Unsullied.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Because Master Kraznys
is generous.
MISSANDEI: The gold
you have left is worth 10.
But good Master Kraznys
will give you 20.
The Dothraki you
have with you...
The Dothraki you have
are not worth what
they cost to feed...
MISSANDEI: ...but Master
Kraznys will give you
three Unsullied
for all of them.
Master Kraznys asks
how you propose to pay...
MISSANDEI: ...for
the remaining
7,877 Unsullied?
I have dragons.
I'll give you one.
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
You will win
the throne with dragons,
not slaves, Your Grace.
Khaleesi, please.
Three dragons.
One.
Two.
(INDISTINCT)
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
MISSANDEI: They
want the biggest one.
Done.
(SIGHS)
I'll take you as well, now.
You'll be Master Kraznys'
gift to me.
A token of
a bargain well struck.
(IN VALYRIAN)
Khaleesi,
a dragon is
worth more
than any army.
Aegon Targaryen
proved that.
You're both here
to advise me.
I value your advice,
but if you ever
question me in front
of strangers again,
you'll be
advising someone else.
Is that understood?
Do you have a name?
This one's name is
Missandei, Your Grace.
Do you have a family?
A mother and a father
you'd return to if
you had the choice?
No, Your Grace.
No family living.
You belong to me now.
It is your duty to
tell me the truth.
Yes, Your Grace.
Lying is a great offense.
Many of those on
the Walk of Punishment
were taken there for less.
I offered water to
a slave dying on
the Walk of Punishment.
Do you know
what he said to me?
"Let me die."
There are no masters
in the grave, Your Grace.
Is it true what
Master Kraznys told me
about the Unsullied?
About their obedience?
All questions have
been taken from them.
They obey, that is all.
Once they are yours,
they are yours.
They will fall on their swords
if you command it.
And what about you?
You know that I'm
taking you to war.
You may go hungry.
You may fall sick.
You may be killed.
Valar Morghulis.
Yes, all men must die.
But we are not men.
TYRION: A surprising place
to keep the royal ledgers.
LITTLEFINGER:
I'm surprised
you're surprised.
This is the safest
place in the city.
Not for bastards.
That's all of them,
my lord.
TYRION: Thank you,
my dear. Pod.
Pod.
Take them outside.
I'll be there
in a moment.
Yes, my lord.
I hear you owe that boy
a significant debt.
Only my life.
Not all that significant,
I'm afraid.
You should have
him knighted.
If only the Master of Coin
had such power.
If only.
I owe you a significant debt.
Our redheaded friend.
You secured her release
when the Queen detained her.
Oh, that.
Of course.
A simple misunderstanding.
Apparently,
Her Grace believed
that you two had
some sort of
special relationship.
We don't.
I did fuck her once.
I know.
But we don't.
How'd the Queen
get that idea?
Why don't you ask her?
Any advice for me
on my new position?
Keep a low profile.
If I had a gold dragon
for every time
I heard that joke,
I'd be richer than you are.
Well, you are
richer than I am.
Good point.
They're only numbers.
Numbers on paper.
Once you understand that,
it's easy to
make them behave.
Trivial even.
You want a real challenge?
Try whores.
I've tried quite a few.
Well, lots of work to do.
Enjoy the Eyrie.
Come on, I'm here
later. Come on.
Tonight, then.
Looks like dull reading.
TYRION: You think all
reading is dull reading.
It's an opinion I share
with some of the finest
men I know.
The secret history
of the Seven Kingdoms
is in these pages.
BRONN: Unless Lord Twatbeard
made up a bunch of numbers
to hide what
he's really up to.
Unless he made
it all up, yes.
Podrick, do keep up.
Yes, my lord.
Podrick.
Yes, my lord?
After a long consultation
with my colleague Ser Bronn,
I finally found
a suitable reward
for the services
you've provided over and
above what might be
considered reasonable.
Tell me, Pod,
have you ever
been with a woman?
No, my lord.
Wonderful.
Genna specializes
in first-timers.
She's not bad with
second-timers, either.
Uh, my lord...
A fair enough repayment
for putting your spear
through my
would-be killer's face,
wouldn't you say?
Now, as it happens,
Marei
is quite
the spear-handler herself.
She's here to thank you
for staying by my side
as the battle
raged all around me.
MAREI: He's handsome.
You didn't tell me
he was handsome.
Kayla is famous
from here to Volantis
in certain circles.
One of four women in
the world who can perform
a proper Meereenese Knot.
My lord, I don't even...
TYRION: She's here to thank
you for being a thoroughly
respectful fellow,
who's never once failed
to address me as "my lord."
Be back in time
for my supper.
Pace yourself, lad.
TYRION: For years
I've heard that
Littlefinger is a magician.
Whenever
the crown needs money,
he rubs his hands together
and, poof,
mountains of gold.
Let me guess.
He's not a magician.
No.
He's stealing it?
Worse, he's borrowing it.
What's wrong with that?
We can't afford
to pay it back, that's
what's wrong with it.
The crown owes
millions to my father.
Seeing as it's
his grandson's ass
on the throne,
I imagine he'll
forgive that debt.
Forgive a debt, my father?
For a man of the world,
you're strangely naive.
I've never
borrowed money.
I'm not clear on the rules.
Well...
(TYRION CLEARS THROAT)
The basic principle is,
I lend you money,
and after an agreed
upon period of time,
you return it with interest.
What if I don't?
Well, you have to.
But what if I don't?
This is why
I don't lend you money.
Anyway, it's not my father
I'm worried about.
It's the Iron Bank
of Braavos.
We owe them
tens of millions.
If we fail to
repay these loans,
the bank will
fund our enemies.
One way or another,
they always get
their gold back.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Ah, the return of
the conquering hero.
Does he have
a little jaunt in his step?
The lad's
practically skipping.
You were gone a long time.
I trust you got
your money's worth.
Or should I say
my money's worth?
Oh, it was a gift, Podrick.
This is more than
I give you in a year.
He's a squire.
You don't pay him.
Oh, then it's much more
than I give you in a year.
They wouldn't
take it, my lord.
Maybe they're trying
to curry some favor
with the new Master of Coin.
Have you ever known a whore
to turn down gold?
They were happy enough
to take it when
I gave it to them.
What did you tell them?
I didn't tell
them anything.
What did you
do to them?
Lots of things.
And they seemed to
like these things?
Yes, my lord.
Of course they did.
They're paid to
seem to like it.
Only they weren't paid.
What are you saying?
These ladies
enjoyed him so much,
they gave him
the time for free?
Is that what
you're telling us?
Sit down, Podrick.
(CLEARS THROAT)
We're going
to need details.
Copious details.
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(GASPS)
(NEIGHS)
Come on! Come on!
Come on! Come on.
(GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
(HORSE NEIGHS)
(WHEEZING)
(GROANS)
You know how we
deal with runaways?
(GROANING)
Take off his pants.
No! No! No, no, no!
I'm gonna fuck
you into the dirt.
No, please!
No, no, no! No, don't!
No, please! No! No!
(ARROW WHISTLES)
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
You little bastard.
(GROANS)
(WHIMPERING)
Come, my lord.
You're a long way from home,
and winter is coming.
(MEN CHATTERING IN DISTANCE)
I'll take
the big bitch first.
When she's good
and wet, you lot
can finish her off.
My lord,
I am Brienne of Tarth.
Lady Catelyn Stark
commanded me
to deliver Ser Jaime
to King's Landing.
Catelyn Stark's
a treasonous cunt.
Orders were to take
the Kingslayer alive.
Nobody said shit about you.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
You're only
making it worse.
(ALL GRUNTING)
Take her over there,
where it's dark.
I'd like a little privacy.
(GROANS)
Come on!
(SCREAMING)
You know who
she is, don't you?
A big dumb bitch
from who cares where.
Never been with
a woman that big.
JAIME: She's Brienne of Tarth.
Her father is
Lord Selwyn Tarth.
Heard of Tarth?
MAN: I'm gonna
cut your throat!
They call it
the Sapphire Isle.
Do you know why?
Every sapphire in Westeros
was mined on Tarth.
Sapphires are gemstones.
The blue ones.
I know what they are.
Lord Selwyn would pay
his daughter's weight
in sapphires if
she's returned to him.
But only if she's alive,
her honor unbesmirched.
(BRIENNE CONTINUES SCREAMING)
Bring her back here.
MAN 1: Yes, my lord.
Get up.
MAN 2: Come on.
Come on, on your feet.
Unbesmirched.
Not defiled.
Fancy word for a fancy man.
I hated to read
as a child,
but my father forced me
to study every morning
before I could practice
with sword or horse.
Two hours every day
holed up in the
maester's chambers.
I learned a lot
of fancy words.
I bet you did.
(BRIENNE GRUNTS)
Your father,
he'd pay your weight
in gold to get you back?
You'll be a rich man
till the end of your days.
And your sons
will be rich men,
and their sons after them.
Lands, titles...
You'll have them all.
The North
can't win this war.
You're a smart man.
You understand that.
We have the numbers.
We have the gold.
Aye, you have both.
Fighting bravely
for a losing cause
is admirable.
Fighting for a winning cause
is far more rewarding.
Hard to argue with that.
Now that we're speaking
together man to man,
I wonder if you need
to keep me
chained to this tree?
I'm not asking to be freed
from my constraints,
but if I could
sleep lying down,
my back would
thank you for it.
I'm not as young and
resilient as I was once.
None of us are.
Unchain Ser Jaime
from the tree.
MAN: Come on, men.
Suppose you'll be
wanting something to eat.
I'm famished, actually.
I think we've got
a spare partridge
on the fire.
Well, I do like partridge.
(JAIME GROANS SOFTLY)
Bring the bird
over here and
the carving knife.
Will this work as
a table, my lord?
Oh, yes.
Yes, this will do...
(GROANS)
On the stump.
You think you're
the smartest man there is.
(GRUNTING)
That everyone alive
has to bow and scrape
and lick your boots.
My father...
And if you get
in any trouble,
all you've got to
do is say "my father"
and that's it,
all your troubles are gone.
Don't.
Have you got
something to say?
(GRUNTS)
Careful. You don't want
to say the wrong thing.
You're nothing
without your daddy,
and your daddy ain't here.
Never forget that.
Here, this should
help you remember.
(SCREAMING IN PAIN)
(THE BEAR AND
THE MAIDEN FAIR PLAYING)