Lord,
cast your light upon us.
ALL: Lord of Light, defend us.
Show us the truth.
Strike this man down
if he is guilty.
Give strength to his sword
if he is true.
Lord of Light,
give us wisdom,
for the night is dark
and full of terrors.
ALL: For the night is
dark and full of terrors.
(GASPS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Get back.
ALL: (CHANTING)
Guilty. Guilty. Guilty.
Guilty.
Kill him!
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
(CHANTING STOPS)
Lord, cast your
light upon this man,
your servant.
Bring him back from
death and darkness.
Restore his flame.
(GRUNTING)
For the night is dark
and full of terrors.
Lord, cast...
Arya, don't!
THOROS: Bring him back
from death and darkness...
(GRUNTS)
(YELPS)
No! Let go of me!
Let me go!
Looks like their god
likes me more
than your butcher's boy.
Burn in hell!
BERIC: He will.
But not today.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Orell says there are crows
patrolling on the Wall.
Tell me what you know.
There are four to a patrol,
two builders to check
for structural damage,
two rangers to
watch for enemies.
How often do
these patrols go out?
It varies.
If I knew where on the Wall
we were heading,
I could tell you.
You'd like to know that.
(SIGHS)
There are 19 castles
guarding the Wall.
How many are manned?
Three.
You sure of that?
Which three?
Castle Black.
Aye, Castle Black.
Everyone knows Castle Black.
Which others?
Eastwatch-by-the-Sea
and the Shadow Tower.
How many men
remain in Castle Black?
A thousand.
Liar.
What happens to your eagle
after I kill you?
Does he drift away
like a kite with
his strings cut,
or does he just flop
dead to the ground?
He's no crow.
Just 'cause you want him
inside, you don't
make him one of us.
I'm not afraid of you.
(GROANS)
I like you, boy.
But if you lie to me,
I'll pull your guts
out through your throat.
A thousand men.
(SIGHS)
We'll find out soon enough.
I don't need
you to protect me.
Of course you do.
Who stopped Rattleshirt
when he was about
to cut your throat?
Who vouched for you
with Mance?
It seems you owe me a debt.
Give it back.
Well, I stole it.
It's mine.
If you want it,
come steal it back.
Ygritte!
Ygritte! Seven hells.
Is Orell right?
Are you still a crow?
It's time
you proved yourself.
Ygritte.
You swore some vows.
I want you to break 'em.
I want you to see me.
All of me.
We shouldn't.
We should.
(EXHALES)
Why are you still dressed?
You know nothing, Jon Snow.
(GASPS)
(MOANING)
That thing you did
with your mouth...
Is that what lords
do to their ladies
in the South?
I don't know.
I just wanted to
kiss you there is all.
Hmm.
You seemed to like it.
Aye, I liked it some.
Who taught you that?
There's been no one else.
Only you.
A maid. (CHUCKLES)
You were a maid.
I was a man of
the Night's Watch.
How about you?
Were you a maid?
What do you think?
Who was he?
Just a boy.
He came trading
with his brothers.
He had red hair like me.
Kissed by fire. But...
He was weak. Not like you.
That was the first one.
Then there was
this Thenn boy.
Spoke no Common,
but, Gods, he was
built like a mammoth...
(CLEARS THROAT) Yeah, thanks.
I think I've heard enough.
We'd best get back.
Tormund...
I'm not done with you yet.
How long's it been
since you had a bath?
Let's not go back.
Let's stay here
a while longer.
I don't ever want to
leave this cave, Jon Snow.
Not ever.
HOUND: I want my gold.
It says clearly on that
note, you'll be paid
when the war is over.
Piss on that!
You're nothing but thieves.
We're outlaws. Outlaws
steal. You're lucky
we didn't kill you.
Come try it, archer.
I'll shove those
arrows up your ass.
You can't let him go.
He's a murderer.
He's guilty.
Not in the eyes of God.
You can't!
Enough!
BERIC: The judgment
isn't ours to make.
Go in peace, Sandor Clegane.
The Lord of Light
isn't done with you yet.
MAN: Riders coming through!
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
MAN: The Kingslayer.
Down!
(GRUNTS)
On your knees.
Lord Bolton,
I give you
the Kingslayer.
(GROANS)
Pick him up, Locke.
(GRUNTS)
You've lost a hand.
No, my lord, he has
it here. (CHUCKLES)
Take this away.
Send it to his father?
You'll hold your tongue
unless you want to lose it.
Cut her free.
Apologies, my lady.
You're under
my protection now.
Thank you, my lord.
Find suitable rooms
for our guests.
We'll speak later.
Lord Bolton.
Is there word
from the capital?
You haven't heard?
Stannis Baratheon laid siege
to King's Landing.
Sailed into Blackwater Bay.
Stormed the gates
with thousands of men.
And your sister...
How can I put this?
Your sister...
Is alive and well.
Your father's
forces prevailed.
Ser Jaime isn't well.
(GROANING)
Take him to Qyburn.
(GROANING CONTINUES)
(JAIME GROANS)
Will I die?
No.
The corruption has spread.
I fear it must be cut away.
The safest course
would be to take
the whole arm off.
Then you'll die.
You're no maester.
Where's your chain?
The Citadel
stripped me of it.
They found some
of my experiments
too bold.
I can leave your upper arm,
make the cut at your elbow.
I don't need
my right hand to kill you.
I can take away
the rotting flesh
and try and burn
out the corruption
with boiling wine.
Mmm. (CLEARS THROAT)
With any luck,
that will suffice.
You'll need
milk of the poppy.
No milk of the poppy.
There will be pain.
I'll scream.
Quite a bit of pain.
I'll scream loudly.
(GROANS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SCREAMING)
CERSEI: Lord Baelish.
Your Grace.
I wonder if I might
ask you for a favor.
Of course, Your Grace.
I believe that House Tyrell
don't hold the crown's
best interests at heart.
I see. And have you
shared these suspicions
with Lord Tywin?
My father's a practical man.
He appreciates facts.
Myself, I often
find them a hindrance.
And he appreciates
those who aid his family,
as you well know.
He's almost as generous
to those who help us
as he is unpleasant
towards those who don't.
You have a good
working relationship
with the Tyrells.
I thought you might
look into it before
you leave the capital.
I shall do my best.
Thank you.
And your best will
prove better than
when I asked you to
locate Arya Stark?
I assure you that it will.
Gods, boy, that's enough.
We're not in a tavern.
Pardon, my lady.
No need to speak.
Are there any figs?
Fetch some.
I always take
figs midafternoon.
They help move the bowels.
To what do I owe
this summons?
Thank you for
seeing me, my lady.
I had hoped we might discuss
a few financial matters.
I climbed all those steps
to discuss financial matters?
It's the royal wedding.
I'm told you had
a hand in planning it.
Naturally.
It's shaping up to be
a very involved affair.
The word "extravagant"
has been used.
What good is
the word "extravagant"
if it can't be used
to describe a royal wedding?
I understand that.
Good.
But, as Master of Coin,
it falls upon me
to calculate
the cost for the crown.
As of now,
it's a huge expense.
And?
And we're at war,
Lady Olenna.
Oh, I'd nearly forgotten.
And maintaining
supply lines...
I can't think how
it slipped my mind.
What is it, 12,000
infantrymen the Tyrell
family has supplied?
1,800 mounted lances.
2,000 in support.
Provisions, so this city
might survive the winter.
A million bushels of wheat.
Half a million bushels each
of barley, oats, and rye.
20,000 head of cattle.
50,000 sheep.
You don't have to lecture me
about wartime expenses.
I'm quite familiar with them.
And we are grateful
for your contributions,
which are necessary
for the preservation
of the realm.
As is a royal wedding.
The people are hungry
for more than just food.
They crave distractions.
And if we don't provide them,
they'll create their own.
And their distractions
are likely to
end with us
being torn to pieces.
A royal wedding is much
safer. Wouldn't you say?
I would.
And traditionally paid for
by the royal family.
I was told you were drunk,
impertinent,
and thoroughly debauched.
Imagine my disappointment
at finding
nothing but
a browbeaten bookkeeper.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Where did you go
for them, Volantis?
My lady...
Oh, very well.
I won't have it said
that House Tyrell refuses
to play its part.
We'll pay for half,
and the celebrations
will go on as planned.
Is that sufficient?
Quite. Thank you.
Very good, then.
That's settled. Good day.
Give me that.
(DOOR OPENING)
ARYA: What are you doing?
Just mending
Lord Beric's armor.
Why?
I'm going to stay and smith
for the Brotherhood.
Have you lost your mind?
When the Lannisters
find this place,
you think they'll
spare the smiths?
They'll cave your head in.
They wanted to kill me
long before I joined
the Brotherhood.
You don't have to.
I want to.
They need good men.
Robb needs good men, too.
We're leaving tomorrow.
And then you...
What? Serve him?
I've served men
my entire life.
I served Master Mott
at King's Landing, and
he sold me to the Watch.
I served Lord Tywin
at Harrenhal,
wondering every day
if I'd get tortured
or killed.
I'm done serving.
You just said you
were serving Lord Beric.
He may be their leader,
but they chose him.
These men are brothers.
They're a family.
I've never had a family.
I can be your family.
You wouldn't be my family.
You'd be "my lady."
(WATER DRIPPING)
(INDISTINCT YELLING)
(SWORDS CLANKING)
Willem.
(MAN GROANING LOUDLY)
Willem!
(GROANS)
Is this a rescue?
Lannister filth! Take him!
Please,
I didn't do anything.
I'm just a squire.
Please...
(GRUNTS)
(THUDS)
Bring them in.
(DOOR OPENING)
Is that all of them?
It took five of you
to murder
two unarmed squires?
Not murder, Your Grace.
Vengeance.
Vengeance?
Those boys
didn't kill your sons.
I saw Harrion die
on the battlefield,
and Torrhen...
Was strangled by
the Kingslayer.
They were his kin.
They were boys!
Look at them.
Tell your mother
to look at them.
She killed them
as much as I.
My mother had
nothing to do with this.
This was your treason.
It's treason to
free your enemies.
In war,
you kill your enemies.
Did your father
not teach you that, boy?
(GROANS)
Leave him.
Aye.
Leave me to the King.
He wants to give me
a scolding before
he sets me free.
That's how he
deals with treason.
Our King in the North.
Or should I call him
the King Who Lost the North?
Escort Lord Karstark
to the dungeon.
Hang the rest.
Mercy! I didn't kill
anyone. I only watched
for the guards.
This one was
only the watcher.
Hang him last,
so he can watch
the others die.
Please! Please, no.
They made me do it! They
made me! They made me!
(INHALES)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Word of this
can't leave Riverrun.
They were
Tywin Lannister's nephews.
The Lannisters
pay their debts.
They never stop
talking about it.
Would you make me
a liar as well?
It wouldn't be lying.
We will bury them
and remain silent
until the war is done.
I'm not fighting for justice
if I don't serve justice
to murderers in my ranks,
no matter how highborn.
He has to die.
The Karstarks are Northmen.
They won't forgive
the killing of their lord.
Your mother's right.
If you do this, the
Karstarks will abandon you.
You tended to their wounds.
You brought them supper.
Now they're dead.
And more boys will keep dying
until this war is over.
You need Karstark men
to end it.
Spare his life.
Keep him as a hostage.
A hostage.
Tell the Karstarks that
as long as they're loyal,
he will not be harmed.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
The blood of
the First Men flows through
my veins as
much as yours, boy.
I fought the Mad King
for your father.
I fought Joffrey for you.
We are kin,
Stark and Karstark.
That didn't stop you
from betraying me, and
it won't save you now.
I don't want it to save me.
I want it to haunt you
to the end of your days.
Kneel, my lord.
Rickard Karstark,
Lord of Karhold,
here,
in sight of gods and men,
I sentence you to die.
Would you speak a final word?
Kill me and be cursed.
You are no king of mine.
(GRUNTS)
ARYA: Joffrey.
Cersei.
Ilyn Payne.
Ser Meryn.
The Hound.
What are you
going to do with me?
At first light
we'll ride for Riverrun.
Your brother's there now.
He'll make
a contribution to our cause,
and you can go home.
I'm a hostage and
you're selling me.
Don't think of it that way.
But it is that way.
It is.
And it isn't.
More is than isn't.
Beric admired your father
a great deal, you know.
He wanted to refuse
your ransom altogether.
So, why don't you?
We need the gold.
(SIGHS)
Do I frighten you, child?
No.
You're angry with me,
and I don't blame you,
but letting him go
was the right thing.
I have more reason
to want him hanged.
I thought he killed you.
He did.
But how...
Thoros, how many times
have you brought me back?
It's the Lord of Light
who brings you back.
I'm just the lucky drunk
who says the words.
How many times?
Five, I think.
No, this makes six.
Six.
There was the first time.
The Mountain.
Show her.
Lance right through the chest.
BERIC: Then I was
stabbed in the belly.
Then it was
an arrow in the back.
And that ax in the side.
Then the Lannisters caught me
and executed me for treason.
Was it a hanging or
a dagger in the eye?
Both. Fuckers couldn't decide.
And the Hound makes six.
Second time I've been
killed by a Clegane.
THOROS: You'd think
you'd learn.
It's not getting
any easier, you know.
BERIC: I know.
Every time I come back,
I'm a bit less.
Pieces of you
get chipped away.
Could you bring back
a man without a head?
Not six times. Just once.
I don't think
it works that way, child.
He was a good man, Ned Stark.
He's at rest now, somewhere.
I would never wish
my life upon him.
I would.
You're alive.
SELYSE: Lord,
cast your light upon me.
Protect me in the darkness.
Burn away my sins.
Help me serve you.
Use me as you will.
(GASPS)
For the night is dark
and full of terrors.
(DOOR OPENING)
I have prayed day and night
for you to come to me.
My lady.
I meant to come sooner.
The battle...
I know of your troubles,
my King.
The Lady Melisandre
has told me everything.
Yes, of course.
(SIGHS)
You mustn't despair.
Your claim is true.
You will be victorious.
I believed that once.
You are the One God's
champion and the finest
man I've ever known.
Selyse.
I've broken a sacred vow.
I've sinned.
No.
I've wronged you.
I have shamed you.
You're doing God's work.
You don't understand.
The Red Woman...
The Lady Melisandre...
I know, Stannis.
The Lady Melisandre
has told me everything.
No act done in service
of the Lord of Light
can ever be a sin.
When she told me,
I wept with joy.
Oh, my sweet boys.
Petyr, Tommard, Edric.
I thank God every day
for bringing Melisandre
to us.
She gave you a son.
I gave you
nothing.
That's not true.
So, you've come
to see her as well?
There is no need.
You must keep away
from such distractions.
She's my daughter.
I want to see her.
You are a king.
You don't need
my permission.
GIRL: ♪ The sea
I know, I know
♪ Oh, oh, oh
♪ The birds have scales
♪ And the fish take wing
♪ I know, I know
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
STANNIS: (WHISPERS)
Shireen.
Father!
You've grown
since I last saw you.
Mother said you
fought in a battle.
Did you win?
No.
Did the Onion Knight
come back with you?
He did. He fought bravely.
He hasn't come to visit me.
He said he'd bring
me back a present
from the capital.
He won't be visiting, child.
Why not? He's my friend.
Look.
He made this for me.
But don't tell
Mother I have it.
It's a secret.
Mother doesn't
like the Onion Knight.
Ser Davos is a traitor.
He's rotting in
a dungeon cell for his crime.
Best forget him.
(DOOR OPENING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Not so hard. You'll
scrub the skin off.
What are you doing here?
I need a bath.
Help me out of these rags.
Now get out.
(DOOR CLOSES)
There's another tub.
JAIME: This one
suits me fine.
(EXHALES)
Don't worry.
I'm not interested.
(SIGHS)
If I faint, pull me out.
I don't intend to be
the first Lannister
to die in a bathtub.
Why should I care
how you die?
You swore
a solemn vow, remember?
You're supposed to
get me to King's Landing
in one piece.
Not going so well, is it?
No wonder Renly died,
with you guarding him.
That was unworthy.
Forgive me.
You protected me
better than most...
Don't you mock me.
I'm apologizing.
I'm sick of fighting.
Let's call a truce.
You need trust
to have a truce.
I trust you.
There it is.
There's the look.
I've seen it for 17 years,
on face after face.
You all despise me.
Kingslayer. Oathbreaker.
A man without honor.
You've heard of wildfire?
Of course.
The Mad King was
obsessed with it.
He loved to watch people burn,
the way their skin
blackened and blistered
and melted off their bones.
He burned lords
he didn't like.
He burned Hands
who disobeyed him.
He burned anyone
who was against him.
Before long, half
the country was against him.
Aerys saw traitors everywhere,
so he had his pyromancer
place caches of wildfire
all over the city,
beneath the Sept of Baelor
and the slums of Flea Bottom.
Under houses,
stables, taverns.
Even beneath
the Red Keep itself.
Finally,
the day of reckoning came.
Robert Baratheon
marched on the capital
after his victory
at the Trident.
But my father arrived first,
with the whole
Lannister army at his back,
promising to defend the city
against the rebels.
I knew my father
better than that.
He's never been one to
pick the losing side.
I told the Mad King as much.
I urged him to
surrender peacefully.
But the King
didn't listen to me.
He didn't listen to Varys,
who tried to warn him.
But he did listen to
Grand Maester Pycelle,
that gray, sunken cunt.
"You can trust
the Lannisters," he said.
"The Lannisters
have always been
true friends of the crown."
So, we opened the gates,
and my father sacked the city.
Once again,
I came to the King,
begging him to surrender.
He told me to bring him
my father's head.
Then he turned
to his pyromancer.
"Burn them all," he said.
"Burn them in their homes.
Burn them in their beds."
Tell me,
if your precious Renly
commanded you to
kill your own father
and stand by
while thousands of men,
women, and children
burned alive,
would you have done it?
Would you have
kept your oath then?
First,
I killed the pyromancer.
And then, when the King
turned to flee,
I drove my sword
into his back.
"Burn them all,"
he kept saying.
"Burn them all."
I don't think
he expected to die.
He meant to burn
with the rest of us
and rise again,
reborn as a dragon to
turn his enemies to ash.
I slit his throat to
make sure that didn't happen.
That's where Ned Stark
found me.
If this is true...
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
Why didn't you tell anyone?
Why didn't you
tell Lord Stark?
Stark?
You think
the honorable Ned Stark
wanted to hear my side?
He judged me guilty
the moment he set eyes on me.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
By what right does
the wolf judge the lion?
By what right?
Help! Help!
The Kingslayer!
(PANTING)
Jaime. My name is Jaime.
SHIREEN: (WHISPERING)
Onion Knight.
Ser Onion Knight.
Princess? Gods,
what are you doing here?
Shh! You'll wake Bert.
Bert?
He's the fat one.
He's on guard duty tonight.
He likes to drink wine
and sleep a lot.
Go back to your room.
You're not
supposed to be here.
If your father knew...
He said you were a traitor.
Are you?
I am, child.
I disobeyed my king,
your father, and now
I'm paying the price.
I don't care.
You're my friend.
You must get bored
down here. I brought you
something to read.
It's about Aegon
and his dragons.
Aegon used to live here.
Did you know that?
And the Targaryens
built this castle.
Aye.
So they did.
You can hide the book
under your cloak.
It's a good one.
I'll bring you more.
Thank you, my lady.
I'm sure it's a fine book,
but it's wasted on me.
Take it.
I have more.
My lady,
I can't read the words.
You can't?
I'll teach you.
I'll come when Bert's
on duty and teach you.
No. No. No.
It's easy. It'll be fun.
Go. We can't.
Why not? What will
they do, lock us in cells?
(CHUCKLES)
I wouldn't know
where to start.
At the beginning.
This word is "Aegon."
When you see "A," "E,"
and "G" together like that,
it sounds like "egg."
And the title
of the whole book
is An History of
Aegon the Conqueror
and His Conquest of Westeros.
(UNSULLIED CHANTING)
JORAH: It was
a bitch of a siege.
BARRISTAN: Mmm.
You were first through
the breach at Pyke?
The second.
Thoros of Myr went in
alone, waving that
flaming sword of his.
(CHUCKLES) Thoros of Myr.
Bloody madman.
Robert knighted you
after the battle?
Proudest moment of my life.
One knee in the dust,
the King's sword
on my shoulder,
listening to the words,
"In the name of the Warrior,
I charge you to be brave."
All I could think of
was how badly I had to piss.
(LAUGHS)
JORAH: In full plate metal
for 16 hours.
Never occurred to me
till the fighting was over.
I was very
nearly the first man
knighted to piss
on the King's boots.
(LAUGHS)
Robert would
have laughed.
He was a good man,
a great warrior.
And a terrible king.
I burned away my years
fighting for terrible kings.
You swore an oath.
Yes.
And a man of honor
keeps his vows,
even if he's serving
a drunk or a lunatic.
Just once in my life
before it's over,
I want to know
what it's like to
serve with pride,
to fight for
someone I believe in.
Do you believe in her?
With all my heart.
These are the ones?
Yes, Khaleesi.
The officers.
(DAENERYS SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
(IN VALYRIAN)
All Unsullied boys
are given new names
when they are cut.
Grey Worm,
Red Flea, Black Rat.
Names that remind them
what they are...
Vermin.
(BOTH IN VALYRIAN)
JORAH: King Robert
wanted her dead.
Of course he wanted her
dead. She's a Targaryen.
The last Targaryen.
I suppose no one
on the Small Council
could speak sense to him.
I didn't sit on
the Small Council.
No?
Doesn't the Lord Commander
of the Kingsguard
traditionally...
Traditionally, yes,
but I killed a dozen
of Robert's friends
during his rebellion.
He didn't want
advice on how to govern
from a man who had
fought for the Mad King.
Can't say I minded much.
I always hated
the politics.
Yeah, I imagine
I would, too.
Hours spent jabbering about
backstabbings and
betrayals the world over.
Mmm-hmm.
Still, she'll have to
wade through that muck
if she wants to rule
the Seven Kingdoms.
She'll have
good men around her
to advise her,
men with experience.
Which men
do you have in mind?
Forgive me for
what I'm about to say,
but your reputation
in Westeros has
suffered over the years.
It suffered for a reason.
I sold men into slavery.
I don't know if your
presence by her side
will help our cause
when we go home.
Our cause?
Forgive me, Ser Barristan,
but I was busy
defending the Khaleesi
against King
Robert's assassins
while you were
still bowing to the man.
We both want her to rule.
Am I wrong?
You only joined us
a few days ago.
I can't speak to
your intentions.
If we're truly
her loyal servants,
we will do
whatever needs to be done,
no matter the cost,
no matter our pride.
You're not Lord Commander
here. You're just
another exile.
And I take my orders
from the Queen.
(NEIGHS)
TALISA: Come to bed.
You were right.
The Karstarks are gone.
(CLATTERING)
Almost half our forces.
Tywin Lannister
knows what he needs to do
to make us unravel.
Nothing.
Only wait.
Don't let him.
What can I do?
Attack King's Landing?
There's nothing
he'd like better.
He'd crush us in a day.
We could ride north.
Take your land back
from the Greyjoys.
Wait out the winter.
Winter could
last five years.
Once my bannermen
are home again,
sitting by the fire,
surrounded by
their families,
warm and safe, they'll
never ride south again.
When I gathered my lords
together, we had
a purpose, a mission.
Now we're like a band
of bickering children.
Give them a new purpose.
What?
I don't know.
I don't even know
where Winterfell is.
Here.
And we're here.
King's Landing...
What is it?
I can't force them to
meet us in the field
and I can't attack them
where they're strongest,
but I can attack them
where they're not.
And Casterly Rock
can't run away.
I'm going to take
their home away from them.
Can you do it?
I need men to
replace the Karstarks
who marched home.
There is only one
person in this kingdom
with that kind of army
who hasn't already
sided with the Lannisters.
(LAUGHS)
The man whose daughter
I was supposed to marry.
Walder Frey.
(GRUNTING)
He's such
a splendid fighter.
Do you have any idea
when we might...
I'll plant the seed
as soon as Joffrey
and I are married.
It should grow quickly.
Joffrey won't let me leave.
He's got too many
reasons to keep me here.
And only one
to let you go.
Because it will please me.
LORAS: Squire.
Well fought, ser.
That was no fight.
I don't know you.
Olyver, if it please you.
I should like to
see you spar with
a proper partner, ser.
(MOANS)
(PANTING)
How did you know?
Know what?
That I wanted to.
My lord...
I'll have you know
I'm to be married soon,
and even my intended
hasn't the slightest notion.
They rarely do,
in my experience.
You have a good deal
of experience, do you?
With the husbands.
That didn't take long.
Well, it took long enough.
It seems
our Knight of Flowers
is engaged to be wed.
Is he?
And...
Who's the lucky girl?
LITTLEFINGER: She may
not be the grandest
ship in the world
or the fastest,
but she's mine.
I've always wanted a ship.
Now I want a dozen.
Strange, isn't it?
What is?
It doesn't matter
what we want,
once we get it,
then we want
something else.
Your hair is different.
Is it?
Lady Margaery
wears it that way.
Many ladies
wear it this way.
I have good news.
I'll be leaving
the city soon.
You still want me
to come with you?
It's not
a question of what I want.
It's what you want.
You want to go home,
don't you?
Of course.
More than anything.
But maybe it would
be better to wait.
I've been thinking how
dangerous it would be.
Not just for me, but for you.
You've been so kind.
I'd feel terrible if
anything happened to you.
I can't tell you
how touched I am
by your concern
for my welfare.
I hope you know that
I'm your friend, Sansa.
Your true friend.
I do, Lord Baelish.
Petyr.
If you wish to stay,
then of course
you will stay.
We'll speak again
when I return.
(EXHALES)
TYWIN: You're late.
What's she doing here?
Our business
concerns her, too.
Sit.
You'll be pleased
to learn that
after one conversation
with Olenna Tyrell,
I've saved the crown
hundreds of thousands
on this wedding.
Never mind that now.
We have something
important to discuss.
I'm Master of Coin.
Saving money is important.
Stop that. You're
making me uncomfortable.
Your sister has learned
that your new friends
the Tyrells
are plotting to marry
Sansa Stark to Ser Loras.
Very well.
She's a lovely girl.
Missing some of Loras'
favorite bits, but I'm sure
they'll make do.
Your jokes are
not appreciated.
It wasn't
my best, but...
I bring them into
the royal fold, and
this is how they repay me,
by trying to steal
the key to the North
out from under me.
Sansa is the key to the
North? I seem to remember
she has an older brother.
The Karstarks
have marched home.
The Young Wolf has
lost half his army.
His days are numbered.
Theon Greyjoy
murdered both his brothers.
That makes Sansa Stark
the heir to Winterfell,
and I am not about
to hand her over
to the Tyrells.
TYRION: The Tyrell army is
helping us to win this war.
Do you really think
it's wise to refuse them?
There's nothing to refuse.
This is a plot.
Plots are not
public knowledge.
And the Tyrells won't
carry this one out until
after Joffrey's wedding.
We need to act first
and kill this union
in its crib.
And how do we do that?
We find Sansa Stark
a different husband.
Wonderful.
Yes, it is.
You can't mean it.
I can and I do.
Joffrey's made
this poor girl's
life miserable
since the day he took
her father's head.
Now she's finally
free of him, and
you give her to me?
That's cruel,
even for you.
Do you intend on
mistreating her?
The girl's happiness
is not my concern,
nor yours.
She's a child!
She's flowered, I assure
you. She and I have
discussed it at length.
There, you see?
You will wed her,
bed her,
and put a child in her.
Surely you're
capable of that.
And if I refuse?
You wanted to be rewarded
for your valor in battle.
Sansa Stark is a finer
reward than you could
ever dare hope for.
And it is past time
you were wed.
I was wed.
Or don't you remember?
Only too well.
You should be thanking
the Gods for this. This is
more than you deserve.
Tyrion will do as he's bid.
As will you.
(TYWIN CLEARS THROAT)
What do you mean?
You'll marry Ser Loras.
I will not.
The boy is heir
to Highgarden.
Tyrion will secure the North,
you will secure the Reach.
No, I won't do it.
Yes, you will.
You're still fertile.
You need to marry
again and breed.
I am Queen Regent,
not some broodmare.
You're my daughter!
You will do as I command,
and you will
marry Loras Tyrell
and put an end to
the disgusting rumors
about you once and for all.
Father, don't make me
do it again, please.
Not another word.
My children.
You've disgraced
the Lannister name
for far too long.
(DOOR SLAMS)