You've got too
much wood in there.
But the more wood,
the bigger the fire.
It needs to breathe.
Take off that big log.
(SAMWELL GRUNTS)
Ah.
You know your fires.
Someone built your fires
for you growing up?
It doesn't get so cold
down in the Reach.
And there were servants,
of course.
I knew you were highborn.
Oh, I found something
at the Fist of the First Men.
Buried treasure.
Thousands of years old.
I think.
What does it do?
I'm not sure that
it does anything.
It's beautiful,
though, isn't it?
(BABY GURGLING)
How much longer?
Not so far. A few more days.
Is the Wall as
big as they say?
Bigger.
So big you can't even
see the top sometimes.
It's hidden in clouds.
You're playing with me.
I'm not.
It's 700 feet high,
all made of ice.
On a warm day
you can see it weeping.
Castle Black is nice enough.
They keep a fire
burning in the long hall
day and night.
And Hobb makes
venison stew with onions.
Very tasty.
Sometimes, one of
the brothers will sing.
Dareon sings best.
Do you sing?
No.
No, no, no. (CHUCKLES)
Not very well.
Sing me a song.
Oh, all right. Let's see.
Oh.
(CLEARS THROAT)
♪ The Father's face
is stern and strong
♪ He sits and
judges right from wrong
♪ He weighs our lives,
the short and long
♪ And loves
the little children
♪ The Mother
gives the gift of life
♪ And watches over
every wife
♪ Her gentle smile
ends all strife
♪ And she loves
her little children ♪
That's not how
you skin a rabbit.
I know how to skin a rabbit.
Not by the looks of it.
OSHA: You grow up
north of the Wall,
you learn the proper way
to handle game.
I didn't see any game
before I got here.
If I had a bow,
I could have shot a dozen.
Well, I made
this bow myself.
Guess you don't learn
how to do that
north of the Wall.
You learn how to
use your fists.
Oh, you're gonna punch
the rabbits to death?
I had someone else in mind.
Well, someone else
is sitting right here.
You're both very good
at skinning rabbits.
Some of us are
just a little better.
Well, some of us
would say thank you
when someone else
hunts down their
breakfast for them.
Or don't they teach you
to say thank you
north of the Wall?
You've got
a big mouth, girl,
and too many teeth.
BRANDON: Stop it!
HODOR: Hmm.
Hodor.
You've been fighting
since you met.
Just stop it.
Lady Reed here's got
a stick so far up her ass,
it's a wonder her feet
touch the ground.
You've been nasty
to her every day.
Of course she's nasty back.
Me? It's my fault?
First time I met her,
she put a knife
to my throat.
First time I met you,
you held a knife at me.
We can't fight each other.
We'll never make
it to the Wall.
I want you both
to make peace.
Your way of skinning
rabbits is quicker.
I said so, didn't I?
Osha!
You're a good little hunter.
Thank you.
See? Not so hard, is it?
Don't push me.
(JOJEN BREATHING HEAVILY)
MEERA: I'm right here
with you.
What's happening?
I'm right here with you.
What's wrong with him?
The visions take their toll.
He's having one now?
(BREATHING NORMALLY)
I saw Jon Snow.
You saw him?
At Castle Black?
He was on
the wrong side of the Wall,
surrounded by enemies.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Used to be you
couldn't find a tree
within a mile of the Wall.
Crows would come out
every morning with axes.
Your flock gets
smaller every year.
You ever climbed it before?
No.
But Tormund's done it
half a hundred times.
You're afraid.
(EXHALES)
Aren't you?
Aye.
Well, it's a long way up
and a long way down.
But I've waited
my whole life to see
the world from up there.
Here, sit down.
I brought a pair for you.
They're too big for you,
but they're good.
You kill someone for them?
Nah.
I didn't kill him,
but I bet his balls
are still bruised.
(LAUGHING)
He wasn't good to me
the way you're good to me.
Well, he didn't do
that thing you do
with your tongue.
Can we not talk
about that here?
(MIMICKING)
"Can we not talk
about that here?
"I'm Jon Snow.
"I've killed dead men
and Qhorin Halfhand,
"but I'm scared
of naked girls."
Did I seem scared
the other day?
You were trembling
like a leaf.
Only in the beginning.
Huh.
You're a proper lover,
Jon Snow.
And don't worry.
Your secret's
safe with me.
What secret?
Do you think I'm as
dumb as all those girls
in silk dresses
you knew growing up?
(CHUCKLES)
You're loyal
and you're brave.
You didn't stop being a crow
the day you walked
into Mance Rayder's tent.
But I'm your woman
now, Jon Snow.
You're going to be
loyal to your woman.
The Night's Watch don't
care if you live or die.
Mance Rayder don't
care if I live or die.
We're just soldiers
and there's more to
carry on if we go down.
It's you and me that
matters to me and you.
Don't ever betray me.
I won't.
'Cause I'll cut your
pretty cock right off
and wear it 'round me neck.
Sink your metal deep
and make sure it holds
before taking your next step.
And if you fall,
don't scream.
You don't want that
to be the last
thing she remembers.
(LAUGHS)
(GRUNTS)
ARYA: Joffrey.
Cersei.
Ilyn Payne.
You're good.
You're not as good
as you think you are.
Face, tits, balls...
I hit 'em right
where I wanted to.
Aye,
but you took your
sweet time of it.
You won't be fighting
straw men, little lady.
Show me your position.
Keep your elbow high.
You want your back
doing the hard labor.
You're holding.
Never hold.
What?
Your muscles tense up
when you hold.
Pull the string back to
the center of your chin
and release.
Never hold.
But I have to aim.
(CHUCKLES)
Never aim.
Never aim?
Your eye knows
where it wants
the arrow to go.
Trust your eye.
(SIGHS)
There's someone out there.
(HORSE SNUFFLES)
That's about far enough.
We come as friends.
ANGUY: Begging
your pardon, m'lady,
but we'll be
the judge of that.
Valar Morghulis.
THOROS: Valar Dohaeris.
(BOTH SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
My friends here don't
speak High Valyrian.
Why are you here,
my lady?
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Forgive my manners.
I don't see many
ladies these days.
Lucky for the ladies.
How many times has
the Lord brought him back?
Six.
(BOTH IN VALYRIAN)
I've always been
a terrible priest.
Drank too much rum.
Fucked all the whores
in King's Landing.
It's a terrible
thing to say,
but by the time I came
to Westeros, I didn't
believe in our Lord.
I decided that He,
that all the Gods,
were stories we
told the children
to make them behave.
So I wore the robes,
and every now and then
I'd recite the prayers,
but it was just for show.
A spectacle for the locals.
Until the Mountain
drove a lance through
this one's heart.
I knelt beside his cold body
and said the old words.
Not because
I believed in them, but...
He was my friend
and he was dead.
And they were
the only words I knew.
And for the first
time in my life,
the Lord replied.
Beric's eyes opened,
and I knew the truth.
Our god is
the one true god.
And all men must serve Him.
You've been
to the other side.
The other side?
There is no other side.
I have been to the darkness,
my lady.
He sent you to us
for a reason.
You have someone He needs.
ANGUY: Bodkin point.
Penetrates plate
at 200 yards.
Can you make 'em?
Yeah, nothing tricky about it.
Just need decent steel.
I'll get you the steel.
MAN: Come on.
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
(WHEELS SQUEAKING)
ARYA: I don't like that woman.
(CHUCKLES)
That's 'cause
you're a girl.
What does that have
to do with anything?
(HORSE NEIGHING)
Forgive me, lad.
(GRUNTING)
What are you doing?
Let go of him.
Tell them to stop.
Come on.
He wants to be one of you.
He wants to join
the Brotherhood. Stop them!
We serve the Lord of Light,
and the Lord of Light
needs this boy.
Did the Lord of Light
tell you that, or did she?
ARYA: You're not
doing this for your god.
You're doing it for gold.
We're doing it
for both, girl.
We can't defend
the people without weapons
and horses and food.
And we can't get weapons
and horses and
food without gold.
GENDRY: You told me
this was a Brotherhood.
You told me
I could be one of you.
You are more than
they can ever be.
They're just foot soldiers
in the great war.
You will make
kings rise and fall.
(PANTING)
You're a witch.
You're going to hurt him.
I see a darkness in you.
And in that darkness,
eyes staring back at me...
Brown eyes,
blue eyes, green eyes.
Eyes you'll shut forever.
We will meet again.
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(METAL CLANKING)
(TORMUND GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
(WIND HOWLING)
(PANTING)
You staring at
me ass, Jon Snow?
Look out!
(GROANS)
You all right?
(GRUNTS)
Just seeing if you
can take a hit, lad.
(TORMUND LAUGHING)
(HORN BLARING)
(GASPS)
Sorry. Were you sleeping?
(PANTS) Wa...
Wa... Wa...
Water? You want some water.
I wish I had some for you.
(WHIMPERS)
So, let's play a game.
Which body part do
you need the least?
Please.
"Please" is not a body part.
I'll tell you everything,
please.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
But you've already
told me everything.
Remember?
(MOCKING)
Your daddy was mean to you.
The Starks
didn't appreciate you.
(NORMAL VOICE) One
good bit, though.
The Stark boys,
they're still alive.
Wouldn't that be
a hunt to remember?
You failed, but I'm
a better hunter than you.
Now...
How about your little
finger? You don't use that
for much, do you?
No? Good.
Let's start with that.
Ah!
You've been wondering
why you're here,
haven't you?
Where you are.
Who I am.
Why I'm doing this to you.
So, guess.
If you guess right,
I'll tell you.
By the Old Gods and
the New, I swear it.
You win the game
if you can figure out
who I am and
why I'm torturing you,
and I win the game
if you beg me to
cut off your finger.
If I win,
you'll let me go?
If you think this
has a happy ending,
you haven't been
paying attention.
Please.
You say "please" again
and you'll wish you hadn't.
You first. Where are we?
The North.
Too vague.
Deepwood Motte.
(BOY LAUGHS)
Terrible guess.
(GROANS)
(GROANING)
Now, where?
Last Hearth.
(LAUGHS) Do I look like
a fucking Umber to you?
(SCREAMS IN PAIN)
Karhold!
Karhold?
How did you know that?
Did you see any banners
flying when we came in?
No.
It was just a guess.
Very good, Lord Theon.
And who am I?
Torrhen Karstark.
He's dead.
Strangled by the Kingslayer.
He was your brother.
Your father is
Lord Rickard Karstark.
You swore to
tell me if I...
You're right.
Lord Rickard Karstark
is Robb Stark's bannerman.
I betrayed Robb.
That's why
you're torturing me.
Yes.
You win.
Of course, you forgot
to ask one question.
You forgot to
ask if I'm a liar.
(SCREAMING IN PAIN)
I'm afraid I am.
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
Everything I told you
is a lie.
This isn't happening
to you for a reason.
But, well, one reason...
I enjoy it.
THEON: Please, cut it off!
Cut it off! Cut it off!
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
I win.
ROBB: Thank you for
riding here so quickly.
I know travel isn't
easy in these times.
The roads are crawling
with cutthroats and bandits.
When the King of
the North summons us,
we come.
LOTHAR: Our father
has instructed us to
tell you that his alliance
with the North can continue
if his terms are met.
Lord Frey requires
a formal apology
for your violation
of your sacred oath to
marry one of his daughters.
Of course.
He deserves as much.
I was in the wrong.
As restitution
for this betrayal,
he demands Harrenhal
and all its attendant lands.
I don't think that's...
We are fighting
for the North.
Harrenhal is
not in the North.
It is his once the war is
over and we have no further
strategic need for it.
And there's
something else.
We will do whatever
we can to give Lord Frey
what he needs.
Not what, whom.
What?
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
Uh, no.
Our father requires
Lord Edmure to wed
one of his daughters. Roslin.
How old is she?
Nineteen.
Could I see her first?
You want to
count her teeth?
We depart for
the Twins in the morning.
We need an answer
before we leave,
and a wedding not more
than a fortnight thereafter
or this alliance
is at an end.
Your father does
realize we're in
the middle of a war?
Father is old.
It will put his heart at
peace if he could see her
wed to a good husband.
And his recent experience
has made him wary
of long engagements.
He has every right to be.
Please excuse us
while we discuss it.
(DOOR OPENING)
Why should I let
that old ferret
choose my bride for me?
At the very least,
I should be offered
the same choice you were.
I'm his liege lord.
ROBB: He's a proud man
and we've wounded him.
EDMURE:
I didn't wound him.
My answer is no.
Listen to me and listen
very carefully. You...
The laws of gods and
men are very clear.
No man can compel
another man to marry.
The laws of my fist
are about to
compel your teeth.
It's all right.
You heard him.
If you refuse,
our alliance with
the Freys is dead.
He's wanted me for
one of his daughters
since I was 12.
He's not gonna
stop wanting it now.
When I say no,
he will come back
and offer me
a daughter of my choosing.
You're willing to
risk our freedom
and our lives
for a chance
at a prettier wife?
I have a war to fight.
We can't win it without them.
I have no time to haggle.
You said you wanted
to make amends for
the Stone Mill.
You recall that
heroic engagement?
I had something
less permanent in mind.
I've won every battle,
but I'm losing this war.
If we don't do this and
do it now, we're lost.
I'll marry her.
You're paying
for my sins, Uncle.
It's not fair or right.
I'll remember it.
BOLTON: I see my men have
finally found you something
appropriate to wear.
BRIENNE: Yes.
Most kind of them.
You're a Stark bannerman,
Lord Bolton.
I am acting on
Lady Stark's orders
to return Jaime Lannister
to King's Landing.
When King Robb left
Harrenhal, his mother
was his prisoner.
If she wasn't his mother,
he'd have hanged
her for treason.
I should send you
back to Robb Stark.
You should.
But instead,
you're sitting here,
watching me fail at dinner.
Why might that be?
Wars cost money.
Many people would pay
a great deal for you.
We both know who
would pay the most.
Or make you pay the most
if he found out
you had captured me
and sent me back up north
for a summary execution.
You're right.
Perhaps the safest thing
to do is to kill you both
and burn your bodies.
JAIME: It would be,
if you honestly believed
my father would
never find out about it.
King Robb is keeping
your father quite busy.
He doesn't have time
for anything else.
He'll make time for you.
As soon as you're
well enough to travel,
I will allow you to
go to King's Landing
as restitution
for the mistakes
my soldiers made.
And you will swear to
tell your father the truth,
that I had nothing to
do with your maiming.
Shall we drink on it?
I don't partake.
You do understand
how suspicious that is
to ordinary people?
Very well.
My lady,
may our journey continue
without further incident.
Oh, she won't be
going with you.
I am charged with
bringing Ser Jaime to...
BOLTON: You are charged
with abetting treason.
I'm afraid I must insist.
You're in no place
to insist on anything.
I would have hoped
you'd learned your lesson
about overplaying
your position.
OLENNA: Impossible.
Why?
My grandson is
the pride of Highgarden.
The most desirable bachelor
in all seven kingdoms.
Your daughter...
Is rich,
the most beautiful woman
in all seven kingdoms,
and the mother of the King.
Old.
Old?
I'm something of
an expert on the subject.
Her change will be
upon her before long.
I'll spare you the details
of what will happen then.
You may have a stomach
for bloodshed and slaughter,
but this is
another matter entirely.
The years punish us as well,
I promise you that.
My stomach remains
quite strong, however.
The only thing that
might turn it are details
of your grandson's
nocturnal activities.
Do you deny them?
Oh, not at all.
A sword-swallower
through and through.
A boy with his affliction
should be grateful
for the opportunity
to marry
the most beautiful woman
in the Kingdoms
and remove
the stain from his name.
Did you grow up
with boy cousins,
Lord Tywin?
Sons of your
father's bannermen,
squires, stable boys?
Of course.
And you never...
No.
Not once? Not in any way?
Never.
I congratulate you
upon your restraint.
But it's natural,
boys having a go
beneath the sheets.
Perhaps Highgarden
has a high tolerance
for unnatural behavior.
I wouldn't say that.
True, we don't tie
ourselves in knots
over a discreet
bit of buggery, but
brothers and sisters...
Where I come from,
that stain would be very
difficult to wash out.
I will not
breathe further life
into a malicious lie
by discussing it.
Lie or not,
you must admit many people
find it quite convincing.
Convincing enough
to put swords
in their hands
and send them off
to kill Lannisters
and Tyrells,
thanks to our new affiliation.
I don't care
what people believe.
And neither do you.
(CHUCKLES)
As an authority on myself,
I must disagree.
Now, if the rumors about
my children were true,
then Joffrey is
no king at all,
and House Tyrell
is throwing its prized
flower into the dirt.
And if Cersei is too old
to give Loras children,
we're throwing another
prized flower into the dirt.
It is a chance
we simply cannot take.
The uncertainty
makes you uncomfortable?
All right.
I'll remove it for you.
If you refuse to
marry Loras to Cersei,
I will name him
to the Kingsguard.
I'm sure you're familiar
with the Kingsguard vows.
He will never marry.
He will never have children.
Ah.
The Tyrell name will fade.
And Highgarden will
go to the children of
Joffrey and Margaery.
You would have your
grandson protected by
someone who disgusts you?
I would have my grandson
protected by
a skilled warrior
who takes
his vows seriously.
So, shall I draw up
the order?
Or do you
consent to this match?
It's a rare enough thing,
a man who lives up
to his reputation.
(WIND HOWLING)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(GRUNTS)
(YGRITTE GRUNTS)
(CRACKING)
(CRACKING CONTINUES)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(ALL SCREAMING)
No!
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH PANTING IN RELIEF)
(YELLING)
We've gotta cut them loose!
No! (GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(ORELL GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
Take my hand!
(JON GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
SANSA: That's a wonderful pin.
It's more of
a brooch, really.
Though I suppose a brooch
is a sort of pin, so...
I'm very happy about...
Yes. I am as well.
SANSA: I feel like
I'm in a dream. (CHUCKLES)
Yes, me, too.
Definitely.
I've dreamed of
a large wedding
since I was young.
The guests, the food,
the tournaments.
And the bride, of course.
(CHUCKLES)
The most beautiful
bride in the world
in a beautiful gown of
gold and green brocade
with fringed sleeves.
Have you ever been to
Highgarden, my lady?
No. I had never
left Winterfell
before I came to
King's Landing.
But it sounds wonderful.
I can't wait to see it.
And to leave this place.
It's terrible, isn't it?
The most
terrible place there is.
TYRION: I don't suppose
there's anything
we can do about this.
We can have
them both killed.
It's hard to say
which of the four of us
is getting the worst
of this arrangement.
Probably Sansa.
Though Loras will
certainly come to know
a deep and singular misery.
Father doesn't
discriminate.
We're all being
shipped off to
hell together.
On a boat you built.
The Tyrells were plotting
to undermine our family.
I did what I did to
protect our family.
I'm your family.
A member of your
family who has actively
contributed to that
family's survival.
Whether or not you
or Father or anyone else
wants to admit it.
I do admit it.
If it weren't for your
trick with the wildfire,
Stannis would
have sacked the city
before Father got here.
Our heads would still be
rotting on the city gate.
Trying to have me killed
is an odd way of
saying thank you.
There are two people
in King's Landing
who can give
an order to a Kingsguard.
Did you or did you
not order Ser Mandon
to kill me during
the Battle of
the Blackwater?
The impulse I understand.
He hates me
because I'm the only one
who tells him
what he really is.
So, fair enough.
He wants me dead.
But his stupidity?
He could have had me
poisoned and no one
would have known.
But the King
orders a Kingsguard
to murder the Hand
of the King in full view
of his own army.
The boy's an idiot.
What do you
want me to say?
I want you to tell me
if my life is
still in danger.
Probably.
But not from Joffrey.
He won't do anything
now Father's here.
Seven kingdoms united in fear
of Tywin Lannister.
Not the Tyrells.
Soon they won't need
to be afraid of him.
Joffrey will
belong to Margaery,
the little doe-eyed whore,
and so will his
children and their children.
History will be
taken from our hands.
You may escape, at least.
Once Jaime gets back,
Ser Loras may come
down with a terrible case
of sword through bowels.
When Jaime gets back, yes.
But when will that be?
He's out there somewhere.
Jaime or not,
I'm truly fucked.
Who's going to tell her?
Do you think
people will like it?
SHAE: I don't think
they will even notice it.
You're right.
It's not my wedding.
Anyway, from
what I can tell,
the dressmakers in
Highgarden will be
far superior to
the ones in King's Landing.
They'd never make me
anything as dull as this
for my wedding.
Loras likes green
and gold brocade.
I'm sure he does.
Will they let me
invite my family?
They haven't asked
my opinion.
But do you think they will?
No.
Lady Sansa,
Lord Tyrion to see you.
Should I...
I beg your pardon,
my lady.
Good afternoon, Lord Tyrion.
I was trying on a gown
for Joffrey's wedding.
Yes, it should be
quite a wedding.
I need to speak
with you, Lady Sansa.
Of course.
Alone, if I may.
Why do you need to
speak to her alone?
Shae.
Please excuse her.
She's not from here.
But I trust her,
even though she
tells me not to.
Sometimes we think
we want to hear something,
and it's only afterwards,
when it's too late,
that we realize
we wished we'd heard it
under entirely
different circumstances.
It's all right, really.
How to begin?
(DOOR CLOSES)
TYRION: It's... This...
This... This is awkward.
VARYS: A thousand blades
taken from the hands
of Aegon's fallen enemies,
forged in the fiery breath
of Balerion the Dread.
There aren't
1,000 blades.
There aren't even 200.
I've counted.
VARYS: (SCOFFS)
I'm sure you have.
Ugly old thing.
LITTLEFINGER:
Yet it has a certain appeal.
The Lysa Arryn
of chairs.
Shame you had to settle
for your second choice.
Early days, my friend.
It is flattering,
really,
you feeling such dread
at the prospect of me
getting what I want.
Thwarting you has never
been my primary ambition,
I promise you.
Although who
doesn't like to see
their friends
fail now and then?
You're so right.
For instance,
when I thwarted your plan
to give Sansa Stark
to the Tyrells.
If I'm going to be honest,
I did feel an unmistakable
sense of enjoyment there.
But your confidant,
the one who fed
you information
about my plans,
the one you
swore to protect...
You didn't bring
her any enjoyment.
And she didn't
bring me any enjoyment.
She was a bad investment
on my part.
Luckily, I have a friend
who wanted to
try something new.
Something daring.
And he was so grateful
to me for providing
this fresh experience.
I did what I did for
the good of the realm.
The realm?
Do you know
what the realm is?
It's the 1,000 blades
of Aegon's enemies.
A story we agree
to tell each other
over and over,
till we forget
that it's a lie.
But what do we have left
once we abandon the lie?
Chaos. A gaping pit
waiting to swallow us all.
Chaos isn't a pit.
Chaos is a ladder.
Many who try to climb it fail
and never get to try again.
The fall breaks them.
And some are given
a chance to climb,
but they refuse.
They cling to the realm
or the Gods or love.
Illusions.
Only the ladder is real.
The climb is all there is.
(WIND HOWLING)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH PANTING)
(CAWING)
(JON GRUNTS)