(CAWING)
YGRITTE: How far are we?
About a week, I think.
You think?
You don't know?
JON: When we went
to Castle Black, we took
the King's Road.
(SCOFFS)
You and your roads.
Is that how you
lot do your fighting?
You march down the road
banging drums
and waving banners?
Most of the time, yes.
How do the men
holding the banners fight?
They don't, really.
It's a great honor to
carry your house sigil.
And the drummers...
Is that a great honor, too?
Usually it's the young boys
banging the drums.
So, what good are they?
They help the men march.
How?
Well, it's...
It's the rhythm.
Oh, you mean
right foot, left foot,
right foot,
left foot, right foot?
What, you need
help remembering that?
When Mance gives the signal
and we hit Castle Black,
we won't be banging
on drums to let
them know we're coming.
No.
No, you're just gonna
light the biggest fire
the North has ever seen
to let them
know you're coming.
You know nothing, Jon Snow.
ORELL: She's right, you don't.
I know you cut me
loose on the Wall.
Cut her loose, too.
Do you see her
sulking about it?
That's because
she understands
the way things are.
And are you gonna
share it with me,
the deep wisdom you found
inside the head of a bird?
People work together
when it suits them.
They're loyal
They love each other
when it suits them.
And they kill each
other when it suits them.
She knows that, you don't.
Which is why you'll
never hold on to her.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
That rain will
cost us another day.
Frey will wait.
He knows we're coming.
Lord Walder is
prickly by nature. If...
"Prickly"?
That what you call it?
Might be
the least pleasant man
I've ever met.
Yes, and that is why...
I've seen wet shits
I liked better
than Walder Frey.
Apologies,
Your Grace.
I've spent too many years
around lancers and pikemen.
I've spent two years
nursing wounded men,
watching them bleed and die.
I'm not afraid
of wet shits.
(LAUGHING)
Lord Frey will take
this delay as a slight.
EDMURE: He can take it
as he likes.
He's getting
the wedding he wanted.
He's getting a wedding.
It was a king he wanted.
Edmure is the best match
a Frey has had in
the history of their house.
We should all
get some sleep.
(TALISA MOANING)
(CHUCKLES)
(EXHALES)
(SIGHS)
If you don't put
some clothes on,
I can't promise
I won't attack you again.
Attack. Attack.
(EXHALES)
(GRUNTS)
ROBB: Who are you writing?
My mother.
Is that Valyrian?
Gaaa.
"Gaaa"?
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
Say hello for me.
Rytsas.
"Ritsas."
(LAUGHS)
That was close enough.
Does she know
her daughter's a queen?
Not yet.
That will be a surprise,
I expect.
Many surprises
for her.
How am I supposed to
sit here planning a war
when you're over there,
looking like that?
Will you come with me
one day to Volantis?
When all this is over?
I will.
I promise.
I know she'd love
to meet you.
And her grandchild.
What, now?
Are you certain?
Are you angry with me?
Angry?
You're my queen.
And I have your
little prince or
princess inside me.
Maybe one of each.
Don't get greedy.
(LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
Can you leave
the war for one night?
I love you.
Do you hear me?
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(HORSES NEIGHING)
TORMUND: Most men
fuck like dogs.
(GRUNTING)
No grace, no skill.
A few dozen thrusts,
and done.
You need to be patient.
Give her time.
Your cock
shouldn't go near her
till she's slick
as a baby seal.
And then you go inside,
but slowly.
Don't jam it in like
you're spearing a pig.
(LAUGHS)
Come on!
(TORMUND LAUGHING)
Hey, come on.
ORELL: You think
he loves you, is that it?
What did he tell you?
He's gonna make you his lady
and live with you
in some castle?
No, he didn't
tell me anything.
He barely talks.
I've seen you two
whispering in the night,
giggling like a pair of girls.
What, you're jealous?
Of course I'm jealous.
You should be
with one of your own.
And you're one of my own?
I've never heard
a kind word from your mouth.
You would if you were mine.
I'd tell you that
you're beautiful
and fierce and wild.
I'd be good to you.
You love him?
'Cause he's pretty?
Is that it?
You like his pretty hair
and his pretty eyes?
You think pretty is
gonna make you happy?
Don't touch me.
You won't love him so much
when you find out
what he really is.
SANSA: Growing up
at Winterfell,
all I ever wanted
was to escape,
to come here
to the capital.
See the southern knights
and their painted armor
and King's Landing
after dark.
All the candles
burning in
all those windows.
I'm stupid.
A stupid little girl
with stupid dreams
who never learns.
Come on.
Come walk with me.
I remember the first time
I saw you in the throne room.
I'd never seen anyone
who looked so unhappy.
I want very much for
you to be happy, Sansa,
and so does my grandmother.
You would have been
happy at Highgarden,
but women in our position
must make the best
of our circumstances.
How do I make the best
of my circumstances?
I have to marry him.
Has Lord Tyrion
mistreated you?
No.
Has he been kind to you?
He's tried.
You don't want him,
though.
He's a Lannister.
Far from the worst Lannister,
wouldn't you say?
I'm sorry. Here I am
complaining to you...
My son will be king.
Sons learn from their
mothers. I plan to
teach mine a great deal.
And your son,
if I'm not mistaken,
your son might be
the Lord of Casterly Rock
and the North someday.
What?
My son...
With him.
I'll have to...
We'll have to...
If it's the pain
you're worried about...
I'm not afraid of the
pain. Not after what
Joffrey's done to me.
What is it, then?
He's rather good-looking,
even with the scar.
Especially with the scar.
He's a dwarf.
And Loras...
Loras.
Some women like tall men.
Some like short men.
Some like hairy men.
Some like bald men.
Gentle men, rough men,
ugly men, pretty men,
pretty girls.
Most women don't know
what they like
until they've tried it.
And, sadly, so many of us
get to try so little
before we're old and gray.
Tyrion may surprise you.
From what I've heard,
he's quite experienced.
And that's a good thing?
It can be.
We're very complicated,
you know.
Pleasing us takes practice.
How do you know all this?
Did your mother
teach you?
Yes, sweet girl.
My mother taught me.
TYRION: She's a child.
BRONN: She's a foot
taller than you.
A tall child.
What's the youngest
you've ever had?
Not that young.
How much older?
Older.
You're a lord, she's a lady.
And a beauty, at that.
I don't see the problem.
Shae isn't going
to like it.
Shae is a whore.
Are you gonna
marry her, eh?
How did marrying
a whore work out for you
the first time?
I should never have
told you about that.
You want Shae, keep her.
Wed one and bed the other.
All you have to do
is get a son in
the Stark girl.
He'll be Lord of
Winterfell one day.
You can rule
the North in his name.
You'll have two women
and a whole kingdom
of your own.
Two women to despise me
and a whole kingdom
to join them.
You waste time trying
to get people to love you,
you'll end up
the most popular
dead man in town.
(BRONN CHUCKLES)
You want to fuck
that Stark girl.
You just don't
want to admit it.
I don't pay you to put
evil notions in my head.
The ones already there
don't need company.
You pay me to kill
people who bother you.
Evil notions come free.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Your Grace.
Grandfather.
You wanted to
speak to me?
Yes.
I'd like
a report on the meetings
of my Small Council.
You're welcome to
attend the meetings
of your Small Council,
Your Grace.
Any or all of them.
I've been very busy.
Many important matters
require a king's attention.
Of course.
You've been holding
the council meetings
in the Tower of the Hand
instead of
the Small Council chamber.
I have, yes.
May I ask why?
Well, the Tower of the Hand
is where I work.
To walk from there to
here would take time,
time I could otherwise
spend productively.
So if I wanted to
attend a council meeting,
I would now have to
climb all the stairs in
the Tower of the Hand?
We could arrange
to have you carried.
Tell me about
the Targaryen girl in
the east and her dragons.
Where did you
hear about this?
Is it true?
Apparently so.
Don't you think we ought
to do something about it?
When I was Hand of
the King under your
father's predecessor,
the skulls of all
the Targaryen dragons
were kept in this room.
The skull of the last
of them was right here.
It was the size of an apple.
And the biggest was
the size of a carriage.
Yes, and the creature
to whom it belonged
died 300 years ago.
Curiosities on
the far side of the world
are no threat to us.
But how do we know
these dragons are
just curiosities
and not the beasts
that brought
the whole world to heel?
Because we have been told
as much by the many experts
who serve the realm
by counseling the King
on matters about
which he knows nothing.
But I haven't been counseled.
You are being counseled
at this very moment.
I should be consulted
about such things.
From now on,
I will see to it
that you are
appropriately consulted
on important matters
whenever necessary.
Your Grace.
Yunkai.
The Yellow City.
BARRISTAN: The Yunkish train
bed slaves, not soldiers.
We can defeat them.
On the field, with ease.
But they won't
meet us on the field.
They have provisions,
patience,
and strong walls.
If they're wise, they'll
hide behind those walls
and chip away at us,
man by man.
I don't want
half my army killed
before I've
crossed the Narrow Sea.
We don't need Yunkai,
Khaleesi.
Taking this city
will not bring you
any closer to Westeros
or the Iron Throne.
How many slaves
are there in Yunkai?
200,000, if not more.
Then we have 200,000
reasons to take the city.
(IN VALYRIAN)
(DRUMS BEATING)
Now comes the noble
Razdal mo Eraz
of that ancient
and honorable house,
Master of Men and
Speaker to Savages,
to offer terms of peace.
(DRAGONS SCREECHING)
Noble lord,
you are in the presence
of Daenerys Stormborn
of House Targaryen,
Queen of the Andals
and the First Men,
Khaleesi of
the Great Grass Sea,
Breaker of Chains,
and Mother of Dragons.
You may approach. Sit.
MISSANDEI: Will
the noble lord
take refreshment?
(WATER POURING)
Ancient and
glorious is Yunkai.
Our empire was old
before dragons stirred
in old Valyria.
Many an army has
broken against our walls.
You shall find
no easy conquest here,
Khaleesi.
DAENERYS: Good.
My Unsullied need
practice. I was told
to blood them early.
If blood is your desire,
blood shall flow.
But why?
'Tis true you have
committed savageries
in Astapor,
but the Yunkai
are a forgiving
and generous people.
The wise masters of
Yunkai have sent a gift
for the Silver Queen.
There is far more than
this awaiting you on
the deck of your ship.
My ship?
Yes, Khaleesi.
As I said,
we are a generous people.
You shall have as many
ships as you require.
And what do you
ask in return?
All we ask
is that you make
use of these ships.
Sail them back to Westeros
where you belong,
and leave us to conduct
our affairs in peace.
I have a gift
for you as well.
Your life.
My life?
And the lives of
your wise masters.
But I also want
something in return.
You will release
every slave in Yunkai.
Every man,
woman, and child
shall be given as much
food, clothing, and property
as they can carry
as payment for
their years of servitude.
Reject this gift,
and I shall show you
no mercy.
You are mad.
We are not Astapor or Qarth.
We are Yunkai, and
we have powerful friends.
Friends who would
take great pleasure
in destroying you.
Those who survive,
we shall enslave
once more.
Perhaps we'll make
a slave of you as well.
(SCREECHING)
You swore me safe conduct.
I did,
but my dragons
made no promises.
And you threatened
their mother.
Take the gold.
(DRAGONS SCREECHING)
My gold.
You gave it to me,
remember?
And I shall put
it to good use.
You'd be wise to do the same
with my gift to you.
Now get out.
(MUTTERING IN VALYRIAN)
The Yunkish are
a proud people.
They will not bend.
And what happens to
things that don't bend?
He said he had
powerful friends.
Who was he talking about?
I don't know.
Find out.
(SCREECHING)
SHAE: Chains?
Solid gold from the mines
outside Lannisport.
Smithed in Casterly Rock.
Golden chains.
You could buy
a ship with these.
Do I need a ship?
What?
Am I going somewhere?
Of course you're
not going anywhere.
So, am I invited
to your wedding?
I didn't ask for this
marriage. I didn't want it.
No? She's a beautiful girl.
You said so yourself.
That doesn't mean that...
This is duty, not desire.
Is that what you
will tell yourself
when you fuck her?
I don't have a choice.
My father...
Does not
rule the world.
We can still go
across the Narrow Sea.
What would I do there?
Juggle?
I am a Lannister
of Casterly Rock.
And I'm Shae
the funny whore.
My feelings for you
have not changed.
I will marry Sansa Stark
and do my duty by her.
While I empty her chamber
pot and lick your cock
when you're bored?
I swear to you,
it will not be like that.
No? What will it be like?
I will buy you a good home
somewhere in the city.
You will have fine
clothes, guards to keep
you safe, servants.
Any children we might have
will be well provided for.
Children?
You think I want children
who can never
see their father?
Who would be
killed in their sleep
if their grandfather
found out about them?
Listen. Listen to me,
my lady.
I'm not your lady.
You are.
You'll always be my lady.
I'm your whore.
And when you are
tired of fucking me,
I will be nothing.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
What happened?
Wildfire.
I should have
been here.
After all the running
and fighting,
here I am,
back where I started.
Do you miss it?
King's Landing?
Your father's house.
Never had a father.
Never wanted one.
Haven't you ever
wondered where your
strength came from?
Your talent for fighting?
I'm lowborn. As low as
can be. My mother
was a tavern wench.
Mine was a slave.
So was I.
Bought and sold,
scourged and branded,
until the Lord of Light
reached down,
took me in his hand,
and raised me up.
I was born
in Flea Bottom.
Your blood is noble.
Are you saying my father,
he was some lord or...
There.
Your father's house.
I'm just a bastard.
The bastard of Robert
of the House Baratheon,
First of His Name,
King of the Andals
and the First Men.
Why do you think
the gold cloaks wanted you?
There is power
in a king's blood.
Come sit by the fire, child.
Not talking, eh?
That's a first.
I don't talk to traitors.
I didn't like
giving up the boy.
But you did.
You took the gold
and you gave him up.
The Red God is
the one true god.
You've seen his power.
When he commands,
we obey.
He's not
my one true god.
No? Who's yours?
Death.
(MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
Spotted
a Lannister raiding party.
How many?
No more than 20.
How far?
Less than
a day's ride south.
What do you say, boys?
Time for a lion hunt?
ALL: Yeah!
But what about Riverrun?
It's not south.
It's west of here.
It will still be west of
here two days from now.
ARYA: You swore.
BERIC: To take
you home, and I will.
But we need to
do this first.
Why? So you can
steal their gold?
I swear to you,
this isn't...
I don't care what you swear
because you're a liar.
You lied to Gendry,
you lied to me.
You'll lie to anyone.
I hope the Lannisters
kill you all.
One day you'll understand,
but now...
Anguy, bring her back.
MAN: Come back, girl!
(PANTING)
(MEN CHATTERING IN DISTANCE)
(MUFFLED SCREAMS)
Kick all you like, wolf girl.
Won't do you no good.
(DOOR OPENING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
I thought you were gone.
Tomorrow.
Have they told you what
they plan to do with me?
Lord Bolton's traveling
tomorrow as well.
He's going to the Twins
for Edmure Tully's wedding.
You're to remain here.
With Locke?
I owe you a debt.
When Catelyn Stark
released you, we both
made a promise to her.
Now it's your promise.
You gave your word.
Keep it and
consider the debt paid.
I will return the Stark
girls to their mother.
I swear it.
Good-bye, Ser Jaime.
(DOOR OPENS)
(JAIME GRUNTING)
Here. Let me.
It will take time.
Qyburn hopes your
father will force
the Citadel to give him
back his chain.
My father will
make him grand maester
if he grows me a new hand.
You will give my regards
to Lord Tywin, I trust?
Tell Robb Stark
I'm sorry I couldn't
make his uncle's wedding.
The Lannisters
send their regards.
Safe journey, Kingslayer.
Nothing to say?
I liked you better before.
I don't remember chopping
your balls off, too.
Don't you worry about
your friend. We'll
take good care of her.
(THEON GASPS)
(THEON GRUNTING)
(WOMAN SHUSHING)
(MOANS)
Gentle, my lord.
(GASPING)
Gentle.
(PANTING)
(THEON COUGHING)
(WOMEN SHUSHING)
Myranda knows
what she's doing.
Let her.
She trained as a septa,
only...
(CHUCKLES)
She had other urges.
So did the septons,
only they lied about it.
Where is he?
VIOLET: Who, my lord?
There's no one here
but you, me, and Violet.
Please.
Don't you want us
to see it?
MYRANDA: Oh, come on.
Let us see it.
Everybody talks about it.
Who sent you?
Who sent us?
We sent ourselves,
Lord Greyjoy.
We heard so much about it.
Please.
Oh!
There it is.
Oh...
Do you think we're ugly?
He thinks we're ugly.
Well, he's been
through so much.
Look at his poor face.
Help me.
If he comes back...
We need to make
him feel better.
And how can we
make him feel better?
I have an idea.
VIOLET: Aw!
She's shy.
You know how they are,
these religious girls.
Maybe he doesn't
know how we are.
(MOANS)
I felt something.
Oh, Lord Greyjoy.
As good as they say?
Mmm.
(MYRANDA MOANING)
And why should you
get all the fun?
What?
You like her better?
Plenty there
for both of us.
I was here first.
(PANTING)
(HORN BLARING)
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Terrible timing.
But I was getting jealous.
Well?
Should we see this cock
everyone's always
going on about?
(GROANS)
Everyone knows
you love girls.
I bet you always thought
they loved you back.
(GRUNTING)
Your famous cock must be
very precious to you.
Would you say it's
your most precious part?
(WHIMPERING)
(WHISTLES)
(SOBBING) Please.
No. No! Mercy, please!
Please, mercy! Mercy!
This is mercy.
I'm not killing you.
Just making
a few alterations.
No! No! No! Please, no! No!
No! No, please! Please!
(WHISPERS) You're
gonna scare it off.
(WHISPERS) I'm
not gonna scare it.
I'm gonna kill it.
It's too far away.
YGRITTE: Is that a palace?
It's a windmill.
Windmill.
Who built it? Some king?
Just the men who
used to live here.
YGRITTE: They must have
been great builders,
stacking stones so high.
Winterfell has towers
three times that size.
"Oh, I'm Jon Snow and
I'm from Winterfell.
"My daddy was a fancy lord
"and I lived in a tower
that touched the clouds."
If you're impressed
by a windmill,
you'd be swooning
if you saw the Great Keep
at Winterfell.
What's swooning?
Fainting.
What's fainting?
When a girl sees
blood and collapses.
Why would a girl see
blood and collapse?
Well...
Not all girls are like you.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, girls see
more blood than boys.
Or do you like girls
who swoon, Jon Snow?
(GASPS) Oh, a spider!
Save me, Jon Snow.
My dress is made
of the purest silk
from Tralalalaleeday.
I'd like to see
you in a silk dress.
Would you?
So I could tear it off you.
Well, you rip
my pretty silk dress,
I'll blacken your eye.
Maybe one day I'll
take you to Winterfell.
Or maybe one day
I'll take you there.
After we've
taken our land back.
Ygritte.
You won't win.
I know your people are brave,
no one denies that.
You know nothing...
Six times in
the last thousand years,
a King-beyond-the-Wall
has attacked the kingdoms.
Six times they failed.
And how do you know that?
Every boy in
the North knows it.
We grow up learning it.
Where the battles
were fought, the heroes,
who died where.
Six times you've invaded
and six times you've failed.
The seventh
will be the same.
Mance is different.
You don't have
the discipline.
You don't have the training.
Your army is no army.
You don't know how
to fight together.
You don't know that.
I do.
I know it.
If you attack the Wall,
you'll die. All of you.
All of us.
You're mine as I'm yours.
And if we die, we die.
But first we'll live.
Yes, first we'll live.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
What's he
going on about?
And how come he
always gets to sit and chat
while we do all the work?
Hodor.
That's where we are.
What are
you telling him?
It's all right, Osha.
It's not all right.
You think I can't
hear you every day?
Filling his head
with black magic.
Talking about visions
and three-eyed
ravens and worse.
Leave him alone.
He can speak for himself.
I don't fill his
head with anything.
OSHA: So, what
do you talk about?
What's happening to him
and what that means.
Go on, then.
Tell us what it means.
It's not like that.
I wish I could tell
him all the answers.
It would be much easier.
I don't want you
talking to him anymore.
Until we get to your
brother at Castle Black.
We're not going
to Castle Black.
What did you say?
I told you already.
Jon Snow isn't there.
Bran needs to find
the raven beyond the Wall.
Oh, no. I'm not
going back there.
Your brother is
at Castle Black.
That's where we're going.
Look at me.
The raven's been coming
to me ever since I fell
from that tower.
He wants me to find him.
I don't have my legs anymore.
This is what I have now.
You have a family.
You need to go
back to Castle Black
so you can get back to
them, where you belong.
What if I belong
in the North?
What if I fell from
that tower for a reason?
Is that what he's
telling you? That
it's all for a reason?
All these bad things
happened because the Gods
got big plans for you?
I wish it were true,
little lord.
But the Gods wouldn't spare
a raven's cold shit
for you or me or anyone.
You don't understand.
You don't know.
None of you know.
None of you
have been up there.
I had a man once.
A good man.
Bruni, his name was.
I was his and he was mine.
But one night
Bruni disappears.
People said he left me,
but I knew him.
He'd never leave me.
Not for long.
I knew he'd come back.
And he did.
He came in through
the back of the hut.
Only it wasn't Bruni.
Not really.
His skin was pale
like a dead man's.
His eyes bluer
than clear sky.
He came at me,
grabbed me by the neck
and squeezed so hard
I could feel
the life slipping out of me.
I don't know how
I got the knife.
When I did, I stuck it
deep into his heart.
And he hardly
seemed to notice.
I had to burn our hut
down with him inside.
I didn't ask
the Gods what it meant.
I didn't need to.
I already knew.
It meant the North was
no place for men to be.
Not anymore.
I promised your maester
I'd get you to Castle
Black and no further.
QYBURN: How is
the pain, my lord?
What's the purpose of
an arm with no hand?
Well, we've stymied
the corruption.
Yes, we've stymied
You're a learned man.
All the good
it's done me.
You did well
sewing up this mess.
You're far better
at this sort of work
than Grand Maester Pycelle.
Faint praise, my lord.
So, why did the Citadel
take your chain?
Did you fondle
one boy too many?
No, my lord.
That's not my weakness.
What is?
Curiosity.
The only way to treat disease
is to understand disease,
and the only way
to understand it
is to study the afflicted.
You performed experiments
on living men.
On dying men.
With their permission?
My studies have
given me insight
that has saved many lives.
Dying paupers, I assume.
Men with no families
to complain.
You found them
moaning in the poorhouse
and had them carted
back to your garret
and opened up their bellies
to see what was inside.
How many men have
you killed, my lord?
I don't know.
50?
100?
Countless.
"Countless" has
a nice ring to it.
And how many
lives have you saved?
Half a million.
The population
of King's Landing.
You were in charge of
the ravens at Harrenhal.
Did you... Did you
get a bird off to
Brienne's father in Tarth?
A bird flew off
and a bird flew back.
Lord Selwyn Tarth
offered 300 gold dragons
for his daughter's
safe return.
A fair offer.
Locke won't take it.
Why not?
He's convinced Lord Tarth
owns all the sapphire
mines in Westeros.
(SIGHS)
He feels
he's being cheated.
They'd be fools
to kill her.
These men have been
at war a long time.
Most of them will
be dead by winter.
She'll be their
entertainment tonight.
Beyond tonight,
I don't think
they care very much.
(HORSE NEIGHING)
We have to
return to Harrenhal.
Why?
I've left something behind.
Absolutely not.
I've got orders
from Lord Bolton.
And what are those orders?
To deliver you
to your father
at King's Landing.
You think
you'll get a reward.
I serve Lord Bolton.
Any appreciation
your father...
You think
you're getting a reward.
Let me explain
something to you.
When my father sees me,
the first thing
he's going to ask
is what happened to my hand,
and I'm going to tell him
this man chopped it off.
I had nothing...
Or I could tell him
this man saved my life.
We return to
Harrenhal. Now.
Eyes open, lads.
Be quiet.
(MEN SINGING)
♪ The bear, the bear,
and the maiden fair
♪ From there to here,
from here to there
♪ All black and brown
and covered in hair
♪ He smelled that girl
in the summer air
♪ The bear, the bear,
and the maiden fair ♪
(ALL CHEERING)
MAN: Don't spare her.
Don't spare her!
(GRUNTS)
(ROARING)
Well, this is one shameful
fucking performance.
Stop running and fight.
(BEAR GROWLING)
A wooden sword?
I thought you'd gone.
You gave her a wooden sword!
We've only got one bear.
I'll pay
her bloody ransom.
Gold, sapphires,
whatever you want. Just
get her out of there.
All you lords and ladies
still think that
the only thing
that matters is gold.
This makes me happier
than all your gold
ever could.
And that makes me happier
than all her sapphires.
So go buy
yourself a golden hand
and fuck yourself with it!
(ALL CHEERING)
(GROWLING)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
(ROARING)
Get behind me.
I will not.
(GRUNTING)
What the fuck are
you doing to my bear?
Lord Bolton charged me
with bringing him back
to King's Landing alive,
and that's
what I aim to do.
Pull her up!
(GRUNTING)
Hold my legs.
(GRUNTS)
Pull him up!
(MEN JEERING)
(PANTING)
The bitch stays.
We're taking her
to King's Landing.
Unless you kill me.
She belongs to me.
Lord Bolton's orders.
JAIME: What do you
think is more important
to Lord Bolton?
Getting his pet rat
a reward
or ensuring Tywin Lannister
gets his son back alive?
(BEAR ROARING)
Well, we must be on our way.
Sorry about the sapphires.
(BEAR ROARING)