CATELYN: Are you
sure about this?
No.
It's dangerous.
If we take
Tywin's castle from him,
the lords of Westeros
will realize
he's not invincible.
Take his home, take
his gold, take his power.
Why are you telling me?
You begged me
not to send Theon
to negotiate with his father,
and I ignored your advice.
Now Winterfell is
burnt to the ground,
the North is overrun
with ironborn, and
Bran and Rickon are gone.
So, Casterly Rock...
I'm asking your advice.
We have enough men?
If Walder Frey cooperates.
If reinforcements
arrive from King's Landing
before we take the castle,
we'll be caught between
Tywin's army and the sea.
We'll lose the war and
die the way Father died.
Or worse.
Show them how it feels
to lose what they love.
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(SOLDIERS URGING HORSES)
WALDER: My honored guests,
be welcome within my
walls and at my table.
I extend to you
my hospitality
and protection in
the light of the Seven.
We thank you for your
hospitality, my lord.
I have come to make
my apologies, my lord,
and to beg your forgiveness.
Don't beg my forgiveness,
Your Grace.
It wasn't me you spurned.
It was my girls.
One of them was
supposed to be queen.
Now none of them are.
This is Arwyn,
my daughter.
My daughter Walda,
my daughter Derwa,
my daughter Waldra.
My eldest granddaughters
Ginia and Neila.
Serra and Sarra,
granddaughters, twins.
You could have had either.
Could have had both,
for all I care.
My granddaughter
Marianne.
Freya.
My granddaughter...
Wertha.
Waldra.
Waldina.
I'm Merry.
Fine.
And here's my
youngest daughter Shirei,
though she hasn't
bled yet.
Clearly you don't have
the patience for all that.
My ladies.
All men should
keep their word,
kings most of all.
I was pledged to
marry one of you
and I broke that vow.
The fault is not with you.
Any man would be lucky
to have any one of you.
I did what I did
not to slight you,
but because I loved another.
I know these words
cannot set right
the wrong I have done
to you and your house.
I beg your forgiveness
and pledge to do
all I can to make amends
so the Freys of the Crossing
and the Starks of Winterfell
may once again be friends.
WALDER: Very good.
There she is.
Come closer.
Let me have a look at you.
Still can't see you.
Old eyes.
Love.
That's what the Starks
of Winterfell call it, eh?
(LAUGHS)
Very honorable.
I call it a pretty face.
Mmm.
Very pretty.
Prettier than this lot,
that's for sure.
Very shapely as well.
Oh, you try to hide her
under that dress.
If you wanted to hide her,
you shouldn't have
brought her here
in the first place.
I can always see
what's going on
beneath a dress.
Been at this
a long time.
I bet when you
take that dress off,
everything stays
right where it is.
Doesn't drop an inch.
Your king says
he betrayed me for love.
I say he betrayed
me for firm tits
and a tight fit.
And I can respect that.
When I was your age,
I'd have broken 50 oaths
to get into that
without a second thought.
Well, I've enough room
in the hall for you lot.
We'll set up tents outside
with food and ale for
the rest of your men.
Thank you, my lord.
Well, let's get ready.
The wine will flow red
and the music
will play loud
and we'll put
this mess behind us.
(METALLIC CLANGING)
Where?
There.
There. It's a back gate.
My men use it
when they visit
Yunkai's bed slaves.
Your men, but not you?
DAARIO: I have
no interest in slaves.
A man cannot
make love to property.
This is where we enter
the city. Very few
guards. They know me.
They let me inside...
We're not gonna
sneak an army
through a back gate.
DAARIO: I kill the guards.
I take your two best men
and lead them
through the back streets,
which I know well,
and open the front gates.
Then comes the army.
Once the walls are breached,
the city will fall in hours.
Or perhaps
you'll lead Grey Worm
and me to the slaughter,
cutting the head
off our army.
The masters of Yunkai
will pay you your fee
and you won't have
to split it three ways
'cause you've already
slaughtered your partners.
You have a very
suspicious mind.
In my experience,
only dishonest people
think this way.
(SIGHS) You command
the Unsullied.
What do you think?
(DAENERYS SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
(IN VALYRIAN)
You leave tonight.
Very good.
We'll prepare.
Ser Jorah.
You can use an extra sword.
You're the Queensguard,
Ser Barristan.
Your place is by the Queen.
If we are truly
her loyal servants,
we'll do whatever
needs to be done,
no matter the cost,
no matter our pride.
(WIND HOWLING)
SAMWELL: We're west
of Castle Black,
but the Nightfort's
closest to us.
It was the first castle
on the Wall.
The Watch abandoned it
during the reign
of King Jaehaerys I.
Too big.
Impossible to maintain.
Other than
Castle Black itself,
the Nightfort's
the perfect castle for us.
It's got a secret sally port,
the Black Gate,
as old as the Wall itself.
No one's used it
in centuries, most likely.
It leads through
the Wall right down
into the Nightfort,
if one knows how to find it,
which, it just so happens,
(CHUCKLES) I do.
How do you know all that?
I read about it
in a very old book.
You know all that
from staring at
marks on paper?
Yes.
You're like a wizard.
(GURGLES)
Our father used to tell us
that no wildling ever looked
upon the Wall and lived.
Here we are.
Alive.
(DONKEY BRAYING)
Remember what happens
to children who run.
I'm your father and
I'll do the talking.
The roads have
gone right to hell.
Cracked three
spokes this morning.
Need a hand?
Need about eight hands.
Oh!
Got to get this
salt pork to the Twins
in time for the wedding.
Many thanks.
(GROANS)
Don't! Don't kill him.
Dead rats don't squeak.
You're so dangerous,
aren't you?
Saying scary things
to little girls.
Killing little
boys and old people.
A real hard man you are.
More than anyone
you know.
You're wrong.
I know a killer.
A real killer.
That so?
You'd be like a kitten
to him. He'd kill you
with his little finger.
That him?
No.
Good.
(GRUNTS) Don't kill him.
Please.
Please don't.
You're very kind.
Someday it'll
get you killed.
(MAN GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
Where are we?
The Gift, I think.
Brandon the Builder
gave all this land
south of the Wall
to the Night's Watch
for their sustenance
and support.
Maester Luwin taught me that.
Doesn't seem to be supporting
anyone at the moment.
It's good land,
and there's
no war up here.
Why leave?
Wildlings.
Sorry.
But they come over
the Wall and raid,
steal, carry off women.
Old Nan said they turn
your skull into a cup
and make you drink
your own blood from it.
That's what Old Nan said.
There's a storm coming.
I don't see any.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
It's as good
a place to
shelter as any.
We can drink some
blood while we wait.
I don't need much.
(CAWING)
(PANTING) Only one old man
and eight good horses.
What's one old man
doing with eight horses?
He breeds them
for the Watch.
How's he keep folks
from stealing them?
The Watch protects him.
ORELL: Not today, they don't.
He's selling horses,
he's got some gold in there.
TORMUND: And proper steel.
ORELL: Let's carve him up.
We just take
the horses and go.
The old man's no threat.
I keep telling you.
He's an old man.
A spear through the heart's
a better way to die
than coughing up your
last with no one but
your horses to hear.
The Watch might send
a few men looking
for a horse thief.
They'll send a lot more
to hunt down murderers.
I hope so.
Killing crows in
their castle is tough.
Killing them out
here in the open,
that's what we do.
Spread out.
Surround the hut
and move in.
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(SNUFFLES)
(HORSES NEIGHING)
Ygritte!
TORMUND: Clear the barn!
No one's going to believe
you're a hog farmer
if you eat them all.
Best part of the animal.
Don't worry.
They're still there.
I know they're still there.
You check every five minutes
like you're afraid
they're gonna move.
I'm not afraid.
Of course you are.
You're almost there
and you're afraid
you won't make it.
The closer you get,
the worse the fear gets.
No point in trying to
hide behind that face.
I know fear when I see it.
Seen it a lot.
I knew fear
when I saw it in you.
You're afraid of fire.
When Beric's sword
went up in flames,
you looked like
a scared little girl.
And I know why, too.
I heard what your
brother did to you.
Pressed your face to
the fire like you're
a nice juicy mutton chop.
That give you some ideas?
Might do.
Go ahead, then.
You might get away.
Might even make it
there on your own.
They're just over the river.
The closest
you've been to family
since Ilyn Payne
snipped your daddy's neck.
Someday I'll put
a sword through
your eye and out
the back of your skull.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
How are we going to
get past the Wall?
My uncle said
it's 700 feet high.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
How did you get past it?
Got in a boat and rowed
past the Bay of Seals.
It would take us two months
to get to the Bay of Seals.
Some climb
straight up the ice.
Even Hodor's not
strong enough to
climb the Wall
with me on his back.
HODOR: Hodor.
Nineteen castles
guard the Wall.
Only three
are still manned.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
Hodor!
One of those
abandoned fortresses
will give us a way through.
My uncle said
the gates were
sealed with ice
and stone when
the castles were deserted.
Well, we'll have to
open them up again.
(HORSE NEIGHING)
OLD MAN: Whoa, whoa, whoa!
MEERA: There's
a rider out there.
Just one?
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
MEERA: There's more.
Hodor!
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(WHIMPERING)
It's just thunder,
sweet giant.
Hodor.
OLD MAN: I yield.
I yield.
Wildlings.
(MEN SHOUTING)
Where's Shaggydog
and Summer?
Hunting.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Hodor!
Shh. Quiet, Hodor.
Make him shut up.
If they hear us...
Hush, Hodor.
No... No more Hodoring.
Hodor! (GRUNTS)
Hodor!
Hodor, calm down.
You need to keep quiet.
They're gonna hear us.
BRANDON: Hodor, be quiet.
Hodor!
Hodor, calm down.
Hodor! Hodor!
Hodor, be quiet!
What did you do?
Nothing.
I don't know.
(HORSE GROANING)
What's that?
That's a horse dying.
(EXHALES)
MAN 1: Bring them over here.
MAN 2: That was
the last of them.
The rest are dead.
ORELL: I heard
shouting up there.
Thunder.
I know the difference
between shouting and thunder.
Maybe it's ghosts.
(LAUGHS)
(RAVEN CAWING)
That won't help you,
grandpa.
Where you riding?
Doesn't matter now, does it?
No, it doesn't matter now.
Cut his throat,
or he'll tell
the crows we're here.
You understand.
Let me stand at least.
Let me go with
a bit of dignity.
(GRUNTS)
Make the crow kill him.
You're one of us now.
Prove it.
JOJEN: The wolves
are out there.
I can't do it by choice.
I don't know how.
It happens in my dreams.
You're a warg, Bran.
It's in your blood.
I can't.
You just did, with him.
A wolf is nothing
compared to that.
(WHIMPERS)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
She looks sharp.
(PRAYING INDISTINCTLY)
Do it.
I told you.
He's still one of them.
Go on, boy.
Go on!
(GRUNTS)
(EXHALES)
He's a crow.
He'll always be a crow.
And here's his crow
wife guarding him.
He'll stab us in the back
first chance he gets.
Kill him.
(GRUNTS)
(JON YELLING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
(YGRITTE YELLING)
He's one of them.
No!
Do you hear me? Ahh!
(YGRITTE PANTING)
You're not gonna
die for one of them.
Do it.
They'll find us
if you don't.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SNARLS)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
(YELLS)
(BONES CRUNCHING)
(GROANING)
You were right
the whole time.
(STABBING)
(GASPS)
(CAWING)
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTING)
(URGES HORSE)
(PANTING)
DAARIO: When you hear
a songbird's whistle,
you come.
I'm a great whistler.
The greatest in the land.
(GUARD SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
Daario Naharis.
(DAARIO WHISTLES)
DAARIO: That one was quick.
There may be others.
I doubt it.
The Yunkish prefer
to let their slaves do
their fighting for them.
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
JORAH: That's what
you call a few guards?
(SIGHS)
(ALL SHOUTING)
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING)
Come on! What do
you got, huh?
(ALL CHEERING)
(SIGHS)
Lord Edmure,
I hope I'm not
a disappointment to you.
(HUFFS)
You're a delight
to me, my lady.
You may now cloak
the bride and bring her
under your protection.
In the sight of the Seven,
I hereby seal
these two souls,
binding them as one
for eternity.
Look upon each other
and say the words.
Father, Smith...
...Warrior, Mother...
...Maiden, Crone, Stranger.
I am hers...
I am his...
...and she is mine...
...and he is mine...
BOTH: ...from this day
until the end of my days.
MEERA: Is that safe?
OSHA: They're long gone.
BRANDON: You were right.
I can get inside
Summer's mind
whenever I want.
Of course you can.
North of the Wall
there are wildlings
who can control
all sorts of animals.
But you did
a lot more than that.
You got inside Hodor's mind.
They can't do that
north of the Wall?
No one can do that.
Anywhere.
When I was looking
through Summer's eyes,
I saw Jon.
Where?
He was with the wildlings.
They tried to kill him,
but he got away.
OSHA: He'll be heading back
to Castle Black, then.
That's where we should go.
For all we know,
Castle Black's
already under attack.
If this many
wildlings got through...
I already told you.
I'm not going
north of the Wall.
Everything Jojen
told me is true.
You saw
what I did to Hodor.
I have to find
the three-eyed raven.
Listen to me,
little lord.
Don't worry.
I'm not asking you
to come with me.
It won't be safe for Rickon.
Me? I'm coming with you.
No.
You and Osha and Shaggydog
head for the Last Hearth.
The Umbers are our bannermen.
They'll protect you.
I'm coming with you.
I'm your brother.
I have to protect you.
Right now I have
to protect you.
Robb's at war and
I'm going beyond the Wall.
If something happens to us,
you're the heir to Winterfell.
Would you know how to
find the Last Hearth?
You Southerners
build your big castles
and you never move.
You're easy to find.
We're not Southerners.
And I don't want
to leave you.
OSHA: Shh!
Come here,
little soldier.
You and me,
we're gonna have
some adventures.
You don't have
to do any of this.
(SOBBING)
Your family took me in
and was good to me
without cause.
(OSHA SHUSHING)
We'll be fine,
you and me.
The Umbers are great
warriors. Even I heard
about them growing up.
They'll teach you
how to swing a sword.
I know how to
swing a sword.
You're leaving now?
It's the middle
of the night.
I learned to
walk in darkness.
Say your good-byes,
little man.
Keep this one safe.
He means the world to me.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
We've been
waiting a long time.
Haven't we?
Well, I don't know,
you tell me.
How long does it take
to sack a city?
It was just as you said.
They did not believe
until it was too late.
Their slave soldiers
threw down their
spears and surrendered.
And Daario Naharis?
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
The city is yours, my queen.
(PLAYING LIVELY MUSIC)
(GUESTS CHATTERING)
They're good,
aren't they?
They ought to be
because they cost enough.
(LAUGHS)
(LAUGHING)
Look at the crowd there.
(CATELYN LAUGHING)
He complained
about this marriage
the entire ride
from Riverrun,
and now look at him.
BLACKFISH: The Gods
love to reward a fool.
(CHUCKLES) Uncle.
What?
He's my nephew. I love him.
And he's a damned fool.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
Don't you drink,
Lord Bolton?
Never do, my lady.
Dulls the senses.
BLACKFISH:
That's the point.
Didn't you marry one
of these Frey girls?
Aye. Lord Walder
let me choose any
of his granddaughters
and promised me
the girl's weight
in silver as a dowry.
So I have a fat young bride.
(LAUGHING)
I hope she makes
you very happy.
Well, she's made me
very rich.
Pardon, my lord,
my lady. I need to
find a tree to piss on.
My mother's alone
with Roose Bolton.
I should rescue her.
Your mother is less
in need of rescue than
any woman I've ever met.
Be kind. She's finally
starting to like you.
And I like her.
But if she had her way,
I would be back in Volantis
playing my harp
and you would be
sitting over there,
eating blackberries out
of Roslin Frey's hand.
Perhaps I've made
a terrible mistake.
(GASPS)
Striking your king
is an act of treason.
No, don't.
Don't insult them.
Your Grace.
(KNOCKING ON TABLES)
(MUSIC STOPS)
The septon has
prayed his prayers,
some words were said,
and Lord Edmure
has wrapped my daughter
in a cloak.
But they are not
yet man and wife.
A sword needs a sheath.
(ALL LAUGHING)
And a wedding
needs a bedding.
(ALL CHEERING)
What does my sire say?
ALL: (CHANTING)
To bed! To bed! To bed!
If you think
the time is right,
Lord Walder, by all means,
let us bed them.
(ALL CHEERING)
(BAND PLAYING UPBEAT MUSIC)
ALL: (CHANTING)
To bed! To bed! To bed!
MAN: Go on.
(MEN LAUGHING)
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
Ho-ho!
Careful now, ladies.
Once you set
that monster free,
there's no caging him
again. (LAUGHS)
ALL: (CHANTING)
To bed! To bed! To bed!
Poor girl.
Every bride
suffers the same.
I'm sure you endured
yours with grace.
Oh, Ned forbade it.
He said it wouldn't be right
if he broke a man's jaw
on our wedding night.
(CHUCKLES)
That is a very
strange custom.
I suppose it does
seem strange from
a foreigner's perspective.
It seems
normal to you?
It's a tradition.
Without the bedding ceremony,
there's no real proof
the lord and lady
consummated their marriage.
No, but there
are other ways
of providing proof.
Boy or girl?
I don't know.
But if it's a boy,
I know what
we should name him.
Oh, do you?
It seems to me the father
should have some say
in his son's naming.
Eddard.
Don't you want to
teach little Ned Stark
how to ride horses?
I do.
(MUSIC STOPS)
(BAND PLAYING
THE RAINS OF CASTAMERE)
(GREY WIND WHINING)
(WHIMPERING)
MAN: Go on, line 'em up!
(THE RAINS OF CASTAMERE
CONTINUES PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(MEN LAUGHING)
HOUND: Whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where are you going?
Got salt pork
for the feast.
The feast is over.
HOUND: Doesn't
sound like it's over.
If I tell you
it's over, it's over.
Turn this cart around
and get the hell
out of here.
HOUND: Got pig's feet, too.
Are you soft in the head?
Turn this cart around.
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(MUSIC STOPS)
Your Grace.
I feel I've been
remiss in my duties.
I've given you meat
and wine and music,
but I haven't shown you
the hospitality you deserve.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
My king has married
and I owe my new
queen a wedding gift.
(GASPS)
Robb!
(GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
(ALL GROANING)
(SCREAMING IN PAIN)
(GROANS)
Ohh!
(MEN SHOUTING)
Ahh!
(STARK SOLDIERS SCREAMING)
(SCREAMS)
(NEIGHING)
MAN 1: (LAUGHING)
You ready to head home
to Winterfell, eh?
(MEN LAUGHING)
MAN 2: Feast over yet, is it?
Aye, it's over.
(GROANING)
(STARK SOLDIERS GROANING)
(GREY WIND WHINING)
(BANGING)
(GREY WIND GROWLING)
Aim!
(GROWLING)
(GREY WIND YOWLS)
(GROANS)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(PANTING)
(GASPS)
It's too late.
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
(STRAINING)
The King in the North arises.
(GRUNTS)
(WALDER CHUCKLES)
Lord Walder!
Lord Walder, enough!
Let it end!
Please. He is my son.
My first son.
Let him go,
and I swear that
we will forget this.
I swear it by
the Old Gods and New.
We will take no vengeance.
You already swore me
one oath right here
in my castle.
You swore by all the Gods
your son would
marry my daughter!
CATELYN: Take me
for a hostage,
but let Robb go.
Robb, get up.
Get up and walk out.
Please!
And why would
I let him do that?
On my honor as a Tully,
on my honor as a Stark,
let him go,
or I will cut
your wife's throat.
I'll find another.
Mother.
The Lannisters
send their regards.
(STABBING)
(GROANS)
(WAILING)
(THUDS)