(SOLDIERS SHOUTING)
(SWORDS CLASHING)
(SOLDIERS CONTINUE SHOUTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(SCREAMS)
(URGING HORSE)
MAN 1: Go, move out!
SOLDIERS: (CHANTING)
Here comes
the King in the North!
The King in the North!
Here comes
the King in the North!
The King in the North!
Here comes
the King in the North!
MAN 2: Here comes
SOLDIERS: (CHANTING)
Here comes
the King in the North!
The King in the North!
Here comes
the King in the North!
(ALL CHEERING)
(MEN TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Ser Eldrick Sarsfield
and Lord Desmond Crakehall.
What are you doing?
I have a list.
A list of people
you mean to kill?
For laughing at me?
Do I look like
Joffrey to you?
No, death seems
a bit extreme.
Fear of death,
on the other hand...
You should learn
to ignore them.
My lady, people have
been laughing at me
far longer than
they've been laughing at you.
I'm the halfman,
the Demon Monkey, the Imp.
You're a Lannister.
I am the disgraced daughter
of the traitor Ned Stark.
The disgraced daughter
and the Demon Monkey.
We're perfect
for each other.
(CHUCKLES)
So how should
we punish them?
Who? Whom?
Ser Eldrick Sarsfield
and Lord Desmond Crakehall.
Ah!
I could speak to Lord Varys
and learn their perversions.
Anyone named
Desmond Crakehall
must be a pervert.
I hear that
you're a pervert.
I am the Imp.
I have certain
standards to maintain.
(CHUCKLES)
We could sheep shift
Lord Desmond's bed.
You cut a little hole
in his mattress
and you stuff
sheep dung inside.
Then you sew up the hole
and make his bed again.
His room will stink,
but he won't know
where it's coming from.
Lady Sansa!
My sister used to do that
when she was angry with me.
And she was
always angry with me.
Why "sheep shift"?
That's the vulgar
word for "dung."
My lady...
Well, you asked me.
(BOTH EXCLAIMING)
That's him!
My lord, my lady.
Your father has called
a meeting of
the Small Council.
Killed
a few puppies today?
Show him.
Come on, show him.
PYCELLE: Oh!
Apologies, my lord.
Old fingers.
"Roslin caught
a fine fat trout.
"Her brothers gave her
a pair of wolf pelts
for her wedding."
Signed, "Walder Frey."
Is that bad poetry
or is it supposed
to mean something?
Robb Stark is dead.
(LAUGHING)
And his bitch mother.
Write back to Lord Frey.
Thank him for his
service and command him
to send Robb Stark's head.
I'm going to
serve it to Sansa
at my wedding feast.
Your Grace, Lady Sansa
is your aunt by marriage.
A joke.
Joffrey did not mean it.
Yes, I did.
I'm going to have it
served to Sansa
at my wedding feast.
TYRION: No.
She is no longer
yours to torment.
Everyone is mine to torment.
You'd do well
to remember that,
you little monster.
Oh, I'm a monster.
Perhaps you should speak
to me more softly, then.
Monsters are dangerous,
and just now kings
are dying like flies.
I could have your
tongue out for saying that.
Let him make his threats.
Hmm?
He's a bitter little man.
Lord Tyrion should
apologize immediately.
Unacceptable, disrespectful,
and in very bad taste.
I am the King!
I will punish you.
Any man who must say,
"I am the King,"
is no true king.
I'll make sure
you understand that
when I've won
your war for you.
My father won the real war.
He killed Prince Rhaegar.
He took the crown
while you hid
under Casterly Rock!
The King is tired.
See him to his chambers.
Come along.
I'm not tired.
We have so much
to celebrate.
A wedding to plan.
You must rest.
Grand Maester,
perhaps some
essence of nightshade
to help him sleep.
I'm not tired!
CERSEI: Come.
(DOOR OPENING)
Not you.
You just sent
the most powerful man
in Westeros to bed
without his supper.
You're a fool if you
believe he's the most
powerful man in Westeros.
A treasonous statement.
Joffrey is King.
You really think
a crown gives you power?
No.
I think armies
give you power.
Mmm-hmm.
Robb Stark had one,
never lost a battle,
and you defeated him
all the same.
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, I know.
Walder Frey gets
all the credit.
Or the blame, I suppose,
depending on
your allegiance.
Walder Frey
is many things,
but a brave man?
No.
He never would have
risked such an action
if he didn't have
certain assurances.
Which he got from me.
Do you disapprove?
I'm all for cheating.
This is war.
But to slaughter them
at a wedding...
Explain to me
why it is more noble
to kill 10,000 men in battle
than a dozen at dinner.
So that's why you did it?
To save lives?
To end the war.
To protect the family.
Do you want to write a song
for the dead Starks?
Go ahead, write one.
I'm in this world
a little while longer
to defend the Lannisters,
to defend my blood.
The Northerners
will never forget.
Good.
Let them remember
what happens when
they march on the South.
All the Stark men are dead.
Winterfell is a ruin.
Roose Bolton will be named
Warden of the North
until your son by Sansa
comes of age.
I believe you
still have some work
to do on that score.
Do you think she'll
open her legs for me
after I tell her
how we murdered her
mother and brother?
One way or another,
you will get
that girl pregnant.
I will not rape her.
Shall I explain to you
in one easy lesson
how the world works?
Use small words.
I'm not as bright as you.
The house that
puts family first
will always defeat
the house that puts
the whims and wishes
of its sons and
daughters first.
A good man does
everything in his power
to better
his family's position,
regardless of
his own selfish desires.
Does that amuse you?
No, it's a very good lesson.
Only it's easy for you
to preach utter
devotion to family
when you're making
all the decisions.
Easy for me, is it?
When have you ever
done something that
wasn't in your interest,
but solely for
the benefit of the family?
The day that you were born.
I wanted to carry you
into the sea
and let the waves
wash you away.
Instead, I let you live.
And I brought
you up as my son.
Because you're a Lannister.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Sansa.
It's empty.
Let's find
a place to sleep.
Hodor.
(ECHOING)
Don't, Hodor.
BRANDON: Maybe
we shouldn't stay here.
You'd rather be out there?
There are a lot of
stories about this place.
Horrible stories.
I always quite liked
the horrible stories.
So did I. Once.
You ever heard
about the Rat Cook?
No. Who's he?
Just a cook in
the Night's Watch.
He was angry at
the King for something,
I don't remember.
When the King was
visiting the Nightfort,
the cook killed
the King's son,
cooked him into a big pie
with onions, carrots,
mushrooms, and bacon.
That night he served
the pie to the King.
He liked the taste
of his son so much,
he asked for a second slice.
The Gods turned the cook
into a giant white rat
who could only
eat his own young.
He's been roaming
the Nightfort ever since,
devouring his own babies.
But no matter what he does,
he's always hungry.
If the Gods
turned every killer
into a giant white rat...
It wasn't for murder
the Gods cursed the Rat Cook
or for serving
the King's son in a pie.
He killed a guest
beneath his roof.
That's something
the Gods can't forgive.
"The late Walder Frey,"
old Tully called me
because I didn't get
my men to the Trident
in time for battle.
He thought he was witty.
Look at us now, Tully.
You're dead,
your daughter's dead,
your grandson's dead,
your son spent
his wedding night
in a dungeon,
and I'm Lord of Riverrun.
(LAUGHING)
The Blackfish escaped.
An old man on the run
with no allies.
I have Tywin Lannister
backing me.
Who does he have?
As you say.
They all laughed at me,
all those high lords.
They all thought they
were better than me.
Ned Stark, Hoster Tully.
People snigger when
I marry a young girl,
but who said a word
when Jon Arryn married
the little Tully bitch?
You'll be needing
a new young girl.
Yeah.
Got that to look forward to.
Hmm.
And you,
the Warden of the North.
No more Starks to
bow and scrape to.
Must have been torture
following that stupid boy
all over the country.
He ignored my
advice at every turn.
If he'd been
a trifle less arrogant...
Calling himself
the "Young Wolf."
How's that for pomposity?
(WALDER CHUCKLES)
Well, here's to
the Young Wolf!
(HOWLS)
Forever young.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Will you move to Winterfell
now that the war's over?
At some point perhaps.
But Winterfell's in ruins.
Yeah.
What happened up there?
I heard the Greyjoy boy
seized the place.
I heard he
killed all the ravens.
And after that, nothing.
I sent my bastard
Ramsay to root him out.
Robb Stark offered
amnesty for the ironborn
if they gave us Theon.
Oh. And?
Ramsay delivered the terms.
The ironborn turned on Theon,
as we knew they would.
They handed him over
trussed and hooded.
But Ramsay, well...
Ramsay has his own
way of doing things.
Well, the girls weren't
lying. You had
a good-sized cock.
What?
No.
Pork sausage.
(LAUGHS)
You think I'm
some sort of savage?
People talk
about phantom limbs.
An amputee might
have an itch where
his foot used to be.
So I've always wondered,
do eunuchs have
a phantom cock?
Next time you think
about naked girls,
will you feel an itch?
(WEEPING)
Sorry.
I shouldn't make jokes.
My mother taught me
not to throw
stones at cripples.
(WHIMPERING)
But my father taught me
to aim for their head.
(SOFTLY) Kill me.
Sorry, what?
Kill me.
A little louder.
Kill me!
You're no good to me dead.
We need you.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
You don't look like
a Theon Greyjoy anymore.
That's a name for a lord.
But you're not a lord,
are you?
You're just meat.
(GRUNTS)
Stinking meat.
You reek.
(GASPS)
Reek!
That's a good name for you.
What's your name?
Theon Greyjoy.
(GROANS)
What's your name?
(STAMMERING)
Theon Greyjoy.
Please.
What is your name?
Reek.
My name is...
(SOBBING)
(DISTANT PANTING)
(GASPS)
Hodor.
(DISTANT PANTS ECHOING)
(GROWLING)
(CREAKING IN DISTANCE)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(EERIE GROAN)
(GASPS)
(YELLS)
(PANTING)
Don't kill me!
Who are you?
Sam! Sam!
Gilly. Don't hurt us.
Where are you going?
To Castle Black.
I'm a brother of
the Night's Watch.
My brother,
he's in the Night's...
(SHUSHES)
Who's your brother?
JOJEN: Doesn't matter.
(SUMMER GROWLING)
You're Jon's brother.
The one who fell
from the window.
No, I'm not.
I've been around Ghost
enough to know
a direwolf when I see one.
And I've heard
all about Hodor.
Hodor.
I'd be dead if
it wasn't for Jon.
If you're his brother,
you're my brother, too.
And anything I can do
to help you, I will.
Take us north of the Wall.
What? Why in the world
would you want to go...
I don't want to.
I have to.
How did you get
through the Wall?
Does the well lead to
an underground river?
Is that how you came here?
Come with us.
There are steps carved
into the south
side of the Wall.
Hodor can carry
you to the top.
We'll walk
straight to Castle Black.
Come with us.
There's nothing
north but death.
If Jon is alive,
then Castle Black's
where he'll be.
It's the safest place
for you.
There's nowhere
safe any longer.
You know that.
SAMWELL: What I know
is what I saw.
And if you saw it, too,
you'd run the other way.
You saw the White Walkers
and the army of the dead.
How do you know all that?
The Night's Watch
can't stop them.
The Kings of Westeros
and all their armies
can't stop them.
(BABY CRYING)
But you're going
to stop them?
Please, Sam.
I have to go north.
I have to.
"Balon Greyjoy,
Lord of the Iron Islands
and invader of the North.
"I give you
until the full moon
"to order all ironborn
scum out of the North
"and back to those
shit-stained rocks
you call a home.
"On the first night
of the full moon,
"I will hunt down
every islander
"still in our lands
and flay them living,
"the way I flayed
the 20 ironborn scum
I found at Winterfell.
"In the box you'll
find a special gift...
"Theon's favorite toy.
"He cried when
I took it away from him.
"Leave the North now,
or more boxes will follow
"with more Theon."
Signed, "Ramsay Snow,
natural-born son
of Roose Bolton,
"Lord of the Dreadfort
and Warden of the North."
Get that out of my sight.
Theon disobeyed my orders.
The boy is a fool.
He cannot further
the Greyjoy line.
I will not give up
the lands I have seized,
the strongholds I have taken.
Get this away from me.
He's your son.
Son?
He's not a man anymore.
He's your son.
He's my brother.
He's a Greyjoy.
Watch yourself.
I've made my decision.
And I've made mine.
I'm going to pick
the fastest ship
in our fleet.
I'm going to choose
the 50 best killers
on the Iron Islands.
MAN: Get those ropes!
YARA: I'm going to
sail up the Narrow Sea,
all the way to
the Weeping Water.
I'm going to march
on the Dreadfort.
I'm going to find
my little brother,
and I'm going to
bring him home.
What is it?
Dragonglass.
We found them at the Fist.
Someone buried them
a long time ago.
Someone wanted us
to find them.
Why? What are they for?
Killing White Walkers.
How do you know that?
GILLY: The Walker
came for my baby.
And Sam...
But no one's killed
a White Walker in
thousands of years.
Well, I suppose
someone had to be the first.
Take it, Hodor.
And the archer.
I got lucky with
one of them.
There are more.
Many more.
And for every one of them,
the dead men,
more than you could count.
I wish you'd come with us.
I wish I could.
I really do.
How are you keeping?
Great. Never better.
It was just a bit of blood.
I should have known.
Every time
a highborn asks my name,
it's trouble.
We're not
really people to you.
Just ways to
get what you want.
I'm not a highborn.
She called you "Ser."
I heard it.
A recent state of affairs.
I was born in Flea Bottom,
just like you.
Sure, you were.
You're my friend.
You're here to help.
I lived below
the Street of Flour.
How far below?
How close to
the Red Keep were you?
The shit that poured
from their privy pipes
flowed down
the side of Aegon's Hill,
along Tanner's Row
and right in front
of my front door
on Gin Alley.
Gin Alley.
The Street of Steel,
with your armor
and your knights?
(SCOFFS)
You lived in
the fancy part of town.
And here we are now.
Two boys from Flea Bottom
in the castle of a king.
Yeah, we've
come a long way.
We're all the same,
really.
She went to great pains
to point that out to me.
If you mistrust
fancy people so much,
why were you in such
a hurry to trust her?
You're me.
Never been with a woman.
Never talked to a woman,
really.
And then she comes at you,
big words, no clothes.
What would you have done?
She does know her way
around a man's head,
I'll give her that.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
So how'd you
become a lord?
Oh. That's a long story.
Better not, then.
I'm a bit busy.
Many years ago
I helped King Stannis
out of a difficult situation.
He rewarded me
with a lordship.
And this.
You see?
Highborns.
I didn't want to be a lord.
I nearly didn't accept.
Why did you?
I did it for my son.
I didn't want him to
step over a river of shit
every time he stepped
through his front door.
I wanted him to
have a better life.
Does he?
He's dead.
How'd he die?
Following me.
When did you come to
this strange country?
When I was 13.
You were only a child.
I stopped being
a child when I was nine.
My mother made sure of that.
You've been a good
influence on our mutual
friend, you know.
He used to drink
from sundown to sunup,
visit three brothels a night,
gamble away
his father's money.
Now it's just the drinking.
And now
I'm his wife's servant.
I brush her hair
and clip her nails
and empty her chamber pot.
She is a sweet young thing.
None of this is her fault.
I love that girl.
I would kill for her.
Do you think that
makes it easier for me?
No, I expect not.
She's young
and she's beautiful
and highborn.
We break bread with them,
but that doesn't
make us family.
We've learned their
language, but we'll
never be their countrymen.
If you let yourself believe
that a foreign girl
with no name
could spend her life with
the son of Tywin Lannister...
I have a name.
You have one name.
As do I. Here, only
the family name matters.
What do you want
from me, Lord Varys?
Diamonds.
I'd tell you to beware
carrying so much wealth,
but you know how
to protect yourself.
Get on one of those
ships. Sail to Pentos
or Lys or Myr.
You can buy a house
with these diamonds,
a very large house.
Hire servants.
Start a new life,
a good life, far from here.
The mysterious foreign
beauty. You'll
have suitors lining up.
Why do you want me to leave?
Tyrion Lannister is one
of the few people alive
who could make this
country a better place.
He has the mind, the will,
and the right last name.
And you,
you are a complication.
I know you love him.
And I know it's
true love, not bought
by gold and silver.
I'm not asking you to
leave him for money.
I'm asking you to leave
because your presence
in the capital
endangers him.
This will never be
your home, my lady.
Find a true home
somewhere far from here,
while there's still time.
Lord Varys.
If he wants me to leave,
he can tell me himself.
Keep up.
I don't think I can,
my lord.
It's not easy being
drunk all the time.
(DOOR OPENING)
Everyone would do it,
if it were easy.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Leave.
(DOOR OPENING)
So, enjoying married life?
(DOOR CLOSES)
An unhappy wife
is a wine merchant's
best friend.
She doesn't deserve this.
Deserve?
Be careful with that.
Start trying to work
out who deserves what,
and before long
you'll spend your days
weeping for every
person in the world.
There's nothing worse
than a late-blooming
philosopher.
(CHUCKLES)
Will you be facing
your marriage to Ser Loras
with the same
philosophical spirit?
I won't be
marrying Ser Loras.
I seem to remember
saying something similar
about my own marriage.
You're not me.
You want to make
things better for Sansa?
Give her a child.
So you can tell
Father it was you who
finally talked me into it?
So she can have some
happiness in her life.
You have children.
How happy would
you say you are?
Not very.
But if it weren't
for my children,
I'd have thrown myself
from the highest
window in the Red Keep.
They're the reason
I'm alive.
Even Joffrey?
Even Joffrey.
He was all I had once.
Before Myrcella was born.
I used to spend
hours looking at him.
His wisps of hair.
His tiny little
hands and feet.
He was such
a jolly little fellow.
You always hear
the terrible ones
were terrible babies.
"We should have known.
Even then
we should have known."
It's nonsense.
Whenever he was
with me, he was happy.
And no one can take
that away from me,
not even Joffrey,
how it feels to
have someone.
Someone of your own.
How long does it go on?
Until we've dealt
with all our enemies.
Every time we
deal with an enemy,
we create two more.
Then I suppose
it will go on for
quite a long time.
(MAN IMITATES WHIMPERING)
(MEN LAUGHING)
I'm telling you,
that's what she did.
(IMITATES WHIMPERING)
(MEN LAUGHING)
MAN 1: Sounded
like a cow in heat.
MAN 2: Aye, not for long.
MAN 3: That's right.
Black Walder shut
her up right quick.
None of the Starks
had much to say
about the end of that meal.
I'll tell you what, though.
The hardest thing was
getting that wolf's head
to stay on the body.
MAN 2: You sewed it on?
I did.
I bet there were 1,000 men
claiming they were the one.
It was me.
And Malcolm and Talbott.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Well, the thing was so heavy,
it fell off the first time.
Took the skin
right with it.
What we ended up
having to do was
hook the needle
right under
the collarbone,
give it a nice
firm mooring and...
What do you want?
Mind if I keep warm?
Fuck off.
But I'm hungry.
Does "fuck off" mean
something different
where you're from?
I've got money.
What kind of coin is that?
It's worth a lot.
Sorry.
Little shit.
(GROANING)
MAN: Fool!
(GRUNTING)
Where did you
get the knife?
From you.
Is that the first
man you've killed?
The first man.
Next time you're going
to do something like that,
tell me first.
(WHISPERS)
Valar Morghulis.
(GRUNTS)
(BOW STRETCHING)
(HORSE NEIGHING)
Ygritte, you know
I didn't have a choice.
You always knew
who I was, what I am.
(GRUNTS)
I have to go home now.
I know you won't hurt me.
You know nothing, Jon Snow.
(CHUCKLES)
I do know some things.
I know I love you.
(WHIMPERS)
I know you love me.
But I have to go home now.
(EXHALES)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
(GROANS)
(SOBS)
I know
how this must look.
What I meant was...
I swear to you, my lord...
AEMON: I'm not
a lord, my dear.
Not for many,
many years.
Every man who
joins the Night's Watch
renounces all former titles.
Among other things.
What is your name?
Gilly.
Ah.
For the gillyflower. Lovely.
Yes, my...
Maester.
Master.
And the child?
She hasn't chosen
a name yet.
His name is Sam.
AEMON: Tarly,
do you remember
the oath you swore
when you joined this order?
He's not my child,
Maester Aemon.
She's one
of Craster's wives.
(BABY CRYING)
I remember every
word of the oath.
"Night gathers
and my watch begins.
"I am the shield that
guards the realms of men.
"The realms of men."
That means her
as well as us.
We didn't build 500 miles
of ice walls 700 feet high
to keep out men.
The night is gathering,
Maester Aemon.
I've seen it.
It's coming for all of us.
Gilly, you and your son
will be our guests
for the time being.
We certainly
cannot send you back
beyond the Wall.
Thank you...
Maester.
I can cook and
clean and I can...
Good.
Samwell, fetch
a quill and inkwell.
I hope your penmanship
is better than
your swordplay.
Miles better.
We had 44 ravens
at last count.
Make sure they're all fed.
Every one of them
flies tonight.
"To His Grace
"King Stannis Baratheon.
"Invaded... Invited
"to the name day celebration
"for Rylene Florent
"on the first nigit..."
Night.
"First night of
the full moon."
Why is there a "G" in night?
I don't know.
There just is.
Well, your father's
not going to go to that.
My books are better
than these boring scrolls.
You could read about
Balerion the Dread.
They say you can
still see his skull
in the dungeons
beneath the Red Keep.
I'd like to
see that someday.
I've been trying
to stay out of those
dungeons my whole life.
"His fangs were as
long as bastard swords."
Aye, old Balerion's
definitely better
than anything your cousin
Rylene's got on offer.
But now that I'm your
father's Hand again,
I have to keep him informed.
The King does not have time
for this drudgery.
"To all the lords
and knobble men
of Westeros..."
Noblemen.
"Noblemen of Westeros,
"the Night's Watch
"implores..."
What is it?
(BELLS TOLLING)
Why are they
ringing the bells?
Are we being attacked?
Stay here. Bar the door.
(DOOR OPENING)
The usurper Robb Stark
is dead. Betrayed
by his bannerman.
And you take credit
because you dropped
a leech into the fire?
I take no credit.
I have faith, and my
faith has been rewarded.
Your Grace, the world
has got so far bent.
I've seen things
crawl out of nightmares,
but my eyes were open.
I don't know
if Robb Stark died
because of
the Red Woman's sorcery
or because at war
men die all the time,
but I do know that uniting
the Seven Kingdoms
with blood magic is wrong.
It is evil.
And you are not an evil man.
Do you know who had
this table carved
and painted, Ser Davos?
Aegon Targaryen.
And do you know
how Aegon Targaryen
conquered Westeros?
On the back of his dragon,
Balerion the Dread.
He had a smaller fleet
than the kings he faced
and a smaller army,
but he had three dragons.
Dragons are magic,
Ser Davos.
My enemies have
made my kingdom bleed.
I will not forget that.
I will not forgive that.
I will punish them
with any arms
at my disposal.
You do not need
to burn the boy.
If what you say is true,
a drop of his blood
killed Robb Stark...
And our King is
still no closer
to the Iron Throne.
A great gift
requires a great sacrifice.
His name is Gendry.
He's a good lad.
A poor lad from
Flea Bottom, who happens
to be your nephew.
What is the life
of one bastard boy
against a kingdom?
Everything.
The boy must die.
What are you doing?
You're leaving.
Is this some kind of trick?
Yes, but not on you.
Aim for that star.
Don't stop.
There's bread and water.
Go slow with it.
If you finish it off,
no matter
how thirsty you get,
don't drink seawater.
I know not to
drink seawater.
Row for a full day and night
and you'll reach Rook's Rest.
You'll want to stop there.
Don't. She'll find you.
Where should I go?
You must keep the coast
on your left side
until you reach
King's Landing.
The gold cloaks
are looking for me.
They were looking
for me for 20 years.
Do they know your face?
No.
I'd worry more
about the Red Woman.
The other way.
You ever been
in a boat before?
No.
You know how to swim?
Don't fall out. Go on.
Why are you doing this?
Because it's right.
And because I'm
a slow learner.
When you get to Flea Bottom,
have a bowl of brown for me.
GUARD: Horse approaching!
Halt! Halt!
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(MEN GRUNTING)
Jon! Jon!
Jon, it's us.
I don't think
he can see us.
Pyp?
Sam?
Hush, now. You're home.
Carry him inside. Gently.
(VENDOR SHOUTING)
(CHICKENS CLUCKING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Out of the way.
Step aside, country boy.
People working here.
Cersei.
(GASPS)
You don't deny it?
No. I let him go.
Your mercy saved
the boy's life.
You feel good about that?
Aye, I do.
MELISANDRE:
You saved one innocent.
How many tens of thousands
have you doomed?
There has got to
be another way.
(SHOUTING) What other way?
Tell us about this other way.
DAVOS: I don't know,
Your Grace.
I can't see
the future in the fire.
Very well,
Ser Davos Seaworth.
I, Stannis of
the House Baratheon,
First of My Name,
Rightful King of
the Andals and the First Men,
sentence you to die.
DAVOS: I understand.
But since you haven't
yet unnamed me
Hand of the King,
it is my duty to
advise you against it.
You're gonna need me.
Take him away.
Why am I gonna need you?
My King.
DAVOS: It's from Maester
Aemon of the Night's Watch.
Their Lord Commander is dead.
Took a ranging party north
and never made it back.
One lad did, though.
What he saw beyond the Wall,
it's coming for all of us.
When did you
learn to read?
Matthos taught me
before he died,
so I could be of
better service to you.
This War of Five Kings
means nothing.
The true war lies to
the north, my King.
Death marches on the Wall.
Only you can stop him.
You can't stop him alone.
You need someone to
rebuild your army for you,
someone to convince
this lord and that lord
to fight for you,
to bring sellswords
and pirates to your side.
I've made my decision.
He's right. You need him.
He has a part to play
in the war to come.
(SCOFFS)
(LAUGHING)
You see, Ser Davos?
You've been saved
by that fire god
you like to mock.
You're in His army now.
They will come, Your Grace.
When they're ready.
Perhaps they didn't
want to be conquered.
You didn't conquer them.
You liberated them.
People learn to
love their chains.
(DRAGONS SCREECH)
(IN VALYRIAN)
No.
Mhysa!
ALL: Mhysa!
ALL: (CHANTING)
Mhysa! Mhysa!
Mhysa! Mhysa! Mhysa!
What does it mean?
It is old Ghiscari,
Khaleesi.
It means "mother."
(ALL CONTINUE CHANTING)
(DRAGONS SCREECHING)
It's all right.
These people
won't hurt me.
ALL: (CHANTING)
Mhysa! Mhysa!
(DRAGON SCREECHES)
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
(IN VALYRIAN)
(SCREECHING)
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
Mhysa.
ALL: Mhysa! Mhysa!
Mhysa! Mhysa!
(DRAGONS SCREECHING)