I'll give you one try, girl.
Kill me and you're free.
But if I live,
I'll break both
your hands.
Go on, hit me.
Hit me hard.
Sulk all you want.
The truth is,
you're lucky.
You don't want to be
alone out here, girl.
Someone worse than me
would find you.
There's no one
worse than you.
(SCOFFS) You
never knew my brother.
He once killed
a man for snoring.
There's plenty
worse than me.
There's men who like
to beat little girls,
men who like to rape them.
I saved your sister
from some of them.
You're lying.
Ask her, if you ever
see her again.
Ask her who came back
for her when the mob
had her on her back.
They would have
taken her every which way
and left her there
with her throat cut open.
Is that the Blackwater?
The Blackwater?
Where do you think
I'm taking you?
Back to King's Landing,
to Joffrey and the Queen.
Fuck Joffrey.
Fuck the Queen.
That's the Red Fork.
I'm taking you to the Twins.
But why?
Your mother and
brother will be there,
and they'll pay me for you.
Why would they
be at the Twins?
(LAUGHS) Those outlaws
you love so much
never told you?
The whole countryside
is yapping about it.
Your uncle is marrying
one of the Frey girls.
So quit trying to
bash my skull in,
and we might
just make it there
in time for the wedding.
(HORSES NEIGHING)
Men who fight for gold
have neither
honor nor loyalty.
They cannot be trusted.
JORAH: They can be
trusted to kill you
if they're well paid.
The Yunkish are
paying them well.
You know these men?
Only by the broken
swords on their banners.
They're called
the Second Sons.
A company led by
a Braavosi named Mero,
the Titan's Bastard.
Is he more titan
or bastard?
He's a dangerous man,
Khaleesi. They all are.
How many?
BARRISTAN: 2,000, Your Grace.
Armored and mounted.
Enough to make a difference?
(FLY BUZZING)
It's hard to collect
wages from a corpse.
I'm sure the sellswords
prefer to fight
for the winning side.
I imagine you're right.
I'd like to talk
to the Titan's Bastard
about winning.
He may not agree to meet.
He will.
A man who fights
for gold can't afford
to lose to a girl.
BARRISTAN: Your Grace,
allow me to present
the captains of
the Second Sons,
Mero of Braavos,
Prendahl na Ghezn,
and, um...
Daario Naharis.
You are
the Mother of Dragons?
I swear I fucked you once
in a pleasure house in Lys.
Mind your tongue.
MERO: Why?
I didn't mind hers.
She licked my ass like
she was born to do it.
(MERO CHUCKLES)
You, slave girl,
bring wine.
We have no slaves here.
You'll all be
slaves after the battle,
unless I save you.
Take your clothes off
and come and
sit on Mero's lap,
and I may give you
my Second Sons.
Give me your Second Sons
and I may not
have you gelded.
(CHUCKLES)
Ser Barristan,
how many men fight
for the Second Sons?
Under 2,000, Your Grace.
We have more, don't we?
BARRISTAN: 10,000 Unsullied.
I'm only a young girl,
new to the ways of war,
but perhaps a seasoned
captain like yourself
can explain to me
how you propose to
defeat us.
I hope the old man
is better with a sword
than he is with a lie.
You have 8,000 Unsullied.
You're very young
to be a captain.
He's not a captain.
He's a lieutenant.
Even if your
numbers are right,
the odds don't
favor your side.
The Second Sons have
faced worse odds and won.
faced worse odds and run.
Or you could
fight for me.
(MERO CHUCKLES)
We've taken
the slavers' gold.
We fight for Yunkai.
DAENERYS: I would pay you
as much and more.
(SNIFFING)
PRENDAHL: Our contract
is our bond.
If we break our bond,
no one will hire
the Second Sons again.
Ride with me
and you'll never
need another contract.
You'll have gold and
castles and lordships
of your choosing
when I take back
the Seven Kingdoms.
DAARIO: You have no ships.
You have no siege weapons.
You have no cavalry.
A fortnight ago, I had
no army. A year ago,
I had no dragons.
You have two days to decide.
Show me your cunt.
I want to see
if it's worth fighting for.
(BOTH IN VALYRIAN)
You seem to be
enjoying my wine.
Perhaps you'd like a flagon
to help you ponder.
Only a flagon?
And what are my brothers
in arms to drink?
A barrel, then.
Good.
The Titan's Bastard
does not drink alone.
In the Second Sons,
we share everything.
After the battle,
maybe we'll all share you.
I'll come looking for
you when this is over.
Ser Barristan,
if it comes to battle,
kill that one first.
Gladly, Your Grace.
Half Robert,
half lowborn.
Show the boy
to his chambers.
Have the maids draw him
a bath and find him
some decent clothes.
I'll come visit you soon.
What do you mean
to do with him?
You know.
Then why bathe him
and dress him
in fine clothes?
If it needs to be
done, do it. Don't
torture the boy.
Have you ever
slaughtered a lamb,
my king?
No.
If the lamb sees
the knife, she panics.
Her panic seeps into
her meat, darkens it,
fouls the flavor.
You've slaughtered
many lambs?
And none have
seen the blade.
(DOOR CLOSES)
DAVOS: (STAMMERING)
"And though
"Visenya
"Targaryen
"rode
"Vhagar
"Vhag..."
(EXHALES)
Fuck me.
(SIGHS)
"Visenya Targaryen
"rode Vhagar,
"the smallest
of the dragons,
"though still
"large
"enough
"to swallow a horse whole."
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Your Grace.
They feeding you enough?
Two meals a day.
Cold for breakfast,
hot for supper.
I cannot complain.
You don't belong
in a place like this.
Well, it's sad to say,
but I've seen worse.
Yeah.
I'm sorry about your son.
Didn't get the chance
to tell you before.
Good lad. Loyal lad.
Melisandre's returned.
I didn't know
she'd been gone.
Came back with
a bastard boy.
Robert's bastard boy.
Why?
She says there's
power in king's blood.
She's going to kill him.
Sacrifice him.
Forgive me, Your Grace,
I'm not a learned man,
but is there a difference
between kill and sacrifice?
The boy is your nephew.
What of it? We're at war.
Why should I spare the son
of some tavern slut
Robert bedded
one drunken night?
Because he has your
blood in his veins.
So did Renly.
Renly wronged you.
Renly declared himself
king when the throne
belonged to you.
He raised an army,
stole your bannermen.
This boy has
done you no harm.
He's an innocent.
How many boys
live in Westeros?
How many girls?
How many men?
How many women?
The darkness will
devour them all, she says.
The night that never ends.
Unless I triumph.
I never asked for this.
No more than
I asked to be king.
We do not choose our destiny,
but we must do our duty, no?
Great or small,
we must do our duty.
What's one bastard boy
against a kingdom?
Your Grace,
why did you come
to see me today?
I came to free you.
If you swear never
to raise your hand to
the Lady Melisandre again.
I swear it.
I can't swear never
to speak against her.
You have little regard
for your own life.
Quite little, Your Grace.
Verging on none.
You could have
freed me yesterday
or tomorrow,
but you came to me now
before this boy
is put to the knife
because you knew
I'd counsel restraint.
You came to hear me
say it because you
believe it yourself.
You're not a man who
slaughters innocents
for gain or glory.
When my son was five,
he said to me,
"I don't ever want to die."
I wanted to say to him,
"You won't, child.
You won't ever."
I hated the idea
of him lying awake
in the dark, afraid.
I think mothers and
fathers made up the Gods
because they
wanted their children
to sleep through the night.
I saw a vision
in the flames.
A great battle in the snow.
I saw it.
And you saw
whatever she gave birth to.
I never believed,
but when you see the truth,
when it's right
there in front of you,
as real as these iron bars,
how can you deny
her god is real?
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(GRUNTS)
That dragon bitch.
She talks too much.
You talk too much.
She won't talk so much
when she's choking
on my cock.
8,000 Unsullied stand
between her and your cock.
My cock will find
a way. Tell him.
Is there any place
that my cock can't reach?
She'll tell me whatever
you pay her to tell me.
Daario Naharis, the whore
who doesn't like whores.
I like them very much.
I just refuse to pay them.
And I'm no whore,
my friend.
She sells her sheath,
and you sell your blade.
What's the difference?
I fight for beauty.
(MERO LAUGHS)
For beauty?
We fight for gold.
The Gods gave men
two gifts to entertain
ourselves before we die,
the thrill of fucking
a woman who wants
to be fucked
and the thrill
of killing a man
who wants to kill you.
You'll die young.
PRENDAHL: What do we do
about the dragon girl?
We can't beat 8,000 Unsullied
on the battlefield.
There won't be a battle,
and we don't have to
deal with her eunuchs.
We only have to
deal with her.
She's well guarded.
Tonight's a new moon.
One of us slips into
her camp past her
Unsullied and her knights.
Which one of us?
Close your eyes, love.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Three coins.
A coin from Meereen,
a coin from Volantis,
and a coin from Braavos.
The Braavosi does the deed.
One for each of us,
darling.
No peeking.
Do you hear me?
Follow my voice.
I'm right here.
(GIGGLES)
You have something
for me?
Valar Morghulis.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(SIGHS)
Lady Sansa.
You look very handsome,
my lord.
Oh, yes.
The husband of your dreams.
But you do look glorious.
Perhaps we could
have a moment alone.
Do you mind?
Podrick, could you escort
Lady Stark's handmaiden?
My lady,
I want you to know
I didn't ask for this.
I hope I will not
disappoint you, my lord.
No, don't.
You don't have to
speak to me as
a prisoner anymore.
You won't be
a prisoner after today.
You'll be my wife.
I suppose that's
a different kind of prison.
I just wanted to say...
I'm just trying to say,
very badly...
I just...
Just want to say
I know how you feel.
I doubt that
very much, my lord.
You're right.
I have no idea
how you feel.
And you have
no idea how I feel.
But I promise you
one thing, my lady.
I won't ever hurt you.
Do you drink wine?
When I have to.
Well, today you have to.
MARGAERY: You look
radiant, Your Grace.
Radiant? Why radiant?
It's the word
that came to mind.
(CHUCKLES)
We're going to
be sisters soon.
We should be friends.
You're a musical girl,
aren't you?
I imagine you
have a lovely voice.
A better dancer than
a singer, I'm afraid.
But you know the song
The Rains of Castamere?
Of course. They play it
so often here at court.
So you know the story
of House Reyne of Castamere?
Not as well as you,
I'm sure.
(CHUCKLES)
House Reyne was
a powerful family.
Very wealthy.
The second wealthiest
in Westeros.
Aren't the Tyrells
the second wealthiest
family in Westeros now?
Ambitious climbers
don't want to stop
on the second highest rung.
If only you could
take that final step,
you'd see further
than all the rest.
You'd be alone with nothing
but blue sky above you.
So Lord Reyne built a castle
as grand as Casterly Rock.
He gave his wife diamonds
larger than any
my mother ever wore.
And finally one day,
he rebelled against
my father.
Do you know where
House Reyne is now?
Gone.
A gentle word.
Why not say "slaughtered"?
Every man, woman, and
child put to the sword.
I remember seeing
their bodies hanging
high above the gates
of Casterly Rock.
My father let them
rot up there all summer.
It was a long summer.
"And now the rains
weep o'er their halls,
and not a soul to hear."
If you ever call me
"sister" again,
I'll have you
strangled in your sleep.
(DOOR OPENING)
What are you doing?
Your father's gone.
As the father of the realm,
it is my duty
to give you away
to your husband.
You may now cloak
the bride and bring her
under your protection.
(SNICKERS)
(CROWD LAUGHING)
(LAUGHS)
Uh...
Could you...
Thank you.
Your Grace, Your Grace,
my lords, my ladies,
we stand here in
the sight of gods and men
to witness
the union of man and wife.
One flesh,
one heart, one soul,
now and forever.
Have you ever
seen one like it?
I've never seen
anything like any
of this. Not in my life.
It's shocking, isn't it,
the first time you
encounter real wealth?
When I was your age,
I lived on one
bowl of stew a day.
And stew is
a kind word for it.
In Flea Bottom
we called them
"bowls of brown."
We'd pretend that
the meat in them
was chicken.
We knew
it wasn't chicken.
(WINE POURING)
Here, taste this.
You think I'm
trying to poison you?
That's good.
That's really good.
Where do you think
it's from?
I couldn't even guess.
Doesn't matter, does it?
It's the real thing
or it's not.
You only need a tongue
to tell the difference.
Go on, have some more.
(CHUCKLES) You
still don't trust it.
You think this
is all a mistake
that you have to pay
for every bite you take.
(CHUCKLES) That thought had
crossed my mind, yeah.
There are no mistakes.
Not for us.
I'm a mistake.
I'm only here because
my father grabbed my mother
instead of the girl
next to her in the tavern.
Your father chose your
mother because the Lord
of Light willed it.
He willed it so you
could be here right now
with a power inside you
you can't even
begin to understand.
And He brought me here
to draw it from you and
birth it into the world.
We're both
a part of His plan.
He wants this for us.
No, He demands this of us.
I don't understand.
This...
This doesn't
seem very religious.
According to whom?
The Silent Sisters?
With their stern looks,
muzzled mouths,
and dried-up cunts?
What have their
gods done for you?
Mmm?
When you pray to them,
what's their answer?
A god is real or he's not.
You only need eyes to see.
Death is coming for
everyone and everything.
A darkness that
will swallow the dawn.
And we can stop it,
you and I.
(PANTING)
Let me show you what
you have inside you.
Come fight death with me.
(BOTH MOANING)
What are you doing?
You have to trust me.
(PANTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
What...
Get it away.
Get it off me.
Don't fight, don't fight.
They won't take much.
Why are you doing this?
I told you there's
power in the blood of kings.
And you have so much blood.
No.
No, no, no, no!
Not there. Not there!
You can blame Ser Davos.
He didn't believe in
the power of king's blood.
He wanted a demonstration.
GENDRY: Please.
Please, Your Grace.
My lord!
(GROANING)
The usurper Robb Stark.
The usurper
Balon Greyjoy.
Joffrey Baratheon.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(MINSTRELS PLAYING
THE BEAR AND THE MAIDEN FAIR)
So their son
will be your nephew.
After you're wed to
Cersei, of course.
And you will be
the King's stepfather
and brother-in-law.
When you marry the King,
Joffrey's mother will
become his sister-in-law
and your son will
be Loras' nephew?
Grandson? I'm not sure.
But your brother
will become
your father-in-law.
That much is
beyond dispute.
(BELCHES)
Will you pardon me,
my lord?
Of course. Of course. Enjoy.
Perhaps you could
talk to your
bride-to-be instead.
I've got a lifetime for that.
(SIGHS)
Stay.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
TYWIN: You seem rather drunk.
Rather less than
I plan to be.
Isn't it a man's duty to be
drunk at his own wedding?
This isn't about your
wedding. Renly Baratheon
had a wedding.
Your wife needs a child,
a Lannister child,
as soon as possible.
And?
If you're going
to give her one,
you need to perform.
What did you once call me?
A drunken little
lust-filled beast.
More than once.
There you have it.
Nothing to worry about.
Drinking and lust,
no man can match me
in these things.
I am the god
of tits and wine.
I shall build a shrine
to myself at the next
brothel I visit.
(GRUNTS)
You can drink,
you can joke,
you can engage in
juvenile attempts
to make your
father uncomfortable,
but you will do your duty.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Well...
My father once told me...
Nobody cares what your
father once told you.
(ALL CHATTERING)
Congratulations, my lady.
Thank you, Your Grace.
Well, you've done it.
You've married a Lannister.
Soon you'll have
a Lannister baby.
It's a dream come true
for you, isn't it?
What a glorious day.
Yes, Your Grace.
I suppose it
doesn't really matter
which Lannister
puts the baby into you.
Maybe I'll pay
you a visit tonight
after my uncle passes out.
How'd you like that?
You wouldn't?
That's all right.
Ser Meryn and Ser Boros
will hold you down.
JOFFREY: Time for
the bedding ceremony.
ALL: Ah!
There will be
no bedding ceremony.
Where's your respect
for tradition, Uncle?
Come, everyone.
Pick her up and carry
her to her wedding bed.
Get rid of her gown.
She won't be
needing it any longer.
Ladies, attend to my
uncle. He's not heavy.
There will be
no bedding ceremony.
if I command it.
Then you'll be
fucking your own bride
with a wooden cock.
JOFFREY: What did you say?
What did you say?
I believe we can
dispense with the bedding,
Your Grace.
I'm sure Tyrion did not mean
to threaten the King.
(LAUGHING)
A bad joke, Your Grace.
Made out of envy of
your own royal manhood.
Mine is so small.
My poor wife won't
even know I'm there.
Your uncle is clearly
quite drunk, Your Grace.
TYRION: I am.
Guilty.
But...
But it is my wedding night.
My tiny drunk cock
and I have a job to do.
Come, wife.
I vomited on a girl once
in the middle of the act.
Not proud of it.
But I think
honesty is important
between a man and wife,
don't you agree?
Come, I'll tell you
all about it. Put you
in the mood.
Is that wise, my lord?
Tyrion, Sansa.
My name is Tyrion.
Is that wise, Tyrion?
Nothing was ever wiser.
Astoundingly long.
What?
Neck.
You have one.
(TYRION SNIFFING)
How old are you exactly?
14.
Well, talk won't
make you any older.
My lord father has
commanded me to
consummate this marriage.
(EXHALES)
Stop.
I can't.
I could, I won't.
But your father...
If my father wants
someone to get fucked,
I know where he can start.
I won't share your bed.
Not until you want me to.
What if I never want you to?
And so my watch begins.
(SIGHS)
(THUDS)
(HORSES NEIGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Nineteen?
Yes, Your Grace.
How can anyone speak
19 languages?
It only took Your Grace
a year to learn Dothraki
reasonably well.
Yes, well, it was
either learn Dothraki
or grunt at my
husband and hope...
What do you mean,
"reasonably well"?
Dothraki is difficult
for the mouth to master.
So guttural and harsh.
(IN DOTHRAKI)
Athjahakar.
Athjahaka.
Ath-ja-hakar.
Athjahakar.
Well, I suppose I'm
a bit out of practice.
Your High Valyrian is
very good, Your Grace.
The Gods could not devise
a more perfect tongue.
It is the only proper
language for poetry.
(MISSANDEI GASPS)
No screaming,
or she dies.
What do you want?
You.
Let her go.
Don't scream,
lovely girl.
You were sent here
to kill me?
(CHUCKLES)
So why haven't you?
I don't want to.
What do your captains
have to say about that?
You should ask them.
Why?
We had philosophical
differences.
Over what?
Your beauty.
It meant more to me
than it did to them.
You're a strange man.
I'm the simplest man
you'll ever meet. I only
do what I want to do.
And this is
supposed to impress me?
Yes.
Why would I trust a man
who murders his comrades?
They ordered me
to murder you.
I told them
I preferred not to.
They told me
I had no choice.
I told them
I am Daario Naharis.
I always have a choice.
They drew their swords
and I drew mine.
Will you fight for me?
Swear to me.
The Second Sons are yours,
and so is Daario Naharis.
My sword is yours,
my life is yours,
my heart is yours.
(DOOR OPENING)
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(SLAMS)
You really ought to knock.
I brought your breakfast.
(DOOR OPENING)
(WIND HOWLING)
(BABY GURGLING)
It's getting dark.
We could stay here
for the night.
(RAVEN CAWING)
How hard can it be
to build a fire?
It doesn't matter.
Come under the furs.
We can keep each other warm.
He winked at me before.
I doubt it.
I saw him wink at me.
He blinked.
I suppose it's a rather
philosophical difference
between a wink and a blink.
A what?
Well, I mean, there's
no real difference.
A wink is on purpose.
You thought of a name yet?
It would be easier
to refer to him
if he had a name.
Sometimes do you talk fancy
on purpose to confuse me?
What? No.
This is just
the way I talk.
I'll build that fire.
Don't you think
he should have a name?
I don't know
many boys' names.
Let's see, there's Duncan,
Kevan, Jon...
(STRIKING FLINT)
Guymon, Feldan,
Tristifer.
Craster.
Uh... Yes.
(STAMMERS)
Maybe that's not...
Mormont.
That's a lovely idea,
but Mormont's a last name.
Why is it a last name?
Well, it's a family name.
For instance,
I'm Samwell Tarly.
Samwell is my birth name
and Tarly is my family name.
You see? So my father
is also a Tarly.
His name is
Samwell Tarly, too?
No, Randyll Tarly.
Randyll is a handsome name.
Please don't
name him Randyll.
Is your father cruel,
like mine?
Different manner of cruel.
Not Randyll, then.
(RAVENS CAWING)
(CROWING INTENSIFIES)
GILLY: Don't.
Don't go out there.
I'll be back.
I just want to look.
(RAVENS CAWING LOUDLY)
Go inside.
Go back inside. I'll...
(CAWING STOPS)
(SNARLING)
It's come for the baby.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Stay back!
You stay back!
(GROANS)
(BABY CRYING)
No, you can't have him!
No!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(ROARING)
(SCREECHING)
(RAVENS CAWING)
(BOTH PANTING)