(ROARING)
(SWORDS CLANGING)
(WAR CRIES)
MAN: Fall back!
(WIND HOWLING)
(PANTING)
Brother?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SAMWELL SCREAMS)
(GHOST GROWLING)
(WHIMPERING)
(PANTING)
Did you send the ravens?
Tarly, look at me.
That was your job.
Your only job.
We need to get
back to the Wall.
It's a long march.
We know what's out there,
but we have to make it,
have to warn them
or before winter's done,
everyone you've ever
known will be dead.
(WIND HOWLING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
First time you've
seen a giant, Jon Snow?
(EXHALES)
Well, don't stare too long.
They're shy.
When they stop being shy,
they get angry.
And when they're angry,
I've seen them pound a man
straight into the ground
like a hammer on a nail.
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
MAN 1: Crow!
BOY 1: Crow!
GIRL 1: Look over there!
MAN 2: Crow!
GIRL 2: Crow!
Look over here! Look!
WOMAN: Look, crow coming!
BOY 2: Crow!
YGRITTE: You're
wearing the wrong color.
Mance was a ranger.
(GRUNTS)
In your hearts, all you
crows want to fly free.
JON: When I'm free,
will I be free to go?
Crow!
Sure, you will.
(GROANS)
(ALL LAUGHING)
And I'll be free
to kill you.
Got no respect,
this lot.
Got no fathers to
slap them when
they're foul.
What happened
to their fathers?
Some of them were
killed by crows like you.
Don't look so grim,
Jon Snow.
If Mance Rayder likes you,
you'll live another day.
And if he don't...
TORMUND: I smell a crow.
We killed his friends.
Thought you'd want
to question this one.
What do we want
with a baby crow?
This baby killed
Qhorin Halfhand.
He wants to be
one of us.
That half-handed cunt
killed friends of mine.
Friends twice your size.
My father told me
big men fall just as
quick as little ones
if you put a sword
through their hearts.
Plenty of little men
tried to put their
swords through my heart.
And there's plenty
of little skeletons
buried in the woods.
What's your name, boy?
Jon Snow.
Your Grace.
(LAUGHING)
Your Grace?
(ALL LAUGHING)
Did you hear that?
From now on, you'd better
kneel every time I fart.
(CHUCKLING)
Stand, boy.
We don't kneel for
anyone beyond the Wall.
So, you're
Ned Stark's bastard.
Thank you for the gift,
Lord of Bones.
You can leave us.
The girl likes you.
You like her back, Snow?
That why you
want to join us?
TORMUND: Don't panic, boy.
This isn't
the damned Night's Watch
where we make you
swear off girls.
This chicken eater
you thought was king
is Tormund Giantsbane.
Can't believe this pup
killed the Halfhand.
MANCE: He was our enemy
and I'm glad he's dead.
He was my brother once.
Back when
he had a whole hand.
What were you
doing with him?
The Lord Commander
sent me to the Halfhand
for seasoning.
Why?
He wants me
to lead one day.
But here you are,
a traitor,
kneeling before
the King-beyond-the-Wall.
If I'm a traitor,
then you are, too.
Why do you want to
join us, Jon Snow?
I want to be free.
No, I don't think so.
I think what you
want most of all
is to be a hero.
I'll ask you
one last time,
why do you
want to join us?
We stopped at Craster's Keep
on the way north.
I saw...
You saw what?
I saw Craster
take his own baby boy
and leave it in the woods.
I saw what took it.
You're telling me
you saw one of them?
And why would that make you
desert your brothers?
Because when I told
the Lord Commander,
he already knew.
Thousands of years ago,
the First Men
defeated the White Walkers.
I want to fight for the side
that fights for the living.
Did I come
to the right place?
We'll need to
find you a new cloak.
(CHILDREN CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY)
What if you took off
that bit there?
(CHUCKLES) Don't you
want to leave something
to the imagination?
Trouble is, I've never
had much imagination.
I want you to take it off.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
Mouth.
(DOOR OPENING)
PODRICK: Ser Bronn.
Ser Bronn.
BRONN: I didn't
hear that.
Apologies, ser.
BRONN: Back away.
Keep backing away
till you're outside
this establishment.
Then back away some more.
Lord Tyrion sent me.
I will murder you, boy.
He said
it was a matter
of life and death.
(SIGHS)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Pod?
CERSEI: It's your sister.
The queen.
TYRION: What are
they doing here?
Protecting me, I assume.
Will you let me in?
No, I don't think so.
If I wanted to kill you,
do you think I'd let
a wooden door stop me?
They stay outside.
I'm not afraid of you,
little brother.
(CREAKING)
Why are you here?
I wanted to see your face.
They said you'd
lost your nose,
but it's not as
gruesome as all that.
The man who cut me
lost more than his nose.
I should hope so.
The rebels came
for Joffrey's head,
they lost their own.
Thanks to Father.
Of course, it wasn't a rebel
who tried to kill me.
No? Curious.
Bit of a comedown
from chamber of the Hand.
But then I don't suppose
you need much room.
Grand Maester Pycelle
made the same joke.
You must be proud to
be as funny as a man
whose balls brush his knees.
You're meeting
Father today?
How do you know that?
Because I have
hundreds of spies
in my employ.
The Master of Whisperers
owes me a favor or two.
Father told me.
What do you want from him?
What do I want from him?
He's my father.
Do I need to
want something?
I'm sure he loves me dearly,
as any father loves
his child, his baby boy.
Yet he hasn't
come to visit once...
Hmm.
...since arriving
in King's Landing.
I lay here,
my face split in half,
but Father never came.
You're going to
make me cry.
Why do you care
what I want from him?
Because
you've slandered me
to Father before.
Slandered? When?
You told him I had my guards
beat that servant girl
at Casterly Rock.
You did have your
guards beat her.
A girl of nine, I believe.
I was nine, too.
She lost an eye,
if I remember correctly.
If I remember correctly,
she never stole
a necklace again.
(LAUGHS)
It's not slander
if it's true.
And what's this truth
you plan on
telling him today?
Why are you so nervous
about what I'm
going to say to Father?
Because you're a liar.
I expect you'll
tell lies about me,
about Joffrey.
Any lies in particular?
(SIGHS) You're
a clever man,
but not as clever
as you think you are.
Mmm. Still makes me
more clever than you.
(DOOR OPENS)
Ah.
Look at these two
shining warriors.
Ser Taryn Mant and
Ser Whosit of Whocares.
Ser Meryn Trant.
Ser Bronn
of the Blackwater.
You're no knight.
Pod.
Ser Bronn of the Blackwater
was anointed by
the king himself.
You're an
up-jumped cutthroat,
nothing more.
That's exactly who I am.
And you're
a grub in fancy armor
who's better at
beating little girls
than fighting men.
Now, I have an appointment
with Lord Tyrion.
You put your
hand on that door,
you lose the hand.
As much as I appreciate
a walk in the sunshine,
I am wondering
why you sent for me.
Many people in this
city want to kill me.
You're here to protect me.
I've been doing
that for a while now.
Do you grow
bored protecting me?
I grow poor
protecting you.
Poor? Poor?
Under my patronage
you've become a knight,
you've served as Commander
of the City Watch.
Briefly.
I'm sure you
filled your pockets.
And now my pockets
are empty.
You've given me
a taste for
the finer things.
And if you want me
protecting you,
you'll need to pay more.
I thought we were friends.
We are.
But I'm a sellsword.
I sell my sword.
I don't loan it out
to friends as a favor.
How much?
Double.
Double?
I'm a knight now.
Knights are
worth double.
I don't even know
how much I'm
paying you now.
Which means
you can afford it.
(SOFT GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
Here. Here!
Help me!
(EXHALES)
(SHIP HORN BLOWING)
(PANTING)
Who are you?
I was in
the battle at Blackwater.
I was a captain
and a knight.
Aye, ser,
and serving which king?
The one true king
of Westeros,
Stannis Baratheon.
I thought you were dead.
Everyone
thought you were dead.
And your son?
He may have swam
ashore as you did.
No, the wildfire took him.
I saw it.
I'm so sorry, my friend.
I, too, have lost a son.
There is nothing
worse in this world.
But, Davos,
you were a good father.
If I was a good father,
he'd still be here.
Stannis lives?
He licks his wounds
at Dragonstone.
Will you take me there?
There is nothing
for me at Dragonstone.
This war is not over.
Not for you, maybe.
But for Salladhor Saan,
the war is over.
We're both sworn
to King Stannis.
I am sworn to no man.
I promised you 30 ships
and you promised me
riches and glory.
I delivered the ships.
Stannis never
gives up. Never.
Now he will regroup...
He's a broken man.
His fleet lies
at the bottom
of Blackwater Bay.
They say he sees no one,
not his generals,
not even his wife.
Only the Red Woman
whispering in his ear,
telling him what
she sees in the flames
and burning men alive.
What?
They built a great fire
when Stannis returned.
All those who spoke
against her she called
servants of darkness.
They say she sang to
them as they burned.
I'm a pirate.
You're a smuggler.
Servants of darkness.
I'm thinking Dragonstone
is a good place
for us to avoid.
Take me back there, please.
(SCOFFS) You cannot turn
Stannis against her.
Maybe not, but
I could carve her heart out.
You could try.
If you fail,
they will burn you.
If you succeed,
they'll burn you.
And you've only
just come back to life.
(CHUCKLES) Stay alive
a little longer, my friend.
You call me friend.
You drank with me
on my wedding day.
And you drank with me
on four of mine,
but I don't ask
you for favors.
I have to stop her.
Please, do this for me.
When you are dead,
I will gather your
bones in a little sack
and let your widow
wear them around her neck.
We should set
the siege lines 1,000
yards from Harrenhal.
There won't be a siege.
The Mountain
can't defend a ruin.
The Mountain will defend
whatever Tywin Lannister
tells him.
The Lannisters
have been running
from us since Oxcross.
I'd love a fight.
The men would love a fight.
I don't think
we're going to get one.
(BLOOD DRIPPING)
(FLY BUZZING)
RICKARD: Two hundred Northmen
slaughtered like sheep.
The debt will be repaid,
my friend.
For them and for your sons.
Will it?
They rot in the ground
while their killer
runs free.
The Kingslayer won't
remain free for long.
My best hunters
are after him.
ROBB: A Mallister?
CATELYN: Ser Jeremy.
My father's bannerman.
(SIGHS)
Find her a chamber
that will serve as a cell.
TALISA: She's your mother.
ROBB: She freed
Jaime Lannister.
The Lannisters
robbed them of their sons
and she robbed them
of their justice.
(COUGHING)
QYBURN: Water.
(WHISPERS) Water.
This needs to be
cleaned and closed.
What's your name, friend?
Qyburn.
You're lucky
to be alive.
Lucky?
The badge looks
good on you.
Almost as good as
it looked on me.
Are you enjoying
your new position?
Am I enjoying it?
I was very happy
as Hand of the King.
(TYWIN CHUCKLES)
Yes.
I heard how happy you were.
(BLOWS)
You brought
a whore into my bed.
It wasn't your bed
at the time.
I sent you here
to advise the king.
I gave you real
power and authority.
You chose to
spend your days
as you always have,
bedding harlots and
drinking with thieves.
Occasionally I drank
with the harlots.
What do you want, Tyrion?
Why does everyone assume
I want something?
Can't I simply visit
with my beloved father?
My beloved father who
somehow forgot to
visit his wounded son
after he fell on
the battlefield.
Maester Pycelle assured me
your wounds were not fatal.
I organized
the defense of this city
while you held court in
the ruins of Harrenhal.
I led the foray
when the enemies
were at the gate
while your grandson,
the king, quivered in fear
behind the walls.
I bled in the mud
for our family.
And as my reward,
I was trundled off to
some dark little cell.
But what do I want?
A little bloody gratitude
would be a start.
Jugglers and singers
require applause.
You are a Lannister.
Do you think I demanded
a garland of roses
every time I suffered
a wound on a battlefield?
Hmm?
Now, I have seven
kingdoms to look after
and three of them
are in open rebellion.
So tell me what you want.
I want what is mine
by right.
Jaime is your eldest son,
heir to your lands
and titles.
But he is a Kingsguard,
forbidden from
marriage or inheritance.
The day Jaime put
on the white cloak,
he gave up his claim
to Casterly Rock.
I am your son
and lawful heir.
You want Casterly Rock?
It is mine by right.
(SIGHS)
We'll find you accommodations
more suited to your name
and as a reward for
your accomplishments
during the battle
of Blackwater Bay.
And when the time is right,
you will be given a position
fit for your talents
so that you can
serve your family
and protect our legacy.
And if you serve faithfully,
you will be rewarded
with a suitable wife.
And I would let myself
be consumed by maggots
before mocking the family
name and making you
heir to Casterly Rock.
Why?
You ask that?
You, who killed your mother
to come into the world?
You are an ill-made,
spiteful little creature
full of envy,
lust, and low cunning.
Men's laws give you
the right to bear my name
and display my colors
since I cannot prove
that you are not mine.
And to teach me humility,
the Gods have condemned me
to watch you waddle about
wearing that proud lion
that was my father's sigil
and his father's before him.
But neither Gods nor men
will ever compel me to
let you turn Casterly Rock
into your whorehouse.
Go, now.
Speak no more of
your rights to Casterly Rock.
Go.
One more thing.
The next whore I catch
in your bed I'll hang.
SANSA: Dorne.
It's going to Dorne.
SHAE: Why Dorne?
It's carrying silk
and it's supposed to bring
back wine in exchange.
But it's not coming back.
The captain's tired
of risking his life
so King's Landing
lords and ladies
can get drunk
on better wine
than they deserve.
He's going to
stay in Dorne.
Wait out the winter
where it's beautiful
and warm.
I met some people in Dorne
who weren't so
beautiful and warm.
Don't ruin the game.
I told you,
I don't want to play.
What about that one there?
SHAE: That one?
It's going to Volantis.
Why?
Because when I got
on a ship in Volantis,
it looked like that one.
That's not
how the game works.
You're not supposed to just
blurt out the right answer.
You've got to invent
a story about where
the ship is going and why.
Why should I make up a story
when I know the truth?
Because the truth
is always either
terrible or boring.
Lovely day for it.
Watching the ships.
Lord Baelish.
Might I speak
with Lady Sansa
alone for a moment?
I saw your mother
not long ago.
She's very eager
to see you.
And your sister.
Arya's alive?
You said you'd take me home.
You said King's Landing
was your home.
You are the property
of the crown. Stealing you
would be treason.
If you were to tell
just one person...
I won't tell anyone.
How do I know?
Because I'm a terrible liar.
You said so yourself.
Please, Lord Baelish.
Tell me what to do.
Tell me when.
I'm waiting for
word on an assignment
that will take me
far away from the capital.
When I set sail,
I might be able to
take you with me.
But you'll need to
be ready to leave
on a moment's notice.
You're her handmaiden?
Yes. And you're his...
I help manage his affairs.
He's an important person.
So is she.
I grew up in the shadow
of her father's castle.
The day she was born,
they rang the bells
from sunrise till sunset.
We've both done
rather well, you and I.
Yes.
Given where we started.
And where is that?
It's not easy
for girls like us
to dig our way out.
Watch out for her.
I always do.
Watch out for her with him.
(DRAGON SCREECHING)
(ALL SCREECHING)
They're growing fast.
(PURRS)
Not fast enough.
I can't wait that long.
I need an army.
We'll be in Astapor
by nightfall.
Some say the Unsullied
are the greatest
soldiers in the world.
The greatest slave-soldiers
in the world.
The distinction
means a good deal
to some people.
Do those people
have any better ideas
about how to put you
on the Iron Throne?
It's too beautiful
a day to argue.
(MAN VOMITING)
You're right.
(MAN COUGHING)
Another lovely day
on the high seas.
DAENERYS: Don't mock them.
They're the first
Dothraki on a ship.
They followed me
across the poison water.
If they'll do it,
others will. And
with a true khalasar...
The Dothraki follow strength
above all, Khaleesi.
You'll have a true
khalasar when you
prove yourself strong.
And not before.
DAVOS: Your Grace.
I heard you were dead.
Not yet.
I had hoped to speak
to you alone, Your Grace.
We are alone.
Your Grace,
you are the rightful king.
Not only by blood.
You're an honorable man,
a just man.
And there is
still a war to fight.
I am fighting.
By burning
prisoners alive?
How would you punish
the infidels, Ser Davos?
I do not judge people
for the Gods they worship.
If I did, I'd have
thrown you in the sea
before you ever set
foot on Dragonstone.
I'm not your enemy.
You are my enemy.
Was it me you fought
on Blackwater Bay?
Did I set
your ships ablaze?
I wasn't there
when the wildfire
killed our men
by the thousands.
I could have
saved those men.
You would have taken
the city, Stannis would sit
upon his rightful throne,
and you would
stand beside him.
But I wasn't there
because you convinced
your king to leave me behind.
Do you hear them screaming?
All those burning men
in the water crying
for their mothers,
for their Gods for help?
Until the moment
the Blackwater
swallowed them.
Don't despair, Ser Davos.
What I told
your son is true.
Death by fire is
the purest death.
(GRUNTS)
This woman is evil!
(KNIFE CLATTERING)
She's the mother of demons.
Take him and
lock him in a cell.
Your Grace!
Come on.
You've chosen the darkness,
Ser Davos.
She will destroy us all!
MELISANDRE:
I will pray for you.
DAVOS: Your Grace!
(DOOR CLOSES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
MAN 1: Halt. Down.
MAN 2: Halt. Down.
(THUDDING)
Why have we stopped?
It's Lady Margaery,
Your Grace.
JOFFREY: What is she doing?
Who gave her permission?
FEMALE SERVANT: My lady.
We should have guards,
my lady.
MARGAERY: Why?
Pardon me.
Stop, my lady.
You'll ruin your dress.
I have others.
(BABY CRYING)
Would you like to
speak with her, Your Grace?
(ALL MURMURING)
No.
He was a soldier.
He went to fight on
the walls when the ships
came into Blackwater Bay.
He never came back.
And your mother?
She died when she had me.
Bad men wanted to
come into this city
and do terrible things,
but your father
stopped them.
Whenever you
look at this knight,
I want you to
remember your father.
He wasn't a knight.
He was just a soldier.
And what do
knights swear to do?
Protect the weak
and uphold the good.
Your father did that.
Be proud of him.
Was your father
a soldier, too?
You should be proud, too.
Under King Joffrey's
leadership, your
fathers saved the city.
They saved us all.
From now on,
we're going to
take care of you.
All of you.
(CHILDREN CHATTERING
EXCITEDLY)
(CHUCKLING)
Come to me for what
you need to feed them,
clothe them, or house them.
Directly to me.
(MARGAERY CHUCKLING)
(DOOR OPENS)
Your Grace.
Please, sit. Sit.
I do apologize, my lady.
Small Council meetings.
At what point does
it become treason
to waste the king's time?
(CHUCKLES)
That's a lovely gown,
my lady.
Yes, it suits
you perfectly.
I imagine you
might be rather cold.
The climate is
a bit more forgiving
back in Highgarden,
Your Grace.
JOFFREY: Shall I have them
bring you a shawl, my lady?
I am touched by
your concern, Your Grace.
Luckily for us Tyrells,
our blood runs quite warm.
Doesn't it, Loras?
Yes.
Loras, isn't
the queen's gown
magnificent?
The fabric, the embroidery,
the metalwork.
I've never seen
anything like it.
You might find a bit
of armor quite useful
once you become queen.
Perhaps before.
Joffrey tells me you
stopped your carriage
at Flea Bottom
on your way back from
the sept this morning.
Yes. I paid a visit
to an orphanage the
High Septon told me about.
Margaery does
a great deal of work
with the poor
back in Highgarden.
MARGAERY: The lowest
among us are no different
from the highest
if you give them
a chance
and approach them
with an open heart.
CERSEI: An open heart
is what you'll get
if you're not careful,
my dear.
Not long ago,
we were attacked
by a mob there.
We had a full complement
of guards that
didn't stop them.
The king barely
escaped with his life.
My mother's always had
a penchant for drama.
Facts become less and
less important to her
as she grows older.
Our lives were
never truly in danger.
You're right, of course.
But you are
your father's son.
We can't all have
a king's bravery.
(SIGHS)
Hunger turns
men into beasts.
I'm glad House Tyrell
has been able to
help in this regard.
They tell me 100
wagons arrive daily now
from the Reach.
Wheat, barley, apples.
We've had a blessed harvest.
And it's our duty
to assist the capital
in time of need.
Well, as Ser Loras said,
Lady Margaery
has done this sort
of, uh,
charitable work before.
I'm sure she knows
what she's doing.
I'm sure she does.
(DRAGONS SCREECHING)
(SPEAKS VALYRIAN)
MISSANDEI: The Unsullied have
stood here for a day and a
night with no food or water.
(KRAZNYS CONTINUES
SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
MISSANDEI: They will
stand until they drop.
(KRAZNYS CONTINUES
SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
Such is
their obedience.
They may suit my needs.
Tell me of their training.
(BOTH SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
MISSANDEI: They begin
their training at 5.
Every day they
drill from dawn to dusk
until they have
mastered the shortsword,
the shield,
and the three spears.
Only one boy in four
survives this
rigorous training.
(SPEAKS VALYRIAN)
MISSANDEI: Their discipline
and loyalty are absolute.
They fear nothing.
Even the bravest
men fear death.
(IN VALYRIAN)
MISSANDEI: My master says
the Unsullied are not men.
Death means nothing to them.
(IN VALYRIAN)
He begs you attend
to this carefully,
Your Grace.
(SPEAKS VALYRIAN)
Tell the good master
there is no need.
MISSANDEI: My master
points out that
men don't need nipples.
(IN VALYRIAN)
(KRAZNYS CONTINUES
SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
To win his shield,
an Unsullied must go
to the slave marts
with a silver mark,
find a newborn
and kill it before
its mother's eyes.
This way, my master says,
we make certain
there is no
weakness left in them.
You take a babe
from its mother's arms,
kill it as she watches,
and pay for her pain
with a silver coin?
(IN VALYRIAN)
My master would
like you to know
that the silver is paid
to the baby's owner,
not the mother.
How many
do you have to sell?
(MISSANDEI REPEATS
IN VALYRIAN)
Eight thousand.
(IN VALYRIAN)
MISSANDEI: Master Kraznys
asks that you please hurry.
Many other buyers
are interested.
DAENERYS: Eight thousand
dead babies.
The Unsullied are
a means to an end.
Once I own them,
these men...
They're not men.
Not anymore.
Once I own
an army of slaves,
what will I be?
You think these slaves
will have better lives
serving men
like Kraznys
or serving you?
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
You'll be fair to them.
You won't mutilate
them to make a point.
You won't order them
to murder babies.
You'll see they're
properly fed and sheltered.
A great injustice
has been done to them.
Closing your eyes
will not undo it.
(CHUCKLES)
(DAENERYS GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(HISSES)
The warlocks.
I owe you my life, ser.
The honor is mine,
my queen.
You know this man?
I know him
as one of
the greatest fighters
the Seven Kingdoms
has ever seen
and as the Lord Commander
of Robert Baratheon's
Kingsguard.
King Robert is dead.
I have been searching for
you, Daenerys Stormborn,
to ask your forgiveness.
I was sworn to
protect your family.
I failed them.
I am Barristan Selmy,
Kingsguard to your father.
Allow me to join
your Queensguard and
I will not fail you again.