We shouldn't be
out here alone.
Why not?
If your father...
He'll never know
we're gone.
But if he finds out...
You don't need to be
afraid of my father.
GIRL 1: Are you sure?
GIRL 2: Yes.
We shouldn't go in.
Of course we should.
(ANIMAL SCREECHES)
(SCREAMS)
Get out! Get out!
Let's go.
No.
Listen to your friend.
They said that
you were terrifying,
with cat's teeth
and three eyes.
You're not terrifying.
You're boring.
You don't know what I am.
I know you're a witch
and you can see the future.
Tell me mine.
Everyone wants to
know their future
until they know
their future.
This is my father's land.
My land.
Tell me my future,
or I'll have
your two boring eyes
gouged out of your head.
(LAUGHS SOFTLY)
Your blood.
Give me a taste.
(GASPS)
Three questions you get.
You won't like
the answers.
I've been promised
to the prince.
When will we marry?
You will never
wed the prince.
You will wed the king.
But I will be queen?
Oh, yes.
You'll be queen.
For a time.
Then comes another,
younger,
more beautiful,
to cast you down and
take all you hold dear.
Will the king and I
have children?
No. The king will
have 20 children,
and you will have three.
That doesn't make sense.
Gold will be their crowns.
Gold their shrouds.
(LAUGHING)
GIRL 1: Come on,
we have to go.
We have to go! Cersei.
MAN: Bearers, put it down.
(BELL TOLLING)
Bearers, up.
Away.
SEPTON: Your Grace,
we are honored
by your presence.
The mourners are waiting.
They will keep waiting.
I want a moment
alone with him.
But, Your Grace,
many of these
lords and ladies
have traveled day and night
to be here from
all seven kingdoms.
CERSEI: They will wait.
(DOOR OPENS)
He never wanted you
to be a Kingsguard,
but here you are,
protecting his dead body.
What he built,
it's ours.
He built it for us.
He meant it for us.
They're going to
try to take it away.
All of it.
They?
All of them out there.
Our enemies.
They're waiting in line
to make sure he's really dead.
And as soon as they see
the stones on his eyes,
they'll set to work
on tearing us apart.
They have nothing
to do with it.
The man who
murdered our father,
he tore us apart.
He's the enemy.
I've been
telling you for years.
You've been
defending him for years.
This is exactly
what they want.
And now
our father is dead,
and that little monster
is out there somewhere
drawing breath.
Did you set him free?
Tyrion may be a monster,
but at least he killed
our father on purpose.
You killed him by mistake.
With stupidity.
You're a man of action,
aren't you?
When it occurs to
you to do something,
you do it.
Never mind
the consequences.
Take a look.
Look at the consequences.
Here they are.
He loved you more than
anyone in this world.
(SEA WAVES CRASHING)
(SEAGULLS SQUAWKING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(GRUNTING)
(WOOD CREAKS)
(STRAINING)
Apologies.
I still don't see
why I had to stay
in this fucking crate
once we set sail.
I saved your life.
If they catch you,
they catch me.
I cannot say I feel
overly guilty
about leaving you
in that fucking crate.
Do you know what it's like
to stuff your shit
through one of
those air holes?
No, I only know what it's like
to pick up your shit
and throw it overboard.
Pentos?
The home of my colleague,
Illyrio Mopatis, a merchant.
He and I met many years ago
through mutual friends.
A group of people who
saw Robert Baratheon
for the disaster he was.
We tried to do what
was best for the realm
by supporting
a Targaryen restoration.
And thus began
the chain of mistakes
that has led us both here.
Things have gotten
worse, not better.
Westeros needs to be
saved from itself.
Mmm.
Much better.
My lord?
I don't think
I am anymore.
A lord.
Are you a lord if
you kill your father?
I don't imagine they
revoke your nobility
for killing a whore.
It must happen
all the time.
You already drank yourself
across the Narrow Sea.
In a box. Why stop now?
Because we are talking
about the future
of our country.
The future is shit.
Just like the past.
(MEN GRUNTING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(WOMAN MOANING LOUDLY)
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
(SHUSHING GENTLY)
(HUMMING)
(CHOKING)
DAENERYS:
The Sons of the Harpy?
BARRISTAN: Yes, Your Grace.
They left it on the body.
They've never
killed before.
It was only a matter
of time, Your Grace.
Conquerors always
meet with resistance.
I didn't conquer them.
Their own people did.
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
He did not risk his life
fighting for his freedom
so cowards in masks
could take it away.
And I did not
take up residence
in this pyramid
so I could
watch the city below
decline into chaos.
What was the name
of the man you lost?
White Rat, Your Grace.
I want him buried
with honor, publically,
in the Temple of the Graces.
The Sons of the Harpy
will hear that message.
Make them very angry.
Angry snakes lash out.
Makes chopping off
their heads
that much easier.
Find the men who did this
and bring them to me.
Your Grace.
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
I wanted to speak with you.
Why do you come?
White Rat,
the Unsullied who...
I have heard they found
his body in a brothel.
I have heard that more
than one Unsullied
has been known to visit
Meereen's brothels.
May I ask you why?
Why would an Unsullied
go to a brothel?
I do not know.
I must go.
(GRUNTING)
(METAL CLANGING)
Get your shield up.
It's too heavy.
If it wasn't heavy,
it wouldn't stop a sword.
Now get it up.
Come. Try it again.
Drive at me.
Keep your shield up,
or I'll ring your
head like a bell.
Shouldn't you
be training, too?
Well, I'm hardly
a new recruit.
How many brothers can say
that they've killed
a White Walker and a Thenn?
I might be
the first in history.
JON: Shield up.
ALLISER:
These men need a firm hand.
Always have.
They're poachers and thieves.
Not soldiers.
That one hates me.
SAMWELL:
If Ser Alliser is chosen
as the new Lord Commander...
He hates the wildlings.
(BABY CRYING)
All the wildlings.
Don't let them
send us away.
It's not a sure thing.
Ser Denys Mallister
has commanded
the Shadow Tower for 20 years,
and people say
he's a good man.
He's running
against Ser Alliser...
Sam, don't let them
send us away.
I told you.
Wherever you go, I go, too.
You can't leave.
They'll execute you.
Good, good, pivot.
Don't forget to pivot.
Shield up.
The king wants a word.
(CHAINS RATTLING)
(WIND HOWLING)
You're not cold, my lady?
Never.
The Lord's fire lives
within me, Jon Snow.
Feel.
Are you a virgin?
No.
Good.
Your Grace.
The bastard of Winterfell.
You know who rules
at Winterfell now?
Roose Bolton.
Hmm. The traitor who
plunged a dagger
in Robb Stark's heart.
Don't you want
to avenge him?
I want a great many things,
Your Grace.
But I'm a sworn brother
of the Night's Watch now.
I've been talking to
your sworn brothers.
Many of them love you.
They're good men.
DAVOS: Many don't.
You were seen taking
the body of a wildling girl
north of the Wall.
Why?
It's where she belonged.
Some of the Night's Watch
feel you have
too much affection
for the wildlings.
They were born
on the wrong side
of the Wall.
That doesn't
make them monsters.
STANNIS: No matter.
I shall take back the North
from the thieves who stole it.
Tywin Lannister is dead.
He can't protect them now.
I shall mount
Roose Bolton's
head on a spike.
But if I'm to
take Winterfell,
I need more men.
The men of the Night's Watch
are sworn to play no part...
I'm not talking about
the damn Night's Watch.
I'm talking
about the wildlings.
Your Grace,
you want the wildlings
to march in your army?
If they swear
to follow me,
I'll pardon them.
We'll take Winterfell.
Once the North is won,
I'll declare them
citizens of the realm.
I'll give them
land to live on.
It's a fair offer.
More than fair.
I'll offer them their
lives and their freedom
if Mance kneels before me
and swears his loyalty.
I don't think that's likely.
STANNIS:
You admire him, don't you?
I respect him.
He likes you.
Convince him
to bend the knee,
or he burns.
Your Grace.
How much time do I have?
STANNIS: Nightfall.
The sun drops fast
this time of year.
Hurry, Jon Snow.
MAN: Shield up.
(ROBIN WHIMPERING)
MAN: Attack, my lord!
Attack!
(ROBIN GROANING)
Don't cross your feet.
My sons had
swords in their hands
from the time
they could walk. This one...
LITTLEFINGER: Lord Arryn
will never be a great warrior.
ROYCE: Great warrior?
He swings a sword
like a girl with palsy.
My lord.
MAN: Sword up, my lord!
LITTLEFINGER: Some boys
develop more slowly.
He's still young.
ROYCE: He's 13.
Boys go to war at 13.
He has other gifts.
Does he?
The gift of a great name.
Sometimes
that's all one needs.
(GROANS LOUDLY)
Good-bye, Lord Royce,
and thank you for
all you've done for me.
I have done nothing more
than my duty, my lady.
I have no doubt
that on my return,
Robin's skills will have
improved immeasurably.
He'll be safe here.
As for his skills,
I make no promises.
Will we head north
at some point?
He said Sansa had
a brother at Castle Black.
We're a few days' ride
from the King's Road.
But that will take us...
Us?
The only reason
you're here
is because Jaime Lannister
told me you weren't
safe in the capital.
You're hundreds of miles
from King's Landing.
No one knows
what you look like.
No one cares. You're safe.
But I'm your squire.
Do you even know
what a squire is?
An attendant to a knight.
I'm not a knight.
That means
you're not a squire.
Well, where would I go?
I don't care.
I'm not your mother.
You swore to find
the Stark girls.
I found Arya. She
didn't want my protection.
Sansa still might.
Will you shut your mouth?
I didn't ask
for your advice.
I don't want
anyone following me.
I'm not a leader.
All I ever wanted
was to fight for
a lord I believed in.
The good lords are dead,
and the rest are monsters.
(HORSES NEIGHING)
You told Lord Royce
we were going
to the Fingers.
I did.
But we're heading west.
We are.
If he wanted to betray us,
he already would have.
Lord Royce might
be as honorable
as he thinks he is,
but he's not alone
in that castle.
Do you trust all
those knights and ladies,
stable boys and serving girls?
No, do you trust
the carriage driver
or the knights escorting us?
No. (CHUCKLES)
But I pay them well,
and they've seen what happens
to men who disappoint me.
So where are we going?
To a land where
you trust everyone?
To a land
so far from here,
even Cersei Lannister
can't get her hands on you.
It was such a deep,
deep shock to us all.
Your father was a...
A force to be reckoned with.
He truly was.
I wouldn't presume
to claim to have known
him as such, but...
But just being in
his presence was enough
to make it so clear
just how formidable
a person you
were dealing with.
What a force to
be reckoned with.
Thank you so much
for your kind words.
Deepest condolences,
Your Grace.
This tragedy...
I never trusted Varys.
I often warned...
Your Grace.
Cousin Lancel.
I hardly recognized you.
My deepest sympathies.
I apologize for my
son's appearance.
Uncle, that's
quite all right.
They call themselves Sparrows.
Bloody fanatics.
Religion has its place,
of course,
but at a certain point...
They never would have
come to the capital
when Tywin was alive.
I'm sure he'll grow out
of it, whatever it is.
Excuse me.
Of course.
Your wounds
from the Blackwater
seem to have healed.
It wasn't my wounds
that needed healing.
What can I do for you?
You can forgive me.
What could you possibly
have done to warrant
my forgiveness?
I led you into the darkness.
I doubt you've ever
led anyone anywhere.
I tempted you into our...
unnatural relations.
And, of course,
there was the king,
his boar hunt.
His wine.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I'm a different person now.
I've found peace in
the light of the Seven.
You can, too.
They watch over all of us,
ready to dole out mercy
or justice.
Their world is at hand.
I will pray for
your father's soul.
(LAUGHS)
The day
Tywin Lannister's soul
needs your help...
OLYVAR:
It looks like Dorne.
LORAS: It doesn't.
(OLYVAR LAUGHS)
It does.
That's the Sunspear bit,
right there.
And that's where
the mountains are.
And over here is...
Is Sunsnake?
Stonespear?
Sandstone.
Yes.
Yes, Sandstone.
Just there.
Fine.
It's Dorne.
We should go there.
I think we would
have a lovely time,
judging by my experience.
That would be wonderful.
Dorne, Highgarden.
Anywhere but here.
We're late for
dinner as it is.
You're very respectful.
I'm very hungry.
What's your name?
Olyvar, my lady.
I'm afraid my brother
is keeping the king
waiting, Olyvar.
My lady.
Perhaps you might consider
being a bit more discreet?
Why?
They all know
about me anyway.
Everybody knows
everything about everyone.
What's the point in trying
to keep a secret
in a place like this?
In any event,
you shouldn't keep
your intended waiting.
My intended? Please.
Tywin's dead.
That means no one can
force Cersei to marry me.
Lucky you.
Unlucky you.
You think I want that woman
married to my brother?
If she doesn't marry me,
she doesn't go to Highgarden.
Which means she stays
in King's Landing.
Which means
you're trapped here
with Cersei Lannister
as your mother by law.
Perhaps.
Perhaps?
Eunuch, the spider,
the Master of Whisperers.
Imp, halfman.
There are faster ways
to kill yourself.
Not for a coward.
You are many things,
my friend,
but not a coward.
You never told me
why you set me free.
Your brother asked me to.
Could have said no.
Refuse the Kingslayer?
A dangerous proposition.
Not as dangerous
as releasing me.
You risked your life,
your position, everything.
Why? You're not family.
You owe me nothing.
I didn't do it for you.
I did it for
the Seven Kingdoms.
A drunken dwarf will
never be the savior
of the Seven Kingdoms.
I don't believe in saviors.
I believe men of talent
have a part to play
in the war to come.
You're going to have
to find another soldier.
I'm done with Westeros,
and Westeros
is done with me.
You have many
admirable qualities,
self-pity is not one of them.
Any fool with a bit of luck
can find himself
born into power.
But earning it for yourself,
that takes work.
I'm not well-suited for work.
I think you are.
You have your father's
instincts for politics,
and you have compassion.
Compassion? Yes.
I killed my lover
with my bare hands.
I shot my own father
with a crossbow.
I never said
you were perfect.
What is it
you want exactly?
Peace.
Prosperity.
A land where the powerful
do not prey on the powerless.
Where the castles are
made of gingerbread,
and the moats are filled
with blackberry wine.
The powerful have always
preyed on the powerless.
That's how they
became powerful
in the first place.
Perhaps.
And perhaps we've grown
so used to horror,
we assume
there's no other way.
If you sat
on the Iron Throne,
would you spread misery
throughout the land?
I will never sit
on the Iron Throne.
No, you won't.
But you could help another
climb those steps
and take that seat.
The Seven Kingdoms
need someone
stronger than Tommen,
but gentler than Stannis.
A monarch who can intimidate
the high lords and
inspire the people.
A ruler loved by millions
with a powerful army
and the right family name.
Good luck finding him.
Who said anything
about "him"?
You have a choice,
my friend.
You can stay here
at Illyrio's palace
and drink yourself to death,
or you can ride
with me to Meereen,
meet Daenerys Targaryen,
and decide if the world
is worth fighting for.
Can I drink myself to death
on the road to Meereen?
When did the Unsullied
start patrolling
the streets of Meereen?
Looks like your friends
haven't been
behaving themselves.
Our mission to Yunkai
was a resounding success.
The Wise Masters of Yunkai
have agreed to cede power
to a council of elders
made up of both
the freed men and
the former slaveholders.
All matters of consequence
will be brought
to you for review.
Good.
They did ask for
some concessions.
Concessions?
Politics is the art of
compromise, Your Grace.
I'm not a politician.
I'm a queen.
HIZDAHR: Forgive me.
You're right, of course.
Still, it's easier
to rule happy subjects
than angry ones.
DAENERYS: I don't expect
the Wise Masters to be happy.
Slavery made them rich.
I ended slavery.
They do not ask for
the return of slavery.
They ask for the reopening
of the fighting pits.
DAENERYS: The fighting pits?
Where slaves fought
slaves to the death?
In the new world that
you've brought to us,
free men would fight free men.
The pit fighters you liberated
plead for this opportunity.
Bring some here and
ask them yourself.
No fighting pits.
Opening them would
show the people of
Yunkai and Meereen
that you respect
their traditions.
I do not respect
the tradition of
human cockfighting.
If you...
How many times must I say no
before you understand?
Whatever he wants from me,
he's not going to get it.
If he really believes
I'm going to reopen
the fighting pits...
DAARIO: You should
reopen the fighting pits.
What?
My mother was a whore.
I told you that.
She liked to
drink pear brandy.
The older she got,
the less she made
selling her body, the more
she wanted to drink.
So one day when I was 12,
she sold me to a slaver
she fucked the night before.
I'm sorry.
Why? I was a bad child.
I wasn't big,
but I was quick
and I loved to fight.
So they sold me
to a man in Tolos
who trained fighters
for the pits.
I had my first
match when I was 16.
You were sold
into slavery,
forced to fight to the death
for the amusement
of the masters,
and you're defending
the fighting pits?
(LAUGHS)
I'm only here
because of those pits.
I learned to fight
like a Dothraki screamer,
a Norvoshi priest,
a Westerosi knight.
Soon I was famous.
Ten thousand men
and women screamed
my name when I
stepped into the pit.
I made so much
money for my master,
he set me free when he died.
I joined the Second Sons,
and then I met you.
You're the queen.
Everyone's too afraid
of you to speak truth.
Everyone but me.
You've made
thousands of enemies
all across the world.
As soon as they
see weakness,
they'll attack.
Show your strength
here, now.
That's why I have
the Unsullied
patrolling the streets.
(SCOFFS)
Anyone with a chest
full of gold can buy
an army of Unsullied.
You're not
the Mother of Unsullied.
You're the Mother of Dragons.
I don't want
another child's bones
dropped at my feet.
No one's seen
Drogon in weeks.
For all I know,
he's flown halfway
across the world.
I can't control them anymore.
A dragon queen
with no dragons
is not a queen.
(CHAINS RATTLING)
DAENERYS: Viserion?
Rhaegal?
(ROARING)
Easy. Easy.
Easy.
(SCREECHING)
(DOOR OPENS)
So here we are.
Here we are.
When we first met,
you were my prisoner.
And now,
for our last meeting...
This doesn't have to
be our last meeting.
No, but it will be.
You know what
Stannis wants?
He wants me
to bend the knee.
And he wants the free
folk to fight for him.
I'll give him
this much, he's bold.
Shouldn't a king be bold?
Oh, aye.
I respect him.
If he gets what he wants,
I expect he'll
be a better ruler
than the fools
sitting on the Iron Throne
the last hundred years.
But I'll never serve him.
You told me you
weren't here to conquer.
You told me your
people have bled enough.
That's right.
I don't want them
bleeding for
Stannis Baratheon either.
You spent your life
convincing 90 clans
to come together for
the first time in history.
Thenns and Hornfoots,
the ice-river clans,
even the giants.
A life's work uniting them.
You didn't do it for power.
You didn't do it for glory.
You brought them
together to save them
because none of them
will survive the winter,
not if they're
north of the Wall.
Isn't their survival
more important
than your pride?
Pride?
Fuck my pride.
This isn't about that.
Then bend the knee
and save your people.
They followed me
because they respected me.
Because they
believed in me.
The moment I kneel
for a southern king,
that's all gone.
And how many tens of thousands
are out there right now?
How many women?
How many children?
And you won't go out
and rescue them because why?
You're afraid of
looking afraid.
Oh, I am afraid.
No shame in that.
How will they do it?
Beheading?
Hanging?
They'll burn you alive.
Bad way to go.
I'll be honest with you.
I don't want to die.
And burned to death?
I don't want people to
remember me like that,
scorched and screaming.
But it's better
than betraying
everything I believe.
And what happens
to your people?
You preserve your dignity
and die standing,
and they'll sing
songs about you.
You'd rather burn than kneel.
The great hero.
Until winter comes,
and the White Walkers
come for us all,
and there's no one
left to sing.
You're a good lad.
Truly you are.
But if you can't understand
why I won't enlist my people
in a foreigner's war,
there's no point explaining.
(JON KNOCKING ON DOOR)
I think you're making
a terrible mistake.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
The freedom to
make my own mistakes
was all I ever wanted.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Mance Rayder, you have
been called
the King-beyond-the-Wall.
Westeros only has one king.
Bend the knee,
I promise you mercy.
Kneel and live.
This was my home
for many years.
I wish you good fortune
in the wars to come.
We all must choose.
Man or woman, young or old,
lord or peasant,
our choices are the same.
We choose light,
or we choose darkness.
We choose good,
or we choose evil.
We choose the true
god or the false.
Free folk,
there is only one true king,
and his name is Stannis.
Here stands your king of lies.
Behold the fate of those
who choose the darkness.
(GASPS)
(WHIMPERS LOUDLY)