MAN: (SHOUTING)
We're going to Braavos!
(SEAGULLS SCREECHING)
In the old times,
whenever Braavos
stood in danger,
the Titan would step
with fire in his eyes.
He'd wade into the sea
and smash the enemies.
He's just a statue.
(HORN BLOWS)
(LAUGHS)
Don't be afraid.
He's announcing our arrival.
I'm not afraid.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SIZZLING)
The House of Black and White.
This is where you'll
find the man you seek.
Here I leave you.
Thank you for bringing me.
Any man of Braavos
would have done the same.
Valar Morghulis.
Valar Dohaeris.
(KNOCKS)
Hello.
Valar Morghulis.
Um...
Jaqen H'ghar gave me this.
No one here by that name.
Please.
I crossed the Narrow Sea.
I have nowhere else to go.
You have
everywhere else to go.
But wait...
(LOCK CLANKS)
Cersei.
Walder Frey.
The Mountain.
Meryn Trant.
Cersei.
Walder Frey.
The Mountain.
Meryn Trant.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Cersei. Walder Frey.
The Mountain.
Meryn Trant.
Cersei.
Walder Frey.
The Mountain.
Meryn Trant.
Cersei.
Walder Frey.
The Mountain.
Meryn Trant.
(SIGHS)
(PEOPLE CHATTING)
Must be good food
if it's crowded.
Ale?
Before we left,
a maester gave
you a raven scroll.
You are becoming
an observant young lady.
My mother used to say,
"Dark wings, dark words."
An old saying.
Inaccurate in this case.
Excuse me.
SANSA: So, it was good news?
My marriage
proposal has been accepted.
I thought you still mourned
the death of my
beloved Aunt Lysa.
Ale?
SANSA: I'll have some.
My lady.
What is it?
PODRICK: Sansa Stark.
Don't look.
You sure?
She's dyed her hair,
but it's her.
She's sitting
with Petyr Baelish.
Littlefinger?
A bunch of knights with him.
A bunch? What's a bunch,
Podrick? Six? 20?
Ten, I think. Too many.
My lady, I don't
think this is the right...
Ready the horses.
We only have one horse.
Find more.
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
LITTLEFINGER:
Do you like the taste?
I don't see what
all the fuss is about.
Why do men love it so much?
It gives some men courage.
Does it give you courage?
GUARD: That's far enough.
Lord Baelish, Lady Sansa.
My name is Brienne of Tarth.
We've met with
Renly Baratheon.
What did he say about you?
He said
your loyalty
came free of charge.
Someone appears to have
paid quite a bit
for it since then.
Lady Sansa,
before your mother's death,
I was her sworn sword.
I gave my word
I would find you
and protect you.
I will shield your
back and keep your counsel
and give my life
for yours if need be.
I swear it by
the Old Gods and the New.
Please, Lady Brienne,
no need for such formality.
You were Catelyn
Stark's sworn sword?
I was.
Strange.
I knew Cat from
the time we were children.
She never mentioned you.
It was after Renly's murder.
Ah. Yes.
You were accused
of killing him.
I tried to save him.
But you were accused.
By men who didn't
see what happened.
And what did happen?
He was murdered by a shadow.
A shadow with the face
of Stannis Baratheon.
A shadow?
With the face...
(SCOFFS)
LITTLEFINGER: This woman
swore to protect Renly.
She failed.
She swore to protect
your mother. She failed.
Why would I want somebody
with your history of failure
guarding Lady Sansa?
Why should you have
any say in her affairs?
Because I am her uncle.
I married her Aunt Lysa
shortly before my
beloved's untimely death.
We're family now,
and you are an outsider.
Forgive me, Lady Brienne,
but experience has made me
wary of outsiders.
Lady Sansa, if we
can have a word alone...
No.
Please, my lady.
If I could explain...
I saw you at Joffrey's wedding
bowing to the king.
Neither of us
wanted to be there.
Sometimes we
don't have a choice.
And sometimes we do.
You should leave.
We don't want our
new friend wandering
the countryside alone.
The roads in these
parts aren't safe.
Why don't you stay?
The man asked you to stay...
(GUARDS SHOUTING)
(HORSES NEIGHING)
Hyah! Hyah!
(GRUNTS)
GUARD: After her!
(MEN SHOUTING)
BRIENNE: Yah! Hah!
PODRICK: Oh!
PODRICK: Stop!
GUARD 1: I'll take him!
Podrick!
(SCREAMING)
GUARD 2: Hold on to her!
Take her!
GUARD 3: Keep moving!
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(WHIMPERING) Stop!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
(HORSE NEIGHS)
That's a good boy.
Come on. Come on.
(NEIGHS)
No, no, no, stop!
(HOOF BEATS)
(HORSE NEIGHS)
I guess that
means you're unarmed.
BRIENNE: Down, Podrick! Down!
(WHIMPERS)
(BOTH SHOUTING)
(GRUNTS)
Podrick.
Yes, my lady?
You can stand now.
Yes, my lady.
Sansa Stark?
Wary of strangers,
as she should be.
I saw her riding
on the East Road
with Littlefinger.
We'll follow them.
My lady,
If both Stark girls
refused your service,
maybe you're
released from your vow.
I swore to their mother
I would protect those girls.
But if they don't
want your protection...
Do you think she's
safe with Littlefinger?
No, my lady.
Get your horse.
(DOOR OPENS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
A summons from the queen.
CERSEI: There are only
two like it in the world.
The one I'm wearing,
the one I gave to Myrcella.
It's a threat.
Of course it's a threat.
Our daughter's alone in Dorne
surrounded by people
who hate our family.
"It's a threat."
No note?
They blame us for the death
of Oberyn and his sister
and every other tragedy
that's befallen
their cursed country.
I will burn their
cities to the ground
if they touch her.
Softer.
What?
Not so loud.
Our daughter's in danger
and you're worried
I'm speaking too loudly?
The world can't know
she's our daughter.
Then don't call
her your daughter.
You've never been
a father to her.
If I was a father to
any of my children,
they'd be
stoned in the street.
And what has your
caution brought?
Our eldest child murdered
at his own wedding.
Our only daughter
shipped off to Dorne.
Our baby boy set to marry
that smirking
whore from Highgarden.
I'm going to
make things better.
You've never made
anything better.
I'm going to Dorne
and I'm bringing
our daughter home.
(SCOFFS)
You can't just
ask Prince Doran
to give her back.
She's promised to his son.
I'm not going to
ask him anything.
You go down
there with an army,
it's an act of war.
No army.
Do you know where
they're keeping her?
Oberyn mentioned
the Water Gardens.
I'll find her.
Is there anything else,
Your Grace?
(CHUCKLES)
You're going to Dorne?
A one-handed man, alone.
I never said I
was going alone.
No sunflowers.
I don't like yellow.
Roses are very nice.
Definitely roses.
And music. I adore music.
But no flutes. I hate flutes.
We can have a harp if
you like, but no flutes.
Then there's the food.
Food is the most
important thing.
Don't you agree?
We're going to
need pigeon pies.
That's what they eat in
the capital, don't they?
Don't they?
Don't who?
People eat pigeon
pie in the capital.
They certainly do, my dear.
It's a fine place, isn't it?
A fine place.
I never thought I'd end up
settling down in
a place like this.
You won't.
Pardon?
We won't get to
live at Stokeworth.
When Mother dies,
my sister gets the castle
because she's older.
She hates me.
She calls me mean names,
and sometimes, even still,
she pulls my hair when
Mother's not looking.
You know what I think?
I think you're a good person.
And your sister
is a mean person.
She is.
I've been all over the world,
and if there's one
thing I've learned,
it's that
meanness comes around.
People like your sister,
they always get
what's coming to
them eventually.
One way or another.
Who's that?
Jaime fucking Lannister.
Ser Jaime.
Ser Bronn of the Blackwater.
I was very sorry to
hear about your father.
Thank you.
This is my betrothed, Lollys.
A pleasure.
Run along, love.
Beautiful young
bride you've chosen.
When were you
planning on getting married?
Just get on with it.
On with what?
What you're here for.
There's no way this
little visit could
possibly mean
anything good for me.
It's very good for you.
Lollys will be
marrying Ser Willis Bracken.
Mmm.
We made a deal,
your sister and I.
I would have
advised against that.
How is this good for me?
'Cause you're
going to come with me
and help me with
something important.
And when we return,
I'm going to give
you a much better girl
and a much better castle.
Return from where?
As far south as south goes.
TRYSTANE: My future queen.
(SPEAKING SOFTLY)
You are beautiful.
The prince does not
wish to be disturbed.
Remove yourself from
my path or I'll take
that long axe and
I'll shove it up your...
DORAN: Captain.
Let her pass.
Your brother was murdered,
and you sit here in
the Water Gardens,
staring at the sky
and doing nothing.
Oberyn was slain
during a trial by combat.
By law, that is not murder.
Your brother.
You don't have to remind me.
He was my brother
long before he
was anything to you.
What will you do
about his death?
I will bury him.
I will mourn for him.
And then?
You would have me go to war?
The whole country
would have you go to war.
Then we are lucky
the whole country
does not decide.
The Sand Snakes are with me.
They have
the love of their people.
They will avenge
their father while
you sit here in your
chair doing nothing.
Oberyn is dead,
and this Lannister girl
skips about the Water Gardens,
eating our food,
breathing our air.
How many of your
brothers and sisters
do they have to kill?
Let me have her.
Let me send her to
Cersei one finger at a time.
I loved my brother.
And you made him very happy.
For that, you will always
have a place in my heart.
But we do not
mutilate little girls
for vengeance.
Not here.
Not while I rule.
And how long will that be?
DAARIO: The Unsullied
are too conspicuous.
Anyone can see you
coming from a mile off.
Of course you haven't found
any Sons of the Harpy.
You haven't, have you?
(GRUNTS)
My Second Sons,
on the other hand,
they drink, whore,
fight in the streets,
they blend in.
They overhear
things in taverns,
follow people to nice,
quiet alleys,
break a few fingers,
overhear a few more things.
Before you know it...
No one here.
We go.
In a hurry? You're afraid?
Unsullied fear nothing.
Right.
That's your problem.
You understood
fear once long ago,
but you've
forgotten what it means.
Someone who's forgotten fear
has forgotten how to hide.
(MAN SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
Fear is useful that way.
(SCREAMS)
Sons of the Harpy,
they want to put
a collar back on my neck.
On all of our necks.
Please, Your Grace,
you must kill him.
It would send a message.
I think you should
exercise restraint,
Your Grace.
Why?
For one thing,
he may have
valuable information.
The Son of the Harpy
has no more
valuable information.
How do you know that?
Because I questioned him.
HIZDAHR: And
the information you did get,
he is young and poor.
He is born free.
Why should he want
to bring back slavery?
What did it do for him?
Perhaps the only
thing that gave him pride
was knowing that
there was someone
lower than he was.
They pay him.
Great families
afraid to do a thing.
They pay poor men
to do it for them.
And how do you know this?
Everyone know this.
I don't know it,
and I'm the head
of a great family.
BARRISTAN: We do not know
what this man
did or didn't do.
Give him a trial at least.
A fair trial.
Show all
the citizens of Meereen
that you're better than
those who would depose you.
Teach them a better way.
I do not know the place
from where Old Ser comes.
Things maybe are
different there, I hope.
But here in Meereen,
before Daenerys Stormborn,
they own us.
So we learn much about them,
or we do not live long.
They teach me what they are.
Mercy, fair trial,
these mean nothing to them.
All they understand is blood.
DAENERYS: Thank you
all for your counsel.
Your Grace,
a word, please, I beg you.
About what?
About your father.
About the Mad King.
The Mad King?
You're here to remind
me of my enemies' lies?
Consider me reminded.
Your Grace,
I served in his Kingsguard.
I was at his
side from the first.
Your enemies did not lie.
Go on.
When the people rose
in revolt against him,
your father set their
towns and castles aflame.
He murdered sons in
front of their fathers.
He burned men
alive with wildfire
and laughed as they screamed.
And his efforts to
stamp out dissent
led to rebellion
that killed every
Targaryen except two.
I'm not my father.
No, Your Grace.
Thank the gods.
But the Mad King
gave his enemies
the justice he
thought they deserved.
And each time,
it made him feel
powerful and right.
Until the very end.
I will not have
the Son of the Harpy
executed without a fair trial.
Your Grace.
(NEIGHING)
(BLEATING)
There's a bug.
Yes, best be careful.
You might accidentally
consume some solid food.
When I agreed
to come with you,
did I
misrepresent my intentions?
Besides,
what else is
there for me to do
inside this fucking box?
You don't like it?
I want to take a walk.
You can't.
Cersei has offered a lordship
to the man who
brings her your head.
She ought to offer her cunt.
Best part of her for
the best part of me.
Well, I suppose a box
is as good a place
for me as anywhere.
Are we really going to
spend the entire
road to Volantis
talking about
the futility of everything?
You're right. No point.
The road to Volantis?
You said we were
going to Meereen.
What's in Volantis?
The road to Meereen.
And what do you hope
to find at the end of
the road to Meereen?
I told you. A ruler.
We've already got a ruler.
Everywhere has
already got a ruler.
Every pile of shit on
the side of every road
has someone's
banner hanging from it.
You were quite good,
you know, at ruling.
During your
brief tenure as Hand.
I didn't rule.
I was a servant.
Still, a man of talent.
Managed to kill
a lot of people.
Yes,
but you showed great promise
in other areas as well.
She wanted me to
leave King's Landing.
She begged me.
I wouldn't go.
Why?
'Cause I liked it.
Power.
Even as a servant.
People follow leaders.
And they will never follow us.
They find us repulsive.
I find us repulsive.
And we find them repulsive,
which is why we
surround ourselves
with large, comfortable boxes
to keep them away.
And yet,
no matter what we do,
people like you and me
are never really
satisfied inside the box.
Not for long.
You're right.
Let's go for a walk.
No.
How many dwarves are
there in the world?
Is Cersei going
to kill them all?
(FLY BUZZING)
Not him.
Are you trying to
deceive your queen?
Shall I throw them
in a cell, Your Grace?
That won't be necessary,
Ser Meryn.
I don't want to
dissuade the other hunters.
Mistakes will be made.
Thank you, Your Grace.
Take the head.
Pardon me, Your Grace.
I would take it,
if you don't mind.
It could prove
useful for my work.
Very good.
Over there will be fine.
You heard the man. Over there.
(DOOR CLOSES)
You're the Hand of the King?
No, Uncle.
Clearly it would
not be appropriate
for a woman to
assume that role.
I'm merely advising my son
until he comes of age
and chooses
a Hand for himself.
Your Grace,
I would be willing
to serve provisionally
as the King's Hand
until he becomes old enough...
You're a good man,
Lord Tyrell,
but I don't imagine
you'll have the time.
In addition to
being Master of Ships,
the king has
appointed you Master of Coin.
Oh, Your Grace.
He called your
experience and wisdom
in financial
matters unparalleled.
He said he would be
honored to have you
represent the crown's
interests in the same.
The honor is all mine,
Your Grace.
Your Grace, in
the past on several occasions,
a grand maester has served
as the King's Hand.
The king has named Qyburn
the new Master of Whisperers.
Your Grace, him? This man?
This
embarrassment to the Citadel?
Your Grace,
what qualifications
can he possibly
have for this post?
The qualification of loyalty,
Grand Maester.
That's far more than
the eunuch ever had.
Far more than many ever have.
I must say, I cannot see...
Uncle Kevan,
in light of your position
as commander of
the Lannister armies,
it would please the king
if you would serve
as his Master of War.
No man living better
deserves the title.
That is kind of you to say.
I would like to hear it
from the king himself.
The king is very
busy at this moment.
He should be here
learning what
it means to rule.
He is learning.
On this occasion,
in his capacity as ruler,
he's asked me to
speak on his behalf.
I returned to
the capital to pay my
respects to my brother.
And to you.
And to serve the king.
I did not return to
serve as your puppet.
To watch you stack
the Small Council
with sycophants.
Sending your own brother away
so he wouldn't be...
My brother has
left the capital to
lead a sensitive
diplomatic mission.
What mission?
That is not your
concern as Master of War.
I do not
recognize your authority
to dictate what is
and is not my concern.
You are the Queen Mother,
nothing more.
You would abandon your king
in his time of need?
If he wants to send for me,
I will be waiting for him.
At Casterly Rock.
(DOOR CLOSES)
SHIREEN:
Come on, you know this one.
It looks like an animal.
Snake.
Snake. S.
It's an S.
Right, very good.
Huh!
Did you know that the youngest
Lord Commander in history,
Osric Stark,
was elected at the age of 10?
I know S.
You'll learn, I promise.
I taught Ser Davos,
and old people
are terrible at
learning new things.
Well,
you're a wonderful teacher.
Very patient.
I only said that the more time
that you spend practicing,
the faster you'll
be able to read.
That's all right.
We're doing just fine.
I'm sure you and Ostrich Stark
have a lot to talk about.
How old were you
when you learned how to read?
Three.
Three?
Who taught you, your mother?
No, old Maester Cressen did.
I had a lot of
time to practice.
My mother kept me
inside because...
What do you call
it in the south,
what happened to your face?
Greyscale.
What do you call it
north of the Wall?
I don't know.
But two of my sisters had it.
They both died.
How did they cure you?
I don't remember.
I was a baby.
Lots of people came
and tried, I think.
Whatever they did,
it went away.
What happened to your sisters?
My father made them
move out of the keep
into the hut outside.
None of us were
allowed to go near them.
But we heard them,
especially at night.
They started to sound
not like themselves.
Did you ever see them?
Only once at the end.
They were covered with it.
Their faces, their arms.
They acted like animals.
My father had to drag them
out to the woods on a rope.
What did he do with
them in the woods?
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Mother.
Leave us.
Your Grace.
You need to stay
away from that girl.
Why?
She's a wildling.
Her name is Gilly. She's nice.
I'm teaching her to read.
She's a wildling.
Your father
defeated her people.
He executed their
king for treason.
They could strike at
him by striking at you.
Gilly wouldn't do that.
You have no idea
what people will do.
All your books and
you still don't know.
STANNIS:
I ordered Mance Rayder
burned at the stake.
You prevented that order
from being carried out.
You showed mercy
to Mance Rayder.
A king's word is law.
Perhaps you
should ask Ser Davos
how much mercy I
show to lawbreakers.
Show too much kindness,
people won't fear you.
If they don't fear you,
they don't follow you.
With respect, Your Grace,
the free folk
will never follow you
no matter what you do.
You're the man who
burned their king alive.
Who, then?
You?
No.
Only one of their own.
Do you know
this wretched girl,
Lyanna Mormont?
The Lord Commander's niece.
Lady of Bear Island
and a child of 10.
I asked her to commit
her house to my cause.
That's her response.
JON:
"Bear Island knows no king
but the King in the North,
"whose name is Stark."
That amuses you?
I apologize, Your Grace.
Northerners can be
a bit like the free folk.
Loyal to their own.
STANNIS: I know.
My brother, Robert,
went on often and loudly
about how difficult
it was to control them.
Even with your father's help.
Tonight, the Night's Watch
elects a new Lord Commander.
Ser Alliser
Thorne is going to win.
Most likely.
Unpleasant man.
He thinks you're a traitor.
What's your life
going to be like here
at the Wall with
Thorne in command?
Unpleasant, I expect.
Your bravery
made him look weak.
He'll punish you for it.
I don't punish
men for bravery.
I reward them.
I don't doubt it, Your Grace.
But I'm a brother
of the Night's Watch.
I pledged them my life,
my honor, my sword.
I don't know what I
have left to give you.
You can give me the North.
I can't.
Even if I wanted to,
I'm a bastard, a Snow.
Kneel before me.
Lay your sword at my feet.
Pledge me your service
and you'll rise
again as Jon Stark,
Lord of Winterfell.
He'll make you a Stark
with the stroke of a pen?
It's the first thing I
ever remember wanting.
I'd daydream that my father
would ask the king
and just like that,
I would never be
the Bastard of
Winterfell again.
You deserve this. You do.
I couldn't be happier for you.
I'm going to refuse him.
But you'd be
Lord of Winterfell.
I swore a vow to
the Night's Watch.
If I don't take my
own word seriously,
what sort of Lord of
Winterfell would I be?
ALLISER: Crowded. You'd think
we were serving venison stew.
(MEN LAUGHING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Does anyone wish to
speak for candidates
before we cast our tokens
for the 998th Lord Commander
of the Night's Watch?
Ser Alliser Thorne
is not just a knight,
he's a man of true nobility.
He was acting commander
when the Wall
came under attack
and led us to victory
against the wildlings.
BLACK BROTHERS: Hear, hear.
JANOS:
He's a veteran of 100 battles
and has been
a defender of the Watch
and the Wall
almost all of his life.
BLACK BROTHER: Aye.
He's the only true choice.
BLACK BROTHER: Yes!
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
(POUNDING ON TABLES)
Ser Denys Mallister
joined the Watch as a boy
and has served loyally,
longer than any other ranger.
Through 10 winters he served.
As commander of
the Shadow Tower,
he kept the wildlings away.
We could do no better.
(BLACK BROTHERS CHEERING)
AEMON:
If there is no one else,
we will begin the voting.
The triangular tokens
count for Ser Alliser Thorne.
The square tokens for
Ser Denys Mallister.
Each brother will...
Maester Aemon.
AEMON: Samwell Tarly. Go on.
JANOS: Sam the Slayer.
(LAUGHTER)
Another wildling lover
just like his friend Jon Snow.
How's your lady love, Slayer?
(LAUGHTER)
Her name is Gilly.
Brother Slynt
knows her quite well.
They cowered
together in the larder
during
the battle for the Wall.
(LAUGHTER)
Lies!
A wildling girl,
a baby, and Lord Janos.
I found him there
after the battle was over
in a puddle of his own making.
(ALL LAUGHING LOUDLY)
Whilst Lord Janos was hiding
with the women and children,
Jon Snow was leading.
Ser Alliser fought bravely,
it is true.
And when he was wounded,
it was Jon who saved us.
He took charge of
the Wall's defense.
He killed
the Magnar of the Thenns.
He went north to
deal with Mance Rayder
knowing it almost certainly
meant his own death.
Before that,
he led the mission to
avenge Lord Commander Mormont.
Mormont himself chose
Jon to be his steward.
He saw something in Jon
and now we've
all seen it, too.
He may be young,
but he's
the commander we turned to
when the night was darkest.
(BLACK BROTHERS CHEERING)
I can't argue
with any of that.
But who does Jon
Snow want to command?
Night's Watch,
or the wildlings?
Everyone knows he
loved a wildling girl,
he spoke with Mance
Rayder many times.
What would have
happened in that tent
between those two old friends
if Stannis' army
hadn't come along?
We all saw him put
the King-beyond-the-Wall
out of his misery.
Do you want to choose
a man who has fought
the wildlings all his life,
or a man who
makes love to them?
It is time.
It appears to be a tie,
Maester.
(LOUD CHEERING)
(BLACK BROTHERS
CHANTING) Jon Snow!
Jon Snow! Jon Snow! Jon Snow!
(COOING)
You. You.
What have you got there?
(LAUGHING)
I said...
Turn around and go.
That's a nice little sword.
Worth 100 pigeons,
a sword like that.
Nothing's worth
anything to dead men.
THUG: Come on.
Quickly, go! Go!
Who are you?
Why were they scared of you?
You lost this.
You said there was
no Jaqen H'ghar here.
There isn't.
A man is not Jaqen H'ghar.
ARYA: Well, who are you, then?
No one.
And that is who
a girl must become.
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
(SPEAKS VALYRIAN)
DAENERYS: Why?
CROWD: (SHOUTING) Mhysa!
Mhysa!
Mhysa! Mhysa!
(SHOUTING CONTINUES)
Mhysa!
She should have cut
off the traitor's head
in the Great Pyramid
and been done with it.
Which is what I keep
telling her to do to you.
CROWD: (SHOUTING) Mhysa!
Mhysa!
(SPEAKS VALYRIAN)
(CROWD MURMURING)
(INDISTINCT YELLING)
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
Mhysa.
(SPEAKS VALYRIAN SOFTLY)
(CROWD SHOUTING)
(HEAD THUMPS)
Mhysa!
(SHOUTING STOPS)
(HISSING)
(HISSING CONTINUES)
(CROWD SHOUTING)
(STONES THUDDING)
I'll stand guard
outside your door tonight,
Your Grace.
We all guard tonight.
Leave me.
(SOFT THUMPING)
(WIND HOWLING)
(SOFT GROWLING)
Drogon.
(DROGON SCREECHES)
(SCREECHING)