(WATER DRIPPING)
(VOICES WHISPERING)
Valar Morghulis.
Valar Dohaeris.
I've been sweeping
this floor for days.
Good.
I didn't come
here to sweep floors.
No? Why come, then?
You said I could
be your apprentice.
You said you'd teach me
how to be a Faceless Man.
A man teaches a girl.
Valar Dohaeris.
All men must serve.
Faceless Men most of all.
I want to serve.
A girl wants to serve herself.
Here we serve
the Many-Faced God.
To serve well,
a girl must become no one.
Which one's
the Many-Faced God?
I see the Stranger.
I see the Drowned God.
I see the weirwood face.
There is only one god.
A girl knows his name.
And all men know his gift.
Where are they taking him?
(BELLS TOLLING)
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
Queen Margaery!
MAN: Queen Margaery!
MARGAERY:
I am his and he is mine.
TOMMEN:
I am hers and she is mine.
BOTH: From this day
until the end of my days.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Did I hurt you?
No. You were lovely.
It all happened so fast.
Yes. (CHUCKLES)
I was scared maybe I hurt you.
It sounded like...
No, no, no.
You're very sweet.
The sweetest
king who ever lived.
This is all I
want to do all day,
every day,
for the rest of my life.
(LAUGHS) Wouldn't
that be glorious?
Shouldn't we
rest a little while?
Just to catch our breath?
There's no rush, is there?
Of course not.
Are you hungry?
Should I have them
bring you some cake or
pomegranate juice?
No, I'm fine.
I just want you all to myself.
I want to know
everything there is to know
about King Tommen,
First of His Name.
King Tommen.
Still sounds strange to me.
Does Queen Margaery
sound strange to you?
So strange.
Husband.
Wife.
(LAUGHS)
Sometimes it feels odd.
I'm the king,
I've married the most
beautiful woman in the world,
and it's all
because my brother died.
I understand.
But it's not your fault.
You know that, don't you?
You mustn't feel guilty.
I don't feel guilty.
That's what's odd.
Do you like to sail?
I love to sail.
I do, too.
I think we're
going to be very happy,
you and I.
I do, too.
Living in a tower
so high it touches the clouds.
Of course, my grandmother
couldn't wait to go home.
The capital's not for
everyone, I suppose.
Does your mother like it here?
I don't think so.
She told me
never to trust
anyone in King's Landing.
It's so wonderful
to have her watching over you.
A lioness guarding her cub.
Well, but I'm a man now.
You are.
And the king.
But you'll always
be her baby boy.
I suppose.
I adore her. She's always been
so generous with me, so kind.
And the horrors
she's had to endure...
Losing her husband,
her eldest child,
and her father.
It's no wonder she's
so protective of you.
She'll never let
you out of her sight.
CERSEI:
You look very much in love.
The first days of marriage
are often so blissful.
She's certainly
very pretty, isn't she?
Like a doll.
She smiles quite a lot.
Do you think
she's intelligent?
I can't quite tell.
Not that it matters.
Do you ever
miss Casterly Rock?
There's nothing for
me in Casterly Rock.
That's where you grew up.
You always told me
that you liked
the people there better.
You said that King's Landing
smelled of horse
dung and sour milk.
(CHUCKLES)
Why are we
speaking of Casterly Rock?
The way that you
talked about it,
I always thought
that you missed it.
That you...
That it was your real home.
This is my real home now,
where my family lives.
I want you to
be happy, Mother.
I know that.
I know you do. My sweet boy.
But wouldn't you be happier
in Casterly Rock?
MARGAERY: I said,
"Darling,
surely four times is enough.
"Are you trying to
set a new record?"
(WOMEN GIGGLING)
He said,
"Well, what is the record?
I'm sure we can break it."
Mother.
Welcome.
Don't you look lovely?
Marriage agrees with you.
Can we bring you
anything to eat or drink?
I wish we had
some wine for you.
It's a bit early
in the day for us.
No, no, I can't stay.
I just wanted to let
you know if there's ever
anything I can do for you...
You are very sweet.
Tommen seems quite taken
with his new queen.
I absolutely adore him.
You raised
a gallant young man.
I'm forever grateful.
Good.
Good. I'm glad to
hear you're happy.
Ecstatic. I really am.
Exhausted, to be honest.
(WOMEN GIGGLE)
But what could I expect?
He is half lion, half stag.
(WOMEN LAUGH)
I'll leave you to it, then.
Oh, forgive me.
I haven't been
at court for long.
I get so confused.
What's the proper
way to address you now?
Queen Mother or Dowager Queen?
There's no need
for such formalities.
In any event,
judging from
the king's enthusiasm,
the Queen Mother will be
a Queen Grandmother soon.
Won't that be a lovely day?
Can you imagine
the celebrations?
They'll ring
the bells all day and night.
Remember,
anything you need.
(WOMEN GIGGLING)
(LAUGHTER ECHOING)
(HORSE NEIGHS)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(ANIMALS SQUAWKING)
(FLIES BUZZING)
(CAWS)
BOLTON:
We can't hold the North
with terror alone.
RAMSAY:
You can't hold the North
if you let these
lesser lords insult us.
BOLTON: I sent you
there to collect taxes,
not bodies.
RAMSAY:
Lord Cerwyn refused to pay.
Said the Warden of the North
would always be a Stark,
and he'd be damned
if he'd kiss
a traitor's boot.
BOLTON: He left you no choice.
I flayed him living,
along with his
wife and brother.
Made his son watch.
And?
The new Lord
Cerwyn paid his taxes.
I've something
important to tell you.
Stop eating and listen.
We don't have enough
men to hold the North
if the other houses
rise up against us.
Do you understand that?
Our pact with
the Lannisters protects...
I had a pact with
Tywin Lannister.
And Tywin Lannister is dead.
The remaining Lannisters are
a thousand miles away
dealing with that fact.
They've never once,
in the history of
the Seven Kingdoms,
sent their army
this far north.
If you think they will
for us, you're a fool.
We've become a great house
by entering into
alliances with other houses,
and parlaying those alliances
into greater power.
The best way to
forge a lasting alliance
isn't by peeling
a man's skin off.
The best way is marriage.
Now that you're
a Bolton by royal decree,
it's high time you
married a suitable bride.
And as it happens,
I've found the perfect girl
to solidify our
hold on the North.
That's Moat Cailin.
Yes, a bit shabby, isn't it?
You've been here before?
On our way down
to King's Landing
with my father and Arya.
Where are you taking me?
Home.
The Boltons have Winterfell.
Your marriage proposal,
it wasn't for you.
No.
Roose Bolton
murdered my brother.
He betrayed my family.
He did.
He serves the Lannisters.
For now.
I won't go.
Winterfell is your home.
Not anymore.
Always.
You're a Stark.
Dying your hair
doesn't change that.
You're Sansa Stark,
eldest surviving child
of Ned and Catelyn Stark.
Your place is in the North.
I can't marry him.
You can't make me.
He is a traitor. A murderer!
You're not
marrying Roose Bolton.
No, you'll be marrying
his son and heir, Ramsay.
One day he'll be
Warden of the North
and you...
No.
Sansa.
No, you can't make me.
I will starve myself.
I will die before
I have to go there.
I won't force
you to do anything.
Don't you know by now
how much I care for you?
Say the word and we
turn the horses around,
but listen to me.
Listen.
You've been
running all your life.
Terrible things
happen to your family
and you weep.
You sit alone in
a darkened room
mourning their fates.
You've been
a bystander to tragedy
from the day they
executed your father.
Stop being a bystander.
Do you hear me?
Stop running.
There's no
justice in the world.
Not unless we make it.
You loved your family.
Avenge them.
(HORSE NEIGHS)
MAN: Banners!
PODRICK:
How do we get through there?
BRIENNE: We don't.
We go around.
Takes us miles out of the way.
We'll lose sight of them.
BRIENNE: Doesn't matter.
I know where they're going.
Aren't you getting
a bit old to be a squire?
How did you end up
squiring for the Imp?
He hates that nickname.
Well, he's not here
to complain about it,
is he?
I squired for
a knight named Ser Lorimer
during the War
of the Five Kings.
One night, he had
a bit too much to drink,
and he was famished,
so he borrowed a ham.
He borrowed it?
He wasn't a thief.
He was drunk, and hungry,
and he wasn't thinking.
I was drunk, too.
He gave me half the ham.
Next morning,
one of the guards
saw him passed out
under a wagon
with the hambone
still in his hand.
They hanged him
that afternoon.
They tied
the noose for me, too,
but Lord Tywin heard
my family name was Payne,
so he pardoned me,
and sent me to King's Landing
to squire for his son.
As punishment for both of you.
It didn't seem that way.
Lord Tyrion was
always very good to me.
Yes, all your lords
have been very kind to you.
All except me.
Sorry, you had to squire
for such a nasty person.
I'm not sorry.
You're the best
fighter I've ever seen.
You beat the Hound.
I'm proud to be your squire.
I'm sorry I'm
always snapping at you.
If you didn't snap at me,
I wouldn't learn anything.
You want to be a knight, Pod?
Yes.
Starting tomorrow,
we'll train with
the sword twice a day,
before we ride in the morning
and after you make
camp in the evening.
And I'm going to show you
how to ride properly.
Thank you.
I can't knight you,
but I can teach
you how to fight.
I suppose that's
more important.
You weren't a knight,
but you were a Kingsguard
to Renly Baratheon,
weren't you?
I was.
Lord Tyrion said
he was a good man.
He was.
How did you end
up serving Renly?
When I was a girl,
my father held a ball.
I'm his only living child,
so he wanted to make
a good match for me.
He invited dozens of
young lords to Tarth.
I didn't want to go,
but he dragged me
to the ballroom.
And it was wonderful.
None of the boys noticed
how mulish and tall I was.
They shoved each other
and threatened to duel
when they thought it
was their turn to dance.
They whispered in my ear
how they wanted to
marry me and take me
back to their castles.
My father smiled at me,
and I smiled at him.
I had never been so happy.
Till I saw a few of
the boys sniggering.
And then they all
started to laugh.
They couldn't keep
the game going any longer.
They were toying with me.
"Brienne the Beauty,"
they called me.
Great joke.
And I realized I was
the ugliest girl alive.
A great lumbering beast.
I tried to run away,
but Renly Baratheon
took me in his arms.
"Don't let them see
your tears," he told me.
"They're nasty little shits,
"and nasty little shits
aren't worth crying over."
He danced with me,
and none of the other
boys could say a word.
Renly was
the king's brother after all.
But wasn't he...
Lord Tyrion said he was...
Yes, Pod, he liked men.
I'm not an idiot.
He didn't love me.
He didn't want me.
He danced with me
because he was kind,
and didn't want
to see me hurt.
He saved me
from being a joke.
From that day
until his last day.
And I couldn't
save him in return.
Nothing's more hateful
than failing to
protect the one you love.
One day I will
avenge King Renly.
But you said
a shadow murdered him.
How do you fight a shadow?
A shadow with the face
of Stannis Baratheon.
I know it was Stannis.
I know it in my heart.
Stannis is a man,
not a shadow.
And a man can be killed.
Lord Commander.
Your Grace.
I'd like to speak alone.
Olly is my steward now,
as I was Lord
Commander Mormont's.
I want him to
attend my meetings
to learn from men
with experience.
One day he might command.
Very well.
Have you considered my offer?
I have.
And I thank you for it.
You do me great honor.
All my life I
wanted to be Jon Stark.
Say the word and you will be.
But I have to refuse you.
I'm Lord Commander
of the Night's Watch.
My place is here.
I'm giving you the chance
to avenge your family,
to take back
the castle where you grew up.
To rule the North.
I wish I could
fight beside you.
Believe me, I do.
But I swore a sacred
vow at the godswood.
I pledged my life
to the Night's Watch.
You're as
stubborn as your father.
And as honorable.
I can imagine
no higher praise.
I didn't mean it as praise.
Honor got your father killed.
But if your mind's made up,
I won't try and dissuade you.
May I ask how long you plan
to stay at Castle Black?
Are you bored of us already?
You saved us from
Mance Rayder's army.
We will never forget that.
But it's
a question of survival.
The Night's
Watch can't continue
to feed your men
and the wildling
prisoners indefinitely.
Winter is coming.
I know it.
We march on Winterfell
within the fortnight,
before the snows trap us here.
And the wildlings?
If they'd rather
burn than fight for me,
so be it.
I leave their fate to you.
You could execute them.
That's the safest course.
Or you could see if
this Tormund fellow
is more willing to compromise
than Mance ever was.
I assume the brothers
of the Night's Watch
would rather see
the wildlings dead.
Most of the brothers, yes.
There's little love
for the free folk here.
You're the Lord Commander.
Your decision.
(DOOR OPENS)
You have many
enemies in Castle Black.
Have you considered
sending Alliser
Thorne elsewhere?
Give him command of
Eastwatch-by-the-Sea.
I heard it was best
to keep your enemies close.
Whoever said that
didn't have many enemies.
DAVOS:
He sees something in you.
Might not be
apparent from his tone,
but it's the truth.
He believes in you.
I'm sorry I disappointed him.
The king is a complicated man,
but he wants to
do what's right
for the Seven Kingdoms.
As long as he's ruling them.
He's the one true king.
He has a blood
right to that throne.
I've sworn to stay
clear of the politics
of the Seven Kingdoms.
Have you now?
How does the Night's
Watch vow go again?
I'll bet you've
got it memorized
since you got here.
Night gathers and
now my watch begins.
No, not that bit.
The bit at the end.
I am the sword
in the darkness,
the watcher on the walls,
the shield that
guards the realms of men.
I pledge my life...
Right, that's enough.
The shield that
guards the realms of men.
That's what you swore to be.
Now, I'm not a learned man,
but the best way to
help the most people
might not be
sitting in a frozen castle
at the edge of the world.
It just might mean
wading in the muck,
getting your boots dirty,
and doing what
needs to be done.
And what needs to be done?
As long as
the Boltons rule the North,
the North will suffer.
Just one man's opinion.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(DOOR OPENS)
What do you want?
Who are you?
What?
You, who walk in here
with a coin you never earned,
whose value you
do not respect.
Who are you?
No one.
Ow!
Cunt!
A lie.
A sad little lie. Who are you?
I told you, I'm...
Do that again, and...
Who are you?
You're about to find out.
What are you doing?
We were only playing.
The Game of Faces.
A girl is not ready.
Clearly not.
I am ready.
For what?
For whatever you want.
To be a Faceless Man.
To be no one.
JAQEN: Whose sword is that?
It belongs to Arya Stark.
Arya Stark's sword,
clothes, stolen silver.
A man wonders,
how is it that
no one came to be
surrounded by
Arya Stark's things?
(SIGHS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
What do we do with
them after we wash them?
MAN 1: Open gate!
MAN 2: Honor guard, stand to!
MAN 3: Hold up. Easy.
Lady Sansa. Welcome.
Lord Bolton.
May I introduce my son,
Ramsay Bolton?
It's an honor to
meet you, my lady.
I'll bring you
a bowl of hot water.
You must want to wash.
Thank you.
Welcome home, Lady Stark.
The North remembers.
(MEN CHATTING)
Sam?
Maester Aemon?
He apologizes
for not being here.
He's not feeling well.
Take good care of him.
Brothers.
(CHATTER STOPS)
As you all know too well,
it's long past time to
dig a new latrine pit.
(MEN LAUGHING)
First Builder Yarwyck and I
have decided to
appoint a latrine captain
to oversee this crucial task.
(MEN LAUGH)
Brian.
Seems like a good
job for a ginger.
That's him!
That's him.
Ser Alliser.
You have more experience
than any other
ranger at Castle Black.
You proved your
valor many times over
while defending the Wall
from the wildling attack.
I name you First Ranger.
MEN: Hear, hear!
(POUNDING ON TABLES)
Lord Janos.
I'm giving you
command of Greyguard.
Greyguard is a ruin.
Yes,
the fort is in a sorry state.
Restore it as best you can.
First Builder Yarwyck
can spare 10 of his...
JANOS: I was charged
with the defense
of King's Landing
when you were soiling
your swaddling clothes.
Keep your ruin.
(MEN SHOUTING)
All right!
That's enough of that.
(SHOUTING STOPS)
You mistake me, my lord.
That was a command,
not an offer.
Pack your arms and armor,
say your farewells,
and ride for Greyguard.
I will not go meekly
off to freeze and die.
Give it to one of the fools
who cast a stone for you.
I will not have it.
Did you hear me, boy?
I will not have it!
Are you refusing
to obey my order?
You can stick your
order up your bastard ass.
(MEN MURMURING)
Take Lord Janos outside.
Olly, bring me my sword.
Get out.
You cannot do this!
Get your hands off me!
Scum, all of you!
If the boy thinks
he can frighten me,
he's mistaken.
Yes, very mistaken.
Disgrace!
I have friends.
Important
friends in the capital.
You'll see.
Kneel!
If you have any
last words, my lord,
now's the time.
I was wrong.
You're the Lord Commander.
We all serve you. I'm sorry.
Not only for this,
for all I've done and said.
I was wrong.
My lord, please! Mercy! Mercy!
I'll go! I will! (SOBBING)
Please.
I'm afraid.
(WHIMPERING)
I've always been afraid.
(WOMEN GIGGLING)
You have served
us well, my son.
Thank you, Father.
Which of the Seven
will you worship today?
The Maiden.
Always the Maiden.
SEPTON: And the Stranger.
Two is extra, you realize?
Yes, yes.
(SNAPS FINGERS)
(GASPS)
What are you doing?
This establishment belongs
to Lord Petyr Baelish.
You can't...
(GROANS)
You have profaned our faith,
the faith of our
fathers and forefathers.
I am the High Septon of the...
You are a sinner.
(GROANS)
And you shall be punished.
(CRACKS)
Ah!
(WOMAN LAUGHS)
Sinner.
SPARROWS: Sinner.
Sinner. Sinner.
MAN 1: Repent!
Sinner.
(GROANS)
Sinner. Sinner.
MAN 2: Shame on you.
SPARROWS: Sinner.
(DOORS CLOSE)
Your Grace,
Grand Maester, Lord Tyrell...
Uh...
It doesn't matter.
As the High Septon of
the Faith of the Seven,
I give voice to
the will of the gods
and am their foremost
servant in this world.
An insult to me is
an insult to the gods.
An assault on my person
is an assault on
our very religion.
You were assaulted?
I was.
By those fanatics
who call themselves Sparrows.
They humiliated me,
they beat me,
they left me
naked and bleeding
on the cobblestones.
I am lucky to be alive.
I heard
this assault began in
Littlefinger's brothel.
This is a rather
shocking thing to hear.
SEPTON: I tend to
both the highest born
and the lowliest amongst us.
Even prostitutes
may earn
the mercy of the Mother.
So, you were ministering
to the needs of
these devout prostitutes?
A man's private affairs
ought to stay private.
What do you want
from us, High Septon?
Justice.
I ask that you
protect our faith
by arresting these
criminals and throwing them
in the Black Cells.
I ask that you
execute their leader,
this so-called High Sparrow.
He's a threat to
everything we hold sacred.
If he goes unpunished...
And where
do I find this man?
This High Sparrow?
I don't think
this is a good idea.
Nonsense, Ser Meryn.
These are deeply
religious people.
Where can I find
the High Sparrow?
MAN 1: Seven blessings.
(PEOPLE COUGHING)
(FLIES BUZZING)
(BABY CRYING)
MAN 2: Thank you.
MAN 3: Just a little more.
(BABY CONTINUES CRYING)
WOMAN 1: Thank you.
MAN 4: Thank you.
A young man said I'd find
the High Sparrow back here.
Where is he?
High Sparrow?
Sounds ridiculous,
doesn't it?
Like Lord
Duckling or King Turtle.
Still, it's meant to.
We're often
stuck with the names
our enemies give to us.
The notion that
we're all equal
in the eyes of the Seven
doesn't sit well with some,
so they belittle me.
WOMAN 2:
Seven blessings to you.
Seven blessings
to you, my dear.
It's only a name.
Quite an easy burden to bear.
Far easier than hers.
CERSEI: Why no shoes?
Because I gave them away
to someone who
needed them more.
We all do that.
It stops us from
forgetting what we really are.
Is that why you
came to King's Landing?
To remind everyone?
Everyone? Hard enough job
reminding myself.
Well,
I tell them no one's special,
and they think I'm
special for telling them so.
Perhaps they're right.
It would be
comforting to believe that,
wouldn't it?
Have the gods sent
you here to tempt me?
I hope not.
I had assumed
you'd only come
here to arrest me
for that incident
with the High Septon.
An unacceptable
way to treat
the chosen representative
of the gods in this world,
wouldn't you say?
Hypocrisy is a boil.
Lancing a boil
is never pleasant.
Although they could have been
more careful with the blade.
The High Septon came
to speak to me today.
He doesn't want
me to arrest you.
He wants me to execute you.
I wouldn't presume
to know your
thoughts on the matter.
My thoughts on the matter
are in line with your own.
The High Septon's
behavior was corrosive,
as was his attitude.
Having a man like
that reside in the sept
eats away at
the faith from the inside.
So now he resides
in the Red Keep
dungeons instead.
The faith and
the crown are the two pillars
that hold up this world.
One collapses,
so does the other.
We must do
everything necessary
to protect one another.
(SQUEAKING)
(FLESH SQUELCHES)
( RAT SQUEALS)
Your Grace.
Send a raven with this message
to Littlefinger at the Eyrie,
or wherever he's
slithering about.
At once, Your Grace.
How's your work coming along?
Very well.
You've made progress?
More than I expected.
Still a way to go, but...
Very good.
I'll leave you to it, then.
Make sure
Littlefinger is clear
on the meaning of
the word "immediately."
(BOTTLES RATTLE)
Shh.
Easy, friend.
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
RAMSAY: She really is lovely.
I hope I can
make her happy.
I hope so, too.
I've become quite
fond of Lady Sansa
during our travels together.
She's suffered enough.
I'll never hurt her.
You have my word.
I've heard very
little about you,
which makes you
quite a rare thing
as lords go.
I haven't been
a lord very long.
I was a bastard.
And you're not anymore.
Allow me a moment
alone with Lord Baelish.
Yes, Father.
And thank you, Lord Baelish.
I'm forever in your debt.
He seems pleased.
Shouldn't he be?
I assure you,
she's still a virgin.
Tyrion never
consummated the marriage.
By the law of the land,
she is no man's wife.
Inspect her, if you must.
I'll leave that to
the brothel keeper.
It's her name I need,
not her virtue.
Then I have delivered
everything I promised.
And you're prepared
for the consequences
when the Lannisters hear
I've wed Sansa
Stark to Ramsay?
The Lannister name
doesn't mean what it once did.
Tywin is dead.
He kept his house in power
through sheer will.
Without him,
Jaime has one
hand and no allies.
Tommen is a soft boy,
not a king to fear.
The queen will be enraged.
Queen Margaery adores Sansa.
Cersei is Queen Mother,
a title whose importance
wanes with each passing day.
And yet she still has friends,
men in important places
whom she can ask for favors.
A message for you
from Cersei Lannister.
A rider arrived from the Eyrie
shortly before dawn.
Apparently she thinks
you're still in the Vale.
A message for me, you say?
Strange that
the seal is broken.
I'm sure you
understand my position,
Lord Baelish.
If you receive
word in the night
from the Queen Mother,
it does make me
question our new alliance.
The Lannisters made you
one of the great
lords of Westeros,
yet here you are in the North
undermining them.
Why gamble with your position?
Every ambitious
move is a gamble.
You gambled when
you drove a dagger
into Robb Stark's heart.
It appears that
your gamble paid off.
You're Warden of the North.
I had Tywin
Lannister's backing.
Who supports me now? You?
The Eyrie is mine.
The last time
the lords of the Eyrie
formed an alliance with
the lords of the North,
they brought down
the greatest dynasty
this world has ever known.
I'd like to borrow
one of your birds.
Cersei will expect a reply.
I'd like to read the reply.
I have to get out
of this wheelhouse.
Volantis is a large city.
I have to get out
of this wheelhouse.
The likelihood of
you being spotted here
increases a hundredfold.
Mmm, I have to get
out of this wheelhouse.
(SIGHS) I'm not
sure how many new ways
I can find of saying this.
I will not be of any
use to Daenerys Targaryen
if I lose my mind.
I can't remember
the last face I saw
that wasn't yours.
It's a perfectly good face.
I am losing my mind.
If anyone recognizes you,
you'll lose more than that.
Look,
we are thousands of miles
from Westeros.
What am I?
One more drunk dwarf.
(KNOCKS)
DRIVER: Whoa!
(HORSES NEIGH)
(SEAGULL SCREECHING)
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
WOMAN: We have to go now.
Come on, hold it. Hold it.
Are you ready?
Slaves.
Yes, the Volantene masters
are very organized.
Flies for dung shovelers.
Hammers for builders.
Tears for whores.
Lest they forget.
(WOMAN SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
(CROWD REPEATING)
We should keep moving.
The only red priest we
had in King's Landing
was Thoros of Myr.
This one's much
better-looking.
Stone men.
Good luck stopping
the spread of
greyscale with prayer.
You'd have better luck
dancing away the plague.
We're going to
meet the savior.
You should have told me.
Who doesn't want
to meet the savior?
Come on.
Let's find a brothel.
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
(ANIMALS CALLING)
MAN:
Build your house in a day.
It's even better luck
to suck a dwarf's cock.
See? We blend right in.
Just two more
travelers mad with lust.
VARYS: Thank you.
(SNIFFING)
What curious hair.
The Mother of Dragons!
(MEN LAUGH)
It appears you're not
the only Targaryen supporter.
We were just
heading east to see you.
I've got a dragon for you.
How much to
make him spit fire?
Someone who inspires priests
and whores is worth taking
seriously.
What makes you
worth that much?
I'm magic.
I'll bet you bloody are.
(LAUGHING)
Well, she's taken.
Where are you going?
I need to speak to
someone with hair.
Hello.
You've got no drink.
You've got no money.
Do I look like
a man without money?
Never trust looks.
Until quite recently,
I was one of
the richest men in the world.
(LAUGHS)
But who needs wealth
when you can
make a woman laugh?
I always pay my debts.
I'm well known for it.
(LAUGHTER)
You like her.
They all like her.
They all want to
fuck a queen.
That's because
they've never met a queen.
You're just saying that.
You know how to spot a liar.
If I could pick any girl here,
I would pick you.
Why?
Because you have
a skeptical mind.
All right, then.
I'm warning you,
we're going to have
to wash you first.
Come on.
I'm sorry, I can't.
Of course you can.
You're shy.
I'm not.
Have another drink.
Gladly, but this, I can't do.
Believe me, no one is
more shocked than I am.
I hope it passes.
What will I do
in my spare time?
Go for a piss.
That's a start.
(URINATING)
(MUG SPLASHES)
No need to worry.
I was just...
Oh.
I thought you were
someone else.
Show's almost over.
I'm sure there
are girls inside
who'd be happy to oblige.
You've made some
kind of mistake.
Why don't you tell me
what you think
you're doing, and then...
I'm taking you to the queen.