I'm so sorry,
my queen.
He was a good man.
DAENERYS:
"Barristan the Bold,"
they called him.
He crossed
a continent to serve me.
He was a loyal friend.
And he died in an alley,
butchered by cowards
who hide behind masks.
We could pull back to
the pyramid district,
secure it,
and use it as a base
from which to operate.
Then we clean the city out,
neighborhood
by neighborhood,
street by street,
until the rats have
nowhere left to hide.
I prefer your
earlier suggestion.
Round up the leaders
of each of Meereen's
great families and
bring them to me.
But... I'm the leader
of my family.
No, Your Grace...
I had nothing to do with this.
Your Grace!
(CHAINS RATTLING)
(DRAGONS SNARLING)
(SPEAKS VALYRIAN)
(CHAINS RATTLING)
(WHIMPERING)
(MEN WHIMPERING)
(PRAYING INDISTINCTLY)
(EXCLAIMS)
(CHAINS RATTLING)
(SCREAMING)
Don't want
to overfeed them.
Tomorrow perhaps.
(DRAGON SCREECHING)
(ROARING)
"And though Daenerys
maintains her
grip on Slaver's Bay,
"forces rise against her
from within and without.
"She refuses to
leave until the freedom
"of the former
slaves is secure."
She sounds like
quite a woman.
And she's alone,
under siege,
no family to guide
her or protect her.
Her last relation
thousands of miles away,
useless, dying.
Don't say that,
Maester Aemon.
A Targaryen alone in the world
is a terrible thing.
Maester Aemon.
Lord Commander.
Sam, I'd like to speak
to the maester alone.
How are you feeling?
Oh, like a 100-year-old man
slowly freezing to death.
I need your advice.
There's something
I want to do,
something I have to do.
But it'll divide
the Night's Watch.
Bitterly.
Half the men will hate me
the moment I give the order.
Half the men hate you already,
Lord Commander.
Do it.
But you don't know what it is.
That doesn't matter.
You do.
You will find little
joy in your command.
But with luck,
you will find the strength
to do what needs to be done.
Kill the boy, Jon Snow.
Winter is almost upon us.
Kill the boy,
and let the man be born.
Where are the rest
of the free folk now?
Where have they gone?
Who leads them?
They followed Mance.
They won't follow
anyone else.
What about you?
Hard to lead when
you're in chains.
What if I unchained you?
Why would you do that?
Because you are
not my enemy.
And I'm not yours.
You sure seemed
like my enemy when
you were killing my friends.
For 8,000 years
the Night's Watch
have sworn an oath
to be the shield
that guards
the realms of men.
And for 8,000 years,
we've fallen short
of that oath.
You belong to
the realms of men.
All of you.
And now everything
is going to change?
It is.
Why now?
Because now
I am Lord Commander
of the Night's Watch.
What would you have me do,
Lord Commander?
I'd have you go
north of the Wall.
Gather the remaining
free folk,
wherever they are,
and bring them back here.
I'll open the gates for them
and let them through.
I'll find them lands to
settle south of the Wall.
They won't kneel for you,
and neither will I.
I don't want them
to kneel for me.
I want them to fight with me
when the time comes.
The day I ask my people
to fight with the crows
is the day my people
cut my guts from my belly
and make me eat them.
And how many of your
people can't fight?
The women, the children,
the old, the sick,
what happens to them?
You're condemning
them to death.
Worse than death
because you're too
proud to make peace.
Or maybe you're not proud.
Maybe you're just a coward.
Easy thing to say
to a man in chains.
Your people need a leader.
And they need to
get south of the Wall
before it's too late.
We don't have much time,
and they have less.
The Walkers are coming,
and they'll hit
your people first.
I'm not asking
you to make peace
to save your skin.
Make peace to
save your people.
Most of them are at Hardhome.
You know where that is?
Up on Storrold's Point.
I can give you 10
horses and nine other men.
You can get there in a week.
We'll need ships.
I'll talk to King Stannis
about lending you his fleet.
All right, then.
You're coming with me.
You're the Lord Commander
of the Night's Watch.
They need to hear it from you.
They need to know
the ships they are boarding
won't be torched in
the middle of the sea.
You come with me,
or I don't go.
(MEN SHOUTING)
You'd bring wildlings here,
through our gates?
Men, women, and children
will die by the thousands
if we do nothing.
Let them die. We got
our own to worry about.
Less enemies for us.
(ALL CHEERING)
Fewer.
What?
Nothing.
Look, well, there is
good farmland in the Gift.
Land that no one uses now.
A dozen abandoned villages.
And why do you think
the farmers
abandoned those villages?
Because the wildlings
raided them for years.
Cut them down
just like they did
this boy's people.
MEN: Aye!
ALLISER:
We've been fighting them
for thousands of years.
They've slaughtered villages.
They've slaughtered
our brothers.
And we've slaughtered theirs.
I will follow you anywhere,
you know that.
But they killed Grenn.
MEN: Yes.
And they killed Pyp.
MEN: Aye.
They killed 50
of our brothers.
I can't forget that.
I can't forgive it.
You were at
the Fist of the First Men.
If we abandon them,
you know what they become.
We can learn to live
with the wildlings,
or we can add them to
the army of the dead.
Whatever they are now,
they're better than that.
(ALL ARGUING)
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
Thank you.
Olly.
If you have something
you want to say to me,
say it.
It's all right.
You don't mean it,
do you?
Telling the wildlings
you want to make peace.
You're just doing
it to trick them.
It's not a trick.
They burned my village.
They put an arrow
through my father's head
right in front of me.
They butchered my mother,
everyone I ever knew.
I know what it's like
to lose the people you love.
I know this is hard for you.
But winter is coming.
We know what's coming with it.
We can't face it alone.
Will there be
anything else you need,
Lord Commander?
No.
(SIGHS)
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
She's far away
from the Lannisters.
This is her home.
Maybe Lady Sansa's
better off here.
Better off with the Boltons,
who murdered her
mother and brother?
Sansa's in danger,
even if she
doesn't realize it.
(DOOR OPENS)
Thank you.
You've lived here a long time?
Aye.
Did you know Lord Eddard?
I knew him,
and his father before him.
The Starks are gone now.
Not all of them.
I know who's
inside that castle.
Everyone knows.
The Boltons.
I'm not talking
about the Boltons.
I need to get
a message to her.
To Sansa Stark.
Who are you?
Someone who swore
to keep her safe.
Swore to who?
Her mother.
Her mother's dead.
That doesn't
release me from an oath.
I served Lady Catelyn.
I serve her still.
Who do you serve?
RAMSAY: Come back here.
Myranda.
MYRANDA:
I saw you staring at her.
RAMSAY:
I'm going to marry her.
That will
involve looking at her
from time to time.
You said you'd
marry me.
And I meant it.
When I was
a bastard named Snow.
But I'm a Bolton now.
What I want is no longer
the primary consideration.
I'm furthering a dynasty.
Do you think she's pretty?
(SCOFFS)
Of course I do.
I'm not blind.
(SIGHS)
You think she's pretty, too.
I'm looking forward
to our wedding night.
But don't worry,
I'll have plenty
of time for you.
Perhaps I'll marry, too.
(LAUGHS)
You're the kennel
master's daughter.
Who are you going to marry,
the stable keeper's son?
You're mine.
You're not going anywhere.
Unless I have to listen
to more of your jealousy.
Jealousy bores me.
You remember what happens
to people who bore me.
You're not going to bore me,
are you, Myranda?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Never.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Beg pardon, my lady.
I've come to refill
the wash basin.
Oh, I don't need...
You still have
friends in the North.
If you're ever in trouble,
light a candle
in the highest window
of the broken tower.
But who...
You're not alone.
I like your dress.
Who made it for you?
Uh, I made it myself.
Really?
Who... Who are you?
I'm Myranda,
the kennel master's daughter.
May I?
Oh, wonderful.
The stitching.
Who taught you?
My mother.
I'm sorry for
what happened to her.
Thank you.
It's good that she taught you.
It was a gift.
Now every time you wear
something you made,
you can remember her.
I'd rather have a mother.
I know.
It's not the same.
Still, it's good to remember.
Remember the way things were.
I almost forgot.
There's something else
to help you remember.
(DOGS BARKING)
Down there,
at the end.
What is it?
That would spoil the surprise.
(DOGS GROWLING)
Go ahead,
it's perfectly safe.
You won't believe
it when you see it.
(BARKING CONTINUES)
(CHAINS RATTLING)
(GASPS)
Theon?
You shouldn't be here.
You smell particularly
ripe this evening.
Pour me some wine.
Do you have
something to tell me?
No, my lord.
Reek.
She saw me.
Who?
Sansa. Lady Sansa.
She came to the kennels.
She saw you?
Yes. I'm sorry, master.
Forgive me.
I didn't think...
Come here.
You mustn't keep
secrets from me, Reek.
Get on your knees.
Give me your hand.
I forgive you.
BOLTON: I trust you find
your chamber suitable,
my lady?
Yes, thank you.
Allow me.
Mother.
Thank you, Ramsay.
My lady, we are all a family,
we northerners.
Our blood ties go
back thousands of years.
So, I'd like to
drink to our wedding.
May our happiness
spread from Moat Cailin
to the Last Hearth.
To your wedding.
It must be difficult for you,
being in a strange place.
This isn't a strange place,
this is my home.
It's the people
who are strange.
You're right.
Very strange.
More wine, please.
I heard you two
had been reunited.
A fitting place for it.
I like to imagine that
the last time you spoke
was in this very room.
Are you still angry
with him after he...
What he did?
Don't worry.
The North remembers.
I punished him for it.
He's not ironborn any more.
Not Theon Greyjoy anymore.
He's a new man.
A new person, anyway.
Aren't you, Reek?
Yes, master.
That's his new name, Reek.
Why are you doing this?
Because Reek has
something to say to you.
Don't you, Reek?
An apology?
Apologize to Lady Sansa
for what you did.
Apologize for murdering
her two brothers.
I'm sorry.
Look at her, Reek.
An apology
doesn't mean anything
if you're not looking
the person in the eye.
I'm sorry.
RAMSAY: Sorry about what?
For killing your brothers.
There, over and done with.
Doesn't everyone
feel better?
I do.
(SNIFFLING)
That was getting very tense.
Whew.
You know what, my lady?
What with him having
murdered your brothers
and the rest of
your family gone,
Reek here is the nearest
thing to living kin
that you have left.
Reek.
You will give away the bride.
Someone has to.
What better person?
Good?
Yes, yes, very good.
Wonderful.
Walda and I have
some good news as well,
since we're all together.
We're going to have a baby.
I'm very happy for you.
From the way she's carrying,
Maester Wolkan says
it looks like a boy.
RAMSAY: How can you be sure?
Sure of what?
That she's pregnant.
I mean...
How can you tell?
Maester Wolkan
has assured us
beyond all doubt.
So, how did you manage it?
Manage what?
Getting her pregnant.
I imagine you're
familiar with the procedure.
Of course,
but how did you find it?
You disgraced
yourself at dinner,
parading that creature
before the Stark girl.
And if it's a boy?
(CHUCKLES)
You're worried
about your position.
My position is quite clear.
I'm your son
until a better
alternative comes along.
You've never asked
me about your mother.
Why would I?
She had me,
she died.
And here we are.
BOLTON:
She was a peasant girl.
Pretty in a common
sort of way.
She was the miller's wife.
Apparently they had married
without my knowledge
or consent,
so I had him hanged,
and I took her
beneath the tree
where he was swaying.
She fought me the whole time.
She was lucky
I didn't hang her, too.
A year later
she came to my gates
with a squalling
baby in her arms.
A baby she claimed was mine.
I nearly had her whipped,
and the child
thrown in the river.
But then I looked at you,
and I saw then what I see now.
You are my son.
Stannis Baratheon
has an army at Castle Black,
but he won't stay for long.
He wants the Iron Throne,
and the road to
King's Landing comes
right through Winterfell.
He means to take the North.
But the North is ours.
It's yours and mine.
Will you help me defeat him?
Yes.
Is this every book there is?
Every book there is?
In the world.
Well, no.
There are thousands
and thousands of
books out there.
This library is
rather small, actually.
Where you grew up,
were there more books?
My father's not
the most literate man.
They say the Citadel
has the largest
library in the world.
Where's that?
The Citadel?
In Oldtown.
I'm sorry
I don't know things.
Oh, Gilly, look at me.
You know how to do
a hundred things
I can never do.
You can build
a fire with wet wood.
You can cook.
You can stitch a wound.
I can wash the linens.
I can sweep the floor.
Well...
Why does the Citadel
have the biggest library?
It's where they
train the maesters.
Like Maester Aemon?
I wanted to be one
when I was young.
Instead, I became
a man of the Night's Watch.
Far more adventure
up here anyway.
I wouldn't have met you.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Ah, Your Grace.
You're Samwell Tarly?
I am, Your Grace.
Your father is Randyll Tarly.
Defeated my brother at
the Battle of Ashford.
Only battle Robert ever lost.
I told him he shouldn't go
so far west so soon,
but he never listened.
Fine soldier,
your father.
You don't look like a soldier.
But I'm told you
killed a White Walker.
I did, Your Grace.
How?
With a dagger
made of dragonglass.
Dragonglass?
What the maesters
call obsidian.
I know what it is.
We have it in Dragonstone.
Why would
obsidian kill a Walker?
I don't know.
I've been going through
all the old manuscripts
hoping to find something,
and all I've learned is that
the Children of the Forest
used to hunt
with dragonglass.
The Lady Melisandre
told me that death
marches on the Wall.
I've seen it, Your Grace.
Seen what?
The army of the dead.
And when they come...
We have to know
how to fight them.
Keep reading,
Samwell Tarly.
It's time.
Uh, Your Grace.
Wouldn't it be better to wait?
When Jon Snow
returns with the wildlings,
we could have
thousands more men.
If Jon Snow returns
with the wildlings.
We can't wait that long.
We have the advantage,
more men, more horses,
all fed and rested.
But every day we wait,
the odds shift in
Bolton's favor.
This could turn to
winter at any moment.
We have to act now.
Give the order.
We march at sunrise.
I'll choose
a dozen men to stay
and guard
the queen and the princess.
No need.
They're coming with us.
It's a tough road ahead,
Your Grace.
Won't they be safer...
Here?
Half these Watchmen
are killers and rapists.
No, they march with us.
As you wish,
Your Grace.
(WIND HOWLING)
(HORSES SNORTING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
SHIREEN: Do you think
Father will let me go
down into the crypt?
DAVOS: Beg your pardon?
At Winterfell.
All the kings in
the North are buried there.
Bran the Builder,
and King Dorren, and...
First things first.
It's a long march ahead.
And then we have
to take the castle.
Is there going to be a battle?
Aye, princess,
but you won't be
anywhere near...
That's enough
talk of battle, Ser Davos.
You'll scare the child.
DAVOS: Yes, my queen.
I'm not scared.
Well, I am.
When the battle comes,
promise you'll protect me.
I promise.
I hope you know
what you're doing
with these wildlings.
I need those ships.
You'll get them back,
I swear it.
Have a safe journey,
Your Grace.
And thank you.
MAN: Mount up!
Colors!
(HORSES NEIGHING)
(GROANS)
No.
You're still too weak.
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
Ser Barristan?
Are you ashamed?
You were ambushed,
outnumbered.
There was no way
you could have known.
This is not why.
Wounded in war,
there is no shame for this.
I am ashamed
because when the knife go in
and I fall to the ground,
I am afraid.
All men fear death.
No, not death.
I fear
I never again see Missandei
from the Island of Naath.
Now you have given
the Masters what they deserve.
If I give everyone
what they deserve,
I'll have no one left to rule.
Ser Barristan counseled mercy
when I took this city,
right up to
the morning he died.
Daario Naharis thinks
I should kill
the former Masters,
and let the rest of
the city fend for itself.
What do you think?
Your Grace, I think that
I am not fit to have
an opinion on these matters.
You are as fit
as anyone I know.
You know why I'm here,
and who will suffer the most
if this all falls apart.
So, what do you think?
I can only tell
you what I have seen,
Your Grace.
I have seen you
listen to your counselors.
I have seen you lean
on their experience
when your own was lacking,
and weigh the choices
they put before you.
And I have seen you
ignore your counselors
because there was
a better choice.
One that only you could see.
My queen,
please do not do this.
What about
"Valar Morghulis"?
I did not want
to die a coward.
Apparently I do not
want to die at all.
(SNIFFLES)
It takes
courage to admit fear.
And to admit a mistake.
I came here to tell
you that I was wrong.
I was wrong,
and you were right.
About tradition.
About bringing the people
of this city together.
I will reopen
the fighting pits.
To free men only.
Slavery will never
return to Meereen,
not while I live.
Yes, my queen.
And in order to
forge a lasting bond
with the Meereenese people,
I will marry the leader
of an ancient family.
Thankfully a suitor is
already on his knees.
Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
Nothing broken,
I don't think.
Where are we now?
Not the Rhoyne.
Long, sullen silences
and an occasional
punch in the face.
The Mormont way.
Let's start over.
I apologize for before.
My mouth sometimes
runs away from me.
This doesn't have to
be an unpleasant trip.
We're going to be spending
a lot of time together
on the way to Meereen.
We are.
What would make
our time together
truly enjoyable
would be some wine.
No wine.
I am a person who drinks.
People who drink
need to keep drinking.
Otherwise, they're not...
I know where we are.
You're taking us
through Valyria.
I am.
TYRION: Have you
sailed this route before?
JORAH: No.
You're going to
bring Daenerys a souvenir
from her ancestral homeland
in case I'm not enough?
I think you'll be plenty.
You know what they say.
The Doom still rules Valyria.
What about
the demons and the flames?
Aren't you afraid of the Doom?
JORAH: No.
But the pirates are.
Oh.
TYRION: The Smoking Sea.
How many centuries
before we learn
how to build
cities like this again?
For thousands of years,
the Valyrians were
the best in the world
at almost everything.
And then...
And then they weren't.
"They held each other close
"And turned their backs
upon the end
"The hills that split asunder
And the black
that ate the skies
"The flames that
shot so high and hot
That even dragons burned
"Would never be
the final sights
That fell upon their eyes
"A fly upon a wall
"The waves the sea wind
Whipped and churned"
"A city of a thousand years
"And all that men had learned
"The Doom
consumed it all alike
"And neither of them turned"
I would clap.
I suppose this is it, then.
This is what remains.
(WATER SPLASHING)
What was that?
Stone men!
(MAN RASPING)
Don't let them touch you!
(RASPING)
JORAH: Get behind!
Mormont, cut me free!
Mormont!
(RASPING)
(SNARLS)
Mormont!
(SHOUTS)
(FAINTLY) Tyrion.
Tyrion.
You're all right.
(PANTING)
You're heavier than you look.
Did any of them touch you?
You?
I've seen greyscale before.
Nothing like that.
JORAH: I suppose that's why
they send them there.
TYRION:
It'd be kinder
to put daggers
in their hearts
and be done with it.
Thank you for saving me.
Of course,
I wouldn't have
needed saving
if you hadn't kidnapped
me in the first place.
TYRION: So, what now?
JORAH: We walk up
the coast. With luck,
we'll find a fishing village.
Maybe another boat.
Without luck?
We've got a long
walk ahead of us.
I'll get some wood for a fire.
Try to get some rest, huh?
That's the best idea
you've had all day.