(LATCH CLANKS)
What are they doing
with the bodies?
Get back to work.
No. I've been here
for weeks.
I'm not scrubbing
one more corpse
until you tell me
why I'm doing it.
You will know why.
When?
When it's time,
not before.
Get back to work.
When do I get
to play the game?
Game?
The game.
The Game of Faces.
You tried already.
You failed.
I didn't even know
I was playing.
Who are you?
No one.
Get back to work.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
How did you get here?
I'm from Westeros,
just like you.
Daughter of a lord,
Except I was
an only child.
Heir to his fortune.
My mother died.
My father remarried,
and his new wife
gave birth to a girl.
My stepmother
didn't want any rivals
for her precious daughter,
so she tried to
kill me with poison.
I found out.
Sought help from
the Faceless Men.
And my father
was widowed again.
I've been serving
them ever since.
Was that true or a lie?
What?
Did you believe
every word I said?
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Get back to work.
JAQEN: Who are you?
Who are you?
Arya.
And where did
you come from?
Westeros.
My family home
is Winterfell.
I'm the youngest
daughter of a great lord,
Eddard Stark.
He died in battle.
(GASPS)
A lie.
After he was executed,
I fled the capital.
Had to kill
a stable boy.
Drove my sword
through his back.
(GASPS)
A lie.
I stabbed him in the gut.
I tried to find my
mother and brother,
but I never did.
They were murdered
by Walder Frey.
An outlaw kidnapped me,
a man called Polliver.
(WINCES)
A man called the Hound.
Sandor Clegane.
He tried to sell me,
but was wounded
in a fight.
He begged me to kill him,
but I wouldn't.
I left him in
the mountains to die.
I wanted him to suffer.
I hated him.
That's not a lie!
A girl lies to me,
to the Many-Faced God,
to herself.
Does she truly
want to be no one?
Yes.
(WHIMPERS)
I'm not playing this
stupid game anymore!
We never stop playing.
So, those villages
we were supposed
to find?
We can't live on
berries and roots.
I can.
You're not hungry?
Of course I'm hungry.
You're an awful
traveling companion,
do you know that?
Possibly the least
charming man I've ever met.
I'm not your
traveling companion.
We are traveling together
in each other's company,
therefore...
Do you ever shut up?
I sailed from
King's Landing to Pentos
in a crate
without ever saying a word.
Why?
It never occurred to you
to ask why until now?
You never wondered
why Tyrion Lannister
decided to visit
a brothel in Volantis?
I'm sure you visited
many brothels
in many cities.
I killed my father.
He wanted to execute me
for a crime I didn't commit.
And he was fucking
the woman I loved.
As miserable as you are,
Mormont, at least your father
was a good man.
JORAH: What do you
know about my father?
TYRION: I met him.
I visited the Wall.
When I asked him
about his men,
he knew all their stories,
every one of them.
He actually cared
about the people
under his command.
How do they put
it in the Watch?
"We shall never
see his like again."
Oh, you didn't know.
I'm sorry. I am.
How?
I only know what I heard.
He was leading
an expedition
beyond the Wall.
There was a mutiny.
He was murdered
by his own men.
We better keep moving.
(GIRL COUGHING)
(LABORED BREATHING)
Valar Morghulis.
Valar Dohaeris.
I have nowhere else to go.
I've taken her to
every healer in Braavos.
I've spent
every penny I had.
(LABORED BREATHING)
She suffers every
day of her life.
I just want it to end.
(WEAKLY) It hurts.
I know.
Don't be afraid.
I used to be like you.
I was sick.
I was dying.
But my father
never gave up on me.
He loved me
more than anything
in the world,
just like your
father loves you.
So he brought me here.
My father prayed to
the Many-Faced God,
and I drank the water
from his fountain.
It healed me.
(BOWL SCRAPES)
I've devoted my
life to him now.
You don't want
to hurt anymore?
Drink.
JAQEN: Is a girl ready?
To give up her ears,
her nose, her tongue?
Her hopes and dreams,
her loves and hates?
All that makes
a girl who she is?
Forever?
No.
A girl is not ready
to become no one.
But she is ready to
become someone else.
Why Daenerys?
Why is she worth
all this?
As I recall,
the Mormonts fought
against the Targaryens
during Robert's Rebellion.
Do you believe
in anything?
I believe
in lots of things.
In something greater
than ourselves, I mean.
The gods, destiny.
Do you believe there's
a plan for this world?
No.
Neither did I.
I was a cynic,
just like you.
Then I saw a girl
step into a great fire
with three stone eggs.
When the fire burned out,
I thought I'd find
her blackened bones.
Instead, I saw her,
Daenerys,
alive and unhurt,
holding her baby dragons.
Have you ever heard
baby dragons singing?
No.
It's hard to be
a cynic after that.
Doesn't mean she's going
to be a great queen.
No, it doesn't.
The Targaryens
are famously insane.
What if she conquers
the world? Then what?
A thousand years of
peace and prosperity?
First we have to
conquer the world.
We?
All right, let's assume
your dreams come true.
She's ecstatic
when you bring her
this enemy dwarf.
She hacks off my head
and restores your position.
You command her army,
sail to Westeros,
defeat all your enemies,
and watch her
climb those steps
and sit on the Iron Throne.
Hurrah. Long live the queen.
Then what?
Then she rules.
So, a woman who has not
spent a single day of her
adult life in Westeros
becomes the ruler
of Westeros?
That's justice?
JORAH:
She's the rightful heir.
Why?
Because her father, who burned
living men for amusement,
was the king?
That's a slave ship.
Why are they anchored?
They probably
came ashore for...
(SWORDS SCRAPING)
MAN: Water.
(GRUNTS)
(MAN LAUGHS)
Got a lot of fight
in you, huh?
(GRUNTS)
(CHUCKLES)
Salt mines?
Yeah, that
or a galley slave.
He looks strong enough.
What about the dwarf?
Worthless.
Cut his throat.
Wait. Wait.
Wait, wait, wait!
Let's discuss this.
And then
chop off his cock.
We'll sell it
for a fortune.
A dwarf's cock
has magic powers.
Wait! Wait!
Wait, wait, wait!
You can't just hand
a dry cock to a merchant
and expect him to pay for it.
He has to know it
came from a dwarf.
And how could he know
unless he sees the dwarf?
It will be
a dwarf-sized cock.
Guess again.
The dwarf lives until
we find a cock merchant.
(EXHALES)
Queen Daenerys has
outlawed slavery.
We're bound for Volantis,
not Slaver's Bay.
Besides, she reopened
the fighting pits.
I've never heard
of free men
fighting in the pits.
TYRION:
The fighting pits
in Meereen?
You're in luck, then.
You're about to be rich.
You are looking at one
of the great warriors
in the Seven Kingdoms.
(LAUGHS)
Him.
Him?
He's got to be
60 years old.
Sure, he's a bit
long in the tooth,
a bit withered,
been in the sun too long.
We can all see that.
But he is a veteran
of 100 battles.
They wrote songs about him.
That true?
He won the tournament
at Lannisport,
unseating Ser Jaime
Lannister himself.
(LAUGHS)
The Kingslayer.
Jousting. You're talking
about jousting.
A fancy game
for fancy lads.
The men who fight
in the pits of Meereen
will swallow him whole.
JORAH: I killed
a Dothraki bloodrider
in single combat.
Liar.
It's no lie.
His name was Qotho.
He was bloodrider
to Khal Drogo.
Take me to Slaver's Bay,
put a sword in my hand,
I'll prove my worth.
(LAUGHING)
(SEAGULLS SCREECHING)
(BELL RINGING)
For my children. Money.
Lord Baelish.
Yes?
Lancel Lannister.
Brother Lancel.
We abandon
our family names.
That's quite
a family to abandon.
The city has changed
since you were here last.
We flooded
the gutters with wine,
smashed the false idols,
and set the godless
on the run.
Well done.
I'm here on urgent business
for the Queen Mother.
Should I send word
that I'll be delayed?
Step carefully,
Lord Baelish.
You'll find there's little
tolerance for flesh peddlers
in the new King's Landing.
We both peddle fantasies,
Brother Lancel.
Mine just happen
to be entertaining.
Do you think it's wise,
Your Grace,
arresting the heir
to Highgarden?
The Faith arrested
the heir to Highgarden.
Of course, and the Faith
were armed on your orders.
The king's orders.
Is the king to blame
for Ser Loras' perversion?
House Tyrell won't
tolerate this insult.
House Tyrell
won't tolerate it?
I'm the insulted party,
Lord Baelish.
Ser Loras was promised to me.
Instead, he chose
the company of boys.
One's choice of companion
is a curious thing.
Most curious.
Lysa Arryn, for instance.
A thoroughly repellant woman.
Forgive me.
I know you're
still in mourning.
Lysa was a good woman.
A kind woman.
She was neither
of those things.
We both know it.
Still, I pity her son.
How fortunate
the young Lord
of the Vale
has a new father
to counsel him.
I know how hard it can be
to lose both your parents
at such a young age.
If war comes to Westeros,
will the Knights of the Vale
fight for their king?
Young Lord Robin
heeds my advice,
and I have always counseled
loyalty to the throne.
Good.
If there's nothing else.
There is another
matter, Your Grace.
Something so urgent
I couldn't trust
the words to a raven.
You once charged me
with finding Arya Stark.
To my shame, I failed you.
But I have found Sansa Stark.
Alive and well and home again
living at Winterfell.
That's not possible.
My sources are well placed.
They tell me Roose Bolton
plans to marry her
to his son, Ramsay,
a bastard
recently legitimized
by King Tommen.
Roose Bolton is
Warden of the North
by the grace of my father.
Indeed, his reward
for stabbing his
own king in the heart.
We were fools to
trust a turncloak.
Marrying his son to
the last of the Starks
gives him more
legitimacy in the North
than an alliance with
a hated southern house.
I will skin him
and his bastard
like that wretch on
their bloody sigil.
I would counsel patience,
Your Grace.
Patience?
Sansa helped murder my son.
Roose Bolton is a traitor.
Stannis Baratheon
is also a traitor,
marching with his
army on Winterfell.
Let Stannis
and Roose battle.
Let the enemies
of the throne
slaughter each other.
And when they're done,
seize Winterfell from
whichever thief survives.
Winterfell is 1,000 miles
away from here.
The weather has
already begun to turn.
That is why it is critical
to strike soon,
while the victor
still licks his wounds.
Surely your Uncle Kevan
could muster a force.
My Uncle Kevan
has all the courage
of a kitchen mouse.
Ser Jaime, then.
Jaime's away
on a sensitive
diplomatic mission.
I have no idea
when he'll be back.
Perhaps I can help.
The Knights of the Vale
are some of the best
fighters in Westeros,
trained to battle in
the ice and the snow.
Forgive me, Lord Baelish,
you have a reputation
as a moneylender
and a brothel keeper,
not a military man.
You wouldn't risk
a single Lannister soldier
or a single coin
from the royal treasury.
What do you have to lose?
A brothel keeper?
And if you succeed?
Name me Warden of the North.
I'll speak to
the king this evening,
have him issue a royal decree.
I'll not rest until the lion
flies over Winterfell.
I'll know you're
a man of your word
when I see Sansa Stark's
head on a spike.
As I said,
I live to serve.
I'm going to ask him
tomorrow.
What if he says no?
He won't.
We've waited long enough.
I want you to be my wife.
Now.
What is it?
Do you want to marry me
because our families
arranged it?
Or do you...
We can't. Not yet.
Why not?
You know why not.
Someone will see.
You are going
to be my wife.
I am going to be
your husband.
We're allowed
to walk through
the gardens together.
How many other girls
have you walked
through these gardens?
I like the way
your eyes go squinty
when you're jealous.
They do not go squinty,
and you didn't
answer the question.
DORAN:
They make a lovely couple.
A Lannister and a Martell.
They have no idea
how dangerous that is.
We must protect them.
Yes, my prince.
You haven't had to use
that axe of yours
in a long time.
I hope you remember how.
I remember how.
BRONN:
♪ The Dornishman's wife
was as fair as the sun
♪ And her kisses
were warmer than spring
♪ The Dornishman's blade
It was made of black steel
♪ And its kiss
was a terrible thing
♪ The Dornishman's wife
Would sing as she bathed
♪ In a voice that was
sweet as a peach... ♪
All right, that's enough.
I'm coming
to the best part.
We're trying to blend in.
Don't want
everyone in Dorne
to hear your accent.
This song really is
all about the ending.
It can wait. There.
That's the Water Gardens.
BRONN: And once
we've got the princess,
then what?
(BRONN SIGHS)
I like to improvise.
That explains
the golden hand.
ELLARIA: Unbowed.
Unbent. Unbroken.
For Oberyn.
ALL: For Oberyn.
Well, she's made
herself at home.
Myrcella.
Uncle Jaime?
I...
I don't understand.
What are you doing here?
Let's speak in private.
I am Trystane Martell.
Trystane is my intended.
Excellent. Good to meet you.
We weren't expecting
you, Lord Jaime.
Why don't you let them
have some time alone, son?
Let's not do
something stupid.
(GRUNTS)
(SHRIEKS)
That was something stupid.
We have to go, Myrcella, now.
You hurt him!
He'll be fine, I promise.
But we have to...
(GRUNTS)
Oh, for fuck's sake.
(SHOUTING)
(WHIP CRACKS)
Take her!
You're coming with me.
I don't want to.
I wasn't asking, princess.
(SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
Drop your weapons!
I am Obara Sand.
Daughter of Oberyn Martell.
I fight for Dorne.
Who do you fight for?
Drop your weapons.
When you were whole,
it would have
been a good fight.
(SWORD CLATTERS)
You fight pretty good
for a little girl.
(SHOUTING)
(HORSES NEIGHING)
(SEAGULLS SCREECHING)
Halt!
Oh.
You can smell the shit
from five miles away.
Well, why have we stopped?
Go on.
(HORSES NEIGHING)
Rumors and gossip,
that's all they've got.
It's theater, nothing more.
If they arrested
all the pillow biters
in King's Landing,
there'd be no room
left in the dungeons
for anyone else.
Everyone knew
about him and Renly.
Renly Baratheon shagged
half the stable boys
in the Seven Kingdoms.
Everyone knew,
no one cared.
But he was
the king's brother.
And Loras is
the queen's brother.
No, no, no, no.
This is unacceptable.
Cersei's behind it.
Yes, of course she is.
She wants to drag our
name through the dirt,
put us in our place.
Get some rest, dear.
You look appalling.
And let me deal
with Cersei Lannister.
Your Grace, I have
traveled a long way.
You must be exhausted.
Put the pen down, dear.
We both know you're
not writing anything.
Ah, yes.
The famously tart-tongued
Queen of Thorns.
And the famous tart,
Queen Cersei.
I beg your pardon?
I know you're behind
this absurd incarceration
of my grandson.
If you apologize
for that comment,
perhaps I'll...
You'll get your apology
when I get Loras.
I was as shocked as anyone
when the Faith
arrested Ser Loras.
I have no love
for these fanatics,
but what can
a Queen Mother do?
Has the crown suddenly
stopped needing
the troops, gold, and wheat
my house supplies?
I can assure you,
our alliance with
House Tyrell remains...
Do you expect
the alliance to continue
after you've thrown
our future into prison?
As I said,
I didn't imprison anyone.
As for your
veiled threats...
What veil?
(SIGHS)
The Lannister-Tyrell
alliance brought peace
to a war-torn country.
Do you really want to see
the Seven Kingdoms
slide back into warfare?
I didn't trust your father.
I didn't
particularly like him.
But I respected him.
He was no fool.
He understood that sometimes
we must work with our rivals
rather than destroy them.
House Lannister has no rival.
The High Septon has
called for an inquest,
not a trial.
Just a small hearing
to determine
whether the charges
against Loras have merit,
which I'm sure they don't.
Loras will be freed,
our happy alliance
will continue,
and we'll forget
this unfortunate
conversation ever happened.
Good day, Lady Olenna.
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
HIGH SPARROW: You are
aware of the rumors
concerning you and Renly?
I don't pay
attention to rumors.
HIGH SPARROW:
You were said to be
despondent when he died.
Witnesses state that you
refused to leave his bedside,
even as Stannis'
army closed in.
He was my friend.
He was my king.
Wasn't Joffrey your king?
He was anointed by the Seven,
not Renly.
I was wrong to support
Renly's claim, I know that.
But I was forgiven
by Joffrey.
I fought for him at
the Battle of Blackwater.
Yes, wearing
Renly's armor.
Why does it
matter what I wore?
Do you deny all
the charges against you?
Fornication.
Buggery. Blasphemy.
Of course I deny them.
You never lay
with Renly Baratheon?
Never.
Nor any other man?
That will be all, Ser Loras.
Well, I think that's
quite enough of that.
The Faith calls
Queen Margaery forward.
You call me forward?
Yes, we have some
questions for you.
I am the queen.
HIGH SPARROW: You are.
And according to
the law of the Seven,
neither kings nor
queens are exempt
from testimony
at a holy inquest.
How do you respond
to these charges
against your brother?
They are lies.
All of them?
All of them.
HIGH SPARROW: Queen Margaery,
in the presence of the gods,
do you swear that
your brother is innocent
of these charges against him,
to the best of your knowledge?
MARGAERY: Yes, I swear it.
Thank you, Your Grace.
Do you know this man?
Yes.
Very well.
He is Ser Loras Tyrell,
heir to Highgarden.
How did you
come to meet?
OLYVAR: I squired for him.
He took a liking to me.
He summoned me
to his chamber
the first day we met.
And what occurred
in his chamber?
We engaged in
intimate relations.
You lay with him?
That night
and many others.
Liar. He's a liar.
Is there anyone else
who can support your claim?
Yes.
Yes, Queen Margaery.
She walked in on us once,
not long ago.
She didn't seem surprised.
This testimony is
an insult to a great house.
Why should
the Faith or anyone else
take the word of a squire
over the heir to Highgarden?
OLYVAR: He has
a birthmark, Your Grace.
Quite high on his thigh.
Wine-colored
and roughly
the shape of Dorne.
No! Liar!
(GRUNTING)
What are you doing?
Let us pass.
The Faith is satisfied
there is enough evidence
to bring a formal trial
for Ser Loras
and Queen Margaery.
What?
Bearing false witness
before the gods is as grave
a sin as any, my lady.
Take her.
MARGAERY: No.
Tommen.
Tommen!
You can't do this.
I am the queen.
Tommen! Tommen!
I am your queen. How dare you?
Take your hands off me!
(SHOUTING) Tommen!
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
(WIND WHISTLING)
What do you want?
Lord Ramsay sent me to
draw your bath, my lady.
You want to be clean
and fresh for your new
husband, don't you?
You're so beautiful,
but you need to
keep him happy.
Ramsay gets bored easily.
You don't want
to end up like...
Well, like the others.
What others?
I shouldn't gossip.
Oh, it's good to
see the red again.
No point hiding anymore.
What others?
Let's see, there was Kyra,
the blacksmith's daughter.
She was tall like you,
lovely figure.
But she talked and
talked and talked,
and Ramsay
grew tired of that.
Then there was Violet.
She had gorgeous blonde hair.
But she got pregnant.
And, well, that was boring.
Then Tansy.
Such a sweet girl.
Of course,
sweet girls get a bit dull
after a while, don't they?
Ramsay let me come
with him on that hunt.
Hunt?
Mmm.
Have you ever seen a body
after the dogs
have been at it?
Not so pretty.
But, well,
it's your wedding day.
Why am I talking
about such things?
What was your name again?
Myranda.
And how long have you
loved him, Myranda?
Did you imagine that
he would be with you
forever, is that it?
And I came along
and ruined it.
I'm Sansa Stark
of Winterfell.
This is my home,
and you can't frighten me.
Are you done with
your bath, my lady?
Go. I can finish on my own.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Yes?
I've come to escort you
to the godswood, my lady.
If you please, my lady,
will you take my arm?
No.
Lord Ramsay, he said
I'm to take your arm.
I'm not touching you.
Please.
He'll punish me.
You think I care
what he does to you?
Who comes before
the Old Gods this night?
THEON:
Sansa of the House Stark
comes here to be wed.
A woman grown,
trueborn and noble.
She comes to beg
the blessings of the gods.
Who comes to claim her?
Ramsay of House Bolton.
Heir to the Dreadfort
and Winterfell.
Who gives her?
Theon of House Greyjoy,
who was...
Who was her father's ward.
Lady Sansa,
will you take this man?
I take this man.
Are you pleased, my lady?
Good. I want you to be happy.
(SIGHS)
My father said
you're still a virgin.
Uh, yes.
Why?
Why are you
still a virgin?
Afraid of dwarves? (CHUCKLES)
Lord Tyrion was kind.
He was gentle.
He never touched me.
You're not lying to me?
SANSA: No, my lord.
Lying to your husband
on his wedding night,
that would be a bad way
to start a marriage.
We're man and wife now.
We should be honest
with each other.
Don't you think?
Yes.
Good.
Take off your clothes.
Oh, no, no, no.
You stay here, Reek.
You watch.
Do I need to ask
a second time?
I hate asking
a second time.
Reek.
I told you to watch.
You've known Sansa
since she was a girl.
Now watch her
become a woman.
(GASPS)
(CLOTHES RIPPING)
(WHIMPERING)
(BREATHING QUICKLY)
(BELT BUCKLE CLINKING)
(RAMSAY GRUNTING)
(SANSA GROANING)
(SANSA CRYING)